drinking
dring with
the hello
everybody Welcome to yet another episode
of drinking with you our very special
guest tonight is comedian Lis
black can you stand
it I said can you stand
it and our very special gu guest tonight
is the
alarmist
yes and now the one the only the man of
my heart and yours
ladies and gentlemen thanks for coming
down to Tri with the tonight how y'all
doing oh my God we're about to have a
champagne Jam aren't
we this is going to be
huge shamp shamp P all right um yet
again thanks for coming down big round
of applause for our Shan tour of the
Stars he's a little juicy right now cuz
he's worked himself into a lather the
Shan tour
Neil and no show would be complete and
no life would be decent without booze
put your hands together for the
bartender the Stars Mr Ali stch get out
of my
shot all right now normally I have like
big long stories to go with the shot of
the night and really tonight's shot
needs no introduction other than that
after almost four years of doing the
show I can't believe we've never thought
of having the money
shot and to make a money
shot you take a
shot of Phillips Union cherry whiskey
whiskey that's a shot
and you take a shot
shot of Pepsi
Cola you add a little ice ice shake it
up and we want this on the Rocks Rock so
you just pour it out and enjoy enjoy the
money shot shots on the
house all right every
everybody the muddy
shot ask for it by name and sporting
events vfw's you name it on three one 2
salute tastes like tastes like freedom
and Cherry Coke
together all right everybody we have um
we generally try to do topical stuff we
try to do stuff that's very recent
tonight we're going to go in a slightly
different direction is that cool is that
all right I know we're branching out a
little bit here people we're taking a
historic look at Salem you know Salem
you know the home of the witch trials
all that stuff exactly this is called
Salem a hasty documentary let's take a
look Massachusetts
1692 with an Indian War raging near
nearby and Rifts forming in a
traditionally uniformed Church hysteria
grips the Puritan town of Salem from
Winter until the summer of this year
hundreds face accusations of
Witchcraft and many innocent people will
be executed you turn one guy into a toad
and and all of a sudden I'm the bad guy
I'm the bad guy the accusations come
from family neighbors friends and Men
about town I did not know she had cast
her lot with Satan not upon first gazing
her as it happens I asked to court her
and finding my wooing
denied that's when I began to suspect
her of richual he asked me to show him
my ankles my ankles what do I look like
a god Lutheran evidence needed to
convict a woman of Witchcraft was
minimal the important thing is that the
accused be linked back to Satan but this
was not always
easy look I make sexual congress with a
lot of Puritans what am I supposed to
remember every Goodie and Proctor that I
lay under the full moon
Jesus lacking corroboration from The
Lord of Darkness a confidently spoken
rumor would often do the trick I accuse
you of the dark
arts or we'd say I accuse you of being a
witch or I accuse you of witchery or
sometimes just witch witch you know
whatever whatever you feel at the moment
it will be months before the Panic of
the Salem Witch Trials comes to an end
and after that there will be a time of
Sorrow of reflection of
healing but until then each person must
look deep inside themselves and ask
whether they have what it takes to just
make up in
court love getting me some
pilgrims that was
Salem a hasty documentary done by your
friends at drinking with the big round
of applause for
them all right um in the four years
drink with Ian has been on television
it's justed up we really should have
found something better today
uh We've made a couple friends and some
of them were in high places and some of
which we've been trying to get on the
show for a while we're really lucky to
get our next guy on because we've known
him for a while he's been friends and
we're just waiting for the time to work
out so put your hands together for Louis
black all right we're on a big time
famous bus with the big time famous
person this is Louis black who you've no
doubt familiar with and yes he is too
damn famous to be on our show and yet
some we got a blue thanks for doing this
yeah no problem show you I'm just trying
to prove how I'm not really that famous
yeah well get the word out slowly you
know mean people people are beginning to
hear about you these movies I guess
people are watching but yeah the the
dreaming with the in audience we really
need to get that deliver that to you um
but yeah you started um as a playwright
uh back in the 60s um how did you make
that jump from from playwriting to this
yeah well I was just doing this for fun
and uh CU you we do plays and nobody
really does plays I me if you get one
and done a year you're lucky so I did
this on the side for grms thinking you
know at least I can write and do it so
that was so I just kept doing it and
then I thought this is nuts I can't
really be the comic I I never even
inspired anything really yeah and but
what inspired you to be a playr I
started watching uh I went to the
theater when I was a kid uh my father
took me to a show and then it's like
there's a I think there's a certain
quality to uh there's a certain group of
people much like heroin addicts that get
introduced to heroin and they decide
they want to do heroin and there's a
group of people that get into just to
theater there's a lot of vomiting with
both too well there is a lot of vomiting
especially if you write this stuff and
uh um so I uh I kind of got hooked on it
and I was kind of fascinated by it and
then I became more interested in then uh
but I couldn't write I mean I couldn't
act I couldn't direct um I wanted to be
a drama critic which is just and were a
few critics that I really thought really
wrote were and were as uh important as
the as the people writing stuff but
those guys have passed on very few of
those types left but um but that was so
I started I said I got to do some so I
started
running and as you said you're doing
comedy on the side just as something you
know it's kind of a diversion really um
and how did that end up outlasting uh
being a playright um uh being a
playright is the equivalent of uh uh
financially of Migrant R and less maybe
because um so I I ended up uh I was
doing the stuff on the side I would go
to I would do to go to theaters really
and and uh and do the stuff and then
when I made the when I got to New York I
tried to work in uh like uh The Improv
or catch rising star and I I just hated
the whole setup of it so I kind of stuck
to my own M then I started running my
own space in New York and uh with some
other guys and uh would introduce every
show and the more that I introduce shows
the more comfortable I became uh and
then I was kind of started people
started to kind of uh you know after 3
or four years I was kind of known within
at least the New York Community um we
would do a free show on Saturdays
because most of our friends were
brok so you the responses were favorable
early on uh yeah I mean you know I mean
at least I was I was figuring it out
pretty quickly once I figured out what
was what I I started to figure out how
to uh
uh get it across to to any audience and
has the voice matured like that as well
I mean is I mean basically I mean
everybody knows you is you know there's
a lot of pointing and a lot of lot of
yelling I mean was that at the beginning
as well the beginning was no the
beginning was mostly uh I was angry but
not really showing it another comic from
Michigan Dan ballor came up to me one
night at the club and said uh you're you
know you're you're uh you're um you're
angry but you're not yelling and I'm not
angry and I'm yelling you should be
yelling yelling M go up there and yell
and I did and that kind of and then it
became and then I that's what really
created the final kind of a nail on it
and that's when so and then just you
know just touring around doing small
clubs here and there uh what did you do
that got the attention of The Daily Show
and you look at that as the big jump I
mean was well it was a big it turned out
to be the big jump at the time I just
thought well that's it's great I mean I
was GL to be you know just GL to be on a
a show and I assume at this point you
have to be like one of the longest
standing members if not I am yeah
there's nobody with the with coar
leaving I'm in I'm the last I'm the Last
Comic
Standing and um so now you made the jump
and you're doing a fair amount of movies
uh you're just with uh Robin Williams um
and with with The
uncomp Wil
vama yeah how's he to work with he's
actually he's like two people he's the
guy you read about in the paper and uh
you know because he goes in somewhere
and uh and you know and beautiful women
you know writes up to him and then we do
the movie and he's got no brings no BS
to the table none he was the one yeah
and what's it like with having a player
right background doing uh movies you
know I mean is it are you picking it
apart or going the hell is that really I
don't really stick my nose into
anybody's writing cuz uh unless I have I
kind of go oh like I you know this is
fastic you know uh you get um people
writing that you know that somehow and
and this I find this just it's just so
irritating from intelligent people that
you get in you know you you you start
reading about well I can't believe he
made the choice to do that movie well
like I have choices yeah um yeah and um
are you worried about uh being typ
casted from the character you know that
you know you do live that you do on uh
you know it doesn't bother me um what's
interesting thing there again is is that
people get upset that in the movies I'm
not doing what I do MH and it's like
well you you you're damned if you do and
you're damned if you don't so um so
screw them all really yeah really so I
mean if I you know if as long as I feel
like um there's something uh to be
gained in doing that character I'll do
it um yeah and the HBO specials I mean
that's you know a totally different
things I mean you're basically walking
in coling all the shots I mean how's
that been working for you I mean you
really I mean this has to be just
another dream come true basically carry
as much time as you want and just like
basically go up there and [ __ ] in front
of a whole bunch of people and they all
then they all love it and it's on HBO I
yeah no that's been uh that was a huge
uh that's the biggest as far as I'm
concerned as comic that's what I aspired
to um in that uh yeah and um to tight
all in I know Minneapolis has kind of
played a weird role uh for you here I
mean cuz it seem you taped a lot of the
early albums at Acme uh what's your
background here is just kind of like
dumb luck that just we have you no yeah
well I mean I came into acne uh I was 12
years ago and uh and then it there was a
Dan listle that Maniac was he approached
me to do these CDs we did the first one
in Milwaukee and the second one I
decided to do here um and then um Louis
Lee had AC me wanted to do a uh a
fundraiser here we did that show C endo
and a few other guys that came to you
know and that kind of put me into the
the theater here and then dve T and I
came back yeah and then now it's been a
a regular occurrence yeah so the crowds
have been uh treating pretty well here
though yeah they're great yeah well it
kind of works cuz they're they get it I
mean you guys it's you know you San
Francisco uh Seattle the gay the gay
places yeah exactly there's a lot of
homos around play as well yeah you well
the people get it in in these canaries I
mean you got a uh you got a theater
scene is uh as Bowman was saying today
that goes you know his head and
shoulders above most of
it all right well Le has to go run and
do yeah we're getting the wrap so he's
got to go do an important show out there
at State Theater and Lou thanks for
thanks for doing this so that much thank
you back to you in the studio
in thanks so much thanks
I you ever wonder what it was like to
watch lisis black get interviewed by
Ronald McDonald now you know
hey all right Louis black everybody it's
amazing he said
yes another man who is equally is
amazing yeah yeah who am I talking
about hi Jim
everybody thanks thanks
R uh you know something I for one I
can't speak for you but I think it's
great that comedians can use drinking
with the in as a spring board two bigger
and better things Lou black you know
keep up keep up the good work kid yeah
and I have a tip come on four
Comedians and Lewis
Black um I don't want to really give up
all of my secrets but I can tell you
that this Haiku thing it's com it's it's
comedic gold gold so I have a little
something for you right now yeah advice
for Lou black
here's my comedy
secret it's
5 7 and
five ladies and gentlemen IQ
Jim all right we're going to watch a
bath time in uh Clarenville now I don't
know anything about clerkenwell it's
going to be awesome just pay attention
to the big
screen oh
what Happ
Happ
do
Bo
we're out here now man I hope you're
happy yeah I'm happy well good now what
well I just think we should have W AR
safety vest oh come on man those those
vest are for dag on people who really
like to use them dear don't even see
them they're color blind stupid
golly hey T did you get something tiny
what'd you get tiny
tiny oh my
God 911 what is your emergency please
yes please help us I think my buddy I
think he's dead what do I do sir calm
down I can help you we'll walk through
this together first I need you to make
sure he's
dead well I can do that hold on a second
he's dead now
what ladies and gentlemen how you doing
tonight thanks for sticking around and
drinking with Ian we're thrilled to have
this next band on they have an album out
right now called a detail of soldiers
put your hands together for the
alarmists
got time
go
the Tak time to make
it you know how to be
while
I I'm
watching while you are walking
away while you are walk
away while you
never is time to take it slow take it
the door go make it all right just night
it's just one
night
my way I don't but
it's when it
get the other
way she got time she
she wants mine but mine is mine we got
Liv we need to
make
always
away why can't you hear what I
say my Shadows what you st
there always walk in
Way You Are
she
she she got
she she baby she mind she got baby she
Mindy she don't mind baby she don't mind
she got time baby she don't mind baby
she don't mind
every
thanks a lot you guys ladies and
gentlemen the
alarmists one more time the alarm
I would like to thank Lewis
Black I would like to thank the
television audience and I'd like to
thank the people who are here right
now that's trigger with the end this
week we'll see you next
time we suggest you patronize these
neighbors for friendliness courtesy and
value
drinking with the in is proud to be
sponsored by Gold Medal winner Phillips
UV Vodka UV Vodka no carbs distilled
four times charcoal filtered a clean
crisp start to your night where you take
it from there is up to you please visit
ubv vodka.com for additional information
and recipes and please remember to
always enjoy Philips products in
moderation dear drinking with Ian viewer
there are few things in life more
fulfilling than drinking alcoholic
beverages while watching a TV show about
drinking alcoholic beverages the fine
folks of pizza luche would like to make
your current DWI experience even more
awesome you may ask yourself or those
around you how can I possibly have a
greater time than I am right now well if
you order a pizza luch delivery right
now we can ensure that within about 30
minutes you'll be having the time of
your life in fact our Studies have
proven that watching DWI while eating
Tasty Pizza luche Pizza will make our
already super delicious pizza taste even
better we don't know why this show makes
their pizzas taste so good but we think
that Ian's crazy hair might have
something to do with it Triple C draft
energy drink is made for the night life
and not for sport triple CF draft energy
drink is only available at establishment
selling Spirits mix Triple cap with your
favorite intoxicant you will come to
appreciate the lasting effects of the
world's first draft energy drink Triple
cap tap one off and Spike
It guess God needed another little angel
poor little guy had so much left in him
well burgers are done
cheers cherish a classic Green Belt
premium a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest news source and the AV club
bringing your reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at new stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at the onion.com
and avclub.com
live music on drinking with Ian is
sponsored in part five Billy thejack
Productions online at Billy the jack.com