it's my pleasure to introduce your host
and MC for the evening Mr Keith lol
Jensen all right 420 huh
cool I'm a little bummed because I
didn't get my drug of choice before this
show my pharmacist cut off my supply of
psea
fed yeah for real I have allergies
they're terrible I went in I said hey I
need my psea fed and he said no you've
uh exceeded the amount that you can have
in this allotted amount of time I said
what it's over the- counter [ __ ] and he
pulled out a folder and they've been
keeping track of how much suda fed we
all Buy
and I bought too much and I said why do
you do that that's crazy and he said oh
it's a government thing they're afraid
you might be making meth out of it so
man I can't buy ped cuz they think I
might be making meth out of it that's
really weird cuz I can get all the meth
I
want like Mikey ain't even keeping
track it says bro come over I got Xbox
and we hang out anyway now I'm on Google
trying to find a recipe to turn meth
back into psea
fed if anyone can offer any
help I uh celebrated my fifth wedding
anniversary
recently oh thanks that's nice I I
didn't do it for the Applause break it
was mostly for the
sex uh but my wife and I had been
together for 14 years before we got
married so yeah so now we're at like 19
years and I feel weird telling people
that cuz the way people respond to that
I know in their heads are thinking man
this guy has been in a monogamous
heterosexual relationship for almost two
decades I bet he's boring as [ __ ] in the
bedroom like people think I'm kind of
vanilla and that's not true I'm kinky as
[ __ ] thank I need you to know
that let me tell you about my trip my
thing is I really want to bang an old
lady
and I'm super
patient do want you get that one that's
a very sweet
joke pretty sure it's the most romantic
way you will ever hear anyone say I want
to bang an old
lady I got the record for that one uh we
have a kid so I got this kid now who I'm
not hitting
yeah zero beating my child I didn't
think that was a controversial decision
like hey you want to hit the adorable
little creature that depends on you for
everything it's helpless like oh no I'll
pass that's good uh and then I have
friends that actually found a way to
take issue with that like you're not
hitting her seriously bro you're not
hitting her dude bro bro dude you got a
hit
her dud listen we got hit when we were
kids remember we got hit then I have to
have that awkward conversation where I
remind them that we are not what I'm
aiming
for what the [ __ ] so great about us
you know set my sight a little bit
higher my girl's awesome she's a
tiger yeah my little girl's a tiger
because she loves Tigers so much she
decided that she was one she has that
power makes feeding her awkward
sometimes daddy what's this oh that's
oatmeal honey daddy tigers are on the
top of the food
chain we don't eat
oatmeal it's uh mice that I boiled and
Blended in the
blender Max it down I've lost 10
lbs so my tiger is very lucky compared
to some kids she has three grandmas cuz
grandpa doesn't know how to behave
himself thank
you man this guy's really fond of
cheating
grandpas it's a bold career aspiration
sir I wish you luck with it uh but these
uh these three grandmas they didn't know
they were going to get a tiger so they
buy my daughter boring little girl
presents that are of no use to a tiger
like the three baby dolls she has that
just sit on her bed ignored most of the
time until last week when I see her
pulling a box down the hallway and she's
got all three baby dolls in the box and
I said oh that's great you're playing
with your baby dolls and as she throws
the Box up on the couch she says to me
over her shoulder tiger food
dad said oh [ __ ] I did what a
responsible parent in 2013 does I ran
and I grabbed my my camera and I started
recording
her cuz I could use the YouTube
hits she takes one of the baby dolls and
she puts it in a drawer and she closes
the
drawer and I said oh what are you doing
there sweetie she said it's an oven
daddy you got to cook
them thought maybe we'd compare recipes
I said
okay how long do you cook a baby
girl she didn't hesitate oh about 2
hours or until they stopped
squirming that came out of my sweet
little Angel's mouth my little girl has
a fantastic
imagination she does and I'm proud of
her and I can't wait to see where that
imagination takes her and I'm going to
be proud of her no matter what no matter
where she goes in her life Daddy's going
to be proud and friends that try to call
me on that they're all wherever she goes
no matter what would if she becomes a
serial
killer well female serial killers are
rare I can just see myself bragging
someday oh excuse me that's uh it's
actually 17 known
victims my little girl my baby
I uh I packed my uh packed my little
tiger up one day and I took her off to
the dog
park and uh it was crazy it was a grand
opening of the dog park everybody was
out with their dogs there were hundreds
of dogs I don't know if you guys have
ever been to a fullscale dog party but
it was badass they travel in packs
biting each other's faces and they'll
knock you over if you're standing there
I've got her on my hip and we're just
laughing and we're having a great time
and then then in the middle of the dog
party the biggest dog in the park walks
over and stops right in front of us and
squats down to take a
[ __ ] and we stopped to
watch cuz that kind of stuff is
fascinating when you're
three or
me and so this big dog's [ __ ] and
the second the [ __ ] hit the ground I
mean the second it hit the ground this
little tiny white dog comes flying over
from the other side of the park and just
gobbles it right up yeah I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm just reporting the facts
that's nature sometimes nature is
disgusting and
hilarious we started laughing so hard it
was just so out of the blue I mean the
dude with the big dog was down there to
pick it up he had the baggie inside out
on his hand and everything he's
like thank you
and my daughter starts doing what a
precocious three-year-old will do when
something's funny she keeps repeating
what was funny so she keeps saying Daddy
Daddy that doggy pooped Daddy and that
doggy ate it daddy that doggy right
there and she's narking off the little
dog like he cannot disappear into the
crowd at this point there he is the
little [ __ ]
eater and I'm laughing so hard and I'm
thinking man like I love comedy I study
comedy I perform comedy every night I
will never be as funny as that little
dog like that dog has bested
me and now I'm laughing so hard that my
face is glowing red I've got tears
flowing down my
cheeks and at this point a woman nearby
decides that she doesn't approve of this
kind of fatherdaughter
bonding and she leans over to us and she
says um excuse me but
that's
disgusting and I said no no not really
cuz if you think about
it that little dog totally within the
5-second
rule then I thought man that was pretty
funny maybe I could open for that little
dog in
Vegas take our ax on the road
marijuana
huh yeah woo I don't I don't smoke it
myself uh and a lot of people don't
believe me when I say that they think
I'm playing games they're like oh cuz
you eat it right uh no I just have
sensitive
eyes I just look like this and I'm often
hungry and a little bit
slow you guys smoke weed to get like me
is what I'm saying I'm already here but
I'm still totally in favor of legalizing
it yeah I feel very strongly about this
and I don't see why whether or not I
smoke it should have anything to do with
my attitude about legalizing it like
that seems ridiculous to me I get
frustrated when I talk to older people
and they're like well I don't smoke it I
don't see why anyone else needs to
either and I'm like yeah well you don't
listen to very good music or have sex
with Attractive people either old man
how about I [ __ ] decide for
me would that be all right and my thing
is I just don't see much of an argument
against it I see it as a fairly
innocuous drug uh and if you ask people
well what's wrong with it like they
still are throwing the same lamest thing
at you that they've been throwing around
since I was a kid it causes
paranoia that's the one like
psychological side effect they can throw
at you smoking marijuana causes
paranoia well [ __ ] I bet that one's true
I bet smoking pot does make you par
paranoid I have a little theory about it
though I think it might be because we
keep [ __ ] arresting people for
it does it seem like they could be
related I'm just saying legalize that
[ __ ] and that symptom might go
away I mean [ __ ] masturbation will make
you paranoid if you live with your
parents
sir I'm conflicted about the movement to
legalize it though like I'm glad I'm
glad and also surprised I'm I'm glad to
see it becoming legal in some states and
then just baffled that they're getting
to it before us like other states are
beating California at gay marriage and
legalizing weed who the [ __ ] are we now
like I thought that was our
[ __ ] how did we fall behind in gay and
weed like I thought we had that down
bat it's funny traveling the country CU
a lot of people think that weed's
already legal here they're like oh it's
pretty much legal in California and I'm
like no no it's not it's through these
dispensaries and you got to have a
legitimate medical issue like scoliosis
or cataracts or
freckles and I love the dispensaries I
have one right by my house I walk past
it every day and they're so funny
because they try to look like legitimate
pharmacies uh this one says all about
wellness and yeah they're nice people uh
but they have it they have it
written with the little American Medical
Association sign I'm like oh that's very
nice but they wrote it in that like
Thrasher skater font with the lightning
and everything else like wait a minute
that doesn't say all about Wellness that
says all about
Wellness might as well add [ __ ]
I walk by at Christmas and they've got a
wreath on the door that's made out of
marijuana
leaves and I'm like hey you know what
other farmes don't treat their product
like that like I've never walked into
Safeway and heard oh you're standing
under the paxel let's have a kiss come
on
now I've been doing a lot of writing
lately I'm uh working on a country
western song I haven't gotten very far I
just got the title so far but I like it
uh it's called her safe word was
goodbye I've been writing suicide notes
lately well thank
you for those of you giggling [ __ ] you
that was the appropriate
response uh don't worry about me I'll be
okay appreciate it I just think it's
underappreciated art form thought I'd
take a stab at
it I uh I've come up with one I really
like it's uh goodby why you can have my
records but I'm taking all my
pills
kisses I do I do get a little depressed
sometimes I got depressed buying life
insurance I'm a father now I got to have
life insurance it's a responsible thing
to do but it's depressing being
workingclass poor and then having this
like million-dollar policy when your
three and a half-year-old says to you
Daddy I hope you never die
your first thought shouldn't be ah you
sure cuz you know you could go to
college I want to talk to you guys about
this uh this tattoo that's been going
around on the internet I don't know if
you guys have seen it but this dude
decided to get this tattoo on his bicep
that says Thou shalt not lie with a
man as one lies with a woman it is an
Abomination which I think means snowman
really dig
it I don't know I didn't finish High
School uh under that is the attribution
Leviticus this comes out of
Leviticus that's important because this
dude was so excited when he found that
quote To Get Inked Up on his arm that he
didn't even flip the page CU on the next
page of Leviticus it says don't get a
tattoo you
douchebag I'm paraphrasing but that
shit's in there you can look it up but
what's really funny about it to me is
just the wording Thou shalt not lie with
a man as one lies with a woman I don't
think that says don't be gay that's just
advice on positions isn't
it good advice the Bible's like oh you
know you [ __ ] the lady you probably
want to try [ __ ] a dude sometime why
wouldn't you uh but listen listen we
made the anatomy a little bit different
adjust the Bible's trying to help you
out it's like don't just jump right into
missionary position you will end up
frustrated and possibly even injured you
got to get the legs up a little higher
uh sorry I didn't mean to get too
graphic at the end there but I had gay
friends coming up to me after shows all
the time going uh dude we can do
missionary position and then me being
who I am I always answered yeah well
prove it and then my night got weird and
so I put that in the joke but uh
obviously that's not how this guy meant
it I mean this guy had a chance to say
something from inside himself and to
externalize it to put it on himself in a
way that's permanent given his religious
beliefs probably something he even
thinks he's going to take with him to
the next life and what did he have to
express from the depths of his soul what
was the sentiment that he had to share
with the world don't [ __ ]
dudes that's what he needed tattooed on
his arm right there don't [ __ ] dudes
that was this guy in a nutshell don't
[ __ ] dudes which makes me wonder how bad
is his memory
cuz mine's [ __ ] awful and I almost
never forget not to [ __ ]
dudes like I'm not going all momento on
my ass or anything I just don't do it
you never catch me at Safeway like [ __ ]
I need to get bread we're almost out of
tofu oh don't [ __ ] dudes oh my God sir I
am so
sorry I'm not supposed to be in this
public restroom right now I got to get
out of here all right you guys ready for
more
well that's good cuz we got more for
you I'll be your host I'll be coming up
here all night that's why they picked
they picked one guy who doesn't smoke
pot uh cuz someone had to keep coming
back up and introducing the other
guys so that was me that's token non
toer it's a roll I'll
take uh well this next guy is a local
favorite here people really love him
came up from La for this please welcome
to the stage Mr Jasper
red yo ski W ski what's
happening how's everybody
doing all
right so uh I'm a man of
ideas it don't look like it but your boy
be
thinking I'll be pondering
I'll be
wandering was driving in
traffic and I had a idea pop into my big
ass
head light bul went off like in the
cartoons I think car horns should sound
like
gunshots I'm trying to get a patting on
that sound of a horn is not representing
my road rage prop
anymore in these streets you feel
me I ain't you know I'm said we ask some
outdated technology I need to upload
some machine gun
fire where is that at on
iTunes I ain't never been angry with
someone all of a sudden had the urge to
to the
trumpet D I had I sell the disputes in
the hood know what the [ __ ] you just say
nah I'm good Charles now what we keep on
talking [ __ ] y hey all right
what
[ __ ] hey Jabar go get your oo
and your tube out your trunk dog we
about to do a parade on this
[ __ ] and I just got out of jail
for a parade charge but I don't give a
[ __ ] you can take the man after parade
but you can't take the parade after man
what's up [ __ ]
wood
wins see I just want to simulate gunfire
out of my steering wheel right for
cathartic
reasons so your boy won't be in the
streets like a loose
cannon I can simulate it like Call of
Duty gun violence is a serious problem
in this country I ain't trying to make
light of it I know what's the deal out
there we even got a say guns don't kill
people people kill people right that's
been around for years in fortune cookies
and
whatnot but to your boy that's a
perplexing type of
statement very vague to me that's like
somebody going hey y'all camera don't
take
pictures where the Instagram pictures
take pictures you see what I'm saying
picture and picture use your eye toast
don't toast
toast toast toast toast you
understand
Illumina hope you're
drinking I'm
drinking I'm lit up right
now I know this is 420 but I'm drunk as
a [ __ ]
I had a friend in La my homeboy
Randy right we in our local dwellings
local hole in the wall bar right my my
boy Randy he's very generous he's go hey
next round on me J
red get some 1800 to
Kaya
right I was like uh no thank you Randy
he's like come on J red I'm buying I was
like I understand appreciate it but I
don't drink 18 to
Caleb like why not so
because that wasn't a good year for
black
people now if you got some 1992
tequa we can get this party cracking
that was a good year Dre dropped the
chronic Chris Cross is making people
jump second season of fresh prison B
what I'm talking about as die [ __ ] will
at his biological
father see I I I just don't like things
that remind me of slavery you know what
I'm saying I I had an argument recently
with my uncle right I told him I've
never ever seen
Roots [ __ ] almost had a contion
y'all you ain't never see Roots what
kind of black person ain't never see R
what is wrong with you boy you need to
go to Blockbuster
right and I don't understand that about
black people right we hate slavery but
love slavery
movies you know that's a very
interesting Dynamic you know that's like
a cow watching how hamburgers are
made why you want to do that to
yourself I don't like things that remind
me of slavery it's one of the reasons I
don't eat cotton candy
I don't even pick the cotton out of
medicine
bottles I use a Visa not a MasterCard
you
understand you get the
picture thanks for coming to the show
man I have some laughs you know what I'm
saying release those
endorphins and heal yourself
laughter does hell man we all need a
laugh every day should have a laugh cuz
we go through hard times I recently had
a friend pass
away and uh it was abruptly on your boy
and I and ever since then I've been
feeling the blues you know trying to
deal with it that was my dog and I
remember during the week of the funeral
right I caught a mutual friend of the
deceased my homeboy Jabar like he Jabar
will you be attending a funeral this
week he's like nah J red I'm not really
a funeral
person and I thought to
myself who
is anybody know any funeral
Enthusiast [ __ ] I'm a funeral
mâché if you dead I'm
there Count Me
In wake me up before you go go
bro [ __ ] be f feral
hopping you know if you rearrange the
letters in the word funeral you'll get
the phrase real
fun is that a subliminal
message are we doing them wrong should
we move the services the Six
Flags I think I would like my granny to
go out like
that roller
coaster do a Lo the loop in the heaven
I don't know if y'all
religious but if you believe that heaven
is above hell is
below shouldn't we stop burying our
loved ones in the ground starl to they
ass in the
space that seem
theological to be closer to
God how come you never see no black
ghost H black people dead too
I'm tired of white people monopolizing
the
afterworld I know there's a black
section if we got a black president it's
time for us some black
ghost no offense I hate white ghosts
yeah I said it play Too Many mind
games while I'm eating my waffles you
know what I'm saying messing with my
light
fixtures open up draws on my armo I
don't appreciate that making weird
noises woo
wo see a black ghost be more
laidback be like
he hey let me holl at you for a second
my
man you got $20 I can borrow real quick
cuz you know they done send me to the
wrong [ __ ] house dog I ain't
even trying to Spook y'all like that
y'all good [ __ ] so if you just
got a couple of dollarss
I'm a sports fan how about
y'all I'm a Raiders
fan I don't
care ain't nothing you can do to talk
somebody out of being a Raiders fans
once you commit you about that life
ain't no going
back I love
football they got rules in the NFL I do
not quite agree with I don't see eye to
eye they have a uh no excessive
celebration in the end zone after you
score a
touchdown they don't appreciate that you
doing the uh
butterfly how dare you show you enjoy
what you do yeah you know yeah sing it
to me brother everybody would dance if
they made a million dollars to play a
damn
game imagine if you made a million
dollars to play
Scrabble oh that's a triple word
score you going to walk it
out I hate that rule no excessive
celebration if I was a white football
player I'd be very
offended like the hell you mean ref I
just ran past 11 black dudes
it is my time to
shine you throw a flag if you want to
I'm about to take five
minutes I love basketball as
well one of my favorite players in the
NBA is Lamar Odum
right I love him and uh I was surprised
when he tied the out with Cho
Kardashian that caught me off g a little
bit so I thought it was illegal for two
men to get
married nonetheless I keep up with the
Kardashians I love them
girls and
dudes they got a taste for chocolate
that won't be
thei they like the Negro College Fund
they they they suck them up man come
here
Kanye I love interracial couples though
I love to see two coaches Collide and
make a happy
happy that's what it's all about man
opposite attract and even myself I've
had my fun in in a racial
son I done bash in
I dated many women from many ethnicities
and through my experiences let me know I
don't care what a woman looks like you
be purple green
turquoise a
fuchsia don't matter to your
boy just as long as you look white
that's what's
important can I get a amen Nicki Minaj
stereotype says black men love white
women that's false truth is all dudes
love white
women it's a black dudes are we run
faster so we get to them first you
understand come here mly
sarus you putting out those Nick feromon
look at our president he's a product of
interracial
Bliss president
obesy got two
terms who thought and I think it's time
we change the name of the White
House that's right the streak is over
now I'm not suggesting we call it the
Chocolate
Factory though that would be
tight he being an accurate you know he
not he he he he's he's like human fruit
punch he got a little bit of everything
in so the name should reflect his
multiracial ethet
background so that's why I'm proposing
we call it the halfway house
he may get commemorated on some money
one
day that'll be a dream come true for me
I've always Envision a black man on some
money cuz I like just just one you know
what I'm saying Stevie Wonder James
Brown just one Mr T just
one cuz I've always had to look up up to
the penny as my black
representative cuz the penny has a
parallel existence to African Americans
if you can't see the
connection cuz look at the penis story
y'all it's the only coin that's a
different color from the rest of the
gang you think that's
coincidence secondly he has the least
value of all the coins ain't appreciated
in the community
thirdly it's not accepted in vending
machines parking meters of
payones otherwise saying we don't serve
your
kind hey come on in Quad nickel and dime
we got drinks in the back DJ spinning
hold on Penny what the [ __ ] I just
say wishing whes and fountains down the
street see I see these racial undertones
y'all don't detect in your everyday
lives but I be using my third eye I be I
be Dan
St that's why I don't eat white
chocolate no
more I realized what Nestle was trying
to tell
me and I know inside your mind it's just
an advancement in candy technology all I
blue
raspberry but what you don't recognize
this is gentrification of
chocolate moving out the dark element
for the safe lighter and
whiter
chocolate how can chocolate be white and
don't make
sense making everything white white
grapes they ain't even white white
grapes white wine it ain't
white use your third eye look at where
you do your laundry that's a very racial
activity
separate I mean segregate the whites
from the
colors why Scar the colors going to [ __ ]
up the white that's right wrong rent
cycle
[ __ ] use your third eye look at
the Michelin Man what is the Michelin
Man he's a person composed the tires
from head to
toe but what color is
it what color a [ __ ] TI
use your third
eye right now and then you know as a
black person you know the nword becomes
very
controversial recently had uh Paula Dean
M
she why did she admit that if there was
a time to lie that was
it yeah she said yes like she they asked
her if she had a Facebook page like of
course who does
it of
course see the N word is very
controversial they say it's about how
you say it and who says it right you can
say [ __ ] but you can't say [ __ ] and I
ain't never understood that
science it's very impractical if you ask
me like if I'm hanging out somewhere and
all of a sudden I hear somebody go get
that [ __ ]
at that moment I ain't thinking about
who said it I ain't thinking about how
they said it I'm just thinking I want to
be the [ __ ] they about to
get so I'm a moon walk out of that
situation I ain't going to take off my
ipod like hey can you repeat
that I need to check the
phonetics black people for years have
tried to count punch the N
word calling white people
crackers and you can't assault somebody
with a snack
term that [ __ ] just rolls off white
people
back epic fail black
people try harder next
time sugar cookie
sorry that's like somebody calling me a
Kit Kat how mad am I going for [ __ ]
big why yes I am sweet and crispy I
appreciate
that I do a lot of jokes about race but
it's just to make fun of the absurdity
of it all that we treat each other
different on on color you know as just
ridiculous cuz I can never judge someone
by the color of their skin that's stupid
instead I choose to judge someone by the
color of their
teeth cuz that's when [ __ ] color
matters if it ain't white it ain't right
white power for
real [ __ ] orange and green and
yellow purple hearts blue
moons I've been thinking about starting
a hate group called The coate
Clan just go around a
horseback looking for fenders of our
law find somebody flossed up from a tree
just
dangling Listerine strips on the
ground I remember I was 5 years old I
lost my two front teeth in a candy apple
incident I was at the state fair I bit
into the apple and my teeth did not come
back strong ass
caramel but I took him out the Apple
and I went home cuz I knew the protocols
to fairy
time and I remember put my teeth under
my
pillow waking up the next morning to a
surprise when I didn't find any
money I found the
joint and I was too young at the time to
appreciate such a
gesture from the weed fairy I Ain
know he
existed you know it would have made k
interesting but I grabbed it and ran
into my parents bedroom my father's
getting out of bed hey morning son like
hey look dad it smell
funny and my father's eyes looking on
humongous as he realized what's in my
hands like oh let me get that from you
son and gave me a
dollar to this day I still don't know if
I sold my father
weed that an awkward transaction
thank you I been Jasper
R hey keep it going for
Jasper my wife needs me to go buy her
feminine hygiene products I don't make a
big deal out of it I just take care of
that
[ __ ] yeah cuz I'm a adult man not some
giggly little high school boy who's like
I can't my bad no I just rise up and go
hey I know that you need that stuff
right now and at the time that you need
it you're not mistake where you want to
leave the house or put anything on other
than the
sweatpants and so I will March out and
buy it like the mature adult partner of
yours that I am and I just go on and on
and on because I don't want to go buy
that stuff cuz it's
embarrassing but eventually I bolster up
my nerve and I cross the park to little
corner store by our house where I can
buy that stuff and as I'm approaching
the door I'm saying cute girls don't be
here cute girls don't be here cuz
there's three really cute girls that
work there and I didn't want to buy
feminine hygiene products from those
cute girls and I get to the door and I
hear Run to the Hills by Iron Maiden
blasting and I go yes cuz that meant
that heavy metal guy was there alone
that day and I open the door and I go
over and I get her the stuff that she
asked for and then I also I guess as
camouflage grabbed a candy bar and a
coke that I didn't even want thinking
[ __ ] he'll never notice him sandwich
between these sugary
treats and I go up and I set it all on
the counter and dude Rings it up but he
doesn't even give a [ __ ] he just knocks
it all into the little bag and tells me
how much money I owe him and I thought
oh great this is perfect thank you heavy
metal dude and I pay him and he doesn't
say a word to me until I'm walking out
the door at which point he says so you
bleeding
Keith to which I would replied like a
stuck pig I am and I ran
home where my wife saw the chocolate bar
in the Coke and thought you really do
get
it and she loves
me my dad was really bad at talking to
us about sex he just was terrible at it
and one day me and my little brother
were in the house alone with my dad and
my little brother comes walking out with
a box of maxi pads and he says hey Dad
what are these and I said that's it
you're on old man what are those and my
dad said oh those yeah those are
Band-Aids for
women my little brother said cool and he
was satisfied I was like all right dodge
a bullet this time and then he goes out
to skateboard and I guess he ate
[ __ ] cuz I see him leaving again a few
minutes later with the board under his
arm only now he's got maxi pads stuck
all over his [ __ ] legs covering every
inch of them I kick my dad and point
this out my dad looks at him and goes
what the hell are you doing my little
brother says what we were all out of
dude
bandaids I said you're on Dad this is
your
moment my dad did the right thing he
said all right sent my little brother
out to get
tough it worked he's a good kid he's
ready for the world you guys ready for
another comedian
W oh man this next guy uh he spent some
time in the Sacramento area doing comedy
while he was going to UC Davis and yeah
now he tours all over the damn country
you guys ready to welcome
him please welcome Dan
Gabriel hi everybody how's it going
I met uh I met Keith uh when I sold him
some
tampons and no I'm not heavy metal guy
all right didn't dress the part hi I uh
I flew up here for this everybody yeah
right put an effort I uh at the airport
in La they pulled me aside and they
peeled apart my luggage in front of
everybody didn't like it I think if they
peel apart your [ __ ] and they don't find
anything you should win a
prize right you should get to claim
something that was confiscated from
somebody
else they're not smoking
it I think that they should put a bucket
outside airport security so when you're
going to go through and you don't want
to throw away your perfectly good uh
lighter or bottle of water or shaving
cream or shampoo you can put it in the
bucket and then when somebody coming off
of one of the planes needs a lighter or
bottle of water some shaving cream it's
free in the bucket it's a good idea huh
yeah uh that would cost nothing I'll buy
the
bucket I also think they should put a
doctor next to the X-ray machine so when
you go through he can tell you if you
have
tumors you know what I mean as long as
they're scanning you might as well tell
you all the information
available doctor be like hey have a good
trip seriously live your life
I get upgraded on the flight I have some
miles and they put me in first class
yeah I'd never been in first class
before and I never ever want to go back
to
coach It's So Good In First Class you
don't even know how good it is when
you're back there you don't even realize
it in first class they're nicer to you
they give they they give you all kinds
of [ __ ] they give you food on a
plate you get
silverware you get alcohol a lot from
the minute you sit down
booze boo booze yeah yeah it's like a
it's and you can have like like one
drink in coach you got to pay for it
it's it's one drink and they make a big
production you got to swipe the card
it's big they make you feel like an
alcoholic In First Class it's like a
frat party they'll hold your head back
and mix
[ __ ] you can do shots out of the uh
flight attendant's belly button
sweet our flight attendant got on the
speaker and she's like attention
passengers we need you to put your
chairs in their upright and locked
positions and put away all portable
electronic equipment and she's looking
over at first class going
it's true there's also no turbulence In
First
Class don't believe they're lies
turbulence is just for the cheap seats
turbulence is actually a button that the
people in first class get to
push sweet don't say
nothing I live in uh I live in LA I live
in the valley in Koga Park in a little
two-bedroom condo that I bought at the
end of ' 07 when it was worth more than
it will ever be worth
again and my creditors are screwing with
me they're all named after [ __ ] that
they really do like
Chase or watch over
you and look I'm I'm a cheap skate all
right I buy the I buy the generic
version of everything I got a Walgreens
across the street from my house I buy
Walgreens everything I don't buy
robotussin I buy wall
batusin I don't buy Jack Daniels I buy w
Daniels I buy cotton
walls
walnuts those are
peanuts cheaper
though I'm on Facebook clap your hands
if you're on
Facebook no clap your hands if you hate
Facebook now fight
all right I'm spending too much time on
Facebook I'm ashamed of it you know what
Facebook is I figured it out Facebook is
the life version of when you're not
hungry but you open the fridge
anyway why am I doing this
it's weird I I hadn't even met Keith the
host before but we're Facebook friends
and I've like it's weird cuz I thought
we'd met before in person we hadn't but
I'm like that's weird I've seen pictures
of your
family why is that why we're very we're
intimate seen your I've seen your most
cherished moments all of them you post
them feel like I know you never seen him
though you know Facebook needs it needs
a dislike button
right yeah it's got a like button I I
would like a dislike button I want to
hate on some
[ __ ] cuz the closest I got now is liking
things that I got no business liking
right you got fired huh
like got dumped huh
like broke your leg huh like buried
alive somebody help like good reception
I uh I watch I watch a lot of the
History Channel you guys watch The
History Channel yeah love the History
Channel makes me feel like I'm not
wasting my day if I'm
learning and when I am learning over and
over again is that I did not learn [ __ ]
in high
school right I spend the whole time
watching The History Channel going
nuh-uh for
real and I recommend not knowing
anything about history for watching The
History Channel right if I don't know
who won that war this is a better
show
compelling I know I know some history
but the the the gaps in my history
folder are are are
thick I know the obvious stuff right I
know George Washington invented the $1
bail and then uh Ben Franklin tied a key
to a kite and freed the slaves with it
and then we got into a World War to save
Private
Ryan and then some other [ __ ] and then
now I watch like four hours on the
Revolutionary War and I'm amazed at how
much footage we have from back
then we got all that [ __ ] on
tape I don't know why they're using
muskets if they had cameras that good
it's hard to watch TV when you live in
LA CU you you get jealous of the people
on TV you get mad at them so now I tend
to watch shows where I'm not jealous of
the stars of the show like
hoarders you guys watch
hoarders I love hoarders hoarders makes
me feel like I got my life together
I can walk through my
hallway I feel bad for the people on
Hoarders I feel like they just ended up
on the wrong
show right if you sent the guys from
American Pickers in there they could
find some good
[ __ ] give them a day get two shows out
of those people one one show and
then treasure and then dead cats
unless the dead cats are
valuable they're golden dead cats then
Pickers hoarders is good I here's what
happens when I watch hoarders I don't
sit and watch hoarders I start cleaning
while I watch
hoarders you guys do that right you have
to while you watch it you need to you
want to make sure you don't turn into
them I don't do that with other shows
sometimes I do the opposite of the show
I'm watching like when I watch The
Biggest Loser I eat a gallon of ice
cream I screams good when I'm watching
fat people
run and skinny people yelling at them
until they
cry and that's how the weight is lost
it's tear
weight
FYI I'm on a diet now I'm on a special
diet I'm on the vowel diet you heard of
it
it's I'm on the vowel diet I can only
eat foods that begin with a
vowel like
apples eggs oats
iy sometimes yogurt
I uh I was watching TV in the morning
and I don't like morning time um
commercials the morning time commercials
make me feel like I'm going to die any
minute right it's always for life
insurance or the scooter
store or I'm Wilford Brimley and I'm the
president of old
people something something something
diabetes really that's how you say that
and then during the afternoon the
commercials change they're they're also
depressing but they they're a different
kind of depressing they make you feel
like a lazy piece of [ __ ] afternoon
commercials make you regret watching
whatever you're watching they make you
feel bad for sitting there right it's
always like do you need a
degree have you lost your way is it
about time you got your
G were you injured in a motorcycle
accident you must been injured right why
else would you be sitting on your ass at
two and then if you can't sleep in the
middle of the night every commercial is
penis
related right oh your dick don't work
take this
pill you want a bigger dick take this
pill oh your dick works then call the
girls on the chat
line got every aspect of your dick
covered oh it's all dick like maybe I
just drank coffee
late is it why is it my dick my dick
coffee I like cooking shows I watch the
[ __ ] out of some cooking shows it's
weird I like like food
porn I got a crush on giat from the Food
Network oh godamn I love giat right
she's always leaning forward showing you
some
cleave she's always got cleavage on that
show I watched that show 500 times I
have no idea anything she's
cooked busy staring at her
rack she's got a dirty look in her eye
like she'd do some crazy [ __ ] and then
make you a
snack right like she toss your salad and
then toss a
salad I knew paulan was a racist I saw
that coming I do I I got her cookbook it
says right in there beat three eggs like
slaves who tried to
escape I'm GNA let that guy finished
laughing sip think of a
joke I was in Vegas like a month ago
clap your hands if you've been to Vegas
hi all of you all right when I'm in
Vegas I got two jobs at night time I do
comedy and during the day I hand out
those hooker cards with the phone
numbers on them flick flick here you go
flick
flick those are like hooker baseball
cards they got stats on the
back there's no
rookies one of my favorite things about
Vegas is the fountain in front of the
Bellagio Hotel you know that Fountain
I'm talking about the best fountain in
the whole world that Fountain is so
awesome that Fountain it's it's if you
don't know the fountain I mean it's the
fountain at the end of the movie Oceans
11 right it's the victory Fountain it's
the fountain that's so kickass that 11
guys who just robbed a casino are still
hanging out out
front every half hour they play a song
over the speakers and the fountain
dances to the song right and if you get
a room at the bage you can look out your
window and see how they do it it's
actually a thousand Mexican dudes with
their thumbs over the end of a garden
hose snorkel
one time I was in Vegas for my sister's
wedding my sister got married there and
I had to arrange my brother-in-law's
bachelor
party that's a weird spot to be in right
he's marrying my sister I don't want to
see that dude getting
pervy I told him I was going to take him
to a place with a lot of young girls and
a pole and when we got to the merry-go
round he was pissed
off cuz I'm not good in the strip clubs
I'm bad at that [ __ ] I'm bad at strip
clubber
cuz I'm more of a cheap skate than a
pervert I'm the dude in the corner
rubbing money on my own
crotch like yeah you're coming home with
me aren't
you it's just you and me sack of your
wheel I was online looking at naked
girls and I saw a girl I went to high
school with and I remember back in high
school I would have given a million
dollars to see that girl naked and I'm
glad I held
out some
money I went to uh go I I had have a new
doctor now at switch insurance and I
went to go meet my new doctor and it
sucks you guys my new doctor is gorgeous
she's hot I don't want a hot doctor it's
messing up my health care I'm lying to
her I can't even help
it she's like Mr Gabriel are you
experiencing any chest pain I'm like you
know only when I bench more than
700 are you experiencing any shortness
of breath like [ __ ] I'm not experiencing
shortness of
anything know what I'm talking
about I've seen Clips where this ends
well I asked the doctor for advice for
my sister my sister and her husband are
trying to have a baby and I asked the
doctor how she could help her chances
and the doctor said if your sister is
trying to have a baby tell her she's
doing it wrong trying is not how babies
are made babies come from the opposite
of trying babies magically appear when
it's the most inconvenient time in your
life if your sister wants a kid tell her
to quit her job and start a
band baby
ah sometimes I think of jokes there
aren't as much jokes per se as they are
theories that I have about some [ __ ]
just uh just some truth I think I
discovered and uh let's do some of
those I think that the drunkness that I
experience from alcohol or the high that
marijuana creates is actually the spirit
form of my brain cells dying and going
to heaven
Che on
it I think seedless watermelons don't
taste as good because they got no reason
to
live I think if video cameras recorded
smell porn would not be as popular
I think based on how they kiss Eskimo
[ __ ] must be terrible
one way to describe the other night is I
had a
threesome another way to describe that
night is I jerked off in front of two
mirrors
framing if you see a guy smelling his
finger he looks like a loser right but
if he's smelling two fingers he kind of
looks like a winner
saying all right this one this one's
kind of
heavy I think that your personality was
created by how good the sex that made
you
was some heavy [ __ ]
right like if you're fun cool outgoing
kind of person it's cuz the sex that
made you was fun and cool and
outgoing and if you're an [ __ ] it's
cuz you're mom wasn't awake
I like it when athletes make bad
decisions cuz it makes me feel like they
don't have the whole world figured out
you know makes me feel better by myself
when when uh people who are perfect
screw
up like um uh you know that like certain
ones I can understand certain ones like
um like uh Tiger Woods I'm not mad at
Tiger I mean he told his wife he was
going out for 18
holes all right let's edit that one out
I'm not mad you know who my favorite my
favorite athlete screw up is is um is
Michael
Phelps I love Michael Phelps he's my
favorite because he's a stoner and a
champion you feel
me I I was mad at Michael Phelps when he
apologized for smoking that weed if
anybody could have gotten away with it
it's the dude who just won more gold
medals than anybody ever right I think
he earned himself a bong
hit if he would have just stood up for
himself he could have proved that weed
ain't so bad yeah he could have proved
that weed doesn't stand between you and
more gold medals than anyone
ever should have been yeah he should
have grew some balls she been like yeah
look I smoke a little weed and I wear a
little gold suck it
[ __ ] have you seen them have you seen
them I'm wearing
them and they're heavy
oh my neck I need a bong
hit my gold so
heavy I was mad at the guy who took that
photo of Michael Phelps right what kind
of [ __ ] friend of yours takes photo
of you doing a bingy and puts on the
internet for your grandma to see a dick
move I started thinking what would what
would make a guy do that and I started
maybe thinking that maybe just give that
guy the benefit of the doubt for a
second maybe that maybe Phelps was was a
[ __ ] that night maybe Phelps you know
what I mean maybe the guy was a good
host maybe he was like hey Michael
Phelps come on in buddy come on I got
some beer you want some pizza I got a B
you want a bong hit pH is like all right
a bong
hit you believe the lungs on this
[ __ ]
dude it's been 8
minutes did he just repack mid
hit that's all the weed we
have [ __ ] this guy where's my
camera that's how that night
happen my other favorite um athlet screw
up or or I think he's a [ __ ] it's
OJ I'm not mad at the murder I get
that I get that I get that [ __ ] not mad
at all fine get it it's the it's the
breaking into the hotel to steal OJ
memorabilia like dude why don't you just
buy a new football and sign
it you're an OJ memorabilia Factory
[ __ ]
take a photo of yourself and sign it in
fact take a photo of yourself wearing
that glove holding a knife and
smiling hot
cakes all right I got to go in a minute
um I thought of an invention I want to
tell you guys about my invention before
I get out of here uh I I I thought this
I want to make an alarm clock that
instead of waking you up with a sound it
wakes you up with the smell of bacon
cooking right how great would that be
6:00 a.m. instead
of you get to
go
ban it's a better way to wake up and
just in case the bacon would work its
way into your dream you ever do that
instead of waking up to the song on the
radio you just start dancing to it in
your dream and then you sleep through
work right so just in case you just
dream you're eating a big pile of bacon
the next smell after the snooze is [ __ ]
you could have woken up to bacon but you
blew
it poo time now get
up you got [ __ ] to
do it's a reminder you go oh yeah I got
to do
that you do it all right quick little
side note I did that joke uh on I'm
sorry to uh repeat the joke but I did
the joke on Showtime like a year ago and
then um a couple of months after that I
got a hundred emails in my in in my
thing uh in my inbox because a dude made
it he made the bacon alarm clock and he
went on Shark Tank to try to get money
for
it and they turned him
down here's the thing I wasn't going to
put in the effort to make that [ __ ] I
just wanted it to exist so I put the the
the I put the wish out in the
world and now I would like a [ __ ]
alarm clock
thank you very much everybody have
a oh damn
Gabriel all are you guys ready to close
this thing
out oh man this guy is H one of our
favorites uh he has opened for Dave
Chappelle and Weird Al
Yankovic but not at the same show cuz
that would be too
awesome please welcome Mr Ango
beum let's hear again for Keith and Dan
and Jasper and Johnny and
yourselves good show Good
Times uh I see you staring at my suit
like are you the black Wily Wonka what
the the Hennessy tastes like Hennessy
it's just good to be here
I am higher than a chola eyebrows right
now
so I Love Weed I don't care who knows I
love Mar I do it makes me a better
parent right I don't beat my kids I'll
talk to them three or four hours they
probably wish I would hit them they're
like man are you still talking can I get
a spanking Jesus wrap it
up my kids know I smoke weed it's not a
secret they know that thanks to
marijuana dad will take him to any
animated feature
ever right what the panda nose fol hell
yeah get in the car why don't you say
some [ __ ] hurry up I don't want to miss
the previews is it 3D tell me it's
3D right you guys go get the
tickets go get the tickets don't look at
me look for cars
go cuz weed and movies go together like
weed and movies you know what I'm
talking
about right that's why I like weed so
much to me it's like the Umami it's like
the ranch dressing it's like the ketchup
of life you know what I'm talking about
maybe some shit's really cool you put
some weed on it it's even a little
cooler you know what I'm talking about
right maybe it's not so cool you put
some weed on it all
right right some [ __ ] I don't want to do
man I don't I'm not I don't want to wash
these dishes you know what I'mma get
high and wash the dishes it takes an
extra
hour right cuz I have to make a
playlist I wash the dishes playlist is
off the hook too it is depends I got
different playlists how many dishes what
kind of of dishes there's extra spoons
there's more sound
garden Spoon
Man love it I love marijuana can we
legalize marijuana in California please
can we do that please pretty please all
over the country really but I live in
California so please right I would like
to open a butt and
breakfast would you come visit me at the
wak and bacon would you come say hi good
morning good afternoon really
because we're not getting up that early
that chocolate I put on your pillow
should knock you the [ __ ] on
out wake up
refreshed matter of fact eat half of
that chocolate first
before you know what I'm talking about
the weat the weed food will get you you
got to be careful right a weed a weed
brownie is an
adventure you can't always time that
[ __ ] anybody you ever been merked on an
edible just
straight got just surprise just
overmedicated just sweaty and confused
on an
airplane where are you taking
me I'm cool I'm
cool can I get some
coffee weed and coffee Poor Man's a ball
I
uh I do I Love
Weed I go hard for weed we try to
legalize weed in California 2010 I went
hard on that [ __ ] I went door too in my
neighborhood behind that [ __ ] right like
a weed hov's Witness
just knocking on doors like I have some
good news about weed can I share it with
you good morning I'd like to talk to you
about my personal relationship with
marijuana do you have a few
moments hi have you accepted weed in
your
life I have some
papers right CU weed is beneficial for
people Beyond just the recreational and
the spiritual uses it has medicinal
properties it helps people all the time
you always [ __ ] marijuana helps with
this marijuana alleviates that marijuana
mitigates this all the time they just
published a study a little while ago
marijuana alleviates the symptoms and
the onset of Alzheimer's disease it's
true how it works is you get so used to
forgetting
[ __ ] you develop a
system right then the Alzheimer's kicks
in you don't even know you just think
you're
high which is not a bad way to
live right it's funny that we Health
with Alzheimer's cuz you do you you
forget [ __ ] when you smoke you really do
really I found hash in my passport one
time that's not a good
idea right never hide hash in your
passport that's the first place they
live like can we see your passport
no I'll race you to the consulate right
now I don't I don't carry weed I don't
carry weed internationally uh uh
domestically I don't give a [ __ ] and
here's a secret TSA doesn't give a [ __ ]
either they don't I've been caught once
or
twice back in the day back in the day
you used to have to tuck it under your
nuts and it was just an Open Secret and
everybody would pretend but now they
don't care I had to go through a scatter
machine one time right and they pulled
me aside sir what's that in your pocket
oh it's a pipe and a small amount of
medical marijuana oh that's not going to
affect the safety of the plane at all I
agree have a nice day you
too wi me toward the
coffee you do you uh I forgot what oh I
remember we
I almost became a Smuggler one time I
had been in Amsterdam for seven days
straight so I
was
high right higher than rant in New York
higher than Grandma's draws you
understand higher than giraffe titties I
was crazy high and I wanted to bring
some of that hash home so I'd come
across a full prooof foolproof plan I
was just going to take a big chunk of
that nepes Temple ball hash and stick it
right in my butt cuz I'm old
school I'm a traditionalist in some
matters sometimes the old ways are in
fact the best ways right you stick it in
your butt and you get on the plane the
Amsterdam hamster gram is what I'm
talking
about when it's
time A friend of mine she brought some
weed back from Amsterdam however she did
not smuggle at home in her
butt you understand the marsupio method
Nature's pouch that's how she brought it
back and of course we smoked it and it
was [ __ ] delicious oh my God I still
it had kind of a Tang to it you know
what I'm talking about just like a pint
of copper and sea water do you know
where I'm coming
from you know what I mean
the only time ever honky lift a joint
that's what I'm
saying you guys don't have
sex there's only one thing better than
having sex smoking weed and having
sex weed and secks go together like weed
and sexs you feel me I like to
incorporate it into the
foreplay I do let her hit the joint
while I do some [ __ ] then I hit the
joint she does some
[ __ ] do the smoke
Pokey right do the smokey pokey and you
smack that ass around that's what it's
all about stick your fingers in all
right take your fingers
out yeah all right put your fingers in
and you make like a come
here here like that motion like that
right feel there's a spongy part feel
for the spongy part it's usually like
are you uncomfortable don't be
uncomfortable this can only help
you if you don't know now you will thank
me later oh my God that Stoner is a
[ __ ] genius watch this [ __ ] this is
crazy we need more
towels only one thing better than
smoking weed and having sex that's
smoking weed and having sex at a hotel
room Hotel sex anybody like hot Hotel
sex I'm Hotel sex [ __ ] gets freaky it
gets loud gets kind of wild try to break
the headboard you know what I'm talking
about about it's not a secret hotels
know you're coming to [ __ ] they know the
fancy hotel has the the padded headboard
now that's so nice right honey this one
has the padded headboard you can leave
the helmet in the car come on let's
hurry
up right it gets wild you're not the
only you ever hear people in the Next
Room doing it and you got to start doing
it in self-defense
right do it enjoy yourself get loud
those aren't your real neighbors you
don't give a [ __ ] you're not going to
see them again I want them to know I
know I went hard she went hard everybody
had a great listen I get crazy side eye
at the breakfast
buffet and I don't give a [ __ ] that's
not the Walk of Shame that's the Walk of
game [ __ ] good
morning good morning yes I am in room 43
yes I
am I'm sorry you had an uncomfortable
conversation with your children I
apologize
but she had the fish nets on man that's
one of my triggers I can't even no I'm
not even hungry I'm just waiting for him
to fix the
headboard and I'm going get some butter
and syrup from the waffle
bar and try to get a late checkout you
feel
me come here my little chicken and
waffle you got to get the ratio
right I Love Weed have I mentioned that
I love it and I know listen listen I've
been smoking weed a long time and I know
it's probably kept me it has probably
kept me from a few things it's true
right I know that it's too late for me
to ever fulfill my childhood dream of
becoming a
ninja I smoke too much weed I forget to
disappear this a big puff of smoke I'm
still standing there
well because it's too late for me
doesn't mean it's too late for other
people I know that there are Stoner
ninjas in the world I know maybe I don't
have empirical evidence but I have
anecdotal evidence of ston and ninjas
you ever walk down the street and smell
weed but you don't see anybody smoking
weed Stoner
ninja weed has also taught me a lot of
things right thanks to marijuana I'm I'm
a good
cook I will every I will invent [ __ ] to
eat every day is like a [ __ ] episode
of
chopped you know what I'm talking about
if we got biscuit and peanut butter we
got peanut butter rolls coming in 12 to
minutes I looked at the pantry one time
we had marshmallows barrin and Top Ramen
I'm making ramen
treats and they were hella good they
were don't use the flavor packet that'll
[ __ ] it up it's not savory
I'm glad you guys know what Top Ramen is
because right sometimes you get an
upscale crowd they just [ __ ] stare at
you like
Robin I had to break it down to a crowd
one time I was like well y'all know a
couple noodles right uhhuh well I can't
afford a [ __ ]
cup trying to get o
noodles no noodles here's the thing
there's a lot of myths about pot smokers
right pot smokers never do anything you
guys are lazy you never do anything we
never do anything like become president
or win million gold [ __ ] medals
swimming our ass off at the Olympics
pots smokers do [ __ ] all the time my
whole point is I like to smoke a joint
and then do something right smoke a
joint and write a song you know smoke a
joint get some booty that's the whole
like the whole thing it's like I
especially love it on the golf course I
love the GOL look at me again black
people should golf every day anytime you
can hit white balls with a
stick it channels aggression did I
mention I get pulled over for [ __ ]
all the time I me straight to the golf
course registration my
ass
four
uh no one's shocked in California no
one's surprised when I pull out a bag of
weed no one's ever right you got a
whiskey and a cigar I got a blunt a Diet
Coke it's a beautiful day we're having a
wonderful time I got paired up with this
random middle-aged white dude one time
down in Sacramento down in El Grove and
uh round around the third hole time to
dial the swing in a little bit right so
I pulled out a fat hoop took a couple
puffs did the neighborly thing hey man
you want to no thank you but do you have
any
crack
no and might I answer I find your
presumptuousness somewhat
off-putting and secondly who the [ __ ]
smokes crack on the golf course what the
[ __ ] that doesn't help your swing
right drug for the right activity that's
my point weed and golf makes sense booze
and golf make a little bit of sense
crack and golf don't make a liquor sense
right you don't do crank and go to the
chess
tournament you don't eat a bunch of
mushrooms and try to run a
marathon what do you mean I'm off
course this whole planet's off
course why am I wearing a number
can't run a marathon of mushrooms take
you three
days laughing and crying the whole time
right crying cuz your feet hurt and
laughing cuz you're happy to have feet
so
uh that's how mushrooms
work some people give weed a bad name
through sheer
dumbassery dumb
acidness the dumbass ification of
America
couple years ago uh Damon sire former
point guard for the Spurs for the
Trailblazers University of Arizona
Wildcats point guard by the way I found
that ironic because we smoked a joint
and he didn't pass it one [ __ ]
time right the point guard supposed to
think pass first you feel me right we
had to put a full court press on his ass
and force a turnover I locked him
down he got arrested at Tucson
International Airport for possession of
weed and the way they found his weed was
he had it wrapped in aluminum foil with
his dumb ass I called this house hey man
it's called a metal
detector they didn't detect them it's
not a marijuana detector they detected
the metal your dumb ass had it wrapped
in dumb ass tuck it under your nuts next
time old school put it in your butt
whatever don't don't put
the everybody in the world knows what
this means everybody you go anywhere in
the world you speak a lot of sign
language you don't know you don't know
you don't know that you know already you
go anywhere in the world this means
let's go some a joint right this means
let me bum a cigarette right
this means I'll trade you for some of
this or maybe a
little just a little
bit see you guys speak s
language it's impressive it's impressive
the human
brain what it's killing you that's good
that's the whole point of a comedy show
I know I know my God I came I didn't
think I was going to laugh this is
amazing to laugh at a comedy
show least you're laughing somebody
holler out to me one time I was on stage
he was all sing a
song the [ __ ]
what goddamn comedy show you don't go
see Willie Nelson tell a joke you hippie
[ __ ] my God hippie K [ __ ] not hippie
[ __ ] although Willie Nelson both are
probably true
this is what happening I maybe I smoked
a little hash and I'm getting kind of
rambly that's what happens when I smoke
I can smoke weed and come out and tell
jokes no problem I practice hash makes
me rambly like Old Hippie rambly you
ever hang out with old hippies those
cats
digress [ __ ] gets
tangential you know what I'm talking
about you ask him how to make a pie
he'll tell you how to grow a tree you
know what I'm coming from are you on my
pie recipe brother that's fantastic I'm
glad that you asked me because we you've
been friends for a while and uh I think
you've earned it um it's very simple
very easy easy to make the first
ingredient as always is love and I know
that sounds corny man but I think it
needs to be said because people always
forget to put it in there right so it's
love and then it's two cups of apples I
recommend a cross between a pink lady
and a Fuji Fuji's a Japanese Apple you
know apples started all the way in
kazakistan and they came all the way
around the world and there's so many
different varieties now so it's a cross
between a pink lady and a Fuji you know
what I have seeds for those come over
here follow me oh check out this poster
I got this in winterland in
1972 and that's Dave grisman and that's
Miles Davis Miles signed it we stayed up
all night miles had this kind of opium
that he had brought back from Nepal and
we wrote this 12 tone Blues thing listen
brother it's two cups listen it's love
it's two cups of apples qu teaspoon
cinnamon oh not you know what I have
wheat seeds in here too I almost forgot
I got them from my friend Running Bear I
met him in 1982
at a rainbow gathering in Wyoming we
stayed up and we did these mushrooms and
we hybridized a new weed it's
gluten-free but you still get the flaky
crust cuz the government is [ __ ] up
the food supply listen so it's love two
cups wait a
minute what are your intentions with
this
pie cuz it affects the nutmeg is this
like a pie of Love or a pie pie of
hunger and then it soon became a pie of
patience it took me 15 years to get that
recipe but it was the best pie I'd ever
had in my life but only because I was
ready for
it my tree had
grown some of you are completely with me
some of you just staring at me like
trout right
now talk about your dick or something
it's huge
I'm kidding you're going to feel a
little bit of pressure right behind your
eyes now look
uh yes yes you used to be legal did you
know that in America the United States
it was legal till 1937 the founding
fathers grew it smoked it Declaration of
Independence originally written on hemp
paper hemp right Marijuana pot better
paper than trees better fabric than
cotton and you can smoke it and talk
about [ __ ]
right life liberty and the pursuit of
happiness write that
down we'll forget don't forget that [ __ ]
write that [ __ ] down right that's why
John Hancock signature was so big he was
high as hell hell yeah I'll sign that
[ __ ] look look I'm on one
foot the founding followers were high
you have to be high a fly kite in a
thunderstorm Ben Franklin the biggest
little left-handed Stoner of them allall
what's the national bird the bald eagle
what bird did Ben Franklin want for the
national bird turkey
Stoner Ben the eagle flies graceful
Majestic and free above the clouds yeah
but you can eat a turkey
brother there's John Hancock [ __ ] I'll
sign for that man
starving let me just say by the way I
don't care what drugs you're on right
now if you're on the booze that's cool
if you're here underage drinking that's
cool too don't tell me just know that I
don't give a [ __ ] I really don't uh we
all did the underage drink and everybody
did the underage drink and all the bars
in my neighborhood were surprised when I
turned
21 they were shocked right I showed up
woo it's my 21st birthday [ __ ] you
have a tab
here it's your picture on the wall what
the [ __ ] you're on the softball team
what the [ __ ] do you mean
youve been drinking here six years how
the [ __ ] are you just
now everybody's on drugs you're all on
some sort of drug right now whatever
drug booze weed Valium oxy Aderall yoga
ass whatever drug whatever drug you're
on and that's cool I don't give a [ __ ] I
don't care just let me know right if
you're acting all crazy and I ask you if
you're on drugs be honest cuz I don't
care I just want to know like are you
crazy or are you just [ __ ] up because
it makes a difference and I'm down to
help I don't care I don't do a bunch of
easy I'll give a [ __ ] I'll buy you an
orange juice I will I'll let you rub my
jacket put your face in it I'll give you
the car wash Lean Back Lean Back
I just stand behind
you I don't really know how to do
that but you get the gist I'm a helper
yes I'm a
giver oh
weed Love It I Love Weed tell you a
story long time
ago me and my homie Brian did a show up
in hul County California hul county
right right exactly uh for those who
don't know they grow some of the best
weed in the continental United States
right now uh it's a college town and yet
the children send money
home
um so we came back from humbo we had no
money but we had a
bat
sack crazy Northern California humo
County stinky F you know the kind of
weed you don't smoke right away you
invite all your friends over just to
look at it for oh come let us adore it
oh please L me fat bhe it was 3 o of
weed and it was on one bud you said
three one bud it was like a tree really
we put it in the corner we put lights on
it and [ __ ] people came over with gifts
we held hands in a circle oh mighty Bud
oh mighty bud please get us through the
solstice Brian had made a bong out of a
bicycle
pump one of those old schoolers right
just straight up
they were just over High just Jaba the
Hut
sto arguing over who's going to use the
remote control you do it I
can't I can't even call Little
Caesars cardboard
cardboard this is way back in the day so
we're watching Nick at night
surprise Mr Ed which is a fine show of
course of
course and then after Mr Ed was The
Patty Duke Show right cuz they're
cousins identical cousins in every way
and Brian couldn't take it wait hold on
wait time
out identical cousins
that doesn't make any
sense I'm sitting there brother you just
watched a talking horse for half an
hour you have [ __ ] to
say why are the Kardashians famous and
everybody's like well she made a sex
tape I'm like Have You Seen Her tape
she's not good at that
either oh you can't make fun of people
[ __ ] yes you can if they're bad at it
and then they try to sell it yes you
can sorry I've seen
professionals guys are all confused porn
is a$1 15 billion doll a year industry
it's not just me I'm not the only
[ __ ]
guy watch porn girls watch a lot of porn
everybody watches porn I like to make up
freaky sounding pornsite names in my
head and then I type them into the
internet to see who beat me to it
yeah hairy thrusting monkey
ass.com well I'll be
damn
bookmark you don't don't bookmark the
porn your mom might want to come over
just going to update my Facebook what's
this thrusting monkey ass ah [ __ ]
cats I'm
excited cuz Hempfest season is coming
up I [ __ ] love a Hempfest I do them
all every single one everyone I can go
to right Seattle Hempfest Portland
hempstock Southern Oregon Hemp Fest Bay
are H Fest International cannabis and
hbi hemp con Kush KH I'm throwing a
Cannabis Cup I'm I went to the other
Cannabis Cup I'm going to the other
Cannabis Cup we're doing a cannabis
comedy night right [ __ ] now and it
occurs to me that weed is the only
illegal drug that people throw festivals
for
right you never go to meth
Fest hey welcome to meth
Fest who stole the [ __ ] sound
system smoke weed you guys my name is
have a good night
he