[Music]
drinking with the Earth it's fun get
Dr well
hello hello
[Music]
welcome to a very very very special
edition of drinking with Ian we have got
a lot of surprises in store for you our
guest tonight is mistress Jean
BAU and our musical guest tonight is
plastic cord and now the one the
only i' come between you two guys how
you doing welcome down to the show how
you doing you need to get another beer
how you doing how's everybody doing
tonight
hey welcome to drink the everybody can I
get a hell
yeah sweet um there table's gone this is
the first uh episode of our fifth
season I know and this is that means
it's been three seasons since I figured
we'd have been Famous by now okay we'll
do this for a couple seasons and then
we'll move on to the big time and you
know wipe the dust off our shoes of this
one horse town but I guess it hasn't
happen ladies and gentlemen in a man has
been with us the entire time ladies and
gentlemen
[Applause]
Neil oh it's been five SE Five Seasons
where I keep on saying ladies and
gentlemen when I'm nervous isn't that
horrible um then hey the bartender the
Stars Mr Ali
stench hey everybody how you
doing you ready for a
shot all right uh before I I actually
tell you the shot I got a little story
uh the neighborhood I grew up in in
South Minneapolis in the in the mid '70s
uh there was this place that I always
thought was a Thai restaurant and it was
called the bamboo Hut and uh one day I
was out walking around and I was kind of
hungry and I went in and everything on
the menu was really really expensive and
I couldn't figure it out and uh so I
turned around and walked out but the the
one thing that that I remember was uh
there was something called the happy
ending and it was
$100 and I'm trying to think you know
what the hell is worth a hundred bucks
at a at a place called the bamboo Hut
and I still haven't figured it out out
but in honor of that tonight's shot is
called the happy
ending and to make a happy
ending oh I trained you people so
well you take a shot shot of
icehole cherry
schnaps and you take a shot shot of soda
water water and you take a shot shot of
lemon lime Li
add a little ice
ice yeah it's good to live in the past
isn't
it 3 seconds in the past but still in
the past you shake it up up you strain
it
yes and if someone can tell me why a
happy ending cost $100 in a tie Place
shots on the house and tip your
waitresses yeah all right everybody if
you wonder why a happy ending cost you
$100 not here it's free shots on the
house let's bring them out Make Way for
our lovely and talented shot
professionals that coming through the
audience right now who needs
shots oh that dude we're coming back out
for you
off everybody have them
now all right well here let's just pull
them off we'll give them back we'll give
them you some more in a little while
that's good enough we've killed enough
time here already times of the essence
man we're all young right all right
everybody what were we saying oh yeah
hey everybody the Happ Ever After on
three one 2 3
salute ah damn taste sensation as I say
every time that was good that actually
wasn't bad that's icehole schnaps what
are you yelling
about what did I
say oh that was from a different episode
what was this one the happy ending
sorry I'm getting old that was the happy
ending everybody a round of applause
yeah we'll be able to edit around that
it um speaking of editing things um we
have our friend Neil here one more time
Round of Applause um now thank you he uh
he is much more than just the Sean tour
of drinking with the and he is also a
man about town a bond Vivant if you will
um and especially uh in the goth scene
is that right Neil well I I like to turn
myself a recovering goth yeah yes how
are you recovering you're wearing more
eye makeup than I am well and I'm
wearing a lot see but back in the day I
used to wear about are we going to are
we going to we going to have a flashback
yeah is the screen going fuzzy we're not
no on the weekends I actually wear um
about four times as much I makeup all
right and uh there's something here in
town called goth prom that evidently is
a favorite amongst you people I love it
when we Nam check and nobody applauds
yeah
nobody and we set Neil there we taped it
we edited just for you let's watch
[Applause]
[Music]
it at goth BR good evening this is Neil
shant tour to the stars of drinking with
Ian I'm here at the fourth annual goth
prom at the saloon in Minneapolis okay
do you like boys I like boys and girls
oh we got one of those by now gay later
people here so chaps are good I mean
well for example if you don't
mind this my friend Ricky yeah I know
Ricky that that's Ricky's butt yes right
there I can put the microphone on it I
don't know if it talks it doesn't
talk well sometimes I think I'm not sure
actually yeah I've heard it talk a few
times it was sort of a low
growl oh please you know it's my peeps
actually they're my geeps I guess
they're my goth
Peeps and do you like boys or girls boys
he likes boys so tell me
Rainer Neil Sean tour of drinking with
Ian coming to you in my Gothic
confessional I've got the coat I don't
have the collar but I've got the
initiative let me tell you something I
actually got two people to come and join
me my dear friend's
Moren hello and my dear friend Jason
hello you're very popular in the Jewish
Community that's what I heard because
I'm circumcised have you ever been to
church before I've been in churches yes
I was never raised in a religious
atmosphere but yes I have been to church
I've never knelt on anything this is
kind of freaky never knelt on anything
she
says I find that hard to believe
in if there was one um album in your
collection that was very embarrassing
that you wouldn't admit to
anybody what would that album be
ail
LaVine ail
LaVine did you know that goth prom was
tonight actually no I had no
idea um are either of you in the
slightest bit gothy at all probably no
after tonight maybe ooh we've got a
recruit
[Applause]
that was uh Neil at goth
prom and it's honest we didn't even
really need to send Neil to goth prom
that's pretty much every night with
Neil um all right now uh we have our our
next guest somebody we've tried to get
on the show for a while now she's a
local Legend of sorts and we're thrilled
to have her with any uh further Ado put
your hands together for mistress Jean
day how are you I'm doing great how you
doing I'm
C thanks for showing up to this thing
hey fa uh you're the only guest we've
ever had that uh brings their own
suitcase but I guess we'll get back to
that won't we we have a suitcase right
here that's yours I assume it's full of
Contraptions treats treats hey there's
going to be treats tonight who doesn't
like
treats all right so tell me about your
childhood we're on a big couch let's go
back in time
are you ready for this I'm Dam yeah damn
straight yeah I came from a normal
Catholic uh you know family I have two
sisters a mom and a dad yeah and uh we
grew up on a farm uh milking cows is
that around here um suburb above oh okay
so in the neighborhood all right it's
about 40 minutes 50 miles away something
and when did you realize that you didn't
want to be Jean anymore you wanted to be
mistress Jean like how how young of a
gal were you 10 wow
11 uh and what there there 10-year-old
boys that were yeah um I grew up on a
farm so therefore I did not grow up in a
neighborhood there was no neighborhood
Clan there you know miles and miles of
cattle wow okay yeah cattle cattle that
need to be hurted oh okay restrained
controlled controlled wow all right and
uh and what brought you to town when did
you when did you finally let this
you can see into my soul can't you I
look into your eyes and you can see into
the dark recesses can you this is pretty
good damn therapist I know you are
unfortunately I have a lot of [ __ ] I
want to keep married you get back to
Indiana often no no I haven't been there
in years are you okay with that I'm
[ __ ] great with it when's the last
time you've been to Indiana it's it's
been a while
[Laughter]
yeah you are so cute look at
that it's rare when I blush when I have
an erection this is nice all
right uh what's like uh now when you
hear about uh this you generally think
it's old businessmen or at least I do
because I'm a jaded jaded bastard um but
yeah you just kind of imagine it's you
know guys who are 45 we have three kids
who just you know need to get you know a
little bit of smacked out of them is
that the case you no it's not I have I
have men and their girlfriends and their
wives come and visit me Jesus really
that was that's he said these guys
aren't rich cuz they have a girlfriend
and a wife damnn you
know hell I I'm broke I ain't got
[Laughter]
nothing but yeah so what kind of people
do you generally have uh being dominated
je people who are very open sexually
iing imagine yeah which we have a
volunteer here don't we who's a woman
it's not me no it's not um all right hey
okay well everybody round of applause
our
volunteer all right here come on um all
right so what's your name Angelina
you're not miked are you Angelina that's
okay it doesn't matter what you have to
say all right well let talk into my
chest talk into my chest um all right so
we have M Jean and you volunteered for
this by the way why what made you say
hey holy Christ I'm going to totally
volunteer for this I assume this mic
will be on soon because I'm a very bad
girl you're a bad girl so you need to
get you need to get punished she's bad
everybody and she and you came here just
to dram with e you just came here to
have a whole bunch of drinks and have a
good time little did you know you'd be
on stage about to be you know bound ooh
hey paddles I brought some paddles with
me hey nice leather they got the holes
so there's no have to worry about you
know air resistance and stuff or some
hearts you know a Little Valentine a
Little Valentine experience you know a
little
love and what are we going to do to our
our Ur while volunteer here oh God lots
of things can I have you take your shirt
off please
let's be sexy about
it there you go a hand
there and your shoes darling thank you
set up front yeah we're in Chuck Taylor
huh glad you dressed up for tonight all
right sweet these are my special loc hey
you took your shirt off you're fine with
me hours ago
cool all right we have what seems to be
a normal chair a noral First Avenue Bar
Stool and God I'm well to bed it's never
seen anything like this before I want
you to stand right here in front of it
okay face me okay undo this and undo
that
right did you wear the good undies today
no no no just that's all you had to
do get the hell out of the way give me
your right hand right hand and and and
and right now I am tying her yeah yeah
yeah cuz I'd like to immobilize her a
little bit well yeah I want to see some
squirming but I don't want her to run
away exactly yeah you don't want her to
start swinging back either that's that's
that's why I do it so I'm going to tie
her up give me your other hand
honey hes
there usually I take more time at this
yeah oh a little well yeah but she's
also not oh wow hey there's
yeah now we're GNA doing so far we
enjoying the night no no bend over bend
over there we go
and I was nervous at the interview
portion of this this is don't fall down
how's that do we got the crane on this
one there how's it looking I I hey it
looks great yeah yeah do you want to
help oh honey uh yeah if you want me to
help Yeah by all means I really don't
know what the hell I'm doing put your
hands together like this what I'm doing
what
[Applause]
yeah thank
you you know you figure we'd really you
know know how much ratings we get you
know oh hey there's a lot
of that works all
right [ __ ] really this was not this was
not disgusting at
[Music]
B I I didn't know about it either
[Applause]
no oh somebody's
fired oh honey are you okay and you were
offended when I moved your
mic I want this to be safe St and
consensual honey it's okay that's fine
okay then we're going to get rid of
spanking you ready oh sure yeah
[Applause]
I can't see
anything you can't see anything I I can
see
[Music]
plenty oh hey how you doing hey the mic
works now
sweet you go harder oh we're getting a
request for it to be done harder that's
she wants it harder yeah that's what she
said yeah why don't we have a mic on
somebody give her a mic this sounds
great
Ian you were so easy to tie up hey
you're telling me are you kind of [ __ ]
yes are you a little [ __ ] girl
yes I'm a [ __ ]
oldy not that
I know that's the second time I've done
that on this show by the way those are
cute panties by the way there's like
little you have a
cat not that
[ __ ] hey Ollie do we have any of those
shots left
over ladies and ladies and gentlemen you
can use
things hey I have one of those
toothbrush you don't have any plaque
back there do you any
buildup are we using a fluoride with
this is this like
a
hey hey stereo that is
nice is that tickle honey tickle
what else do I have oh I have one of
these
yeah say
something
hey that that that's the good kind of
untie all
rightwe you're free yeah I know I'm just
a [ __ ]
oh Ian do you want to help would you
like to spanker oh yeah sure why not um
I'm a train professional why not yeah
yeah use oh some love all right I don't
do I use the I should use the I assume
for detail work here just
like all right so are you right-handed
or left-handed I'm left-handed well it
depends on what I'm doing I guess you
know you're spanking you're spanking
leftand or right well you know what
oddly enough this is the first time this
is coming let's find out see what works
you know I think I'm right handed yeah
all
right how's that does that suck is that
all right sweet all right let's try that
one
then hey look your butt's on TV can you
see that no what about now all
right hey Jim just runs on stage um all
right well I think um I think we
probably need a high coup right about
now don't we
here you take the top I'll take the
bottom this will be great come
on I'm getting comfortable now this is
sweet use the ball gag right I don't
know where that might's been I do all
right ladies and gentlemen yeah we have
a hiker jimm here uh you just stay where
you are don't
worry you here you try it feels good I
to give it now come on get some wrist
into it there you are right
all right ladies and gentlemen hiu
[Music]
[Applause]
Jim wow what a great gig this is isn't
it I do have a haiku
today and of course it's in honor of
mistress Jean and our uh lovely
contestant and it goes like this the
dominatrix rubber suit whips
thigh high boots sure beats
waitressing I love how you fit in beats
um let one more time for hu
jip all right believe it or not we have
a short film too this one's by our
friend Chris Lynn take a
look for years balloon animals have
fascinated us with their bright colors
and interesting
shapes get as beautiful as they are
these creatures often live tragically
short lives that are filled with abuse
torture neglect and ultimately
abandonment so what happens when these
normally docel creatures have had enough
what happens when the balloon animal
gets pushed too far for the first time
on television prepare to explore the
Dark Side of balloon animals and see
what happens when balloon animals attack
back see amazing actual footage of
balloon dogs rabbits giraffes and even
tiny turtles getting their revenge on
unsuspecting humans it's the television
special the rubber balloon industry did
not want you to see and want you and
your family cannot afford to miss when
balloon animals attack this Friday at 8
pure discretion is
[Music]
advised hey everybody believe it or not
we have
sponsors people who give us their money
to so we can keep on doing shows like
this and why wouldn't you want to
support them here let's take a look at
them we'll be right back with a plastic
[Applause]
card our next band is spectacular
they're new to the scene but I think
they kick a whole lot of ass and I think
you will too uh they have a new new uh
album in stores right now called
Colonial conundrum put your hands
together for the plastic card
[Applause]
[Music]
come us
the
face in
[Music]
the cross the station
yeah oh
[Music]
n
[Applause]
ladies and gentlemen the plastic C
ladies and gentlemen a plastic
[Music]
card I'd like to thank [ __ ] all right
I'd like to thank blastic cord I would
like to thank mistress Jean BAU
everybody and most of all I'd like to
thank all of you for showing up tonight
that's drink it with the end this week
see you next
time every Saturday night I will
publicly um um humiliate and dominate
people that willingly come up to me and
ask me to do such things okay uh and and
by humiliate what does that mean so you
just tell them they're fat that's kind
of what I my stick's been so far you'll
save money and time you'll get the best
of merchandise and service when you
patronize these good neighbors no beer
in the midwest has a grander brewing
tradition than Grain Belt for over 100
years grain Bel has been the beer that
fathers have passed on to sons and
friends have passed amongst each other
at local bars and watering holes it is a
beer with tradition that spans
Generations which is why it has become
legendary both here and across the
country next time you go out ask for a
premium shamur is France's most exciting
new brand of wine uniting the colors
flavors and Aromas of France's most
celebrated wine making regions shamur is
delightfully and deliciously original
our wide pallet of wines contains a
treat for every taste bud offer yourself
a glass of shamur and see what the
flutter is all about to find out more
say bonjour to shar.com if there's one
thing we like better than booze it's
cheap booze and that's why we chose
Merwin Liquors as the official drinking
withian liquor store great deals a huge
selection they even have a contest where
customers can win free drinks for a year
Merwin Liquors is hard to beat yeah it's
a bit ghetto but up your street cred and
Save A Buck or two stop in at Merwin
Liquors at Lindale and West Broadway in
North Minneapolis just two blocks west
of 94 or visit Merwin lick.com
[Applause]
drinking with the end is proud to be
sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV Vodka
no matter if it's UV blue raspberry UV
red cherry UV green apple UV Ivory
vanilla or UV orange vodka UV flavored
vodka offer a premium product without
the high price tag please visit UV
vodka.com for additional information and
recipes a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest news source and the AV club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at news stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at theonion.com
and avclub.com pizz luche proudly
supports drinking with Ian free delivery
until 2:30 a.m. weekdays and 3:30 a.m.
weekends download our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with Ian is nothing
without our sponsors please support them