[Music]
with the end it's time let's
drink oh thank you thank you so much
we've got a great show for you guys
tonight we we have our special guest
Philip Hansen and the band is disaster
[Applause]
Ai and now the man the one the only
yeah hey
everybody Welcome to Dr with how you
doing tonight nice to see so many happy
people
[Music]
here how everybody doing
[Applause]
tonight oh God we have a Humdinger of a
show for you are you ready I mean are
you guys ready look a little you look a
little green you look a little pink you
look a little scared but God we have a
great show I cursed twice and we haven't
even introduced Neil Neil
everybody our Shan tour and of course
every episode dring with Ian has one
very special thing it's not my charming
personality it's shots to deliver that I
want to rousing Round of Applause for
Oli Stitch the bartender of the
[Music]
[Applause]
Stars hey everybody how you doing
now uh I'm going to take you back to a
simpler time a simpler time when I hung
out with my friends Richie and poy and
Ralph and
Fonzi and we hung out at this place
called Arnolds and it was really cool
and uh some of you may know about it
they they made a little TV show about it
called happy days but let me tell you a
secret the reason we were all so like
happy and
Blissful was because of a secret
ingredient that Arnold would put in his
uh Cherry Cokes for us
and that secret ingredient was icehole
Cherry schnaps yeah so in honor of those
simpler times tonight's shot is called
Arnold's
icehole and to make Arnold's ice hole
you take a
shot of icehole cherry
schnaps you take two shots
shots of Coca-Cola
add a little ice ice shake it to the
left left shake it to the right
right take a strainer which I lost
temporarily
temporarily good good going uh strain
it and the thing that got me through all
Ralph mouth's bad
jokes Arnold's ice hole shots on the
house ladies and gentlemen
get ready for Arnold's ice hole we have
our shot professionals making their way
through the crowd all right everybody
Arnold's
icehole all right on three 1 2 3
salute ah now that's an AM sensation am
I
right ring Round of Applause for the
first shot of the
night now believe it or not uh we
actually have sponsors on this show we
have great people that help bring this
quality entertainment to you gr belts
one of them icehole obviously one of
them as well but we have a new one and
this new sponsor might kind of scare off
our existing sponsors that's why we
signed them to
contracts this is a good one take a look
at the big screen and now another fine
product from Redneck Trailer
Farms breakfast is boring and eally
impure
hey kids W you ready to segregate
breakfast from other meals of the day
it's the BR
wizard
[Music]
yeah W uh-oh this Cal's in the wrong
neighborhood I better say the magic
words ncar
Kazam yay thanks Brand wizard hey no
problem kids Clan brand is pure fleach
white O Cereal it's great for breakfast
or lunch
y it's nice and soft because racist
people got rocking
teeth and hey guys check this out the
milk stays white
yeah hey who wants more Clan brand I do
I do
[Applause]
yeah Clan brand cereal from the makers
of separate but total
[Applause]
[Music]
you can quit your own show right you can
just Clan brand ask for it by name and
store in the South
probably all right um our first guest
tonight is somebody I'm thrilled to have
on the show he's a local artist of great
repute um you see him all the time on
the internets cuz he does a lot of
really cool stuff and show some of this
to you I want to Rouse a round of
applause for our first guest Mr Philip
[Applause]
[Music]
Hansen oh
[ __ ] I made
it one for you one for
[Music]
[Applause]
me let down with
belon all right well um let's uh let's
uh introduce you to these guys a little
bit tell me a little bit about yourself
uh came to Minneapolis 2 years ago to
focus on Art left Seattle and all my
friends in my life and family and just
became a Hermit uh work at Regions
Hospital and just focusing on Art it's
been a fun year and I'm waiting to see
what goes on from and what brought you
to what brought you to our Fair Twin
Cities middle of nowhere yeah exactly
throw a throw a dart at a map that's
what I did yeah and uh you mentioned
you're all about the art what got you
interested in this stuff this wacky art
stuff that the kids do well I mean I've
been doing art for years but then got
introduced to YouTube and found more
that I could use YouTube
to actually expose more people to Art
and to uh uh record my art and show the
process and just kind of have a
different sense to the art as well all
right now um I'm going to I'm going to
give you a word and then I want you to
tell me what you have done with well I'm
going to give you a product or a you
know some sort of substance and uh I
want you to tell me what you have done
with it uh wine I froze different colors
of wine and make a picture of Amy wine
housee and then let it deaw and just
watch her degrade
away which which you can just do on
Perez Hilton but yeah yeah matches
matches uh actually we will get to see a
little clip of this um but I colored all
different kinds of matches did 6,000
matches stuck stacked them all to make
Jimmy Hendricks lit them on fire
nice french fry greas french okay hold
on we we have a mic
thing like
it's i' help but we're professionals
here we want them to be heard just talk
loud talk loud yeah Pat a face towards
me cuz that's where the mic's hiding now
all right um yeah all right here just
say something real quick uh something
real quick that's not bad it's better
okay going to work um all right uh
french fry grease french fries I took
french fries and smeared them onto paper
and I had a black canvas behind that so
then of course paper becomes transparent
I used one large fry from McDonald's to
make a picture that was like 14 feet
wide 8 feet tall that's a lot of that's
a lot of damn lot of Grease um now uh
here's here's a good would you rather
hear blood or chewed pastries who says
blood who says who says chewed pastries
chew past so tell me about the chewed
pastries chewed pastries I went to a a
Starbucks and got one of every pastry
they had in a little glass case um
chewed him up and spit him out and made
a picture of Britney Spears Britney
Spears and the blood the blood uh I used
I took a 6,000 Band-Aids and made a 4x8
foot canvas of Band-Aids just a little
white part that you'd actually stick on
the cut and then I stabbed myself and
got 500 milliliters of my own blood and
made a picture of Kim Jong El wow you
know what the street value of 500 mlit
of of blood is probably like 30 bucks
not bad yeah um but hey he's not just
talking about it he's actually doing it
let's uh take a look at some of a we got
a short film here showing you in
action so here we have the Jimmy
Hendricks one oh it's choppy
oh well when we put it in later I'm sure
it'll look great here okay here's HRI
and all the all the matches and then
this piece this was 30 different
pictures I painted one on top of another
they was were all people or things that
represented people that influenced me
and at the end here I actually peel the
entire thing off it about a qu in thick
and I was able to cut a self-portrait
out of it all the influences and here's
my Bruce Lee one many people have seen
this one I dip my hand in paint and Kate
chop the wall to make a picture of Bruce
Lee and sometimes I use my head or my
feet or whatever well yeah you got paint
you got body parts why
not yeah 14t 7 and 1/2 ft tall somewhere
long in there boom that was pretty
awesome
now we get to see the reason for the
tricycle I wrote up on this is my newest
piece uh so I was able to pour paint
into that top part and it dripped onto
the wheels and I rode around and
eventually I was able to make a picture
of Lance Armstrong after two weeks worth
of work that thing's damn yeah 12 pretty
intense that was huge and and that's the
clip okay wow well more round of
applause for Philip here this is
insane now um and they said this is on
YouTube now you get a lot of hits people
checking out what you're doing yeah
online it's kind of wild uh I I think
people I you know I always strive to
keep my work as high quality as possible
so I'm not putting crap out there yeah
so whenever I put something out people
tend to go for it and I've have
somewhere around 20 million views
overall now damn now how interactive
does this get I mean I know that I know
you've done some work but they actually
relied heavily on the people who are who
are watching you do this stuff on the
internet like how's that affected you um
well actually I tend to be I tend to
isolate myself more now than that's what
happens when it start talking to people
like yeah I'm done yeah originally you
know it was great because all this you
know all these emails and everything
then I realized that you know I got a
lot of hate emails well that doesn't
make you feel good that doesn't make you
think you're heading in the right
direction so after a while I was just
like screw it and just kind of kept
doing my own thing and ignored a lot of
it yeah ignore hate maale people it's
just drags you down we don't have time
for the hater
R all right um now how do the internet
actually change your art now did you
make it did you start aiming for what
people were looking for or did you just
totally you know get rid of that like uh
well I mean because I mean the large uh
what's what's the one it's the large
round one um a moment I call it a moment
yeah and that one and tell people about
this one cuz this one's really cool yeah
this one it was a 10ft rotating disc
kind of like this table except 10 ft and
the whole thing would spin I spent uh 6
days locked in my brother's garage I had
um a bed there everything I ordered food
so I never left the garage for six days
and I took phone calls I broadcast my
phone number on the internet had people
call me tell me something that CH yeah I
had to change numbers after that and I
wanted them to tell me something that
changed their life and so I got
everything from being raped to having
children and just all you know drugs but
coming out of drugs going into drugs
anything that you can think of had like
over 600 people from everywhere from
batswana Russia uh Germany all over Asia
and America and whatnot and all these
people contributing to this one piece it
was amazing and cuz you're taking what
they were saying and when you pull back
it's a large self- pure right yeah it's
something else and uh what's the website
uh fill inthe circle.com pH yeah I mean
seriously go check the stuff out it's
pretty damn amazing um what's the one
big thing you haven't done yet what do
you what do you want to do next or what
do you what after it's all said and done
you're laying in your death bed what's
the one thing you want to say that
you've done uh actually there's there's
one that I want to do out in the desert
but it's going to take probably three
months of my time and just kind of
isolating myself with some probably some
illegal illegal immigrants hired and
just go I thought you going with drugs
generally when I'm generally when I'm in
the middle of the desert I'm not looking
for
immigrants look some peyote man come on
seriously help a brother out but anyway
but yeah but coyot fans are here
tonight yeah but uh well that's actually
that's probably all I'll say about it
but oh see that that's the biggest dry
HP of an answer ever oh it's going to be
great and I ain't telling you nothing
aome you view it from above it'll be in
the you know it'll be in the square mile
size range viewed from above that be
good wow yeah well you have any words of
wisdom for our fine television and
studio
audience just keep doing it you know
ignore everything else in life friends
family just total isolation
it works it does ladies and gentlemen a
man a man
pH now another man and myth I want to r
a round of applause yet again for Mr Hau
Jim wow thanks everybody uh I appreciate
that you know this one um goes out to Mr
Phil Hansen you need to go to his
website and check it out and go to
YouTube and check it out it's pretty
cool Phil inth circle.com that's pH in
in the circle check it out it's
mindboggling what he does okay now I
have a little artsy haiku for you as
well goes like this Phil Hansen's
genius thousands of whispering
Parts one bellowing
hole thank you I don't get
[Music]
[Applause]
it do you need an explanation on this
you need CRI notes well take a look at
take a look at I mean it's we're talking
6,000 pieces of band
oh yeah and each of those little Parts
is Whispering to make one huge final
dramatic product am I wrong okay no
you're right no no yeah when you say
huge billowing hole I don't know how you
spell hole hole okay I haven't made
haven't made art with that yet but yeah
exactly in due time all right everybody
we'll be back in a couple minutes with
more wacky drinking with stuff maybe
next
time you'll save money and time you'll
get the best of merchandise and service
when you patronize these good neighbors
no beer in the midwest has a grander
brewing tradition than Grain Belt for
over 100 years Grain Belt has been the
beer that fathers have passed on to sons
and friends have passed amongst each
other at local bars and watering holes
it is a beer with tradition that spans
Generations which is why it has become
legendary both here and across the
country next time you go out ask for a
premium if there's one thing we like
better than booze it's cheap booze and
that's why why we chose Merwin Liquors
as the official drinking withian liquor
store great deals a huge selection they
even have a contest where customers can
win free drinks for a year Merwin
Liquors is hard to beat yeah it's a bit
ghetto but up your street cred and Save
A Buck or two stop in at Merwin lickers
at Lindale and West Broadway in North
Minneapolis just two blocks west of 94
or visit Merwin liquors.com
[Music]
drinking with the end is proud to be
sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV Vodka
no matter if it's UV blue raspberry UV
red cherry UV green apple UV Ivory
vanilla or UV orange vodka UV flavored
vodkas offer a premium product without
the high price tag please visit UV
vodka.com for additional information and
recipes a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest news source and the ad club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at news stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at the onion.com
and avclub.com piz luche proudly
supports drinking with Ian free delivery
until 2:30 a.m. weekdays and 3:30 a.m.
weekends download our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with Ian is nothing
without our sponsors please support
them
e
for
for e
all right everybody thanks for staying
tuned to drink with how you doing
tonight all right well hot Dam we got
something else coming for you we have a
short film by our friends at D sto
digital it's called automated assets
let's take a
[Applause]
look so I went to the Ry Ridge Market
last night
can you believe they took ham off the
dinner
[Music]
menu hang on I got to get
this thank you for calling technical
support for espanol press 9 to purchase
a service or product press one to speak
to a customer service representative
press two for all other issues related
to a purchase already made press three
press seven to repeat this menu
please enter your express service
code please hold while we transfer you
to the next available customer service
representative 10 years I've been going
there every time I get the ham dinner I
had to get
turkey it was
dry we appreciate your patience and
assure you that help is just around the
Corner some brilliant guy must have gone
up to an executive and said you know
what I've got it no more ham on the
dinner
menu our staff is working hard to take
your call next while waiting feel free
to browse our new online
catalog you know I was a dissatisfied
consumer
we regret to inform you that all
circuits are busy we apologize for the
inconvenience have a nice
day 10
years that's just no way to run a
company all right everybody um thanks
for staying tuned to drinking with you
our next guests are spectacular they
have a new EP in stores right now called
the midnight creep you go buy it I want
a rousing round of applause for disaster
rotting
[Music]
a minute of your time it is provided for
and there's no need to sign all I need
from you is a piece of your mind all you
see all you see see is a dollar sign I
am salesman hey man got my C I am the
salesman I'll take your sh I am the
salesman a man got my C I am the
salesman I always got someone to
S all right you the microphone all right
I out tell you to bend over get you high
all feel your should
I'm see your children and in the place
only need to do our vacate the space I
am the salesman hey man got
my I am the salesman I'll take your sh I
am the salesman hey man got my C I am
the salesman I always got someone to
sell
what
[Music]
[Applause]
what and have a SE need a minute of your
time and all I needs for 54 is no need
to sign all I need from you is a piece
of your mind and all you see oh you see
I see all a sign I am the salesman hey
man got my card I am the salesman I'll
take your sh I am the salesman that man
got my C I am the salesman I always got
some the
[Music]
[Applause]
sale ladies and gentlemen disaster
R got again they have a new CD in stores
right now it's called The Midnight
creepy P I suggest you go buy it another
round of
applause he another round of applause
for Philip Hansen keep it going our
lovely guest tonight hey and that's Dr
to the end this week we'll see you next
[Music]
[Applause]
time by the way it's reallying hot up
here yeah
that's how fing hot it is up here