[Music]
with the
Earth it's
fun get drunk drink lot drink
[Music]
it how y'all doing
now I can't hear you
[Music]
oh come on better than
that that's good that's good we got a
great show lined up for here tonight
kids uh we have our very own special
edition of Win Lose or
drink and our musical guest tonight is
Gospel gossips and now the one the only
man that you want in your heart and in
your homes
yeah everybody how you doing
welcome down to drinking of in how in
we're
drinking hot damn how you doing no I'm
hanging in there sweet we always keep
meeting this way people are going to
start asking
questions oh yeah we have a hell of a
show for you we got a win lose or drink
it's a game show that sweeping the
nation and gospel gossip it's going to
be good but not as good as our shour
Round of Applause for
[Applause]
Neil and might not be as good as the
shot we're about to have bartender star
is Mr Ali
stench hey everybody how you doing
tonight Aces tonight's shot is called a
cherry surprise and I'm going to preface
it with a little bit of a story and the
story involves my high school
girlfriend and uh we've been dating I
don't know 3 weeks or something we
finally decided to
uh to to consummate our relationship and
she had she had guaranteed me she was a
virgin
and so we get in bed and we start
fooling around and uh just like
tonight's shot there was no Cherry down
there so to make a cherry
surprise
surprise God you people are lame what
the do you expect this is episode number
60 I've had to come up with shot names
and stories for 60
shots you people couldn't come up with
60 between you so shut the up and laugh
at my God
jokes that's
better and to make a cherry surprise you
take a shot shot of fcking Irish whiskey
whiskey you take two shots shots of
lemon lime soda soda and take a shot of
cranberry juice
juice you all know what comes
next you add a little ice ice shake it
up strain it to get all the ice out of
[Applause]
there and I give to you Cherry surprise
shots on the
house all right everybody we have the
Cherry surprise coming through please
make way for our drink
professionals I want to hear more
excitement our drink
[Applause]
professionals they do it for
you and tipping well not necessary
always encourage for our shot girls all
right how many people have shots get
them up in the air Party
People ladies and gentlemen the Cherry
surprise all three one 2 three
salute ah taste
sensation I always say it but it's
always true all right now we have uh
something we've been on air for uh quite
like 10 15 years now I
think and we finally got some G we
actually have to kind of do this it's
like a public service thing we need the
opposite view this is an editorial
response to drinking with Ian let's take
a
[Music]
look he doesn't smoke he doesn't drink
he doesn't like you or what you think
St oh hey there party people how are you
doing tonight drinking with the end
drinking it up having a good time
salute Cherry
surprise
toast to your uh weakness as a human
being that's cool man I used to hate
myself too and then I discovered
straight edge which is how I got my name
straight edge Dave okay
and uh tonight I'm going to demonstrate
my
superiority and uh maybe give you a few
examples of uh how you can stop hating
yourself all right I'm just going to set
this beer right here and we're going to
count it down in fact we've all even
counting down okay and uh I'm just going
to uh hang out with this and
uh um prove to you uh that uh I
am I'm better okay
I people like
me I have
something special and they can see that
in my eyes when I walk down the like
what makes this guy so
different and
uh I know what it is
is or I know what it
isn't I know what I I know what I don't
have okay and the time that you just uh
took a swig I just scored three fold
what you will for the rest of your life
okay I keep a different kind of score
all right it's kind of a score that uh
that makes me
better than you and the person standing
next to
you because I something
else I got something else and it's right
here and it's right here too actually
I'm I'm
better I am
better five four
three let this be an example of how you
can score
without that great job Dave great job
that was a good job wasn't it
yeah it blew me away yeah we sold them
let's never do that again all
right
go hey everybody straight at Jame that's
pretty awesome he's better than us out
here all right now as I mentioned
earlier we're going to have a new show a
new game show that's going to knock you
on your asses it's sweeping the nation
when lose or drink and welcoming up our
contestants where are they
at let's bring them on
stage come on up no this isn't radio
come
on all right these are our
contestants what's your name Rob Rob
everybody and what's your name Amber
Amber we have Rob and Amber now this
these are the fans now these are the
Riders of drinking with Ian we're having
a death match match and since I don't
bother to ever learn the names of the
people who work on the show what's your
name Chris ladies gentlemen Chris yeah
yeah and what's your name Bill exactly
Bill ladies and gentlemen
bill now here's how this works are you
guys familiar with win loser
draw that show that was on like 20 years
ago that nobody remembers or likes and
BD Cony dead well we're going to do
something like that always touching my
butt my LA's off and it's in my pocket
up here if you want to aim for that one
[Music]
too how am I supposed to keep a straight
face if somebody's touching my butt you
can't do it you can't do it now yet
again here are our contestants a rousing
round of applause for all four of
them now we're timing them you have a
minute I'm going to give your partner a
hint or the the clue and then you have
to draw it one of you have to draw it
and then you guess what it is now if you
get it in under a minute you get a point
and whoever gets the most points gets a
bottle of
booze yeah and a 2008 Toyota
Cella no we don't have that and I don't
even think that's a real car just made
something up to end with a pisella I
just I didn't know all right now hold on
hold on I have the sheet of mystery
right here in my
pocket go
down all right here's the hint
all right we have we at one minute on
the
clock all right pen stealer all right we
have one minute are we ready timekeeper
where's our timekeeper there she is all
right tell us when to go all right we
got one
minute you got any guesses come on this
is a timed effort divided by man woman
[Music]
all right half an underwear man
woman that's what I thought my favorite
martian sh we don't no you're not
playing shoot the
devil Running With the Devil that's a
gun gun all right how much time do we
have on the clock what uh 30 seconds
we're halfway through amazing it's just
flying by
I'm drawing a blank I'm drawing a blank
I I I got nothing where's the penis all
right I think are you ah devil devil uh
nothing crickets 10 seconds I
Got 5 4 3 2 one o sorry no score on
that what now what what was it Shout at
the Devil no it wasn't it was Shout at
the Devil that's not even a
phrase who's who's giving who's
receiving I'll be drawing and let me
just say something we don't only draw
conclusions we draw blood
yeah these guys are very excited about
[Applause]
this all right do we have one minute on
the clock all right let's do it
boobs equals
penis oh this could be anything under
garments pig
riding double
Destiny einer Zend no
Bon
rampant
hunger
Chinese clouds
happy dreaming I'm dreaming of a Chinese
white
[Music]
clouds peace is only a
dream we have 10 seconds 10 9 8 7 6 five
penis into a dreaming man cloud
time everybody I'm sorry you did not get
it yes I did I got it
right well I can't win without
that what was it
again it's a penny saved is a penny
earned Penny saved is a penny ear [ __ ]
you all right we have amazingly enough a
tied score
work with this at this point theight
take your seats men take your seats it's
okay all right back again it's you guys
I assume you'll switch rolls now you'll
be the drawer you guys have a marker
Don't Bogart the marker
dude all right everybody here in the
studio audience please I know you're
smarter than the people on stage so
please keep your D to a to a to a d all
right are we ready timekeeper official
timekeeper all right and go
in your head a PL sign a road
um what the all this is this is
interesting I don't know what we're
doing here a penis I don't
know a finger hand stroke [ __ ]
masturbate well I mean if you ask pretty
you got to say please generally come on
he's on stage for Christ's sake he not a
machine
30 seconds stroke
intersection um what is that what what
are you doing intersection
lines I don't know what is this
hangman uh uhoh uh oh going we' got
puppets puppet how much time do we have
on the road 10 seconds finger Road
finger 98
seven stroke five four
three two
one sorry everybody we didn't get that
one that was Master of
Puppets
sorry
yes all right now we have four rounds
this is the fourth round if they get
this they win the drinking with Ian
dream team of Chris and Bill eyes look
at my eyes all right just be where I am
just just be where I am man we're the
same
thing all right you ready
you ready yeah all right do it do we
have one minute on the clock you got the
you got the thing I didn't give you the
clue I was wondering if you're going to
start without it all
right okay now tell me got it you got it
yes tell him through his eyes now you
guys I know there's a certain sympatico
amongst drink with the and Riders so
we'll see if this works out at all and
this is this has not been rehearsed as
you might guess and we we're just flying
by the SE pants here we have 60 seconds
on the clock are we ready Juliet let's
do it 60 seconds starting now a
stitching time saves
nine an apple day keeps the doctor away
Penny saved is a penny earn oo this is a
kind of a strange strategy we have Chris
working on right
now it would be funny an apple day keeps
the doctor
away kill
whitey it was Kill Whitey
actually was Kill
Whitey well there you go the round a
round of applause for our contestants
here the team are fans ladies and
gentlemen right here and the winners
tonight the dreaming with the in writing
staff we're so in tune with each other I
know it's a beautiful thing all right
now get the hell off my
stage the time to shine has passed now
everybody I want a rousing round of
applause for this next man who we're
about to have up he is Legend in his own
time and mind Mr Haiku
[Applause]
Jim thanks
everybody you know you may have guessed
by now that I kid Republicans a little
bit out of love and you know that we
have a national Republican convention
coming up
[Music]
here 45 to 50,000 Republicans descending
onto our great cities
packing the dance clubs and whatnot the
uh the porn
shops and I have an
idea I propose that we give the ladies
who work at these strip clubs during the
convention a couple nights
off we fill a couple of buses of big
hairy Canadians and maybe some livestock
or some farm
animals and this is my hiu that goes
along with that
idea convention
goers our clubs await your
presence enjoy the
livestock ladies and gentlemen the
Mellow moods of haiku
Jim all right everybody believe it or
not we have sponsors let's take a look
at him we'll be right back with more
trigging with Ian
[Applause]
[Music]
turn on tune in and drink up www.
drinking withthe
and.com all right thanks for sticking
around for the first tumultuous part the
second part we're sting to cruise
control to awesome land as you know we
have the first season are drink with
thean DVD out available in stores right
now pause for Applause
and uh now we got uh we're expanding our
media Empire and we have another DVD out
right now let's look at a commercial for
it you've sensed his presence for
centuries now hear his Unholy voice for
the first time available on DVD Josiah
hecubus sings songs of satanic praise
through the power of Satan let the Earth
and ites reenter his
being Josiah travels to the infernal
pits of the underworld to slake Satan's
blood lust with passion and
sensitivity Jesus was a
[ __ ] and God is
[Music]
G drink a cup of blood to wash the taint
away all the classics are here
wallowing wallowing in Temptation
wallowing I'm going to coat myself in
sleev there's even oldtime favorites I
like to burn churches I like to burn
them to the ground I like to burn
churches spread their ashes all
around no other artist has captured
Satan's fury like Josiah and boy has he
done it with class oh come sing watch
you my face off going wear my skin as
your
underwear won't you come bask with me
and say 's Vengeance now s now s now s
now s now s now s now s now sat join
Josiah on his journey to the abisal
heart of the Beast and be part of the
downfall of mankind order your DVD of
Josiah's Unforgettable performances
today offer not available in Jerusalem
Meco Vatican City not responsible for
Eternal damnation or
Hellfire that's a new DVD it's in stores
now Josiah hecubus we're doing it to
make a quick Buck I'm not going to f
with you seriously that's about it all
right now this is a real product it's
really in stores it's out on guilt
ritten pop it's a new album it's really
damn good sing into my mouth the band
ladies and gentlemen gospel gossip
[Applause]
[Music]
she was passed out almost when asked her
to
dance and he was from New
York and to
[Music]
just in
case
s
alone most
far fast years of pain on a
r that school didn't it work out so he
had
extra
money
and to late to
[Music]
but you
know you wouldn't do
[Music]
it B I know you want to move to
the I got
Char minut P decent
money I know you want to run but the
time is wrong you can get a new Pap baby
with the kid
[Music]
CH be
so this house is
so me up
so here's
your here's your R to I hear a storm
coming back into the sky from this to
[Music]
[Applause]
ladies and gentlemen gospel
gossip one more time it's called Sing
into my mouth go buy it
[Applause]
[Music]
now and of course we
that's the end this week see you next
[Music]
time sit Uboo sit good dog