drinking with get
[ __ ]
drunk how y'all doing
tonight I say how y I'm doing T
that we got a great show for you tonight
our very special guest is comedian Dave
ble oh give the man a little more
Applause than
that and our musical guest tonight is
unicorn
basement and now the man you've been
waiting for your whole lives the one the
only yeah
they go away no all right don't worry
about I'm sure it's it's malignant don't
worry about it hey everybody how you
doing welcome down to Trier to the
end I've been through the desert on a
horse with no name but a man who does
have a name and a horrible segue and I
apologize for that sometimes you just
open your mouth and words fall out a
stylish man a wonderful man on tour with
Kanye West all summer Neil
and the man that makes everything makes
sense in this world the bartender the
Stars Mr Ali
Stitch I love me too thank you very much
tonight's
shot is dedicated to an old video game
called Frogger
frog and I'm dedicating the shot to
Frogger frog because when I was coming
here tonight I was trying to cross
Street against the
light and I swear toing God it was like
a game of Frogger in real
life so to make a Frogger
frog you take a shot shot of UV pink
lemonade
vodka it was treacherous Crossing that
road you take a shot shot of lemon lime
soda
and you take a shot shot of Mountain
Dew add a little
ice shake it
up find your strainer
strainer pour it into a glass
glass and dedicated to the greatest
video game of the early 80s I give you
Frogger shots on the
house all right everybody Make Way for
Frogger our lovely ital drink
professionals are on their way
out to get you good and
messy lovely bouquet on this
one Breathe It In Breathe It in let it
let it breathe give it some
air all right oh we got more coming
through everybody who needs some who
needs some put up your hands if you need
some that one guy in the back you'd
probably be smart to come over here
don't no no no no let him come to you
let give him the exercise you got all
the
booze all right I think officially does
everybody have
them put them up if you got
them all right everybody on three
everybody the Frogger
one
three let you guys do all the Talking I
don't care that wasn't bad at all was it
I said that wasn't bad at all was
it all right everybody we have something
interesting coming up it's called roof
sets roof sets sets and it's by our
friend PES let's look at the big screen
oh
ow
I was given faulty information they told
me that' be called roof sets cuz they
knew I'd never allow something like that
on drinking with E and that would just
be wrong wouldn't it
all right maybe it'd be right wouldn't
it all right even better now it's uh
rare uh when I do dring at the end CU I
try to put a strong veneer up and I try
not to act too vulnerable but this
actually kind of makes me Misti on and
I'm not screwing around here we've been
doing five seasons of this show pause
for
Applause and we've been really lucky
we've had a really good run and there
are some people here tonight
um in Minneapolis in Minnesota who were
a big part of
that they've invited us into their
houses they've invited us into their
homes and I we couldn't do this show
without him and I just really want to
take a moment here seriously you know
I'll I'll I'll stuff aside to thank them
and you
guys are so not
them I'm talking about the somal
now think about it we're on public
access television
who utilizes Public Access television
than
anybody the Somali they're there they're
making it happen they're taking
advantage of one of the last one of the
few Bastion of media that you don't have
to be rich to do they are the ones
watching Public Access we are on public
access so I want to have a moment to
thank the Somali are you with
me I want to welcome up to the
stage Hanan Issa this is our Mr
Somali Hanan how you
doing take a seat
sir oh I'm I'm glad to have you here cuz
you're on behalf of the Somali Community
is that right you are here on behalf of
that are you miked you're not miked that
intro went so damn
well lo and behold I have a
mic ladies and gentlemen one more time
seriously let's keep the Applause going
for
hanad thank you thank you um now you are
you are a representative from somal
because apparently uh somal people don't
come to First Avenue very much and I
always wondered what would bring our
cultures together and I'm glad that
dream with Ian could do that I'm glad
too yeah is
awesome I know now um this is kind of
odd because um the small community
generally not allowed to drink why is
that well if you didn't drink as much as
you do there'd be some left for the rest
of write it out that's that's very true
yeah and we do we do kind of soak it all
up
sorry hey we're thirsty it's been a long
day um now do you have anything to say
to the Somali Community well yes I
actually have a speech for now okay
let's here this is good let's bring his
mic up so everybody can hear this is
going to be
awesome do you want to stand while you
do this yeah why
not that's good it's fine don't worry
about he's saying in his native tongue
jackass
I'll get out over
theek
back like Superman
ladies and
gentlemen our representative smia
now we we couldn't just have you show up
and give a speech we a to present you
with
flowers and a drinking with the and
t-shirt and to you and all of our Somali
viewers at home thank you so much you
are welcome to
you can someone call me a cab now yeah
can somebody get this guy a
taxi helloa
everybody all right now that's not the
only guest we have for you tonight his
next guest is spectacular I want a
rousing round of applause for a veteran
of Last Comic Standing the tonight's
show with Jay Leno um every damn show on
television tough tough crowd with Colin
Quinn the one and only Dave
morall do it all
right what's happening not much how you
doing I'm doing well but thanks so much
for showing up for this this is great
I'm glad to finally have you here hey
how about another hand for the female uh
Elvis
impersonator I did that just to [ __ ] up
your episode oh okay yeah I know that
was great home going what I miss that
was very I missed that all right so uh
Hipp us uh if there's anybody here who's
not familiar tell us a little bit about
yourself I'm single I like straight
women who like straight women I hate
tattoos and I hate silicone all
right sorry can't stand
tattoos they make it's all right it's
all right I I I know it's
yeah anyway so but you might be better
known as not just uh a guy who hates
fake tits as as tattoos as as a comedian
of great repute you've been uh turning
around quite a lot I've been very lucky
lately I've been very very lucky I uh
Tonight Show with Jay Leno which was
wonderful to do and uh Last Comic
Standing was a wonderful experience now
how does a guy from Elk River get a
start in National Comedy I mean I just I
went to an audition for this uh reality
show and I happened to win out of 120
comics in in uh Chicago and then tell me
about your career before you were on
Comic Standing oh I was all over the
country just doing little shitty one
nighters and awful horrible bars yeah
but that's when I had the most fun you
know yeah no a doubt and now you're
doing them in in you know marity I
assume you're getting paid pretty well
it's a lot it's you know you do it in
the theater and it's it's not really fun
because it's 1500 people you don't it's
just it's not the same it's but you're
still I mean if you watched uh the first
season Last Comic Standing that Dave was
on um you know you're very Minnesota was
four people watching thanks anybody ever
saw the first season of Last Comic
Standing three of
you I odly enough these people watch
Public Access they don't watch NBC who
who would have thought um now you know
that you're very you're Minnesota based
you're very proud of being here I'm very
proud of being from here and you spent a
lot of time still around here how is
Minnesota is like a home base I mean
because I know we're we're looking at as
great flyover country to everybody every
one of my friends that's ever moved to
LA has got nothing I've gotten
everything right out of Minnesota yeah
everything I never moved I never move I
actually moved to a smaller town now I
live in a town of 32 people now really
I'm just going to keep going until I'm
in war Road name is it Incorporated huh
it's not even Incorporated it has a bar
that's it wow so now how do you get
arrested in an unincorporated Town what
do you have to do cuz there's no police
right there you have to do something
right in front of a sheriff's deputy
which people do yeah yeah but no I've
gotten everything right out of Minnesota
I've got HBO out of here Comedy Central
and everybody else moved but they come
here look for stuff so I never move
because I'm lazy well hey ladies and
genten being up something we all can get
behind now and this kind of almost uh
touches on the same subject um because
you've mentioned both runin with the law
and Jay Leno um you're one of the few
guests we've had that done Jay Leno and
you're I think probably the only one who
has attempted to hold up a gas station I
tried to rob a gas station when I was 18
no this is we're not joking this what
happened it's looking back it was a it
was a bad
idea it really truly was yeah it so was
it in did people know you I mean was
this in Elk River yeah it was it's in a
town of 500 people I mean
it's the cops showed up and said who do
you think did it it's it was Dave
yeah it's that small a town you know
what was he wearing what Dave wears
exactly same Dave's regular boots and
jacket you know you want to catch them
come back at 9:30 we're going
bowling no no I assume you didn't do any
time for that I did uh probation you got
probation back then I don't know what
you get today yeah well that's good news
so yeah if you're watching at home you
can attempt to hold up a gas station get
out if it's your first offense go for it
cuz you're only going to get
probation but don't be one of those
idiots that like robs it and gets eight
bucks yeah I never get the big money go
on Friday probably about 9:30 when they
have the most money yeah exell see words
of wisdom you learn from watching
drinking with the in who thought but you
also forget a lot too so the hell do you
do now you mentioned uh last Comics now
how did that change your life I mean I
know this your career I mean it's got to
be all like whoopy damn Doo cuz you know
people are like booking you and you're
playing all over the damn place but how
has it changed your life uh I get the
really good car
wash yeah it hasn't really it's it's uh
you do make a lot more money but you
spend a lot more money so I mean
everybody's got their hand out
publicists and like that sober so I mean
you're pay to get on drinking with Ian
this was a $2,000 yeah you're ruining
the illusion it's all pale and blow yeah
now would you ever do another reality
show I I didn't mind doing it it's fun I
mean it you know you went back for like
the third season was it I was back for
the third season yep I said second I
came in second on that but it's it's
living in a mansion for 30 days and
having people clean up after you who's
not going to do that yeah no kidding
that's pretty awesome yeah you can I
mean it's wonderful you you make it a
huge mess at night and in the morning
it's like fairies coming and clean it up
it's done it's it's brand new in the
morning and yeah so but how many years
did you been doing standup before you
got made service 10 10 years years years
Tak a long it's like a band you know
bands take forever sometimes yeah but I
mean you got to admit it's a better gig
being a comedian they like fly in and
stuff don't they yeah I mean you don't
have to hang out with three other
jackasses back the I'm not I'm not
grabbing an amp and carrying it 6 miles
cuz the B quit yeah you know all right
now um this man actually and this is new
news he's going to have a show on
Discovery this actually I just found out
last
Wednesday that I have a new show on the
Discovery Channel it will Air October
15th right after Dirty Jobs and tell us
about it what's it called it's called
Adventure guy with Dave Mall basically
he's Adventure guy yeah I'm Adventure
guy basically I'm going to different
places in the country and getting
involved in really dangerous sports and
doing them that's all the show
is like like what kind of sports uh
we're going to do stuff like uh ice
racing with
motorcycles oh well you're not around
like boxing or something you're actually
like doing real hardcore stuff really
nasty stuff but it's going
to getting hurts funny yeah other people
especially when you're my age you know
so you're okay so ice racing what other
kind of kind of we have shotgun bowling
uh lined up I don't have you ever seen
that what's that you don't have a
bowling ball you just have a shotgun and
you got a bowl with a shotgun it's a lot
of fun so you're literally just picking
you're literally shooting like just
towards the center one and trying to get
the SP this a regulated sport this just
sounds like redneck shoot this is a
drinking sport really truly I think you
have to be at 0.10 even to get in you
know that's the kind of stuff we're
doing we're doing uh snowmobile water
skipping maybe you've seen that oh that
stuff looks that would be fun and you're
actually going to be doing this we're
going to be doing it now what's what's
your insurance like they're going to
have to deal with that yeah they're
going to have to deal with that so so we
have a lot of stuff lined up and we're
going to start shooting in two weeks it
could all go to hell if you know
anything about the business it could all
go to hell tomorrow but so we're going
to shoot in two weeks yeah and uh
hopefully it'll be done by October 15th
so awesome now you have any words of
wisdom for beautiful television audience
keep drinking that's all there is to it
ladies and gentlemen our friend Dave
moral thanks for having me on man I
really appreciate it seriously now
another Legend
who hopefully will have a show on
Discovery someday the one and only Haiku
Jim hey thanks
everybody to be succinct this is a haiku
about people who watch people they don't
know play cards on TV like poker and
stuff all
right exactly TV poker
fans I would be willing to bet you are
dull as hell
thank you ladies and gentlemen hi
Jim all right we'll be back in a couple
seconds after you watch some subliminal
messages oh you're too kind all right
welcome back to the show everybody uh we
have something spectacular planned for
you uh something we taped ourselves it's
called bad date number 27 let's take a
look so how was your date last
night hey how was your date last night
oh man oh it was awesome it was awesome
let me tell
you well we talked about like a book
start off with like some of this or
right it's kind of
mostly this but I mean to be honest it's
more
like and I was like no that that's not
good enough I want a little more and
then I like you know flipped her over
kind of got a little this yeah and then
like once it was like that you know yeah
I had no idea she was into it but she is
now not cool right and it was like this
so then I kind of like oh I brought it
up doing a little boom boom boom this I
was I was I was s was like oh hammering
it getting it up oh oh upside down oh
man and let's be honest it was more like
this oh
man straightens my God straight out of
her face man I was I was oh I was I was
like
Moses and it
was
yeah got it oh and then she relaxed a
lot after that like flapping it all over
the place like that underneath and you
stick it up through her mouth oh God I
can't take it anymore
can't Lord I swear to God she is going
to think the world of
me so uh Diablo Cody huh yeah good for
her yeah
great
so did you
see um Spice World no no I didn't no
sorry it was not good really I kind of
heard different but all right all right
yeah yeah know I I'm sure sure it was
all
right so how is
Christmas well I mean that was was quite
a few months ago but it was it was all
right it was all right I mean I got
pretty much everything I wanted how was
yours I don't
remember all right everybody thanks for
staying tuned to drinking with Ian we
have uh something great to close this
episode out with they have a new record
right here on on necessary friction
records it's called greater than sexy
Round of Applause for unicorn basement
read
it it
yes a world is
multiply yes
a a
s
w t HC
c r a f t t u p a c Victorious v i g
oh
it's
the get a
ladies and gentlemen unicard
basement greater than sexy in stores now
you go to stores if they don't have it
you punch whoever works there in the
throat yo where the [ __ ] the Unicorn
basement CD godam it that's
right oh ring Round of Applause for all
of our Somali
viewers and an extra special Round of
Applause for Dave
Bal let stre with the end this week
we'll see you next time everybody
you'll save money and time you'll get
the best of merchandise and service when
you patronize these good neighbors no
beer in the midwest has a grander
brewing tradition than Grain Belt for
over 100 years Grain Belt has been the
beer that fathers have passed on to sons
and friends have passed amongst each
other at local bars and watering holes
it is a beer with tradition that spans
Generations which is why it has become
legendary both here and across the
country next time you go out ask for a
premium
if there's one thing we like better than
booze it's cheap booze and that's why we
chose Merwin Liquors as the official
drinking withian liquor store great
deals a huge selection they even have a
contest where customers can win free
drinks for a year Merwin Liquors is hard
to beat yeah it's a bit ghetto but up
your street cred and Save A Buck or two
stop in at Merwin Liquors at Lindale and
West Broadway in North Minneapolis just
two blocks west of 94 or visit Merwin
liquors.com
drinking with the end is proud to be
sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV Vodka
no matter if it's UV blue raspberry UV
red cherry UV green apple UV Ivory
vanilla or UV orange vodka UV flavored
vodkas offer a premium product without
the high price tag please visit UV
vodka.com for additional information and
recipes a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest new source and the a club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at news stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at theonion.com
and avclub.com pizz luche proudly
supports drinking with Ian free delivery
until 2:30 a.m. weekdays and 3:30 a.m.
weekends download our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with Ian is nothing
without our sponsors please support
them sit ubo sit good dog what