drinking with
the it's drinking with the
get get drunk
drinking how y'all doing
tonight oh we've got a great show lined
up for you tonight our very special
guest making my job easier because not
only is he the interviewee he will also
be performing tonight is Grand
har and now the one the only person in
my life without whom I'd be nothing
Ian how you doing how you doing don't be
shy don't be shy how you doing ladies
and gentlemen thanks for coming down to
dram with Ian tonight how you
doing I said how you do
one oh they're small But Mighty aren't
they
Neil all right anyway ladies and
gentlemen
Neil and I know why you're all here you
Charlton you're not here to see Neil or
eye you're here to get drunk put a
rousing round of applause in your hands
and out your mouth to the one and only
Ali
stetch hey everybody how you doing
tonight now uh for those of you you
watching at home we taped this show down
at uh my favorite Club my home away from
home First Avenue Let's Hear From First
Avenue I've been coming to this club
since I was 16 years old when they had
all ages punk rock shows and uh this
this really has become a a home away
from home and usually my shots are all
silly and everything but tonight I'm
serious uh tonight's shot is dedicated
to the past present and future employees
of First
Avenue and in honor of them tonight's
shot is called the downtown Dan
ateria it's sure ain't dedicated to you
people to make the downtown dance ateria
Dania you take a
shot of UV grape flavor vodka
vodka and because everyone down at first
half has always hooked me up I'm hooking
them
up you take a shot shot cranberry juice
juice you take a shot shot of cola
Cola you add a little ice
ice and Shake It Up
Up take your strainer strainer your
first Avenue strainer
strainer pour it out
out and Doug get over here
here dedicated to the to the past
present and future employees of First
Avenue the downtown danc ateria shots on
the
house all right everybody Make Way for
Drake professionals they're passing out
the downtown dance ateria and tipping
well not you know necessary definitely
uh appreciate somebody hand me a shot I
would appreciate that not everybody
wants all right are we all ready to rock
here
people get him up in the air the
downtown dance interior dedicated to the
best club
in Downtown Minneapolis and America
First Avenue everybody shots on three 1
2 3
salute oh no that's a taste
sensation ah it always is but it's
especially true now now I'm glad that um
I had this shot so this is going to make
this a little bit more uh a little
easier for
me there have been some stuff out on the
internet um as you know we hear dream
with the we're a television show there's
cameras and stuff and some times with uh
a lot of cameras and uh really like
sealess local celebrity it goes to your
head some stuff got leaked and I figured
fck it if anybody's going to make some
money off of it it might as well be
us about a year ago um I had a handful
of
Dianes um and I was stupid enough to
videotape them you should never do that
kids don't do that don't do that that's
wrong so to beat those bastards at Vivid
Entertainment to the punch we're
releasing it
ourselves take it get to the
streets and to try to make some money we
added together a little commercial I
haven't seen this I had nothing to do
with it um but I mean it's a lot of
vanilla stuff it's nothing you haven't
seen before let's take a look at the big
screen warning this video contains
scenes of depravity and vulgarity so
graphic that you just may blow a hole in
your pants the acts depicted are highly
inappropriate for children unless your
kids are cool with it then it's probably
okay but you didn't hear that from us
wink wink it began with Bob Crane then
came Pam and Tommy Paris and Whoopi now
get ready to see the wildest celebrity
sex tape you've ever
seen give me your candy girl want some
your sweet sweet
candy don't make me beat it out you
don't make me beat it without you that's
right it's the outrageously sexy Ian sex
tapes see Ian like you only dreamed of
seeing him caught in the act of his very
own sex video this video is so
outrageously sexy this is all we can
show you of the sexy sexy action want to
see more okay perverts you asked for it
what Back to the Future movies better uh
two wrong ow what's my name Steve Steve
Mr Mr how's that for sexy these tapes
were purposefully lost then found and
remastered to DVD so the whole world can
get in on the sexy sexy action had
enough of the sexy action I didn't think
so you smutty people here's more oh God
how'd you guys even do this stop doing
this don't push don't push all right
yeah I'm going to need the jaws of life
on this one you guys it's uh get it this
video is so wild and so sexy it's been
banned by the entire porn industry for
being just too darn sexy there's so much
of this hot and sexy video we can't show
you but we know how you tiny freaks
think so here it is Sir we've been
getting a lot of complaints about noise
on this and I'm going to have to say and
what the hell is that on your head man
You Don't Own Me man screw this what the
hell do you even work here I don't think
you just bull bull man yes sir I do I
don't know what that's for but what back
to the thing on your head what what were
you doing talk me about the thing on my
head let's talk about the thing on your
head that's unbelievably sexy you people
couldn't possibly handle more of this
wild hot sweaty incredibly sexy footage
so let's see if this sexy sex sexy scene
doesn't blow your mind you ready baby
yeah all right here it
comes oh yes
put's tasty it is tasty you should do
this more often why did we wait so long
tell me that didn't blow your filthy
mind into sexy outer space not since the
Dustin Diamond sex video has there been
such Shameless self-promotion of a sexy
sexy celebrity but supplies are limited
so order your outrageously sexy Ian sex
tape now supplies are not actually
Li well thank you I didn't I
didn't I didn't want you to have to find
out any other way than from us it's
probably available on our on our website
all right um our next guest is uh
awesome he's a personal favorite of mine
he's a a local Legend but screw being a
legend he's still doing uh great stuff I
want to hear a whole bunch of love for
the one and only Grant Hart
yo yo we're in the
house
wow how you doing oh you got you got the
mic on the on the on the necklace there
that's fashionable did it work yeah yeah
it works great good how you doing how
you been I got uh some stuff for your
audience here yay what do you got I have
a uh is this something you made at home
no uh Starburst hey who wants a
starburst who wants a
starburst have yeah here we go and
what's your name Rachel come on up here
Rachel you don't mind if we bring make
it a three-way do no all it means let's
get her in on the action all right
anybody out there want a t-shirt a
drinking with you and t-shirt
yeah all
right so other than taking stuff from
backstage come on up come on up
yeah and she said on
my so what you been up to Grant making
friends I see I enjoy Showbiz Ian yeah
even when it's you know barely Showbiz
like barely Showbiz but yeah so what you
been up to how how's things been going
on a record up in Montreal with uh some
of the fine musicians that's in Canada
up there live in uh well don't tell that
to the cuqua okay but uh yes it is still
part of Canada um Petro Canada you know
had a lot to do with that they' rather
petosexual well they they'd rather uh
they'd rather have fuel than uh be
French so yeah no I can dig it hey in
that's why we're in America and
uh so okay so you got the Sal you're
working on um and I hear I hear rumor
Telly fa exactly yeah we're not
sponsored by them at
all want to be like lady in the [ __ ]
come
on Who you calling lady hey Who you
calling TR um so I so what's up with the
belgians well some belgians contacted me
just about a year ago and they had the
uh Grant we have been working on this
project and we have lots of guest
vocalists and uh are you sure they're
Belgian they sound kind of
Indian they're they're Belgian in uh
they're actually Peron okay all right
yeah
um but anyway uh they asked me if I
would uh do a vocal on their upand
coming record and it turned
out because I don't speak Indian
um I ended up writing the lyrics
which and uh inadvertently long story
short it ended up being in uh heavy
rotation and charting in Belgium as as
we're speaking w which is there any
belgians here tonight that came down
because of
this you want a sticker
no okay we uh we need some better stuff
to give away next time not that these
aren't you know great great
items so okay but so this album's out
and it's charting in in in Belgium and
and that's weird I mean do you find that
strange that you are charting in a in a
far have you been there I I played there
like 5 years ago okay and uh did you
find them friendly oh they're wonderful
people I mean uh the longest bar in the
world is in uh I believe
louang louang louang we're coming to
your town
louang we're going to be rocking louane
and all the people in Brugge Brugge yeah
and then a side yeah side trip to Zurich
what can you do with Zurich I got
nothing oh okay anybody else any amateur
up and coming we haven't really had much
input from our
ladys what's your name what's your name
how you doing what Emily we had talked
to you yet I didn't want you to feel
left out now what do you do for what's
what's your art form my art form I'm a
student she also is not miked she's St
oh these ladies don't have microphones
either that's why they speak mine well
yeah but they're women come on
oh I'm joking I'm joking I'm joking
joking come on hey
hey hey honestly you set the toad let's
not act like I did anything weird here
so whoo whoo how was that oh yeah you
were in a how was that band to be in has
it gotten that bad that we have to bring
that up now no we can we can get this
back on yeah this is H this is where the
like producer comes out and goes yeah
stretch we need to edit for more stuff
um okay why we get her up here too we
had uh Juliet right there Julet come on
she's our stage manager show people what
TV what really happens I can't tell if
it's hot up here or this is flop sweat I
can't tell it's hot it's hot all right
cool um all right but actually know I
have one who's SC do question when's
that when's it going to be remastered on
CD and not sound all
tiny uh well no because it's all it was
all mastered for vinyl so when they put
it out on CD they just didn't put any
any work into it now if you ask that
question to another partner involved in
it he would
go what's wrong with the way it
sounds so Greg that's yeah yeah no no um
some other guy that's the kind of that's
the kind of situation we're in where you
know conversations just kind of reach an
impass I'm real I'm real happy with the
way that you know my life is going I'm
happy the way everybody else seems to be
happy about the way their lives are
going yeah and uh to tell you the truth
uh I think we got to pitch to Haik coup
do we need to pitch to houp I think we
need to pitch to hi coup well if you
want to we can I mean we could we could
keep talking okay I just saw a sign out
one of the audience members was holding
up a sign that said Pitch to High cool
yeah I know know I know I know okay this
we're Deon this is deconstructionist TV
this is great we're really getting rid
of any of the walls I hope so and and
and a fair amount of the comedy too but
that's I've insisted on as as few
barriers between the audience members
and the uh and the performers as
possible depends where you're playing
lot ugly people out there lot of ugly
people not not here of course but out
there outside know I'm being serious L
those ug I wouldn't talk about you guys
if you were ugly you take it personally
there's just ugly people out yeah he
wouldn't show you his sex films if he
thought you were ugly precisely thank
you grant yeah so do you have a name for
this album that's being recorded in
Montreal or Quebec or where I'm
uh I'm playing with a few different
titles but I'm thinking um um South St
Paul Book of the Dead okay but uh
and it's out in stores now probably by
the time this show hits the air it takes
a while to edit these things with my uh
oh it does take a long time to edit when
are you going to show it uh who
knows ladies and gentlemen it could be
out it could be out right now ladies and
gentleman Grant
har now amand it is no introduction but
I'm giving one anyway hiu
Jim do I have to leave with my
girlfriend
okay thank you grant and
gang people gather around here I have a
cautionary haiku for you
today which goes out to all the men out
there who are thinking about growing a
mustache
no and it goes like
this man with stash
appears despite the designer
shirt girls laugh look elsewhere I got
to go though
you don't have to you're fine give me
that mic you
mother yeah news flash I got
a if I was from Ireland my name might be
Liam and I might got teeth but Joe you
can't see them cuz I got a goddamn
mustache drunkly smacking your Catholic
wife in the face b
boom um hey guys shut up red your moue
going down
you want to step to this you better step
back cousin cuz I got a mustache and
you're still Peach fing got a God damn
mustache no I ain't going to buy a beer
kid I was walking by the bakery they was
baking some dough my friend said do you
smell that I was like dude no got a
goddamn mustache I show you what bread
smells like
kid DEA people find my mustache and
obstacles trying to read my lips
impossible I like to drink beer wine and
cider it makes me smile and must stache
gets wider got a goddamn mustache what
the [ __ ] is he talking about
yo my mustache is worth a million yours
is worth a nickel I asked my mom what it
was like when I was borned she said it
tickled
cuz I had a goddamn
mustache busting that out
ride y some people think I'm Buddha some
people think I'm weird some people think
I'm Jesus he had a beard I got a godamn
mustache what a way to spend
Easter
god
yo the hair on my face grows from my fol
and I twist it on the end cuz I'm
diabolical got a goddamn mustache
killing James Bond with the ingenious
planned [ __ ]
yeah
yeah my mustache Rhymes are almost done
I want to give a shout out to Goose from
Top
Gun blonde mustache he died though it
wasn't Maverick's fault
though you kept having those dreams
though you know IC man in his face
you're
dangerous got a goddamn
mustache
yeah
mustach in the summer time you find me
sitting on the stoop with this thing
under my nose that tends to strain soup
with my goddamn must cuz what bad
dog when the fall comes around it ain't
that hard flip me upside down and rake
your yard [ __ ] with my goddamn mustache
all the leaves are brown you stupid
mother
yeah your face will be forgotten mine's
iconic cuz my mustache is real and not
ironic you P Smoking fix gear [ __ ] I
take
your with
Myck T by yeah St Go
kid we need to get better security
here now a word from our
sponsors drinking with the end is proud
to be sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV
Vodka no matter if it's UV blue
raspberry UV red cherry UV green apple
UV Ivory vanilla or UV orange vodka UV
flavored vodkas offer a premium product
without the high price tag please visit
UV vodka.com for additional information
and recipes no beer in the midwest has a
grander brewing tradition than Grain
Belt for over 100 years Grain Belt has
been the beer that fathers have passed
on to sons and friends have passed
amongst each other at local bars and
watering holes it is a beer with
tradition that spans Generations which
is why it has become legendary both here
and across the country next time you go
out ask for a
premium a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest news source and the AV club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at news stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at the onion.com
and avclub.com
Pizza luche proudly supports drinking
with Ian free delivery until 2:30 a.m.
weekdays and 3:30 a.m. weekends download
our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with Ian is nothing
without our sponsors please support
them all right ladies and gentlemen
thanks for sticking around to drink with
Ian how you
doing all right luckily we did not only
just have grant for
interviewee we also have him on as a
musical guest tonight so I want to Rouse
the round of applause for Grant
why don't you all come a little closer
you know I like my audience you know to
be close but not like the other kind of
close Time Heals time goes on and time
really
flies time hurts and time can cut you
cut you down a
size there's no need to tou you now no
well I'm doing
fine life to can cut you when I cut you
out of mine you're making me sorry sorry
somehow you're making me sorry sorry
somehow there's no need to talk to you
you let to know what's on your
mind no need to see you either no I'm
just being
kind whoever cares for your Affairs will
sort it out for
you send me a Suba baby tell me what to
do you making me sorry sorry somehow
you making me sorry sorry
somehow you making me sorry sorry
somehow you making me
sorry
somehow there's no need to think about
you think about the past
those days stand out in my mind you know
those days were the
last I know that the time it is coming
and I'm waiting for the
day I give you everything in the world
just to get it out of the way you're
making me sorry sorry
somehow you making me sorry sorry sorry
somehow you making me sorry sorry
somehow you making me
sorry
sorry somehow
W up I got dressed and went to
herum with no idea what the future
deemed I would become my uncle is an
admiral as for me I have no
trade my name is Clint and these are
observations I have made these are the
last
days nity of pompe these are the last
days
uhhuh hey hey these are the last days
pretty little city barely Inland from
the sea a social life of Suarez and
Deery what took 500 years to build was
the in our flash who the people temples
government houses all covered up in a
these are the last
days in the city of Pompei these are the
last
days
ahaa hey hey these are the
who woke up I got dressed and went to
hulum who I do what the future deed I
would become oh I'm UNC he is an admiral
as for me I have no trade my name is
plint and these are observations I have
made these are the last
days in the city of B P these are the
last
days in the city of Pompei these are the
days in the city of pom Bay these are
the last
days in the city of pmay these are the
last
days in the city of P these are the last
days in the city of Pompei these are the
last days last days last days last days
last days
thank you very much you all have a good
time be good ladies and gentlemen
granart and I'd also like to thank Grant
har Grant har for being the interview
tonight and I'd like to apologize to
that pinata from the sex tape that's
stringing with E and we'll see you next
time we don't smoke and we don't chew
and don't go out with girls who do you