I can't see anything the L all
right hey Neil I'm glad you could make
it yeah I wouldn't miss this for a world
I'm so excited it's going to be a good
time man yeah so what's up with the
camera crew here oh I don't even notice
him anymore um actually the Minnesota
film Project decided all everything I do
is so damn interesting they actually
have given me a pair of Canadian
filmmakers this is John Claude And this
is robes Pierre how's it going e going J
ah it's what's happening I what's going
on you going know I well I don't know
you ready to do that thing that thing
yeah well if you're ready to do that
thing I'm ready to do that thing I'm
talking about the other thing I'm
talking about oh that thing all right
all right what I do
best
[Applause]
drinking with
the it's
fun drinking and
[Music]
driving singing on the street corner
yeah
[Music]
yeah hey hey come on seriously what are
you being paid for yeah it's all about
me I don't necessarily agree that it's
interesting all the time but you know
it's it's all right a yeah from Canada
yeah well we found out that it's cheaper
to film stuff in there you know is
everybody you know everybody shoots
stuff in Toronto and all that uh so
somebody had the bright idea why don't
we bring Canadians here we'll pay them
the same you know we won't we won't have
to worry about taxes we'll pay them the
same amount but we'll do it in America
yeah I think it was Pen's idea this is
like the part of the snow bait nobody
talks about they're nice guys though I
mean they're a little bit close to the
boom sometimes but they're they're ni it
up seriously
um yeah okay that's that's that's
probably better um [ __ ] yeah I don't
know I we they aren't actually
filmmakers they're just Canadians we
thought we thought they all knew what
they were doing yeah uhhuh yeah no no
I'm just on the bus now yeah no I'm
telling you there's a fine line between
pornography and prostitution that's why
he's not even supposed car around he's
not even supposed to be on on the show
yeah yeah no of course I hate cell phone
talkers I know it's like the rudest and
you notice they always talk really damn
loud like they like they have something
to say like look at me I'm like
everybody else in America who has a damn
cell phone that guy know that guy from
that TV show yeah no would love this
yeah no hold on hey you're Conan right
that's me all right I told you yeah it's
Conan no actually I'm I'm not
actually you look just like him though
I've never got that before thank you wow
yeah I'm telling you no he's right no
I'm going to get a picture with him oh
yeah no I'll call you back yeah no okay
hold on all right
bye it's always good to meet a fan yeah
of course holy crap let's see here no
all right that's Tetris hold on uh huh
huh Smile Smile this
guy let's do another one that looks like
turn out yeah it's not my good side yeah
hey
huh yeah oh that looks great that looks
great so your mom your mom watches me oh
yeah she loves your show she's made way
better than Jay well I I I I get I agree
yeah's way too political and everything
you're on later when her DTS kick in
that's why she loves your show but
actually I'm not I'm not cing O'Brien we
do a show here in town called drinking
with Ian it's like a public access thing
it's on Channel 6 it's on all the damn
time you ever seen the bumper stickers
they say drinking with Ian yeah that guy
he saw an awkward hours of the night
right you have no idea who I am to you
yeah that's all right I got to delete
that then yeah well well here can you
send it to me at least it's always good
to I'll put this up in Myspace looks
like we have fans Myspace what the hell
is that uh it's are you familiar with uh
with Google go yeah lot like yep like
Google exactly Jesus do you know David
Hasselhoff personally yes I do actually
nice yeah yeah it's it's like German
solidarity or something are you kidding
me German drunks are awesome
yeah yeah I I'm mostly dramatic know
that I am not Irish everybody thinks I
am but I swear I'm actually I'm I'm
actually mostly German really it's true
I got a little bit of wel [ __ ] me oh
yeah I you had a little bit of wel [ __ ]
yeah I saw that one coming up the street
Sor and uh speaking of Germans and
Germans in the media have you ever seen
a movie called Munich M oh yeah yeah
with the with the really like it's a
workout video because those people are
really skinny on no no no it's uh it's
actually about um people being taken
hostage uh it's it's pretty cool I mean
really I highly recommend it I think
Eric Bana you know who Eric Bana is
don't you oh yeah yeah I think he's in
it he was the hul but we're about to do
something like that right now that's
right excuse me
driver um I got um I hate to tell you
this like this is kind of awkward um
we've got some guns and um I say we just
take a different route what do you think
is that okay all right well well it well
cuz seriously I I will shoot you I'd
hate to have to but I mean yeah so all
right well hey Wayne what do you think
about this yeah Wayne do you like this
Wayne yeah you're all excited about this
being a part of a television show know
who the we were mother I want top a c
your ass anybody else not know who I am
here you who we are what what's the name
of the
show thank you very good God damn it's
amazing you have to do to get [ __ ]
publicity in this goddamn Chan all right
um all right just all cool just keep
going up the way all right all right
cool we have alli's ready Allie's ready
cool right there're right there at the
corner pick these guys up I'd hate to
have to put a cap in your ass good they
have beard too
sweet thank you all right BR it clear
orderly just go right back here hold on
hold
on thank you no problem
sir all right we're going to do a shot
of the night you guys familiar with this
yeah I said are you familiar with
this can we open our beers yes you can
open your beers open theing
beer all
right hey everybody how you doing good
good ready for some free booze that that
isn't beer
yes all
right we have the lovely travel bar here
and tonight shot since we're on a bus
how many of you are familiar with uh
that Old Hippie dude kenkey and has
booked the Electric Kool-Aid Acid
Test read outdated texts he he he ran a
group called The Mary pranksters but
he's aing dead hippie so who cares
tonight we're the merry drinkers
and the electric koola acid test
tonight's shot is called the Electric
Kool-Aid Acid
shot and to make the Electric Kool-Aid
Acid shot shot you yeah oh sorry you
take a shot shot of Trader Vick spiced
rum and since we're in a moving vehicle
I'm actually only going to do a shot
shot you take aot shot shot of cranberry
juice that I have in this handy dandy
flask I swear to God it is just
cranberry
juice Jesus Jesus there you
go Ali stench is cool cool and you take
a splash splash of grenadine grenadine
we got some ice in the cooler cooler so
I'm not going to add it right now you
kind of swishing around
and in honor of Mary drinkers the
Electric Kool-Aid Acid shot shot from
the
house all right we're going to pass
these shots around I'm glad you showed
up prepared Ollie you know I knew you
going well you know I never leave the
house without it yeah Neil yeah all
right now everybody a personal favorite
of
mine the Electric koola Shot Kool-Aid
Acid shot shot all right everybody on
three one two do it along with me God it
no oh
you whoa salute there you
go God so yeah I don't know I figured
it's a nice day for a for a cruise you
know and bus prizes being what they are
and gas prices being what they are you
know good time to use some guns you know
who needs to worry about you know $4 a
gallon when you got big hand Cannon
exactly uh the the crowd seems a little
uh nervous yeah well they should be well
that after that shot they should you
knowell out a little bit you'd think but
these people are iffy at best Neil how
you doing back there is everybody is the
morale good yeah they're they're they're
they're being okay all right they just
had a shot everybody clap right
[Applause]
now shut up wait a second hold on hold
on what the what the hell's that back
there we're getting pulled over all
right everybody that's natural try to
hide all of the beard if you can did you
want you guys call them on me I knew you
I couldn't trust you sons of [ __ ] all
right we just pull over I
guess that's not even aing cop car we're
being pulled over by the god Ghost
Busters we actually are damn it all
right well um I should probably go out
there and uh see what the deal
is fck I'm so not in the mood to deal
with Ghostbusters
what is this I got my knife put it away
put it away put it away that's friend
sir uh are you to this bus sure I don't
mean to alarm you but as you go by we
detected a class three full roaming
Vapor are you guys actually ghost
posters H yeah we are sir we're getting
tremendous readings from your bus all
right yep so um we're going to take care
of this for you old I mean I don't know
I guess it could be H Neil did you pick
up anything in there yeah actually I did
uh at least two or three homeless people
have died on the bus okay I we're going
to take care of this for you you'll be
on the
road you'll be right on the road before
you you guys you guys got this under
under control right I don't need to do
anything here all right stand do this
cost a lot
[Applause]
um everything seems to be okay you got
it trapped yeah yeah right yeah you guys
have a great day you'll be fine the bus
will run you be build the city for this
[ __ ] right yes all
right I'm ready to believe
[Music]
you you know what for hijacking CU I
think this is going pretty well I think
it's actually okay all right everybody
want to keep going we still got plenty
of beer yeah back on the
bus Neil you
go
clap
[Applause]
better make him stop clapping shut up
all right um well as is tradition oning
with the even this is kind of a
non-traditional episode obviously uh we
have a guest just so happens one of our
illustrious crew recently has uh gotten
all sorts of Fame and Fortune this man
has won a Grammy I won a rousing around
of Applause we're all the way in the
back of the bus the one Earthly Dan
schle hey
[Applause]
Dan all right thanks for coming out for
this no problem thanks for having me I
know it's kind of an awkward way I mean
I know you know generally our guests
aren't you know co-conspirators but
today I figur we could do something a
little bit different yeah there's
nothing wrong with being an accessory to
a major crime yeah and you've been
involved with the show since pretty much
the beginning so this is a big deal that
we're finally having you on as a guest
you might remember Dan from our uh
Christmas episode when he was known as
Jewish Dan yep that was that was a good
role for you did you did you have fun
doing that luckily it didn't take a lot
of practice it was a life of PT up
frustration yeah so you've had some big
uh big stuff happen to you lately you
were recently on the cover of City Pages
I was oh I didn't bring that City Pages
Round of
Applause no all right not that damn much
they're not our sponsor the onion is
though um and yeah and and and and the
shells um so how did you end up getting
on the cover though that's pretty insane
um you know it's just a lot of years of
hard work doing comedy and doing it at a
level that uh was kind of accidental but
like stepping in at the top he runs a
label here in town called standup
records it's it's a comedy label and one
of the best comedy labels in the country
if I do say so myself and um you got a
Grammy on your uh on your mantle piece I
do I've uh when I started recording
comedy I started working with Louis
black and uh I've been producing his
records even though he has left my label
he's moved on he's moved on to another
label and I produced his uh Carnegie
Hall album and we wound up uh getting
the Grammy in 2007 yeah I mean that's
that's a big deal man and I mean did you
ever think when you were starting this
cuz you started I know your roots uh
he's started is just doing a little punk
label you know back in Nebraska yeah
yeah in my dorm room in uh in Lincoln
Nebraska at the University uh thereof I
I started and had my closet was my
warehouse and uh you know we did a lot
of bands we did 70 records with bands
from uh the Midwest 70 I didn't realize
he did that many however you know the
reality was you know bands that I
idolized were like fugazi and the Jesus
lizard and buildozer and these are bands
that uh nobody really knew of let alone
could possibly ever be in the contention
for for Award of so to me it was
something that was like it was out there
but it wasn't anything that could ever
be remotely associated with anything
that I yeah no I I understand that not
yeah bands like the bands we like aren't
the ones that get big awards no um so
what made you make the jump into comedy
after you just done dealing with punk
rock I was well you know I helped
discover a big band from Iowa called
slipnot and they he is to blame I am I
am partially partially not entirely yeah
uh once they signed to a bigger label
they kind of turned their back on uh the
people that helped them get to that
level and uh once they moved on I was it
coincided with when I moved here okay so
it was a good time to fold up that
business because it was a lot of
heartache and not a lot of reward either
spiritually or financially I mean and
that's the thing I mean yeah nobody ever
does a record label as a career path
they do a record label because they
really like music exact and I think a
lot of people end up stop liking music
as much because they end up you know
blowing a lot of time a lot of energy
and a lot of money yeah yeah I ran up
credit cards you know I mean I ran up
credit cards to ridiculous ridiculous uh
sums and you know when I approached
Lewis it was on the hope that it was
going to be a one-off thing maybe we'd
sell a th000 copies and it would be
awesome I'd get to work with this guy
who I was a fan of anyway and you just
basically walked up to him after a show
this wasn't like my manager will contact
your manager kind of stuff no no what
what was funny was I I was working a day
job at the time doing text support so I
was driving home from work and I heard
that he was at the comedy club I ran up
to my apartment left my car running in
the parking lot he yeah here get me one
to Two Beards two be up front beard
three beards oh God they're serious
they're serious we don't
care I want a
premium anyway don't shoot
me yes it wasn't that your manager
contacting their man I went I went to
the club and it was really funny cuz I'd
been here so few a little amount of time
I didn't have any uh I didn't have any
stationary I didn't have any business
cards so I took a lined uh notebook and
wrot and basically basically wrote uh
I'm not a stalker I'm a fan I put out
records I want to work with you and
amazingly enough nobody had contacted
him yet no one had contacted at this
because that was kind of like I that was
like the NAT of Comedy recording really
cuz there wasn't too much stuff going on
other than like you know you know crap
like is before L the cable guy but like
Jeff Foxworthy type Foxworthy going
Chris Rock was just barely starting up
recording at this time it was mainly on
cable like pay Network at that time and
not many albums so I happened to step in
and you know Lewis had just been
rejected Ed by Warner Brothers Comedy
Central was not interested in a record
label at that point in their history
yeah so it was the right place at the
right time and then it was just a matter
of staying in touch with his management
for a few months and then the next thing
you know we're recording right before
Thanksgiving in Madison Wisconsin nice
this is in 99 and as you mentioned yeah
I mean Comedy Central was not interested
in doing uh record label at the time but
now they are now they're like your
number one competition they are yeah
they they started out Strong by like uh
aping what I did but with more money
behind them so yeah so watch out no it's
the way it is I mean it's literally
David versus Goliath oh yeah cuz they're
backed by is that that's Warner Brothers
money right it's viom and Warner
Brothers and you're but you're but
you're just a dude who's running this
out of his house I'm a dude running it
out of a house in a storage St yeah so I
mean but still you're managing I mean
despite them being backed by gazillions
of dollars you're still kind of kicking
their ass aren't you kind of yeah I mean
as far as edgy you know
thought-provoking material that's where
we're at you know that's what we care
about and uh you know you know there's
always going to be somebody that doesn't
want to deal with a big corporations so
as long as I have that going for me
it'll be fine and if you're anybody
that's not going to want to deal with a
large corporation it's going to be
comedians cuz they're all a bunch of
jaded bastards who are scared of being
screwed over you know as so many people
have been in the past so I mean you're a
friendly face and you know everything's
up and up exactly and you know it's been
a good thing overall for both The
Comedians and myself and so uh who do
you have on the label now who are you
excited about uh the new folks I'm
excited about I'm going to be working on
a DVD for Rick Shapiro uh we reissued
and he was on Lucky Louie he was on
Lucky Lou as Uncle Jerry okay so uh
we're going to be doing a DVD for him
hopefully in the fall um we're going to
be doing a CD for Al Madrigal really
funny comedian who you haven't heard of
yet but when you do it's going to be
pretty where's he out of he's out of La
okay has he has he done any TV stuff he
has he was on uh the shortlived welcome
to the captain that was on NBC this fall
never even heard of it exactly yeah okay
Jeffy Tambour Jeffrey Tambor is on it I
love Jeffrey Tambour I hate him how the
hell do you hate Jeffrey that's like
hating
ketchup I'm not a fan of ketchup either
well then you're dead to me man ketchup
all right anyway and then we just had
vinyl for Pat and oswal's feeling kind
of patent yeah and you've been doing a
lot of vinyl you're bringing back comedy
vinyl which is pretty cool you had David
Cross Lewis and now Paton Oswalt that's
very good and hopefully more as time
goes on so yeah would you ever get back
into music if if somebody put a gun to
your head uh only metaphorically
metaphorically metaphorically uh only if
it's a band that I knew from the old
days you know we're talking talking
about recording kildo are uh live in
September cuz they're playing some
reunion okay they're back together uh
not fully but kind of okay it's the
original lineup and they're playing some
shows across the us some festivals I'll
be working with them I don't think I'll
be putting it out under the uh standup
or
ismus but I but I will be happy to
record them cuz where the hell are we
driving to we're going off-roading in
the bus um anyway but yeah okay well so
yeah so music's not something you'd want
to get back andz I don't blame itz that
would be a huge pain in the ass I look
at it as my public service years and
I've already done my time in public
service you know comedy is actually
allowing me to slowly make a living at
it and not have to work a day job and I
I prefer it I prefer doing stuff like
that I prefer working with guys like you
who doing the show yeah and actually in
full disclosure he put out our DVD Round
of Applause for our
[Applause]
first now you can buy it though you can
buy it online U fortunately we don't
have a gun to your head at home but if
we did uh we'd highly recommend we'd
highly recommend that we do that um but
anyway a round of applause for our
friend
[Applause]
Dan right here we are in front of deja
vu the home of what is it like 100 cute
girls and one ugly one uh and and we
have Hau Jim ladies and gentlemen hiu
Jim
[Applause]
[Music]
hey how you doing Tex wow am I glad you
guys are here man yeah this cowboy has a
freak
magnet oh no no he's hu Jim's never
unprepared so you're hanging out in
front of deju and you're worried about
freaks huh in in it's it's freak magnet
here I did okay though you did all right
all right uh okay so uh what do you you
got are you prepared I know you always
are I got a hiu for y allall y hey
everybody all
right all right take like that you're
the last person to get shot thank you
all right all right it's actually kind
of a public service announcement it goes
like this Global
Citizens do your part take a bus going
green feels great look at
[Applause]
[Music]
that shut up so how so you actually had
got a green premium that's never a good
sign oh it's delicious yeah yeah going
green
man well that is tasty everybody reduce
your carbon footprint when you're going
to take over a bus make sure you do it
with lots of friends like these and I
think this is the best I've only been
involved in a couple hijackings but you
guys are great nobody's screaming
nobody's freaking out nobody's rushing
the cockpit a round of applause for
yourselves
[Applause]
all right every episode ring with we
have a band um so I think we should
probably get this bus here who's got my
gun oh here I'll take your gun excuse me
Mr driver man can we go to First Avenue
please sure can all right thank
you all right we can do this this is
going to be awesome yeah
all right now just follow my lead follow
my lead you guys you don't don't give me
up I'm serious talking to
you guys how you doing uh you might be
playing a show tonight yeah uh yeah I
don't know if you heard of it first hav
has been turned into a gay bar oh really
sad but true so everybody if you play
this everybody's going to asse ass gay I
know I know we're all manly men aren't
we come on that's right we're as manly
as well anyway so we uh you're taking
over a bus actually I mean I think you
guys are cool I can tell you we kind of
hijacked a bus um what do you think
about just uh loading in here and
playing and stuff no
[ __ ] seriously do I have to kill a
motherucker on First Avenue come on
everybody let's do
this damn musicians all right here's the
deal um we're going to get them loaded
on the on the on the bus um and we screw
it uh we actually have people paying for
this hijacking take a look at at our
sponsor
[Music]
you'll save money and time you'll get
the best of merchandise and service when
you patronize these good neighbors no
beer in the midwest has a grander
brewing tradition than Grain Belt for
over 100 years Grain Belt has been the
beer that fathers have passed on to sons
and friends have passed amongst each
other at local bars and watering holes
it is a beer with tradition that spans
Generations which is why it has become
legendary both here and across the
country next time you go out ask for a
premium drinking with the end is proud
to be sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV
Vodka no matter if it's UV blue
raspberry UV red cherry UV green apple
UV Ivory vanilla or UV orange vodka UV
flavored vodka offer a premium product
without the high price tag please visit
UV vodka.com for additional information
and
recipes a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest news source and the AV club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at news stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at the union.com
and avclub.com pizza luche proudly
supports drinking with Ian free delivery
until 2:30 a.m. weekdays and 3:30 a.m.
weekends download our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with Ian is nothing
without our sponsors please support
them ladies and gentlemen thank you for
sticking around not like you had muching
Choice um we stole this band directly
for First Avenue I want a rousing round
of applause for off with their handsy
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm not going to go to work today want
to feel a sunshot on my face and pretend
like everything's okay well let anything
get to me Cofe cigarett of on
my yeah I'm going to be
[Music]
a yeah got to be a day I want to go
to hey
I'm not going to go to work today want
to feel the Sunshine on my face and like
everything okay let
anything I'm not going to go to work
today feel Sun my face
be yeah I got to be do all day to go
[Music]
go
my and I soon
[Music]
I don't
anyone my neck my leg
[Music]
[Applause]
ladies and gentlemen off with their
heads and I want to thank Dan here for
being our
guest that trigger the end this week
we'll see you next time God or
else around here this is my
[Music]