[Music]
drink
it
with get get
[Music]
Dr how y'all doing tonight I said how
y'all doing tonight
we got a great show lined up for you
tonight our special guest is Mary
Mac and our very special musical guest
is baby
gut now the man of the hour the one the
[Music]
only thanks for showing
up television programming
that one there you go everybody thanks
for showing up yet again how you doing
tonight are you feeling good are you
feeling
sexy a man who always feels good and
sexy me ladies and gentlemen Neil
everybody a man who only feels good and
or sexy at specific times one and only
Oli stench
hey everybody how you
doing I had a whole story built up for
tonight's
shot but I'm just going to get right to
it you can use your imagination
tonight's shot is called the
[Music]
[Applause]
reacharound it involves me being in a
bar last night and being off for 20
bucks
and so to make a reach
around you
take half a shot
shot of fcking Irish whiskey
wh you take a full
shot of Trader Vick's coffee flavored
lur
L you take two two two shots of
cream see I'm so excited I can't even
open it
up add some ey
Swit it
around Shake It
Up we're not going to strain this
one and to demonstrate the reach around
we have our lovely and talented shot
girl
[Applause]
[Music]
Maria here's how you do the reach
around shots on the house
[Applause]
ladies and gentlemen the reach around
coming to a hand near you make way for
our lovely shop
professionals coming at
you hey this
is it's like looking at
Mars there's a whole lot of depth that
shouldn't necessarily be
here but I guess that is the reacher
around really isn't it all right who's
still waiting for the reacher round
other other than all of us really
ultimately 26 years all right everybody
are you ready to do the reacher
out on three one 2 3
salute thank you tasty ladies and
gentlemen Allie stetch
[Music]
everyone I enjoyed that thoroughly
didn't
you and if you didn't blame the
bartender not the sponsors that's the
motto of drink with
Ian all right do you guys like short
films act like you
do I want to welcome up to the stage a
local filmmaker who we've actually had
on before Ryan Taylor where are you at
Ryan so uh we had you on what was it
like second season not that you'd know
why would you pay attention exactly uh
we had you on a while ago a couple years
ago how's how has it been since then for
you as a local filmmaker that's been
pretty good yeah it's been pretty good
yeah g looks
bound not really all right sweet so you
have a new film you're going to show us
yep tell me about it uh well it's called
the expectant uh it was created for the
48 Hour film project and I think the
last one you shown was also 48 hour uh
we drew a horror film and I
figured what was what would be scarier
than the topic that I covered so uh
that's what we decided to do and a hush
Falls over the room you want to watch it
come
on I'm just I'm just baiting you here
let's watch it
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
a hi honey oh hey how was your run it
was uh it was good it was good I think
um I might just head out for a bit more
fresh a though all right well come back
soon cuz I have something important to
tell you yeah okay
hey do do I know you what well you look
very familiar
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
a
great hi honey guess what my sister's
pregnant ladies and gentlemen the
expected by Ryan
Taylor now did this uh this win anything
at the 48 Hour film
festival uh I believe it won best sound
design well that would actually win
something that means something I'm
giving you a premium
[Music]
[Applause]
not to take anything away from the field
of sound design you know maybe a little
ladies and gentlemen Ryan Taylor local
filmmaker extraordinaire thanks for
showing up tonight
[Applause]
man are we done is that it you guys want
to do some more all right well I think
we have another guest backstage ready
for you she's a local
comedian um who actually has made uh
great strides like she actually see
people ask me Ian what do you do for a
living like I know this Tri with Ian
[ __ ] ain't real and the answer
unfortunately is that I'm poor I am like
I don't really do much anything else but
that's because I'm lazy she works her
damn ass off and has actually made a
living at this touring all over the
continental United States and Beyond she
was uh just on Last Comic Standing and
she's about to be on drinking with the
ladies and gentlemen Mary Max
[Applause]
[Music]
thank oh
manow you got a lot of stuff going on
Mary Ma I always have a lot of stuff
with me oops my city accidentally fell
all onto the um table I can put it back
for you if you want okay no no and thank
you so much for having me on the show no
problem Mary Mac how you doing I'm I'm
doing well is this too can you is it too
tiny or can you is it okay can we turn
up the psy Clin
can can can you you know what I like to
do is I like to hold the mini
microphones like it's a a real mic you
have a big microphone too if you want I
do I like it but but this is like um
Yeahs like freaking stereo I guess I'm
not supposed to use this I'm going I was
going to do this cuz I thought oh maybe
this will hurt people's ears yeah I'm
going to tuck this one back into my
bodice your
bodice so all right um anyways you
already mentioned you have c um so how
you how you doing good thank you why do
you keep touching me so much um it's
weird but you should tell okay right now
you said I had to dress up and I I
dressed up and I was going to I was I
was going to wear this dress I I bought
this dress on sale and I was like What
if I get married and then I could wear
it cuz but then but then Ian was like
what you come to the show and then I
said that's good enough and I know so
I'm wearing it and uh this is actually
my second wedding dress that I've owned
yeah and the first wedding dress what
happened to the first wedding dress Mary
oh let's call that one setup um the the
first well I was at a garage sale and um
appropriately for the show I was drunk
and um and then just have you ever just
gotone to a garage sale and you were
drunk and then you're like I need that
wedding dress and then and then you
bought it and then you later you would
hold it up and there's pit stains and
stuff in it like like it's a used it's a
used dress but it's not really that good
of a deal cuz of the of the
sweat but have you ever considered
traveling as a a professional comedian
on the road I have not cuz I'm not even
an amateur comedian I'm more of a song
and dance man got to show up yeah wing
it I don't I can't remember material so
I just got to hope that people don't
hate me I had a dream the other day and
um this was not like a Martin Luther
King dream but it was I know it was
really it was a real white
dream and I've had those yeah you are
really p pale and I know it's probably
been I mean but I'm am pale well no I I
believe I'm the Aryan
archetype yeah and hey I didn't I wasn't
asked for it I didn't I just kind of
ended up redheaded and stuff yeah I'm
sorry I totally stepped on your line no
no no no actually it might not even be
timely um but um I hope people you know
we don't know I don't know when this is
going to air I don't either or if it
ever will well the answer is right now
hello television people oh yeah um a I
have a no-name beer cuz I'm allergic to
the sponsor but I that was that bad was
that bad I I love
premium and um but I do but I drink this
I have to I drink no name beer I like my
beer like I like my bacon and
so so um what else you got going on all
right so anyway uh you were on the Last
Comic Standing um of the NBC the
national Broadcast Network
um how did that work for you was it was
it a horrible experience
yeah it is no name makes it
tasty if uh if that show was a town it'd
be a real hole you
knowz well okay are you fans of the show
are you a fan of that show I am not I
have not seen it for several seasons
well I was I will say I was not sober
for the last episode again several times
in my life I've thank you for tailoring
this for us but uh yeah okay no so
you're basically plucked out even though
you're already a touring comedian do you
prefer comedian or comedian folk
humorist folk humorist all right yeah
you've been a touring folk humorist for
a long time or not a long time but for a
while you you weren't you weren't
obscure and then somehow you ended up on
Last Comic Standing uh how did you find
yourself doing that was it against your
wishes it sounds like it might have been
well they called me and asked me to do
it because it's reality television
um the and that's how that works so but
uh but now I started out in
paa
but ask me what the name of my PO ban
was so you started out in po um I hear
uh what was the name of the PO band you
started out with it was um Shaggy green
band comma thee and um yeah we put the
the at the end cuz um you know that way
that's that's how you'd find it in the
Yellow Pages yep set ourselves apart
from all the other po bands in Nashville
Tennesse at that time and so yeah we
started out like that and then we were
pretty bad so I just St for time yeah
and uh people running get between the
one timeing out with somebody do you
know one time we were playing everybody
was always drunk and so I'm I'm a good
guest for you and um but one time I
looked I always played in the front you
know clarinet or whatever and uh one
time I heard something weird going on in
the Rhythm Section and I looked back and
the tuba player was laying on the ground
he was just on the ground and I was like
asked the drummer what happened I knew
he wasn't dead cuz he was he was a PO
that's a good insurance to have yeah cuz
I generally just assume stand's dead but
he was laying on the ground like he was
still sitting in the chair like RI
mortis had set in you know and he's and
but I knew he wasn't dead cuz he was
still trying to play and uh and I asked
the drummer and and she said I said what
happened and she's like he just tipped
over and so they yeah that was how good
we were I drank a lot but I guess the
power of Poa has never uh reduced me to
a a pile of a pile of guy on the floor
but now what I've been doing now is I'm
in the daytime is hard to make a living
during comedy so on the day what I do is
I'm an eagles cover band and um yeah and
um it's just me it's just me and my uh
washboard and the name of uh my band is
um uh marry Mac and uh that's not a very
good
idea and but we only can you hold this
yeah I'll this we only do Eagle cover or
okay so here's one we do everybody um
probably you know it
already wiy
[Music]
woman that's one on that's one we do
come on thank you an old favorite on
your classic rock radio stations does
yeah does anybody like does anybody like
the eagle son I I love yeah Oh I thought
I thought I heard somebody the yellow
Desperado that's a good one okay um this
one's for you well here we go
um
desper why don't you wait no Desperado
is in
Miner
so I just scoot that I scoot that over w
why don't you come to your
SES we're out
R next
song Welcome to the hotel
[Music]
californ but that's but I wanted to tell
you um every time you hear this Bell uh
an eagle gets its wings
so that's oh thanks a lot that was weird
but Ian can I invite hio Jim up because
that's other he always all
[Applause]
[Music]
right I got I got dressed up tonight as
well who ordered
the so nice to meet you your order's up
um
so I uh I have a hiu all right can I
present it to the people as long as it
doesn't turn into a battle cuz we've
seen the East Coast West Coast Hau Wars
claim too many talents all right that
here we go nude man wait it's going to
be in the normal five syllable seven
syllable five okay right nude
man well he wasn't fully nude he had on
like some Whitey tidies and um I think
one sock in a real must up here but um
that wasn't in the hu that was but I
couldn't fit it in so
um uh nude man on my
steps does push-ups warns of gas leak he
doesn't live
here l g marry
ma she's got a CD called either you wake
up or you don't or CL don't to Mar
comedy.com and you can go to marymac
comedy.com to find out more about Mary
Ma
there's a lot to find out about but in
the meantime the man the fish Mr I Jim
the
[Applause]
Entertainer thanks everybody you know um
I hate to you know take you down a
couple notches but it must be done this
one goes out to the underemployed people
looking for work you know the people who
have a degree maybe uh it's not worth a
hill of beans those of you in college
stay there trust me this one goes out to
you job Market's still
tough let's lean on our mops a while and
give it some
thought go out to all the kurl berett
fans out there ladies and gentlemen hiu
[Music]
Chim all right everybody we'll be back
at scap moments with baby
[Music]
[Applause]
guts you'll save money and time you'll
get the best of merchandise and service
when you patronize these good neighbors
no beer in the midwest has a grander
brewing tradition than Grain Belt for
over 100 years Grain Belt has been the
beer that fathers have passed on to sons
and friends have passed amongst each
other at local bars and watering holes
it is a beer with tradition that spans
Generations which is why it has become
legendary both here and across the
country next time you go out ask for a
premium
drinking with the end is proud to be
sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV Vodka
no matter if it's UV blue raspberry UV
red cherry UV green apple UV Ivory
vanilla or UV orange vodka UV flavor
vodka offer a premium product without
the high price tag please visit UV
vodka.com for additional information and
recipes a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest new source and the AV club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at news stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at the union.com
and avclub.com pizz luche proudly
supports drinking with Ian free delivery
until 2:30 a.m. weekdays and 3:30 a.m.
weekends download our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with Ian is nothing
without our sponsors please support
them oh
hey I'm Rick and I'm Theo and this is
the conspiracy theory hour webcast yeah
hey we want to thank all of you for
checking out our first webcast got so
much to tell you guys we're open these
we're going to open your eyes man yeah
we're going to make you see the truth
yeah about everything all the best
conspiracies man about the new second
sun that's coming about 911 711 and
7-Eleven lesser known 7-Eleven
conspiracies and and the trans Texas
lunar cour to our highway it's going to
make the first Super planet for the moon
huh stench wielding dust Giants some
people call them old people whatever
they know a lot L about morphing they
morph okay yeah this is what we got this
in for you to open your eyes man let you
know the truth yeah like tell them why
you why you got into this man I don't
think they can handle it dude open your
mouth well it started when I was younger
I was going to go down and capture the
Easter Bunny yeah when I got down there
the Easter Bunny had transformed into my
parents yeah I remember that yeah sent
me into a blind rage remember yeah you
can see anything yeah my whole junior
year blind as a bat yeah how about me I
think someone more of me because I used
to be like captain of the football team
and stuff and and then when I graduated
you know I just didn't even have
anything to talk about to anybody and
like I was just a pizza driver loser guy
something happen yeah it's all true yeah
so why are we whispering cuz we don't
want to wake up my
mom why do you live with your mom oh I
don't know why do you live with me and
my
mom shut up yeah all right so check us
out at conspiracy theorist gmail.com
yeah you can send us anything ask us any
questions at all we'll talk to you about
I'll tell you about JFK and how he's KGB
I'll tell you that you know and he
morphed too by the way because if you
watch theuer film you even see him more
if into a dead guy yeah back into to the
left back into to the to the dead yeah
but I'm I'm I'm through man I'm I'm My
Eyes Are Open man I'm through being
brainwashed man hey boys boys what you
doing down there you watching porn again
no Mom no we're not watching porn we're
doing our webcast gosh so check us out
conspiracy theorist at gmail.com yeah
you know and your mom kind of morphs
into a [ __ ] sometimes dude I'll morph
ladies and gentlemen thanks for sticking
around dram with the end tonight how you
doing our next guest has a new CD in
stores it's called the kissing disease
it's out on guilt-ridden pop records
everybody baby guts
[Music]
my to
bre like
to
[Music]
got I got
found you in one found me in one found
you
in found me
[Music]
in
to
everybody where in
my
iome
to
everybody and in my heart
[Music]
it
I I
can't I
can't ladies and gentlemen baby
guts it's called the kissing
disease is it in mono or is it in Stereo
it's in Stereo ladies and gentlemen it's
on guilt ritten pop records you run to
the nearest store you pick it up right
now uh also a round of applause for Mary
Mac and most of all Round of Applause
for you thanks for showing up tonight
that's stre with the end we'll see you
next time I guess