(laughter) Limo's here. You
Ready? Yeah.
Almost.
Yeah. I'm ready.
Let's do it.
Mr. Porter.
What's up buddy? Any thoughts, brother? We're rolling.
Um, I'd like to thank Jesus and small puppies,
and kids who have cancer, because they are what
give me inf… (mumbmbles) in… and, and beer.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome
Chris Porter!
What's up, Kansas City? How you doing?
Sit down. Have a seat.
Uh, it's good to be back. I just got back
from southern Florida.
Hell yeah. Holy shit,
the old people… are fucking everywhere!
Old people in southern Florida are like,
Mexicans are everywhere else.
You know what I'm saying? There's a lot of them.
But you know how Mexicans are cool and funny
and sometimes they can get you weed.
Yeah. Old people are the exact opposite.
They are mean and rude.
They don't give a shit about you or your crosswalk.
And I'm thinking, "Hey, old people!
If you're that close to death,
maybe you should be on your best behavior.
You know What I'm saying? Like a little kid right
before Christmas, your big days are coming.
Maybe You should finish strong."
You know? Maybe let me outta the elevator
before you clip me in the ankles with your fucking scooter.
Spent most of the day watching my new favorite show on MTV.
It's called "Engaged and Underage." Have you seen it?
It's hysterical. It's kids under the age of 21
and they're getting married.
They should rename it to, "Hey, Look,
We're Fucking Up Our Lives."
No one seems to give a shit.
In fact, mom and dad are financing it.
Why do you wanna get married under the age of 21?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
The government doesn't even trust you with beer yet.
Maybe that's a sign you're not ready for a life decision.
You don't know shit about yourself at the age of 20,
'cause you know you're growing up.
You hit plateaus in life where you change.
You know? You hit bigger ones when you get older.
Like when you're 50, the day shows up where you're a dude.
You're like, "Hey, fuck it. Shorts and loafers."
You do that. That's a good look.
Or if you're an 80-year-old woman,
apparently the day shows up
where you're like, "Yeah, fuck you.
I've got a beard.
It's white and it's wispy. Call me Santa.
I don't give a shit. I'm eating.
I'm just happy you're talking to me."
You hit a lot of those plateaus between the ages
of 20 and 35.
I've recently hit one.
I don't talk to stupid people anymore.
I know, I know. Even if I wanted to fuck you.
Remember those days? I mean, there was a day when I was 25.
Ladies, you could have said the dumbest shit in the world
and I would've agreed with you.
I've been like, "Fuck yeah! Coldplay's awesome.
They're The best!"
Now I can't do it. Something happened 26 years old.
,
My ears and my dick got connected.
Now if you say some stupid shit, it quits working. It does.
If you ask me who Led Zeppelin is,
I can't pee for like an hour.
You drink Red Bull with your liquor.
I don't even approach you anymore. I know, I know.
Fucking stop it for all of you guys girls, stop it.
Stop mixing the Red Bull with the liquor.
There's reason that your body shuts down when you've
had too much to drink.
It's 'cause you need to shut the fuck up, okay?
Your body has taken a vote
and decided your face needs to quit it.
That's why when you pass out, your arms are like this.
'cause you fucking tackled yourself.
You're like, "Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
It's three in the morning. Shut up,
okay? I don't want to talk anymore. It's three."
There's two things to do at three in the morning: Sleep…
and fuck. And that's it, right? Guess what?
Second one's not gonna be very good. You know why?
Because it's three in the morning.
That's why! You wanna talk to me at one,
I had to rock your world. It's three
now. I'm tired and grumpy. I did shit today.
If you live in an apartment complex,
you know the people that drink Red Bull,
'cause they don't park their cars,
they just slam 'em into shit.
(crash sounds) Lock it!
You know why these kids are getting married?
'cause these girls won't fuck 'em
until they get married, which is fine.
Ladies, if you wanna hold back the poon, God bless you.
But lemme tell you something, shit's gonna happen, okay?
If you put an obstacle in front of a 20 year-old virgin
and tell him that pussy is on the other side,
shit's gonna get done.
Okay? Marriage. What's that? A trip to the mall.
That's easy! He was going there anyway.
You know, why don't you think about the rest of us, ladies.
If you wield that kind of power,
why don't you think about society for a change?
How about, hey, I'm not fucking anybody
till they cure cancer.
It'll be two weeks. Some 20-year-old will be like, "I got it!
I got it right here! Right here!
It was carrots and mustard. Who knew?
No one had ever mixed them. 'cause they're gross.
But I'll work on AIDS next week,
but right I now I need a blow job,
okay? Then we'll cure your brother."
So I flew back from Florida. I was stopped in Atlanta.
I didn't want to, it's Delta's fault.
I was at an airport. I was at a McDonald's.
and the gentleman in front of me got his order
and it was incorrect.
And he was pissed. He was fucking pissed.
Like someone had dinged his Prius. He was angry.
And I just looked at him like, What's your level
of expectation at McDonald's?
Like, how angry can you get? Because yeah, yeah,
He fucked up your order. He did that. Yeah.
He fucked up his life three years ago.
Okay, he's got enough problems.
He workS at the airport McDonald's.
He can't even lie and say it's close to his house,
'cause it's not it's at the airport!
Just saying, give the guy a break,
you know? He's having a bad enough day.
He was gonna shoot himself in the face,
but they took his gun away at the checkpoint."
I just don't know why people get angry over stupid shit.
People get mad in traffic. I understand
if it's, like, a Saturday and you're on the Plaza
and some retard won't turn
left. I get that.
But Tuesday at 8:30 in the
morning, you can't get pissed.
People act like it's the first time the shit ever happened,
you know? "It's Tuesday at 8:30 in the morning.
What are all these cars doing here?"
So they honked her horns. Has that ever worked?
Have you ever been in gridlock?
And they're like, honk, honk. And everyone started
doing 70 again?!?
Like there are 15 stoners up at the front going, "Oh, shit!
Sorry! Sorry! My bad!
My bad. I was fucking with my iPod."
But I realized something.
It's always the same people
that honk their horns in traffic.
It's always people in shitty cars.
I'm not trying to be mean, but think about it.
Everyone in this room knows
what a shitty car horn sounds like.
You'll be sitting at home, you'll hear, "Meep! Meep!" "Fucking Festiva!
Where is it? Where is it?
It's got a spoiler. It's a '96."
What kind of sound does Rolls-Royce horn make?
I don't know either. No one knows.
Not even people who own a Rolls-Royce.
They're not even driving the thing.
They're sitting in back smoking weed, listening to Zeppelin.
That's what I would do if I had a Rolls-Royce.
The people who honk their horns in traffic are the people
who run out of object and it hits 'em.
They're just like, "I got a shitty car,
shitty job, shitty life.
Meep, Meep, motherfuckers! Meep, Meep!
Look At me! Look at me! Meep! Look at me!
I'm covered in Axe Body Spray.
I am listening to Nickelback. Shit
has taken a turn for the worse."
Nickelback.
Whoever thought there were a band come out
that made Creed look awesome?!?
See sir, there was this band called Creed and they came out
and they were like really whiny rock.
And um, everyone's like, "Get them outta here!"
Then they left and Nickelback showed up
and everyone was like, "Call Creed.""
Uh, someone needs to take me higher than Nickelback.
And Axe Body Spray. I've said it before, "Fucking stop it!
Stop it. All of you," because, girls, you're part to blame
'cause you're fucking these dudes.
You are! You are! 'cause if you weren't,
the shit wouldn't sell would it?
But it's selling like hotcakes.
And ladies, you deserve better.
You deserve better than some douche bag
that spent four bucks at Walgreens.
Axe Body Spray is proof positive that we
as Americans will buy whatever the fuck comes on television.
Okay? They've got us now. They know it.
You know what's coming out next? Poop in a Box!
That's what's next. You're gonna be watching tv.
There's gonna be a closeup of Poop in a Box.
Then they're gonna pull back
and there's gonna be a hot girl dancing
next to Poop in a Box.
And every single pop collared douche bag in the country
is gonna go, "Holy shit!
Maybe if I have Poop in a Box,
a pretty girl dance next to me."
But they're gonna run out and they're gonna jump in their
Scion and halfway
to Walgreens common sense is gonna kick in.
They're gonna go, "Wait a minute… I have a box."
Axe Body Spray is a regression as a society. Okay?
Every time someone uses it, we all take a step backwards.
Because I want you to think about it.
Up until this moment in human history,
even the shittiest colognes in the world did not come
in an aerosol can.
They didn't. They didn't. They didn't.
Old Spice, Aqua Velva, Hai Karate.
They all still had enough balls to have a spritzer.
And now, we've got the Aquanet of colognes…
And everyone knows somebody that uses it. You do.
Right before you walked in here tonight, they're like,
"I'm ready."
But no one had left the car yet.
So now all your friends smell like date rape.
I asked my friend why he did it. I go, "Why do you do that?
Why do you cover yourself in that shit?"
He said, "I don't wanna smell like pot and beer." "Why not?
You know, we've got pot and beer.
Let's advertise. because I'm gonna tell you something.
A girl does not like pot and beer…
She's not gonna like us at all."
So I'm single.
Shocker. What's with that? Mr.
Picky. Sucks being single and a guy.
It's fun for girls. It's nothing but free
drinks and attention. Yeah. For dudes, it's having a penis
and nowhere to put it,
Girls don't know what that's like.
They have a vagina. Yeah.
Walk the earth long enough, someone's gonna fuck you.
It's just a matter time
of you lowering your standards a little
bit.
If you got a penis, there's no guarantees anymore.
You gotta have something else to accentuate your penis.
Like a car or a
job. $40.
Something. You
know?
Penis needs an ad campaign like, Penis:
It's what's for dinner.
Have it your way. Is it in you?"
Because we're going up against a superior product.
You gotta look at it from a marketing standpoint.
The vagina's perfect. It's symmetrical.
It's like a little pocket. I'm gonna lick it.
I'm gonna put things in there. Like
my penis, or my tongue, or the title to my truck.
Only shit I care about. Only shit I
care.
I'd ask her first. You know,
can just can't go shoving shit up there.
They hate that. They
hate that.
That's rape in a lot of counties.
Who needs that on your record? You know what I'm saying?
Gotta start telling people when you move and shit.
I'm just gonna say, you gotta feel
like a douche on that day.
You know? "Hey, I touch a little girl. Sorry!"
Kind of like the day you buy a yellow Hummer, you know?
Yeah. I said it fucking, are you serious?
Are you, do you need a yellow hummer? Really? Really?
How small is your dick? Really?
That small? You're that small.
Really? I understand. Buy a Hummer.
I love rap music. I love it. Why a yellow one?
It's not even attractive.
It's like, "Hey, look! I'm driving the sun
and I got a small penis."
So this is all new to me, being single.
I dated a girl for three years and I learned some shit.
Like if you're gonna do that, she should like you.
Like as a person. This girl would yell at me
'cause she ran outta shit to do not like it was my fault.
We'd be going to bed. She'd be like, "Oh,
there's nothing on TV.
Let's fuck with you for a while." Like, "Oh, damn you Nick
at Nite!" I
woke up in the middle of an argument.
How does that happen ladies?!? Ever?
I've been asleep six hours.
"You listen to me, you cocksucker!"
I didn't know what the hell was going on.
I thought she was on her cell phone. I started laughing.
I was like, "Listen to this poor son of a bitch!"
It was me. So I
broke up with her, a lot.
'cause I'm an idiot. I did. I am. I'm like, "I'll call her."
I'll be like, "You're fucking crazy. Don't call me.
We're over. Bye!" She called me the next day, "I'm not crazy."
"Oh, my bad! See you in 20."
So I finally got away from it, right? Then
it took me like a year just to talk to women. I was scared.
I was scarred. That was more like it.
Women would come up to me after shows
and they'd be like, "Hey, how you doing?"
I'd be like, "I don't want to argue. Peace."
But I moved on and I started dating again
and I was terrible at it.
'cause everything had changed. The scene had changed.
You gotta go to a club now, which is retarded.
'cause clubs are dark and loud.
You end up walking out like, "Oh, shit! All right.
Sorry! Sorry. No, we're cool. We're cool.
We're gonna have to stop by a liquor store. But I'm cool."
Can't talk to 'em. Music's so loud.
It's like, "Hey, how are you?" "What?!?" "I said, 'What's your name?'"
"What?!" "You wanna fuck?" "What?!?" "Like here. I wanna do this… later."
This is what I want to do… later."
That's what you do in a club.
You just rub your dick on chicks until one sticks around.
"This is what I want to do. Rubby, rubby, rub, rub!"
Girls go! They fucking love it.
They're like, "I had eight dicks rubbed on me tonight!
This is my lucky outfit." (whip noise)
You know?
And apparently, if you want to date a girl now,
before you even talk to one,
you gotta call your cell phone company
and get a text messaging plan.
Holy shit ladies. What the fuck?
It's a phone. It's a phone. It's a fucking phone.
Press talk. How about it, huh?
If you want to talk, press the button
that says the shit that you wanna do.
I'm not anti-text message.
Me and my buddies text message each other all the time.
But it's a message. It's one line that needs no answer.
Shit like, "Meet me here," or "I'm running late,"
or, "That girl you're talking to is fucking nasty!" Shit like
that.
Don't look at me like that. 'cause girls do it too.
Doesn't matter what sex you are.
Doesn't even matter what your sexual orientation is.
If you've ever been hitting on somebody
and shit was going well
and then they looked at their phone, looked at you
and walked away, somebody has just reached out
and cockblocked you.
You know what cockblocking is, sir?
Don't Pick on me! No,
I'm just asking. I I, I'm not picking on you.
I'm just asking. You're not really in my
demo, you know what I'm saying?
I'm just making sure I'm crossing over.
If you don't know what cock-
blocking is, I'll explain it to you,
'cause it's a funny joke. You should not get it,
just 'cause you're unfamiliar with the verbiage.
Say, me and this guy right here, we're friends.
We're gonna go out for a night on the town,
try to score some tail.
'cause it's 1942 and people still talk like that.
So Jimmy and I hop out of the DeLorean
And uh,
mosey into the speakeasy.
Jimmy sees this girl here.
He goes, "I'm gonna go hit on that girl." I go, "Sweet!
I'm gonna go to the bar, check out the rest of the talent."
Awesome. I go to the bar, get my beer, turn around, realize
that Jimmy's hitting on the hottest chick in the place.
And I can't let that happen.
'cause I'm number one, he's number two.
That's just how it works. I gotta get Jimmy out of the way.
How do I do it? I go, "Hey, Jimmy! How's the herpes?
You flaring?" That's
how dudes do it.
Girls are a lot better at it.
You never see these bitches coming.
You'll have a friend post it up, right?
And she's totally into you.
She's like, "I'm gonna take you home.
I'm gonna suck on every inch of your body
and bring you to a level of ecstasy you've never achieved."
Awesome outta nowhere. Friend's like, "Hey, we're leaving!"
She's like, "See ya!" And they're gone.
What the fuck was that?
Did you see that? Some sort of cockblocking ninja.
She came out of nowhere.
The girls wanna conversate via the text message.
You ever gotten a text message from a girl?
Holy shit, nothing but questions. "Hey, how are you?
What are you doing? What are you doing later?
What are you thinking? Beepbopboopbopbeepbopbeep!"
"Uhh…
I'm fine. Kind of wishing you didn't have thumbs right now,
because then, maybe we could talk."
Because girls are so efficient with the phones.
You ever seen a girl with a 10 button phone?
She's like a goddamnn court stenographer.
Beepbopbopbop… How about Wednesday? You wanna go to the beach?" (typing sounds)
Every text message I send takes seven minutes.
F… seven…
I don't need a seven.
Meanwhile, she's freaking out.
"Why aren't you texting me back? You seen somebody else?
What's going on?" "No, I'm fucking retarded! Shut up!
Shut up!"
You end up calling her. "Gimme five minutes.
Just gimme five fucking minutes. Okay?
Hey, hey, I'm on the phone…
Just tell me what you were gonna type. Was it 'JK?'
Was it 'LOL?' Was it 'semi colon closed parenthesis?'
What the fuck was it? I'm not
as good at this as you are."
Because you don't know how unfair it is, ladies.
You don't know what it's like to talk to you.
You talk to each other. That's different 'cause you're women.
You got the pheromones and the estrogen
and the vaginas and whatever.
I don't even think you need to talk to each other.
I think you're doing it just to fuck with us,
to be honest with you. See?!? Look!
They're all looking at each other, aren't they?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm onto something!
You're gonna find me gagged out in a dumpster with tampons.
I, yeah, a woman mafia got me. That's what happened there.
I'm gonna be Hoffa in this bitch.
It's hard. It's hard to talk
to you ,'cause you're all unique.
You're all individual. You all have your own little shit
that makes you fucking crazy.
You do. You do. That's why your date's not laughing.
Yeah, because if it wasn't true, he'd laugh. He'd laugh.
He'd be, "This stuff's crazy. I don't know what he's talking about…"
But no, he is like, "Hey Fuckhead, it's Saturday.
Let's not cockblock. Okay, let's not bring up the crazy.
She's doing good." Because you do.
It's always something weird. It's always something crazy
like, "Don't say toast. I hate that word." Like, "What?!?"
"When I was younger I had a bad experience with toast
and I am just not comfortable enough with you
and I to tell you the toast story yet.
But if you could just do me a favor and,
and just say 'baked bread,' that'd be super."
We gotta figure this shit out. It's not just one thing.
It's not just a dozen things. It's a million things.
And they're always changing. We never figure 'em all out.
I know this 'cause my dad has been married to my mom
for 30 years, and that man can still talk to that woman face
to face, piss her off
and have no idea how the fuck it happened, at all.
Dad's still trying to learn.
You'll see him in another room like 20 minutes later
reworking the whole scenario, trying
to figure out where he fucked up.
"Dad, what happened?" "I don't know! I don't know.
I got home from the store, fuckin' all hell broke loose!"
"Didja get everything on the list?"
"I got everything on the list, man.
Apparently there was a list I was unaware of.
And it was in her face."
Dad was smart. Dad realized Mom was pissed
and got the fuck out.
'cause that's what you're supposed to do.
He walked home, he was like, "Honey, I'm home."
And she's like, "Hey." He's like, "Fucking see ya! Bye!"
Because my father knows what most older men know
that: when a woman's mad for the first 20 minutes,
doesn't matter why. It doesn't.
It doesn't! You just get away from it.
It's like right before a tsunami. You don't ask questions.
You just walk out to the beach. You're like, "Oh, shit!
All the water's gone. Fucking run.
Fucking run." Because you
don't wanna be the dude standing on the beach going, "Hey,
where'd all the water go?
Something's wrong. We need to figure this out.
We need to stick around here.
Figure out where all the water went.
Hey, is that a starfish? Oh, shit!"
You know, now you want us to text you
Kind of fucked, aren't we?
You know? 'cause there's no sarcasm, fa. That's a problem.
I'm trying to be funny
and T-Mobile makes me look like a dickhead.
"I meant like, 'No, I meant, "Your sister was a whore,"'
like 'wocka, wocka, wocka,' right? Nothing?
Alright. Nothing?
Alright." Are you guys drinking? Yeah.
Fuck Yeah. It's Saturday. We're in a mall. Fuck it.
Right?
Let's get shit-faced
and go break into Black House/White Market.
I don't know what I would get from there. Maybe some gifts.
Well drink up. Drive home real fast. It'll be sweet.
Uh, see if the Lord loves you,
That's funny, eh?
Do y'all go to church?
Some of you? Some of you like, "Fuck you, dude.
Trying to have fun here. There's
no 'G-O-D' in 'F-U-N.' Know what
I'm saying?"
I'm not saying that. But grammatically, if
that's correct, you know what I'm saying?
Grammatically means words.
Basically what I'm saying is there's not a 'G' or an 'O'
or a 'D' in the word,
'fun.'
I was raised Catholic. Any Catholics here? Yeah.
Surprise that many of 'em clapped.
Usually they don't wanna put their beers down.
Alright if I set this here? Go right ahead. Cool.
Don't spit it in or nothin'. Catholicism's great.
Especially if you do drink. 'cause uh, we have noon masses.
Yeah, that's the latest in the industry.
Some churches have a five o'clock,
'cause they have like a cokehead contingency or something.
I don't know. But it's like…
Because Catholics like to drink.
We love it. That's why Catholic masses are so boring.
A lot of people think we lack soul. That's incorrect.
We're just fucking hung over.
Because you go to a lot of churches,
they're having a blast, man.
They're like, "Yay, Jesus! Whee, tee, teetee, tee!"
Catholics, we're like, "Cut that shit off! Shut up!
Okay, I got a headache.
Let's just sit here and let this dude talk. Okay?"
It's not even the priest.
Priest doesn't do shit for the first 20 minutes.
He's as hung over as anybody else in here.
If you've never been to a Catholic mass,
it's about an hour long.
Sometimes you can get out in 45.
There's this variable in the middle called 'the homily,'
Where the priest can just talk about whatever he feels
is relevant.
And uh, sometimes he's really succinct
and gets to the point and gets out.
And you out there in 45 other days he goes fucking
Allman brothers on it.
You know what I'm saying? Takes him 20 minutes
to bring it back to 'Whipping
Post.'
First half an hour of any Catholic mass is,
like anybody else's church, where they talk
to you, they sing to you.
You know, (sings) "Touching yourself.
Jesus doesn't love you when you're touching yourself," right?
I'm paraphrasing, but that's the gist of it.
And uh, the second half an hour is like a
cooking show with Jesus.
'cause they take crackers and turn them
into the 'Body of Christ.'
Then they take a $4 bottle of wine
and turn it into the 'Blood of Christ.'
Yeah, super cool the first couple times, but two
or three years into it you're kind of like,
"Hey, Padre, what else can you make?
You know? Is there a lasagna or something?
Because I'd love a 'Cheesy Jesus.' That'd be delicious."
I quit going to church and it's not 'cause I got lazy.
It's 'cause one week I showed up
and no one at my church would drink the wine.
'cause the flu was going around.
Where's the faith? You know, if I had the flu,
I'd be bogarting the Blood of Christ.
You know what I mean? Like, "Fuck you, bitches! I got the flu."
Gluck, gluck, gluck, gluck.
"It's the Blood of Christ, according to all your stories.
It saved us from sin.
I think it's gonna do something for my sniffle."
I'm just saying if you're gonna go
to a building every Saturday or Sunday or Wednesday or
whenever the hell you go… you should believe
what these people are telling you.
Otherwise, what are you doing? Missing kickoff, basically.
And I don't care what religion you are, I don't care.
Just believe whatever you wanna believe, we're all wrong.
That's okay. Religions aren't there to be correct.
They're there to be there. They're there
to give you something to believe in.
So believe in it. That's why, of all the religions,
the people I respect the most are the people down in Texas
that dance around with rattlesnakes on their heads.
Those people are fucking crazy!
They believe! You got to.
You got a fucking rattlesnake on your head.
Dancing around with it, asking it questions.
"Lord Jesus, should I buy a Honda?" (snake biting head) "No!
No, I shouldn't. Oh, shit!
Shit!
Shit! Zeke? Come here. Shit! Zeke?
Go tell everybody. Jesus said, 'Buy American.'
That's what He said."
(Laughter and applause)
Don't let my death be in vain.
Gotta kind of hope that the rattlesnake people aren't right.
'cause that means there's rattlesnakes in heaven.
If there's snakes in heaven, you know what's in hell.
Llamas. Right?
Two Ls in hell, two Ls in llama.
I smoke pot.
I do it a lot. That's
what I was doing when I wrote the llama joke.
I thought it was brilliant. I was
like, "Who does a two 'L' joke?
Fucking nobody. I'm Lewis and Clark
in this bitch." They were pioneers.
Pot's my favorite drug. It's the only drug I do,
besides Xanax and mushrooms.
I love Xanax, man. That shit's like the reset button. It is.
If you're having a shitty day, take a Xanax.
Next thing you know, it's tomorrow.
"What the hell happened yesterday?" "Dunno! I don't know.
It was shitty to a point.
And then, apparently, I went to Taco Bell."
Which, by the way, don't get stoned and eat a Xanax.
Holy shit! That's an $18 run for the border.
You're a little too fucked up for choices.
You just kind of pull up to the drive-thru.
"I'll take the left side. No tomatoes. Thank you.
We will sort it out at the house.
I need to get this vehicle off the road, ASAP!"
Oh, cool. I've been dating again,
and uh, they, I got this thing.
I've been getting them, and then I put a stop to 'em.
I don't if you start doing it, I'd tell you, "No."
And I'm here to put a stop to 'em publicly.
And they're called 'handjobs.'
Yeah. Ladies, we don't need them.
We don't need 'em. I don't need 'em.
I don't wanna speak for everybody. Maybe you're into it.
I am not. Okay. I don't.
Ladies, if we hook up later, uh,
and you were gonna do that, rub my back.
You know? Gimme a back rub,
because, uh, I can't reach my back.
I can do that a lot better than you can. I might add, ladies.
Holy shit, fellas. You ever gotten a handjob?!? There's
15 minutes you'll never get back.
Just laying there, staring at each other.
"What's that, baby? What's that? No, no,
it doesn't usually take this long. No, it doesn't. You look tired."
I am just saying, ladies, if that's what you wanna do,
you're just kind of doing some shit
that we haven't gotten to today.
If that's what you wanna do, go iron my shirt.
I'm not trying to be mean. I'm not trying to be sexist.
I'd go iron my shirt while you're doing this, but I can't.
I gotta be here for this. So let me do this.
You go do… Let's be productive is what I'm saying.
That's a weird joke. 'cause not everyone can laugh at it.
And the people, the groups that can't, are very divided.
Like the younger kids can't laugh at it
'cause they'd settle for that.
They'd be like, 'Yeah, if she's touching it,
I'm not complaining at all!"
And older dudes are the same way.
They're like, "Hey, she hasn't seen it in three months.
So if she would just touch it, it'll probably go off."
Really, she doesn't even need to put a full wrap around it."
Are you ladies hearing this shit?
It's fucking hysterical
and you're just staring at me, and you're the only ones,
so I'm starting to think it's you guys.
Something happen today? Your dog die?
You gotta take a poop? That happens to me sometimes.
Has that ever…, Like you had to
poop but you had shit to do,
so you held it 'cause you're an adult, and then you pooped
and then you're like, "Fuck I've been
a dick for the last hour."
Yeah, call people. "Sorry! Sorry!
Yeah, I had to poop and I didn't know it.
Totally forgot about the fact that I had to poop."
Well I'm gonna get outta here.
We're gonna go get stoned and listen to The Black Crowes,
'cause they're my most favorite band in the world.
I dunno if you've heard of them.
Yeah, I just went and saw 'em again.
That's like 17 times the last two years.
Which kind of makes me a dork. But fuck you.
I lead the life. Anyway,
They were broken up for two years
so I didn't really get to see 'em.
So I tried to get to see 'em whenever I can and, um…
'cause for the two years they were broken up.
The only way we could watch 'em was to watch
their Behind the Music, which I have on tape. One weekend,
me and my buddies got really fucking shitfaced.
Like, strip club shitfaced.
You know that? When it finally sounds like a good idea,
That's when you've had too much. Like, "Strip club?"
"Fuck yeah, let's go!"
"Gimme your keys."
'cause sober,
I'm like, "Strip club. No. Fuck that. Let's go to the casino.
We might get it back."
I might get to fuck the dealer.
I bet she doesn't have a coke problem, either. You can laugh.
They're not here. This is their money night.
They're making money.
So one night we got really fucked up
and couldn't find the remote,
so we had to watch the commercials. It's an older tape.
It's got older commercials.
It's got that old OB commercial on
there. That one with the lady.
She walks outta the laboratory and up to the camera.
She's like, "Did you know
that the first tampon was developed by a man?"
What the hell is she asking me for?
Why would I know? I don't know.
Probably. You know, probably the first guy tired
of waking up in the middle of a crime scene.
What? What?
What? Don't look at me like you don't know
what the hell I'm talking about.
Yeah, you call it 'spotting.' Yeah. I got news for you ladies,
that's fucking leaking.
'Spotting' is what you do with a UFO.
That makes me the 'spotter.'
I'm the one waking up in the middle of the night.
I don't know what the hell's going on.
I wake up, I look over, I'm like,
"Oh, my god! You've been shot!
Why'd they shoot you there? Of all places?
Were they mad at me? Because that was my favorite place.
Why wouldn't they shoot you in the mouth or something?"
Like what? No. For efficiency, that's all.
If you're a hit man, your car gets asleep.
You don't go shooting her in the vadge.
That's mean… and unprofessional.
That is bad hit man etiquette.
You guys were cool, man. I did that joke last week,
this chick got pissedd.
She was angry. Stood up, started yelling shit out at me.
"Why would you shoot her in the mouth?" I don't know.
Maybe 'cause questions answer themselves.
Shout-out was funny, but she was drunk and didn't get it.
She kept coming at me.
"You don't go shooting her in the mouth.
Mouth can be just as good as a vagina." What?
I mean, I've had some great blowjobs,
but I have yet to walk by an open vagina.
I wished would shut the fuck
up! Kansas City.
You guys've been a lot of fun, man. Thank you so much for coming out.