drink
with will I coming at
you oo welcome to the fabulous dty dirt
zombie dad we're coming to you live in
Minneapolis we've got a great show lined
up for you our special guest tonight is
the comedian Dwight Y and our specialest
tonight is black and now the one the
only the man that really s speak
hey everybody Welcome down to the show
how's everybody doing
tonight ah it's good to be back um we I
don't know if you know this at home
right there you people at home we
haven't taped a new episode drink with
you in almost a year gasps I know we've
been doing other stuff big and important
things and this is our first episode
Reinventing it doing it a little bit
different from here on out basically
till the end of the year we're doing
live episodes here at Donnie Dirk zombie
d can you dig it I said can you dig it
dig it some more I was
drinking all right well that that dig it
kind of blew anyway though uh starting
September 7th we're going live every
other week till the end of the year
every other Tuesday but tonight we
decided let's do a test run so you're
watching live television done by
amateurs that are very
Rusty excitement huh but somebody who's
never Rusty when Round rousing Round of
Applause for our friend arhan tour Neil
you might not be able to see him in
camera three but he's clay oh right
there he is ladies and gentlemen
Neil I told you we were Rusty anyway um
but luckily and we were very lucky
because we took a long time off and we I
was very happy to bring everybody back
and that means not only do we have Neil
we have the bartender to the Stars Mr
Oli stench
everyone
doing awesome uh I'm a little rusty at
this
uh
yeah all right we'll we'll we'll fix
that in editing uh tonight's sh is
called the take
two oh yeah for for those of you who
don't know I'll pause and you guys
repeat the last word that I say before
the pause so tonight's sh is called to
take two two
now I feel at home here at Donnie Dirk's
zombie
Den in beautiful Minneapolis Minneapolis
so to make a take two two you take a
shot shot of UV grape gra a fine grape
flavored vodka
vodka you take a shot sh shot of
UV cherry cherry vodka your pauses are
Rusty too
you take two shots
shot of lemon lime flavored soda soda
you take a shot shot of margarita mix
mix add a little ice
ice shake it up shake it to the left
left shake it to the right right spill
some down your sleeve sleeve
you strain it
out and something will fix an
editing the take two shots on the
house now we have our lovely shot
professional walking through right now
um I know Dick's gonna come see no you
don't do it
yet we do it all
together sry we do it all together we do
it all together together together so
everybody gra my we do a everybody got
one throw it up in the air like you just
don't care
everybody and the people who did it
before should be able to do another one
because it's called the take two on
three everybody one two three
salute ah
delicious everybody enjoy that everybody
enjoy take to I'm glad to hear now um as
I said ear we looked at tonight as a bit
of a test run we're just kind of seeing
what happens making sure we could all do
it in preparation for September 7th but
the one thing I didn't want to have
happen is this be some crappy test run
where we do it it doesn't get recorded
nobody gives a damn so I said screw it
we want real guests and real bands to be
part of this if it all falls apart and I
cannot be more thrilled to have our our
guest tonight we've wanted him on the
show for a while thank God his schedule
is cleared up local comedian
extraordinaire Dwight York
with a big ass beer look at that damn
beer that's going to suck up all the
shot that's look looks great I feel like
a guinea
pig is yeah well good because we're
testing on you right now exactly yeah um
so yeah microphone we just talk and uh
Dwight York um obviously no stranger to
you um if you've seen where which camera
I'm that camera right now uh we has a
new CD in stores right now called
quickies it's on standup records these
are the same people of course who put
out our DVDs tring with in season 2 in
stores now people keep asking me when's
season 3 coming out when you buy season
two that's when it's going to happen so
uh Jo give me some background where are
you from well I grew up in a small town
of Wisconsin I call the twin City's my
comedy Hometown I worked in a factory
until 1997 quit my day job been on the
road since then lived in my car for
seven years jeez so when did you start I
started doing stand up in 1989 little
Mexican restaurant South Minneapolis
Papito Sunday night now Pito used to be
a big part of the the comedy Hub not so
much anymore they're trying to make a
resurgent Tuesday night but uh it was
the open mic back in the day Sunday
night there was some great Comics I met
Tom Arnold there back in the day but
yeah wow because everybody wow coked out
perhaps it was before he was famous okay
so yes um now I noticed a lot of a lot
of comedians have little plaques there
did you were you lucky enough to get one
of the plaques no screw them yeah screw
Theos yeah don't go there horrible food
infested with
rice I had never even seen the pla I
didn't know about this you've ruined my
entire evening I am sorry well anyway
let's get back to your childhood you're
from Wisconsin a scan here you a Green
Bay fan I am a proud cheese head I am
Packer fan long time been to Lambo field
love the Green Bay Packers yeah now see
since uh this is live we can talk about
this see you can see my hand on
television right now I squish your head
I squish your
head hello in the control Booth how you
doing um but so and because we're timely
now cuz we're live um how what do you
think about this whole Favre thing today
uh that's how you say it right Favre you
know what I have been on this roller
coaster ride myself yeah so I know what
you're going through and I am kind of
excited to see him back because I want
the Packers to beat him this year so
they they didn't come back they he would
have beat them twice and um it would
have been him to us
yeah okay well and everybody freaks out
cu it's like oh you know he he does this
every year and we never know if he's
going to come back but he he comes back
every year so what damn difference does
it make he's like the Freddy K Krueger
of quarterbacks so we're all dreaming
right now and it's a dream and it's
coming reality um that was a horrible
trans transition that's going nowhere
what's going to come to this um so what
are your thoughts because you you look
you know when when jerks talk about the
comedy scene there's obviously you got
your New York and your La that's how it
was in the 70s how do you think uh being
a Midwest comic has worked to your
advantage at disadvantage and how has
that kind of informed what you
do uh good question I guess out wrot
that one down right
here New York and La uh I think there's
a little bit more pressure a little bit
more competition I think uh artists
comedians have a little bit more room to
be creative and grow and be their
individual self there's great audiences
out here which means you can do smart
comedy I think you can develop a smarter
act here here and um I think it's a good
place to become a comedian and I think
it's one of the best comedy towns in the
country right now as it was when I
started are we talking about Minneapolis
Minnesota Minneapolis Minnesota comedy
Town USA am I
right now and it says so right there in
your bio that you're a bit of an
unconventional comic which means that
you will play places other comedians
dare tread is that right uh coming up
next week I'm doing a tattoo convention
huh which is quite a proud
accomplishment the promoter thought I'd
be perfect for uh his clientele and the
people who were coming out to that which
is like I said an accomplishment for a
45-year-old white dude with no holes or
metal or ink grilled into his body yeah
yeah wow so now what what do you think
about it is about your comedy that makes
them go well hot damn let's have you
in well perhaps it's my
look and you know besides the you know I
kind of mentioned the tattoo convention
but the bigger deal and maybe why I got
the tattoo convention is uh just
yesterday I came back from Sturgis South
Dakota where I was performing for all
nine days of the Sturgis Motorcycle
Rally at the legendary Buffalo Chip
Campground Alie Osborne was there wow no
kidding look at that so sturis huh cuz
now I sturis I'm not going to lie to you
it scares of B Jesus out of me should I
be I've heard something about a a a
pickle that gets licked what happens
here here you know last year uh I was my
idea to go out there I uh pitched my
idea to the owner he said come on out
try to find an audience and it was tough
to find an audience so one of the places
I found an audience was following a
pickle licking contest and and what and
what is this pickle licking contest well
I think you can guess the rules okay uh
you got a look a pickle different ladies
did their best job at um getting the
audience to imagine that they were
putting the something else besides a
pickle in their mouth and making the
recipient of whoever that pickle was
attached to
happy I find that that cheapens pickles
you know what I don't think it does much
for pickles either and as far as comedy
it really cheap in the comedy too yeah
and yeah because how do you go over I
mean how do you follow a pickle licking
contest you know let's just say that it
didn't attract the classiest of
competitors on two different occasions I
watched in great Fascination as one of
the contestants made a great show of
first removing her
teeth In fairness you don't want your
pickle
scraped nobody forgets a pickle scraping
uh I'm not saying it's bad for pickle
licking but it's not easy for comedy
following but but you found to this
because how many have you have you done
this in previous years uh this is my
second year and this year the uh owner
of the Buffalo Chip you know he asked me
how it went I said it's tough to do
comedy outside for a skeptical audience
I took a pickle you know I took a
grubbin from the pickle and judges a
couple of times and this year he moved
me indoors to uh the new Buffalo Chip
Comedy Club okay and I had shows uh
inside it was a small place but uh the
audience is receptive I did well and uh
I'm invited back for next year well hell
yeah Round of Applause for Dwight
everybody still going back to sturis now
have you are you do are you a motorcycle
fan have you been on a motorcycle before
uh you know what I owned a uh 66 fully
chopped Sports that I never got running
when I was 19 years old and I've never
owned a motorcycle since but bikers have
always kind of liked what I do I like to
say that I have biker friendly jokes
okay so I could give you an example
please do do we want an example fine
people here today biker friendly joke
not a joke about bikers but one that
they might like uh this one's good for
TV too I know I've gotten older my
sensibilities have changed like when I
was younger it was like I had to get
drunk in order to have a good time
now I don't have to have a good
time now because you are really like a
like a current King of the oneliner like
you you are quick in and out and a lot
of uh of comedians today are more story
based and do you think that's found a
good Niche for you you know for the bike
rally it's quick because these guys got
no
attention they're like skeptical say
something funny and I go like uh just
watch my first porno movie can't believe
much younger I look back
there so I do real quick back and it's
almost like they're almost like
challenging me it's like extreme comedy
and by the way I've got more edgy ones
for the motorcycle rally but we're on TV
here come on yeah no no no and this is
good so now and how many dates do you do
in a year because you're a bit of a road
dog aren't you well you know what for
seven years Road dog is what we call a
comedian who works a
lot if in case you couldn't figure that
out which means that you're kind of
stupid I don't think I'm hacking this
joke because we we use it so much in
comics but you know what you call a um
uh comic without a girlfriend what
homeless yeah so uh I was on the road
without a girlfriend for uh seven years
I lived out of my car and uh when they
you know when you work they put you up
so the idea was to take any gig any hell
gig anywhere just so they get you a
place to live and get out there and uh
you know work on your act so you no I
mean you literally like you had you were
homeless living from date to date well
you know I stayed in hotels well yeah
but but I mean but you had no no place
to hang the hat my stuff was in storage
and I lived out of my car wow seven
years man and so and did you have any
advice to Young comedians cuz I mean or
is it just don't do it or you're going
to live in your car uh get a nice
sleeping bag and a decent
pillow but now not only are you a road
dog you have yet again a where which
camera we at right there we have
quickies on standup records right here
uh beautifully designed by me cuz I work
for standup records too uh a little
known fact uh but it's a great damn
thing and and you're a published author
now tell me a little bit about your book
uh that's I published the uh book myself
back in 2000 it's the name of the book
is called the vile file yeah which
there's no all right you just it just
looks dark on camera subtitle jokes too
sick for the stage they can go online
and look at it amazon.com it's on all
the big Outlets like my website and that
yeah what's your website let's give you
a plug real quick dght york.com Dwight
york.com he opened for Tesla once and we
didn't even get a chance to ask him
about it probably for the best but yeah
go pick up quickies go buy up uh the
vile file jokes too sick for the stage
ladies and gentlemen Dwight
York thank you sir now we have somebody
here um who's an old friend of the show
he's no he needs no introduction but I'm
giving him one anyway so everybody knows
when to clap ladies and gentlemen the
camera's already on them but now oh
there it is ladies and gentlemen hiu
Jim hey thanks everybody thank you so
much uh I am Haiku Jim I do have a Haiku
poem for you this fine evening and it's
a what I would consider a smart hiu uh
for the audience um you know it's
summertime and and I've noticed that one
of the
worst products out there is that uh tan
it's a it's a tan in a in a can Okay a
spray tan sounds horrible and I've seen
women with you know these horrible
orange faces and then wait a minute I
can see your neck that's still white and
it's just not it's a horrible thing porn
starhead is what they call it I've got a
smart I've got a smart Hau for the spray
Tanner out there okay lady spray Tanners
do yourself a big favor Google Al
Jolson ladies and gentlemen the one the
only Haiku
Jim now not only is haiku Jim here today
it is a little known fact that it is his
birthday
everybody 28 years
young all right everybody join me in
this one but do we have to pay rights if
we sing happy birthday it's still under
copyright oh well never mind Jim blow
out your candle I didn't think anybody
loved me I really do appreciate it no
everybody happy birthday to
Jim a hell of a guy and a huge asset
here at drinking with
Ian but a f a further few huge asset
that we're about to have we have a
musical guest tonight hot damn you're
saying to yourself we get music too yes
we do they have a new album or actually
I believe this is an EP it's on guilt
ridden Pop I believe it is available in
stores if not go to your stores and go
what the hell I want to get this clap
sound ladies and gentlemen since Donnie
Dirk's a beautiful room but s yeah yeah
okay yes clap for that um sadly it's a
bit tiny so as you watch this over the
next couple months you're GNA see that
you're going to see that we uh we we
come up with fun and exciting places to
put the band right now all the way from
the smoking patio everybody
claps and you can watch him on the
screen thanks
see
they I understand the feeling of being
alone and then you came and took me
away you are my
love this was my love
I'm R away
seeing myself nothing else I see you in
the bra I feel the same te that annoing
in you were my long
lost this was my love
aome G
away you are my long l
this was my long
lost G
away you
my this
my you
my you my long
lost this was my long
lost away
you were my long
lost this was my long
lost gone
away everybody
claps thank
you they have a new slightly moist CD in
stores right now it's
called no party now that seems like kind
of a downer title it's just a lonely
chair sitting there what was your uh
what was your inspiration for the oh and
you have a gab Beast remix gab Beast
also been on our show great band um what
was your inspiration for calling it no
party and actually let's introduce the
band too while we're doing this can you
build them into the story for sure uh
Patrick I'm vocals jud's on syn s's on
syn as
well oh no no party yeah but anyway what
is it called no party um it was just the
title that we came up with it was
something that for some reason fit it
good reason just because that's why dude
cuz we felt like it everybody want to
hear one more song from claps hell yeah
you do ladies and gentlemen here in a
parking lot in North Minneapolis a place
that people used to get stabbed at all
the time everybody
claps we enter the room
and live so
often but nothing ever
changes your tongue is so forign to
me the love you give a
commod you PR
everything just
leaves all your friends
just the last
resr
reality for others all they me
get out get out
you I get out I get out
you broken hold it on the bathroom floor
it's not
that is it
anymore what have I done
oh what have I
done God forgive
me get out get
out get out get out
never get
out get
out get out
I get out I get out
you
out get out
you're to
you'll save money and time you'll get
the best of merchandise and service when
you patronize these good
neighbors drinking with Ian is proud to
be sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV
Vodka no matter if it's UV blue
raspberry UV red cherry UV green apple
UV Ivory vanilla or UV orange vodka UV
flavored vodka offer a premium product
without the high price tag please visit
UV vodka.com for additional information
and recipes no beer in the midwest has a
grander tradition than Grain Belt for
over 100 years Grain Belt has been the
beer that fathers have passed on to sons
and friends have passed amongst each
other at local bars and watering holes
it is a beer with tradition that spans
Generations which is why it has become
legendary both here and across the
country next time you go out ask for a
premium EMI Audio the twin City's
Premier resource for DJs bands and
drinking with Ian rentals sales
installation and repair of DJ gear PA
systems and effect lighting a
family-owned business for over 35 years
visit emia audio.com for all your audio
video and lighting
needs a portion of drinking with Ian is
sponsored by The Onion America's Finest
news source and the AV club bringing you
reviews and commentary on the Arts and
entertainment scene available at news
stands throughout the Twin Cities and
online at theonion.com and avclub.com
Pizza luche proudly supports drinking
with Ian free delivery until 2:30 a.m.
weekdays and 3:30 a.m. weekends download
our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with Ian is nothing
without our sponsors please support
them sit ubo sit good dog