I like being a dad I like doing dad
things you know I love that they're in
my life I love it
okay it's okay you you can laugh all you
want just don't that's why we're here
that's right just not everybody has to
add commentary to the laughter too it's
just you just chill out we all good we
good
okay all right
it's
okay I I love I love silence I
[Music]
um you know what I see the thing is I do
love I love being a dad but what I can't
stand are the new parents the new
parents that are so in love do you know
what I'm talking about those people that
are just
[Music]
like I did not
know that my heart
[Laughter]
I didn't know it my heart could feel so
much I didn't know that there was a
hole in my soul until these
Angels Came to fill it
I can you even imagine what your life
was like before these
angels she like yeah I I
so so so oh
[ __ ] so oh [ __ ] are you all
right are you okay okay okay okay I was
expecting that from somewhere
else are you all right
okay
okay okay
see see see would you just sit both of
you
ladies do you see what just happened
here that's how you know I've been
married a long time because newly W
Aaron would have been like what the [ __ ]
is wrong with
here couple years in oh my God are you
all right
that was the funniest [ __ ] I have ever
seen But
privately I'm a decent human
being on the
outside we're going to have to add like
a little audio commentary to the CD at
this point a very nice lady tripped and
bit [ __ ]
in the middle of the
show I hope you guys are having a good
time cuz I'm [ __ ] miserable up
here so funny