strangers get in your business even
before you have kids right if you're
married long enough without kids people
like so when you going to get trying
when you going to when you it's like
what what business is it of yours chill
out you know what I mean you have one
kid that's not enough for people so
when's baby number two coming it's like
I don't know if baby number one's even
sticking around slow it
down he's kind of kicking our ass this
is hard this is hard
you know what I mean you have two of one
gender so you're going to try again for
that girl [ __ ]
you slow
down couple summers ago hot hot summer
right my wife my boy my and we were
grocery shopping just the three of us
we're grocery shopping the guy who
bagged our groceries walking us out he's
trying to make chitchat so is this your
only kid like
what why do you care grocery store guy
what business is it of yours what are
you going to do with that information
for the next two like what kind of
dumbass question is that anyway no as a
matter of fact he's not actually we got
five others locked up in the hot
car windows all the way
up this one pissed me off the least
today so he
uh so he won some fresh air as a
prize now we ought to get going right
tick tick tick
[Music]
so funny