this could be the commercial that does
it all you
know this could be uh it's could be big
for us if we get a a lot of
viewers so I want to look good and I
want my wife to look good and that's
it's not that much of a
challenge but i' I'd really like uh I
think it'll go well I think Glenn's a
good director we seeing some of his
other work and uh and like I said my
wife is she's a really great actress and
so you had a chance to look over the
copy then yeah yeah I've got
inflatable come to doua party rental for
the inflatable party
ah oh God hang
on second 1 second hold on hey Vince hey
Mike okay you're helping out on set yeah
we're just we're just getting ready okay
so um we'll see youall there in a couple
minutes okay hey h my dressing room
you're going to make me bird myself I
don't want to
sorry what's going on
okay honey
okay I love you I all right um I need to
focus okay I need to focus for the
shoot ready to
go yeah oh yeah I'm all set okay cool uh
what's Spence here for
Oh I thought that it was a three person
so I was just assuming that I mean
Claudia is the one who contacted you but
I was is he like a model that you guys
brought in or is Vince no God no oh okay
he's our salesman he's a top salesman
he's great but I think Claudia said it
was going to be just us two and I think
that Dynamic works a lot better hold on
put your one second put your shirt 1
second why is it locked hold on
okay honey let me go what sorry all
right okay okay great you guys oh wow
that's great
okay okay so we're just GNA start off
body if you could just hold still okay
just perfect lock that pose it's
beautiful it's beautiful we want to go
right up the front here goes up like
that let's see here how's that guys
I do is save you money how's that all
right is the actress in the family we
don't have a
family honey look like Vin's got a
Shiner see look at me she's a good
actress
so okay yeah
um well how much time I think I think
right now it would' be great well Vince
and I just need a couple minutes yet
okay Vince you look ready maybe you
could just
don't you just come on
out go but don't just take my word for
it ask my beautiful wife Claudia we're
scaring down prices bringing savings
back from the dead to make your house
the spookiest on the Block Mike what are
you
doing you're supposed to be on your Mark
it's just it's kind of throwing it it's
like it gets a little
on just stay on MAR it's not that
difficult but we want to save you
money sure all right we'll work thaty
that my chance
hey need to W here change out of
wardrobe all kind I think um yeah we
want to how did we do that was that was
all right that was it was a little bumpy
but I mean I think it's okay mix it up
what do you mean um you have a mic on
don't you yeah let's he's just the sales
person though he's that's great highest
seller on the floor that we have try it
come here just for fun maybe just for
fun and then we can show it at the
office do for fun fine fine just for fun
this is going to be funny okay shut up 3
2 1 go we're scaring down prices
bringing savings back from the dead to
make your house the spookiest on the
block that's great I think I think we
got that yeah okay oh I mean we can do
if you
yeah it's not that good what do you
think Draculas and Frankenstein God it's
great okay I think we got that covered
so let's go on to that line and then
we'll do the list and Frankenstein plus
everything you need for your partal
event o I dropped
something what are you doing Mike it
fell is there a part that does he have
another line no you can just go home
honey
everything else you need for your
party fing chairs for parties and
castles you [ __ ] my wife
[ __ ] what are you talking about you're
[ __ ] my wife we are in the middle of
a shoot and this is expensive and you
are ruining my big moment clly I love
you can you at least give me
this please Mike go one more chance go
please do you remember when you came in
for party tables party tables spin
wheels calm down oops look at how big my
dick is let go let go I'll take let go
I'm
not he's [ __ ] my wife get it together
right now don't hurt got to get it
together don't hurt him don't hurt me V
don't hurt me V just walk in the shopit
this might be a good time we just finish
it up hey bals party rocks he goes save
you and then you go money got it got it
I did a movie like this once nice I'd
love to see that she's an actress it was
like I had to stay in a position similar
to this for probably let me give you my
number 30 minutes action hi I'm Mike ERS
and we're here to save you money money
that was really good here and then after
I say uh I'll say it's Halloween and
we're slashing prices uhhuh but don't
take my word for it ask my lovely wife
Claudia but it's your okay that's so
close okay it's Halloween blowout sale
too remember that is your Halloween
blowout sale uhhuh blow blow with your
hands blow it out blowout sale blowout
sale blowout sale that's right and what
are you doing to prices you're scaring
you're scaring them you're scaring them
down right slashing is good too I like
slashing slashing but then if you're
going
to slash them right should I do an R
move yeah why not right okay
okay and it's Halloween so that means
that we're slashing
prices h hallowen so low that they're
scary let's go back to scaring down
places