my oldest man he's in fourth grade he's
got real homework he's got real homework
now which is scary right cuz up until
last year it's all been arts and crafts
all arts and and he brought it all home
all of it all of it and it was junking
up our house and I want to throw some of
it away and my wife's like well we have
to save all of it what are we going to
look at later to remember these special
times I'm like how about photos of us in
a nice clean house cuz this is [ __ ]
this is I
can't we don't need all of it like even
the best museums curate right they take
cuz he would bring it all home all of it
there was like popsicle stick art and
snowmen made out of cotton balls it's
cute for a little bit and like 20
pictures a day so much construction
paper with pictures of dragons and
Batman and like ridiculously inaccurate
portraits of his family it's not all
good it's
not and it's not the art so much that
got me it was the crafts it was the
crafts that got me cuz he's not a good
gluer he want a good gluer so shit's
falling off all the time all over my
house it's not enough that it's piling
up there's pieces of it everywhere
go just googly eyes in every corner like
what the I thought I scared an ant you
know what I mean like it's everywhere
pom pom balls all over that look glitter
glitter glitter everywhere glitter all
over the tables glit glitter all over
the like look if I'm not allowed to come
home covered in
glitter it's so funny