we go on vacations now I can I can take
my family on vacations now I couldn't we
didn't go on fancy vacations when I was
growing up you know uh and the thing is
it's great like we took my family to the
water park last summer water park
nothing makes me feel worse about my
body than getting ready to go to the
water park and nothing makes me feel
better about my body than actually going
to the water park you I'm looking around
like I'm kind of chubby kind of hairy
but damn dude look at you that's
you win that is
awesome I'm practically a model
here saved up some money took my family
to Disney World which is an awesome
vacation right it's a magical place you
let your imagination run wild whatever
you want to be the whole time you're
there you get to be you want to pretend
that you are an astronaut you get to be
an astronaut you want to pretend that
you're a pirate you get to be a pirate
you know you want to pretend that you're
a happy Pati well adjusted
family you get to be a pirate it's
awesome but we didn't take vacations
like that when we were kids you know
like my dad was working all the time he
saved up whatever money he could we'd go
away for like a little vacation a little
weekend or something like that nothing
fancy and I drove through one of those
places coincidentally a while back and
it brought back some memories and I
decided to text my dad cuz I I'm older
now I'm more emotional you know and I
texted him like oh Dad just drove
through the fs and it was reminded me of
all those times he took us on trips when
we were kids and I don't know if I fully
appreciated them but I get it now and I
just wanted to take the time to say
thank you and I love you and he texted
back who's this and I was
like sorry new phone you know what I
mean that kind
of it's Aaron your oldest then he just
goes okay and that was it that was the
whole message
it's so funny