[Applause]
[Music]
someone once told me a story about a
famous comedian who was informed on his
hospital bed he was dying said dying is
easy comedy is hard that's me and I
don't know how all this happened you
have called from this
Light release him from all his
sins bless him with eternal light and
peace raise him up to live forever with
all your Saints in the glory of the
Resurrection we ask this for our friend
and Jimmy
schart please be
seated I thought this was for Carrot Top
Carrot
[Music]
Top oh Jimmy you made love to me the
best better than
Tommy better than Johnny even better
than
Jamal
well maybe not
Jamal believe this [ __ ] still is me
bucks I got a better chance getting it
now
[Music]
huh here you're probably going to need a
shoulder to cry on
though we
Jimmy Two Shoes my miss your Irish [ __ ]
he always made me laugh you know that oh
I got something for you super OG y take
wa for that to
go what are you doing he going to his
pockets he owes me a 20 from the Eagle
game it didn't cover no that's one I'm
going to his
pockets it looks terrible
would you expect he hasn't had a drink
in 3
days 3
days we get for the watch on this beats
two to five get out of
here R the parking
[Music]
lot you always made me laugh you silly
son of a
[Music]
[ __ ]
except on the Friday late
shows God spe Jimny got you
[Music]
be thanks sh what's up man how you going
buddy listen I was just thinking
remember the last time we went out we
got hammered and you finger bang the
Rosenberg twins at the same
time you are my hero that
[Music]
day oh Bo listen buddy listen when you
get to heav please put in a good word
for me all right cuz I'm going to need
it things are just not that great right
now and they never have been
I'll tell you what man I'm going to miss
you more than anything even more than my
S Le he's finally quiet it's coming from
a guy who's going to write a book called
Jimmy Schubert the world and how it
revolves around me you want to hear my
Jimmy impression no hey you know every
time I go to fridge I open the door
light comes on I do 15 minutes
SMY did you hear me say
no this ought to keep him
cold take can get to heaven or wherever
it is you're
going P yourself
together
[Music]
so he's in the hotel room and he's
snapping his radish and the maid walks
in second day in a row he snaps he
stands up naked grabs a do not disturb
sign goes down to the lobby throws it at
the front desk chick and says this one's
broken I need
[Laughter]
another hey remember the time that uh
shuy drove Sam kenon off the stage on
his motorcycle a that was a classic tell
me about it bro I was there really well
no but I was supposed to be hey Gary
remember the time you [ __ ] your
sister yeah H I'm sorry I shouldn't have
said that's all right I just didn't need
to see the
pictures anyway toast the shoe let's do
toast youie Dooby May the wind be at
your back may the sun always warm your
face and may you be in heaven a half
hour before you do one
[Music]
stage let's have another one good
idea you know Jimmy was a magician right
let's not bring that
[Music]
up Gary oh no Gary why Gary why Gary
he's in a better place oh no I know
we're out of beer you [ __ ] me hey look
Jimmy would want us to keep his going
away party going Joey you got any more
weed [ __ ] sucks God really any liquor no
it was gone before the beer where the
hell are we going to get a beer at 3:00
a.m. on a
Sunday this is creeping me the [ __ ] out
we're going to hell you no no no no we
got a confession we're good Jimmy would
want this by the way I got dibs on a bit
about this I already got a bit on this
why you don't pay dirt Pay Dirt that's
my punch sign
[ __ ] did you guys hear
[Music]
something
open it up going to open it's not my bit
come on you could have the bit open it
this is creepy I don't even want to be
here come on you're stronger than me
open it no I'm not strong at all I got a
bad dish I don't want no you know what
you I'll open it all right I'm
thirsty I just hope this still
[Music]
cold
T what someone going to die around here
to get a little
attention that's your fault you wanted
to steal his Ros I told you he a
magician I told you not to bring
that never going to tou
again guys was a joke can anybody take a
joke David blae does it everybody goes
nuts I I got a show to do I need to ride
guys looks like I'm muffing
I'm going
to if I'm going
to thank you very much ladies and
gentlemen how are you guys doing all
right
wow man it's good to be here I actually
almost didn't make this gig uh yeah
earlier in the week I was in the
hospital all day not for me this girl
I'm seeing she was doing some modeling
work she was doing a photo shoot and she
got her ankle bracelet caught in her
earring and she fell off a pool
table she's going to be fine she's a
professional so doing a lot of travel a
lot of flying I hate flying I hate
flying like Nigerians hate spam filters
you know what I'm saying they've made it
so convenient you got to get there days
before your plane leaves and camp out at
the airport I don't feel any safer when
I travel I just have to run this
Gauntlet of [ __ ] retards before I can
actually get on the plane now the
TSA what does that stand for take
scissors
away I mean you know the Royal federal
government employees right there that
alone should make you feel about as safe
as a Geral in the front window of a San
Francisco Pet
Shop no let me tell you what happened
let me tell you what happened I'm
getting ready to get on the plane they
pull me and a 70-year-old lady out a
line I'm going ah this must be some of
that racial profiling I've been hearing
so much about you know get the white guy
and the chick with the Walker I think
they're a team you know meanwhile Ahmed
and Mohammad are kind of skipping down
the gang pank you know full headgear
with a couple of camels that seemed to
be okay nobody's batting and eye at that
in the meantime Me and Mrs doubt fire or
spread eagle against the back
wall the guy's rubbing his magnetic wand
in her crotch areas they ripping off
Granny's Orthopedic walking boot making
sure it wasn't filled with
C4 guy's rifle in my carry on he comes
across my nail clip goes sir you're not
going to be able to board the aircraft
with a nail
clipper got to be pretty good to hijack
a plane with a [ __ ] nail
clipper hey you get on the plane you
kick open the cockpit and wrestle the
pilot shoe off all right you take me to
LAX or I'm going to trim your toenails
really short so it hurts when you
walk I'll clip that little pinky toe
till it bleeds [ __ ] you're not messing
around you ever blood to duck through
your pinky toe it's painful
[ __ ] now get this Blain airborne it's
bad pedicures for
everybody Women and Children First I got
a nail
clipper you mental [ __ ] really why
didn't you go gang tackle the 5-year-old
in the SpongeBob SquarePants backpack
one more time cuz his win tooo hair gel
was 2 oz over the legal limit that'll
that'll that'll make us all feel safer
about
flying
look hey I don't know a lot about
airport security I'm not going to
pretend like I do and I'm not saying
everybody from the Middle East is a
terrorist I'm not saying that but I've
been watching the
news and it occurred to me that an awful
lot of these terrorists seem to be
coming from the Middle
East you might want to shift your focus
in that direction a little bit you know
just a
smidge I mean I know some people call
that racial
profiling you know what I call it good
police
work hey if I'm trying to catch the head
of the mafia I'm not going to go out
around the border of guys from
Zimbabwe okay Tut two what do you know
about Tony do no and his dealings with
the JVC crime
family
[Applause]
he's not talking
Chief this is going to be a tough
investigation we may have to play good
head hunter bad head hunter with this
guy and get him to talk then you know
well I I love that everybody's got to
take off their shoes when they fly you
know one guy got on a plane with an
exploding shoe and their solution was
okay that's it now he all have to take
off your
shoes cuz of one
[ __ ]
and
well hey and according to his attorney
he didn't even mean to do it he was just
wearing his exploding loafers that day
and forgot he was flying your honor that
could happen to
anybody I'm going are you [ __ ] me
how do you not see the guy with the shoe
bomb coming a mile
[Laughter]
[Applause]
away and I love you
know you know I love it when the the the
security lines are real long and you're
trying to catch your flight and and
they're making the women take off the
shoes that kills me uh ma'am take off
your heels run through the X-ray machine
I'm standing going yeah like any woman's
going to blow up a perfectly good pair
of
shoes not in this country you know
she's she's wearing a $200 pair of dolci
gab's [ __ ] she's not blowing him up
pick it up I got a plane to catch you
know I mean one guy does it we all get
punished is that how you're running the
operation what happens if one of these
fanatical lunatics manages to smuggle a
stick s a dynamite up in his raising
hole and they catch that
guy what the hell do that mean for the
rest of us
huh I already got my shoes underneath my
arm and a driver's license out I get a
showy 3 feet yeah it's me uh it's still
me uh you're not going to believe it
guess me again hey what do you need a
stool sample a bowling truck I'm telling
you it's me for the ninth time and you
go to get on the plane but you got to go
through that tunnel oh no one more
checkpoint guy's got a big vat of KY
Jelly and a rubber Glover you got to
show your driver's license one more time
and then drop TR while the guy puts his
fingers in your mud cutter all
right as your ass been in your control
the whole
time yes my ass has been in my control
the
time has anyone else packed your ass
nobody's packed my ass you weirdo I'm
just trying to fly home to see my family
for the holiday you sick son of a [ __ ]
you get on the plane you make your way
to your seat and you sit down with that
KY gushy fing in your ass while you fly
to Denver for 3
[Laughter]
hours and next time I'm taking a train I
tell you
that I mean next time I'm going
Greyhound if it means some guy's not
going to throw his knuckle in my dirt
button looking for high explosives for
God's
sake listen people and you go ahead and
laugh you think it's funny pretty soon
we're all going to be standing there and
flipflops and a thong going I got
nothing I got
nothing listen
hey
I'm a comedian I love my job comes in
handy lots of
times not the
airport oh they got big signs everywhere
just no
joking he good thing you're protecting
us from
comedians when somebody trying to blow
something up with a whoopy
cushion I actually think that's the
perfect screening procedure I think you
should have to tell a joke to get on a
compl how many yeah
well I'm just saying how many funny
terrorists you
know did you hear the one about killing
the infidels in the name of Allah all
right you son of a [ __ ] the play that's
like
funny I mean you know you're so
concerned with security why you get
serious and quit [ __ ] footing around
we're Americans we got [ __ ] to do people
I think if you have an American passport
and an above room temperature IQ I think
the airline should give you a gun as
you're getting on an airplane you know
here's a gun for you and and there's a
gun for you you don't get
one get in there
[ __ ] and that way when Ahad stands up
with his box Cut goes mag the plan there
we go I don't think so but
lick sit down and wash Shrek and eat
your
peanuts is this son of a [ __ ] is going
to Philadelphia just like the ticket
says and you stewardess leave the whole
can of
soda the whole damn can lady put it on a
tray you cheap [ __ ] what did they got
one can of soda on an airplane they run
in the back they pull that curtain Shut
they crack it open they take a cotton
ball they dip it into the can they
squeeze it into a glass they dip and
they squeeze oh I bet you get 27 glasses
out of this one can guess who employee
of the month's going to be next month
you know and meanwhile you're in this
pressurized tube at 39,000 ft getting
the moisture sucked out of your head cuz
of the pressure on that
tube sure could use a little
refreshment is all this for
me oh thank you I was so thirsty you
know I what want to just walk down the
aisle with an eye dropper next time you
know hey tilt your head back swallow
tilt your head back swallow tilt your
head back
swallow maybe they could be more
obnoxious with the soda dispersal maybe
just have a bucket of soda just you know
just dip a rag in it and ring it out so
it's a little damp and then just walk
down the aisle and Pat our dry cracked
lips
with ah thanks for
the he sure there's enough for everybody
I don't all right I took that too far
but you know what I'm saying i' I'd like
a whole can if I could get
[Applause]
one well you know it's like it was you
know they take the convenience out of
things you know but the world's
different things are crazier that's why
people need so much coffee they got so
much more [ __ ] to do Jesus how much I
mean how much coffee are people drinking
you people Direction shoes in Starbucks
listen go down three Starbucks make a
left go up two Starbucks make a right
here's the tricky part you're going to
come to an intersection there going to
be a Starbucks on this corner and a
Starbucks on this corner I'll beat the
Coffee Bean on the other side of the
street I'll meet you there about 3:30
and we'll have a cup of
coffee I mean you know I drink it to
wake up in the morning I'm not get
emotionally involved with the fluid you
walk in a start they a little over the
top hey can I get a cup of coffee this
one is a smooth head Ed with a floral
design and a bitter give me the coffee
lady it got caffeine in it cuz that's
all I give a [ __ ] about you crazy [ __ ]
it's not wine it's coffee I'm put cream
and sugar in a drink it nut bag you want
to do something in Starbucks they should
have two lines at the Starbucks that
would be impressive one line for people
who need coffee and another line for
people ordering gay Milkshakes that
think it's
coffee that would be
right yeah that would shave about 40
minutes off my day you ever get stuck
behind one of those people uh I'll have
a triple passion fruit tea latte with
soy milk no sugar at it some sugar-free
vanilla with a pump of almond syrup
vente you
going it's the gayest drink I've ever
heard of in my life why don't you just
order a cup of sperm you
weirdo it's a coffee shop get your
coffee and get out you be sitting around
on your laptop acting like you're
working at and people to your MySpace
account you're not fooling
anybody sorry
people I didn't mean to snap but you got
to put your foot down it's just
coffee man God I'm a little cranky I'm
trying to lose some weight which is
killing me cuz I love to eat you know
it's always as you get older your
waistline grows exponentially with your
age you know you start to get up there I
love food man I can't but I I read an
article that scared the hell out of me
about obesity it said obesity's gotten
so bad in America the two out of three
people have now become four out of five
people that's how bad it's gotten ladies
and gentlemen I'm just saying you know
we we have overweight homeless people in
this country how does that work out yeah
driving around and pulling off the
freeway there's a guy tipping the scales
of a smooth
420 back of his neck looks like a
package of Ballpark Franks and he's
holding a cardboard sign he says will
work for food I'm going look at the
balls on this son of a [ __ ] I'm
screaming out my car window hey take
some time off will
you what are you a
workaholic
I mean Jesus I I understand they're
looking out for us you can't have trans
fats you can't smoke anywhere but
sometimes you just want a [ __ ]
cheeseburger
man sometimes you just want a donut you
know but yeah well you I'm telling you
know P the other day I met a heavy set
vegetarian swear to God she told me she
was a
vegetarian I'm go
really what do you dipping the carrots
and chocolate
what you deep frying the
salad I mean you know it's your story
lady I'm just saying it's not that vegan
physique I'm used to see
it it's it's a problem people we got
Generation X and right behind them we
got generation
XXL we got people suing McDonald's for
obesity the suing McDonald's cuz yeah
it's Ronald McDonald's fault like you
know he just showed up with his big rig
clown shoes and his Burger bazooka and
just kept firing Big Macs Daniel guzzle
shoe while you were chained to a
[Applause]
chair yeah it's his
fault well based on well based on that
logic I wonder if I could do Jose quvo
for all the ugly chicks I [ __ ] over
the year certainly I'm not
responsible I'm just saying people I
like to eat I'm just trying to watch my
weight It's Tricky you have to be
careful so funny cuz I went to your
Diner here this morning to get breakfast
they had a thing on the menu called a
protein scramble I that sounds healthy
and then I read the ingredients and
basically it was an egg omelette with
chicken meat in
it a chicken
omelette yeah which is [ __ ] wrong
people you don't take the eggs out of a
chicken and then cook the chicken put it
in the
eggs that's too much
chicken Who the hell's back there
cooking some kind of chicken cereal
killer who's working to grill the
Barnyard Strangler people that's an
omelet that spans two generations of
chicken that's not breakfast that's a
vendetta who's ordering breakfast Tony
Soprano listen I want the chicken dead I
want his family dead
I want his unborn baby's dead I don't
want any chickens coming back at me
after I eat this
omelette I mean it's not right know
that's like that's like taking your
hamburger and dipping it into your
milk well that's what I'm saying you
don't do it it's not
Kosher literally it's not Kosher people
you have to separate some food items
that's all I'm saying that's why we have
problems with the e like spinach he call
like peanut butter mad cow disease you
know where that come from some idiot fed
cows to the other
cows no wonder the
man I would be
furious you know I like chicken I just
don't like it in eggs I like food that
moves that's what I'm
saying you know God made animals slow
enough to catch he obviously intended
for us to eat them
besides that what's the fun in hunting a
vegetable anybody could sneak up on a
carrot and I don't even trust vegetables
because they get the nutrients from the
dirt would you eat dirt no then why eat
the
middleman and some of that shit's not
even food celery that's not food that's
Dental flaws trapped inside a
carbohydrate I'm telling you ladies and
gentlemen celer is dangerous it's a Nega
of calorie food there's four calories
and one stick of celery but if you eat
it it takes your body six calories to
process it you could kill yourself
eating
celery if that's all you ate you're
operating a calorie deficit and the more
you eat the more trouble you're going to
get into what happened here he was
eating celery and he fell
over I said have some chicken he said no
and that's when we called you guys
[Music]
you know I like the whole fine dining
experience don't you love going out to
eat I love that whole thing where they
bring your rree and you can see it and
you can smell it you go man this looks
delicious and just as you're getting
ready to eat it that guy pops out of
nowhere fresh pepper he you scared the
[ __ ] out of me fresh pepper hey what do
you got there a table leg how much
leverage do you need on the pepper seed
what's the tensil strength on the pepper
seed what are you you're not pressing
apples you know I'm looking for a Tangy
exit on my salad so I said isn't pepper
always fresh you ever bitten into some
and said this tastes like [ __ ] how old's
this
pepper you didn't leave it out in the
Shaker all day did you that stuff will
spoil it's not like salt but I was out
having dinner and it's poor old guy God
bless him he had the worst case of
carpal tunnel syndrome I've ever seen in
my life he couldn't get any traction on
top of the wheel for like five minutes
finally he puts the pepper bazooka up on
his shoulder while a team of bus boys
came running over and worked it from the
back end which I thought ruined the
presentation but that's why you pay the
money to go out to eat because the way
they present it to you you know even the
way they word stuff in restaurants it's
different than you know like d they say
would would you care for some
dessert what do you mean care for like
open bable emotional place for it in my
life and take care of it and support it
when it gets old what are you talking
about say what you mean you still hungry
we have
pie huh you think you can choke it under
900 calories on top of the two wre you
already ate you fat bastard do you want
to live the sea
Thursday cuz we have pie yeah we'll put
some ice cream on that [ __ ] and bring it
over here cuz who doesn't love
pie you know what's funny I was in a
seafood restaurant one night and they
had the audacity to put a giant fish
aquarium as the center piece for the
entire seafood
restaurant why would you do
that I don't need to eat fish while I'm
looking at fish it made me
uncomfortable and I'm sure the fish
weren't [ __ ] crazy about it
either and they got nothing to do all
day except swim around and watch the
waiters walk by with the different ways
that they can be
prepared oh you talk about
inuman you could see the horror on your
little fish
faces that's cuz they don't have necks
doesn't mean they're
stupid well I'm not going to go into a
barbecue joint that has a petting zoo in
the middle of it that's all I'm saying
you know I'm just trying to eat some
fish and and the little fish that isn't
staring at you you
know oh [ __ ] there go another
one on a bed of rice with a side of a
[Music]
sparrow it's just a matter of time for
they coming at us
Larry Larry
[Applause]
Larry
Larry I'm crying for you lar except
nobody knows I'm crying cuz I'm in
water don't you see the cruel irony of
it all don't you even care
yeah well I'm just saying where the
animal rights people on something like
that I guess if you don't have fur
you're out of
luck no because that's all they care
about don't wear fur don't wear fur they
don't care when you wear leather really
just
F I'm guessing that's cuz it's much
easier to harass a woman than it is a
biker that would be my guess otherwise
why don't you run down to the biker bar
and throw red paint on warlocks
colors tell them his fashion choice is
murder and watch your teeth become an
endangered species and let's see how
committed you are to your
cause don't misunderstand me I'm not you
know saying we need to take care of the
animals I mean you know [ __ ] we have
opposable
thumbs and that's a big
responsibility I'm just saying you need
to direct your your efforts I travel to
concrete arteries and to this nation's
highways all I've ever seen are deer
crossing signs but between the deer
crossing signs there are skunks
squirrels and little furry bunny rabbits
to the dead yeah yeah well where's the
little guy supposed to Crosset you give
a [ __ ] so much what a squirrel going a
strap one a pair of antlers he made out
of some
Twigs don't hit me I'm a
deer I'm a really small Deer uh I got a
thyroid
problem can I
go I'm just saying you could direct your
efforts in other ways you know I'm all
for taking care of the animals I love
animals I love watching those nature
shows on television you ever watch that
the wild Discovery boy that's like the
porno channel for
Animals someone's always getting it on
that
show and I don't mind
watching no cuz you learn things yeah
well you know the male rhinoceros is the
only land mammal that could have sex for
30 minutes you know what no known
Predators he's just out
there no one's going to eat his ass lady
he could take his
time I mean some of those other animals
don't have that Advantage those little
prairie dogs are out there trying to
procreate you know they got to keep an
eye out
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I mean they can't even get too into
it he gets too into it he's not paying
attention next thing you know a big
bobcat jumps out of the weeds and just
rips the male's head off you know but
his body's still going cuz of nerves and
the females going that
feels and she's getting dumb from behind
by headless prairie
dog I don't need to see that you talk
about losing a
woody I was watching one afternoon they
had the American Eagle you know how the
American Eagle has sex they do it while
they're Airborne at high speed with no
forplay the female Eagle's flying the
male Eagle's flying and the female eagle
does his little Top Gun move where she
flips up and mid air and the male eal
just bam and I'm going
damn well you better have some pretty
good aim that's all I'm saying I mean
it's a little tough to back off to wck
them at 60 M an
hour you don't want to be going in
through the outdoor that's a whole
another flight
plan besides that I'm sure the female
eagle just doesn't enjoy
it
well
hey hey well yeah well you know you know
how many lonely dear sighted male Eagles
there are out
there how many I mean you
know well that's not even a funny part
because they can't apparently fly and
have sex at the same time once he's in
they just fall to the ground I guess it
did the orgasm where he hit the
pavement and I'm watching it's going
damn no wonder it's an endangered
species I mean that's a tough
call I mean you get a hold of some tight
eagle man you're going down I know it
feels good but I want I know it feels
good pull out pull
out we lost the nutter
Eagle if I could just get him to pull
out well you know that's the funny thing
you know you watch that stuff you
realize some animal species made for
life that's the amazing thing we can't
get that right you know we try but it's
just it's just tough It's Tricky you
know yeah that cohabitation is tricky
you know cuz as a man you know and I
have a lot of respect for women I think
women do everything better than men do I
think they run circles around us they
don't all
right all right settle down it's not a
now rally all right I'm just
saying you know women are just just
amazing they get up in the morning they
want to do [ __ ] you know you wake up
what we're going to do they going to
knock at the back wall and put an
extension on your house you're going go
oh hey I have a penis I'm going to watch
the game I'm going to take a nap I'm
going to get up and seriously consider
taking it a nap you have no idea what
it's like lugging this thing around with
me all
day no it's it's
amazing women are women are tricky
they're crafty you know they're crafty
women women set the alarm to go
shopping they do you know yeah they come
yeah trust me I've witnessed
it well list they buy [ __ ] you don't
even need is what I'm telling you
you know my girlfriend moved in 3 weeks
later my [ __ ] was gone and next thing I
know I had little balls of soaps I
couldn't wash my hands with I had towels
hanging up I couldn't dry my hands off
on and God forbid there was a blackout
was don't light those candles they're
for decoration
own why are we buying this [ __ ] if we
can't use it and what the [ __ ] is a
table
runner I I know I got to take it off and
before we eat I got to put it back on
when we're done
H more [ __ ] for me to
do yeah woman going sney I I learned one
of the tricks by
accident yo because yeah well one lady
one at a time one well you know I I was
getting up and she was coming back in
from
shopping and uh she goes oh look what I
got and she told me the price of
everything only $15 look at this 22
couldn't afford not to get it you go
okay great and she goes say why don't
you jump in a shower and we'll go have
lunch I said okay great so I went to get
a shower but I I forgot I came I can run
she ran back out to the car popped the
trunk grabbed the rest of [ __ ] she
bought I caught her walking in red
handed yeah the old trick I used to make
fun of guys who used to had velcro
wallets now I have one because that's
the giveaway oh what's going
on give me the wallet honey I was going
to go shopping no give me the wallet we
don't need any more table runners or
[ __ ] we can change out seasonally that I
can't
use well you know what I'm talking about
listen everything a guy does you know
that's why we you know women don't
forget anything women don't forget
anything except to buy more T puns
that's the one thing they can't seem to
remember what's the deal with that girls
can you go to Sam's Club or Costco and
pick up a 55 gallon drum with his damn
tampons and it's wheeled upstairs and
put behind the closet door next to your
shoe collection and leave us out of it I
mean we don't send you out for ball
cream and crew X and [ __ ] do we hey
honey I got a clump of grapes hanging
out of my mud whistle and pick me up a
tu of that Preparation H on your way
back in pumpkin I'll be face down the
couch and squirt a little on my balloon
night and rub it in I'm a little
chaed I love you too sweetie happy
Valentine's
Day we don't I'm saying we don't do it
I'm just saying girls police your own
area that's all let's police your own
area and while we're at it trim that
thing up once in a while
seriously you put on your panties it
looks like someone hit a gorilla in the
back with a
hatchet just trim it up a little bit we
just want to be able to see the
bubblegum is that so much to
[Applause]
ask I'm just saying it's a little
Annoying being woken up like that as a
grown man you're laying there sleeping
and the sheets are kind of damp and
Crimson you're like what the hell's did
I get shot last night when I was what
the hell's going on and she's in the bed
go oh my friend came last night I go
yeah who's your friend Charlie Manson
Jesus this police tape along the outside
of the bed laying in the middle of a
crime scene apparently sheet looks like
a Japanese flag that's not coming
up she's in the bathroom hovering above
the toilet you know telling me to go get
more cuz she's wearing her white slacks
and she doesn't have anymore cuz once
again she
forgot and there I am at the right a at
6:30 in the morning just staring at this
wall of
absorbing I don't want get in the padge
of the tonies I don't know absorbance
ratio work
with I got luck up the first time I had
to go buy
tampons well I had the tampon in one
hand and I had my dick in the other I
was
[Laughter]
measuring hey this look like it'll
fit
officer I got busted for comparision
shop right there in Ila it's in our DNA
everything a man does is a about the
vagina
everything that's why we wake up in the
morning cuz there cuz we there's an
outside chance we be bumping some vagina
that day that's why we shower so we'll
smell nice so the vagina will talk to us
that's why we work so we have money to
spend in the vagina that's why Thomas
said Us in the light bulb so we could
see the vagina look at it look at it and
know it's l it's why the phone so we can
call up hey vagina what are you doing
later on that's why Henry Ford got let's
drive out jump in we're going to go
where the vagina is
that's why when a man proposes to a
woman he gets down on one knee he's not
even talking to her he's talking
directly to the vagina listen well you
shut up for a minute Hey listen I've
given up everything for you I've made
sacrifices you can't even begin to
understand what oh you're a match set
okay all right well I
do thank you thank you ladies and
gentlemen
see yeah but you know if you love
somebody that's a beautiful thing and
you know if you get married you spend
you're lucky to have that some people
some people don't you know but they get
divorced like normal people I mean I
live in Los Angeles you don't you don't
even know you don't even know what I've
had to endure the last watching all
these high-profile murder cases where
guys have killed what the [ __ ] is wrong
with people can't you just get a divorce
like a normal person listen I'm not even
a detective but I know if your wife
turns up dead or missing guess who
suspect number one is you you [ __ ]
what do you think the rest of us are
[ __ ] hey and here's a clue don't
double the life insurance policy about 6
weeks before you do it how dumb could
you possibly be listen hey I listen I
watch the A&E Cold Case Files I watch
those new detectives you can't kill
people they'll catch you over something
you're not even thinking about like you
could be in a struggle with somebody and
like a pubic care could dislodge and
fall down your pants like you don't even
know it but CSI is going to show with
some duct tape pick up that whole area
isolate that pubic care and track it
right back to your genit
talian especially if there's a little
roote on the end of it they love that
down the DNA lab that's a 10-point match
[ __ ] with the technology they have you
could fart at the crime seat and if they
got there soon enough and bagged that
Rascal up and sent it down to the FBI
lab and they found out the fart had a
consistency of a cheeseburger a large
fry and a Diet Coke from the McDonald's
on the corner of Maine and four street
because of something to use in the fry
later it's indigenous to that McDonald's
and traces of that showed up in the fart
and it went in there before the day day
before the murder and viewed the tape
and there's your dumbass eating the
cheeseburger with a Happy Meal around
you and your flies down the pubic hairs
hanging out they got
you they could tie you to the crime
scene and then you go into jail where
your [ __ ] and your baseball hat are
going to become the same
size I'm sorry people I didn't mean to
run through your bubble garden with a
pen but that's what happens see we live
in a you know we live in a civilized
society hopefully I mean you know we're
not even a type a civilization but [ __ ]
we're
trying you know but people you you know
there's people who get it there's people
who don't get it I mean all we do in
this country is legislate
stupidity if someone does something
stupid they got to pass the law not that
any of us are ever going to try that but
make sure you pass the
law I mean it's
ridiculous well you know obviously well
you know obviously the world's a better
place because some people are in it but
you know some people it's just must be
happen some people can't handle the
information age or they're not they're
not kind of getting over the
evolutionary speed
bump you know and I I I don't get the
you see this stuff in the news and and
even the news is so irresponsible it's
like there may be a serial killer loose
in your neighborhood T in 11 going no
tell me now tell me now I may not be
here at 11: tell me
now it's enough to get you
paranoid keep from becoming a statistic
and people like you watch these it's
like it's like it's like there becomes
levels of social acceptability like it's
like even with these like spree killers
that seem to be popping up in the news
with more and more frequency what the
[ __ ] is that about Jesus doesn't anybody
just kill themselves anymore call me
nostalgic whatever happened a good
oldfashioned suicide doesn't anybody
just leave a note anymore had enough of
this [ __ ] you people suck I'm out of
here go and I'm not saying it's not sad
when that happens certainly it's sad
people but you know life's not for
[ __ ] you can't handle it check out
we'll see you on the other
side I'm just saying of all the ydes you
could commit fratricide genocide
homicide suicide seems to be the most
civil I'm just saying if you got to a
point where you feel like killing just
do the rest of us a favor and keep it to
yourself cuz we got [ __ ] to
do you know how do we dodging bullets at
the gas pump cuz you're having a bad
day hey sleep it off [ __ ] we're all
having a bad day you selfish prick you
think you're the only one you [ __ ]
[ __ ] oh it's all about you nobody
else is having a bad day some of us just
seem to be able to handle a little
better fact some days I'll get up and
read the horoscope and if it ain't good
I'm going right back to
bed I don't need to deal what is listen
life's too important to be taken
seriously it's just
crazy I don't get I don't even get to
school shootings what is that about
Jesus what is people just it's just
[ __ ] could you just could you just
stop micromanaging your kids' Liv so
maybe they could develop some basic
social interaction
skills Jesus you watch those see those
tapes why'd you do it Johnny why' you
cuz the jocks picked on me
Johnny uh that's what jocks do they pick
on you you go learn computers that way
later on in life you can hire the jocks
and not give them pay raises and fire
them indiscriminately and get your
revenge it's called natural selection
Johnny and if you paid attention to
school you know
that yeah well I wasn't popular yeah
well if you shoot Sally she's definitely
not going to the [ __ ] problem with
you think it through kid and take off
that [ __ ] helmet Jesus these kids
need helmets for everything what are you
doing Billy I'm reading you better put
your reading helmet on in case you fall
while you're reading you one coordinated
little
bastards I never had a helmet for
anything you know I learned how to ride
a bike my brother pushed me down the
freeway on ramp merch bro
merch we weren't babies we could figure
stuff out there computers in every
classroom how easy could you make it God
you got to do a book report today you
jump on the internet cutting paste cut
cut and paste cut and paste hey
plus had to reach it had to figure [ __ ]
out all I had in school was a pencil and
the kid next to
me and if he would applied
himself I could have gone to a good
[Applause]
school I grew up in a big family I got a
big Irish F I got six brothers which
basically means they spent most of my
childhood in Blood Stained hand-me-downs
that's my shirt no it's my shirt all
right it's your shirt let me use it to
start the
bleeding God I got I got I'm used to
this because I got a big crazy Irish
family I have an uncle that carries a
case of beer in the trunk of his car for
emergency kind of kind of emergency
would you have you needed a case of beer
hey we got a flight no spare let's
drink only reason he doesn't have a
spars cuz he took it out so he could 50
case of beer in there perfect he drives
at me out I saw my grandmother I love
the death recently I had seen her a
while I walk in her house first thing
she said to me is Jimmy last time I saw
you you were this
[Music]
High else good to see you too
GRS you
holding you know cuz Grandma's pretty
heavily medicated most of the time
herself I don't want to say she takes a
lot of pills but she has an Elvis Pez
dispenser with valume and Xanax in it
and I love her to death but she's
crazier than cat [ __ ] you know all she
does is make cakes cake cake cake cake
she's like Betty Crocker on
meth you can't stop her but no one's
eating the cake anymore cuz grandma
doesn't remember the original
recipe she lost a few tiles on the
re-entry
she's mixing her cake mix and taking her
pills and some of the pills are falling
in the cake mix she's getting all hopped
up you know make a cake make a cake you
know Grandma's Cake's a secret
ingredients and I'm she gets done with a
cake there's a big butter wrapper
hanging outside of the cake there's a
piece of straw from the broom where she
was checking to see if it was done all
the way and just leaves your [ __ ] in
there I mean you cut a piece of cake you
got to hold it up to the light
and make sure there's not a house key or
a rosary bead in there I got a good
piece here you guys are on your
own start eating it you forget about the
cooked in medication you
go it's cake taste like
[ __ ] yeah but my back feels
great what do you call that a perco set
layer
cake let me try a piece of the Oxy
Cotton upside Downer cake you were
working on yesterday you know Grandma's
cakes of a $250 street value on them now
that's what I'm trying to say but that's
not the weird stuff I people do anything
to get high I saw a story in the news
about these people that were licking
frogs to get
high yeah you see that there's your damn
drug problem right there walking past
the television set gu goz on the news
goes next story up man locked up for
licking the Frog
Went how the hell you get locked up for
licking the Frog I thought the guy had
little frog legs apart
going and if that's what he did he
should be locked up I don't care where
you come from mat
wrong well I'm just saying you assume
the worst when you hear a story like
that how the [ __ ] else would you get
locked up for licking the Frog I didn't
realize these frogs perspire as you
create a substance on his back it's
classified as an endo hallucinogenic
it's a class a narcotic it's a very
powerful toxin it's part of the frog's
defense mechanism like if another animal
triy to eat the Frog the frogs increase
the substance that when when the animal
grabs it its mouth and starts tripping
and [ __ ] drops the Frog and sees like
14 different frogs doesn't know which
one to go after and doesn't really give
a [ __ ] about the Frog anymore I'm I'm
going to go chase up bully right now and
and that's how the Frog gets out of
trouble no I'm not kiding with you
people it's a real thing you can buy the
frog in pet stores as a pat
you were not allowed to lick it it's
against the law lick a frog go to jail
that's why I was on the news they were
making arrest they had a guy in
handcuffs to dragging him out of his
trailer on the evening news I'm watching
this going how the [ __ ] did he get
caught with the Frog squeal on
him and then he licked me I felt so
cheap I was sitting there going ribit
ribit he must have thought I was saying
lick it lick it and he wouldn't stop I
mean I just want to meet the guy and
lick the Frog first and went out and
told everybody else it was a cool thing
to do that's the guy I want to talk to I
want to know how many things he licked
before he got to the damn
frog you don't just stumble across
something like that you got to be
looking fig the guys in his basement
going
Turtle nothing
parakeet
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Geral I think you people know where I'm
going with this one I'm just saying if
you're licking frog you that Clos to
putting a Geral in your corn shoe you
don't put animals in your ass that's a
waist valve [ __ ] comes out of there I'll
tell you another reason why you
shouldn't do it cuz you happen to be
messing around with your
sphincter which happens to be a very
smart muscle whose job it is is to
determine whether it's gas or solid
waste and if you keep [ __ ] around
with it you're going to be
sorry the days of farting with
confidence are over for you my
friend hey man pull my finger never mind
I was in West Virginia not too long ago
you know West Virginia where they do a
family tree in pencil and uh he's my
brother I mean my
father and I'm reading this in the new I
get in this news story I'm going guy got
locked up for having sex with his
dog and I'm going are you [ __ ]
kidding me how afraid of rejection could
you be what sound like how am I
boy told You' like it hold the tail sker
hold his
tail that's [ __ ] wrong that's man's
best friend and there's no way to treat
a best
friend my
friends that's not even a sick part it
was a male dog I know he's an animal
fornicator he's a homosexual animal
fornicator
just saying one day the sick bastard is
going to turn on the TV and see his dog
on the Ricky Lake
Show dogs up
there little pair of shades on so the
other dogs don't recognize after first
having Ricky I felt so dirty I couldn't
even lick my own balls
anymore I mean who could drink toilet
water after that and the Frog sitting
next to the dog going that's nothing
Ricky they were licking me at random
licking and laughing and licking and
left no
I'm and heagles up on the P Ricky I'm
the one that's going to have sex and mid
a and if I get my nut up I'm all over
the
sidewalk this girl's going Ricky I'm the
ones going to wear the stupid headset
just to get across the goddamn Street
hey what about my friend Larry
Ricky and the geril sitting next to the
fish going what they did to me was wrong
Ricky it was wrong talk about ruining a
good coat of fur whever these animal
race people when you need
it's been 3 weeks and I still can't get
this stink
out well I'm just saying you know crazy
people are nuts you know I was having a
bad week A couple couple weeks ago and
just you know kind of get caught up in
my own [ __ ] like we all do and I'm
sitting in the couch feeling sorry for
myself and I'm flipping around the TV
and I came across this documentary they
had on about these conjoined
twins and I'm sitting there watching
this going holy [ __ ] I mean you see
something like that I mean you know you
take things for granted being one
person could you imagine if somebody
connected to you that would suck I'm
sorry I mean as much as you can love
another human being seven days a week 24
hours a day g g g g g I'd be choking the
life out of them you shut up shut the
[ __ ] up and get off my
back I mean I love my brothers I
wouldn't want to share a kidney a spleen
and a liver with them you know two irish
guys one
and that would never work
out anyway the show I was watching they
had this woman woman on who was a
normalized woman and connected through
her head was a much smaller person I
mean this really no nice way to say it
the lady had a [ __ ] hanging off her
head that she had the wheel around on
this little stool like she was a bad
puppet
at I'm just telling you what I
saw I didn't want to see the [ __ ] either
people I'm flipping the channel there
was the [ __ ] I couldn't stop
watching and that's not even the funny
part no the one girl wanted to be a
country western singer I swear to God
who saw the show besides me okay see
yeah I'm not making it up people it's a
real
show she wanted to be a country western
singer and I'm watching this going oh my
God I mean nobody had the heart to tell
her
[Laughter]
you can't really be country western
singer we're [ __ ] hanging off your
head I mean it's not like a mole with a
couple of angry hairs coming out of it
it's a [ __ ] on a stick that you will
in the around I mean why don't you just
become a ventriloquist that's all I'm
saying hey I'm not being mean I'm trying
to save him some heartbreak you want to
get in the show but this fine work in
conjunction with your little sister
people you know how tough it is to
become a country western singer huh you
going to get shenai Twain and Faith Hill
and Gretchen Wilson and I don't know if
you noticed but
damn no
men I mean you couldn't even find a big
old 10 gallon hat to hide your little
sister and hey sis get in that hat I'm
going be me a country western singer and
you get in that [ __ ] the midgets in
the Hat kicking around and the hats
moving all around all right y'all you
ready to boot scoo and Boogie where all
my line dancers at this next song Here
is an old
classic hey hold it down up
there maybe I didn't love you quite as
often as I should have but you Ro is on
my
mind you Ro is all my
mind Hey I'm just saying
I felt bad for
them oh people I'm not even taking it
from the little one's perspective things
are bad enough you're a little person
and then you you wind up connected to a
country western
singer how bad was that who saw the show
you people saw the show here's what
killed me halfway through the program
the larger of the two girls looks right
into the camera and says you know I like
to
dat
well that's got to complicate things is
what I'm thinking a hypothetical
situation let's say you're attracted to
the larger one and you want to take a r
for a nice romantic
dinner I mean you know I mean what's the
etiquette or thatch you get to pick up
dinner for the [ __ ]
too I'm just asking a question people
okay there's 154,000 dating books out
out there not one covers a etiquette a
taken out a a join
twin I mean don't get me wrong I don't
mind springing for a PL of
appetizers uh here me you there some
cheese
sticks so uh how long you been involved
in the country western singing seven
years really and you write all your own
music no kidding that's
[Laughter]
something
[Applause]
who knows maybe at a marvelous time of
your date and you went to drop her off
that night and she was having fun and
she invited you in for a night cap and
one thing led to another and before you
realized that you were inside a country
western singer making love to and
everything seemed to be going reasonably
well given the
circumstances and you going at oh yeah
and the next thing you know the [ __ ]
starts taking off her cloes go
good
[Laughter]
hell you doing Mitch I'm having sex with
your sister what the hell are
you all right Little M come
on come on you freaky little [ __ ] come
on who's your full grown Daddy huh come
on small big small big and then the
[ __ ] reaches up with them tiny little
[ __ ] fingers and wraps him right
around you Johnson and makes you look
enormous like Dirk
digler how great would that how many
fantasies could you cross off to Liz
that night I mean you got the [ __ ] you
got sisters you got the three-way it's
like a fantasy Trifecta done
[Applause]
done
I'm sorry I know it's wrong all right
settle down I just love doing it cuz I
love watching some of your faces it's
[ __ ] priceless no I'm not laughing I
don't think it's funny no he's making
fun of this girl [ __ ] you it's not
funny oh my God he's finger banging the
[ __ ] that sick bastard is finger
banging the [ __ ] he's just ruined my
evening come on you have to admit it
would be a hell of a
story
I mean who's going to top you to
party I once had sex with the
supermodel
really I once [ __ ] this [ __ ] while
our country western singing conal twins
sang I got friends in L places where the
West driv in
[Applause]
be thank you very much ladies and
gentlemen thank you so much really thank
you so much appreciate
[Applause]
[Music]
it you know oh I like to
stay but it's time to
go I must be moving
on so we can raise a
glass to the days and
nights all the good times that we
had so many faces comeing
go one thing never shows
it's my gyy
heart thought I knew you
baby love is so
F you close the door you wouldn't let me
in I tried to fry you
over just to come
inside I need you
again now you'll s in a different song
you know I can't carry
on
anymore My Gypsy Heart be alone you sto
my love you
so all you left me was
p a chipsy heart will always wrong my CH
I can't find no home you let me out in
the days Al long the nights are I can't
find Shelter From the C I'm lost without
no
[Music]
love
so many faces come and
go one thing never
shows my Tipsy
H my Tipsy H out alone St my love you so
much
so all you live me was pain
a gypsy H always wrong Gypsy H can't
find no home you left me out in
the the days are long the night
[Music]
are
don't
Al Jimmy
shuber