I got a new bank I'm so happy I love my
new bank I got sick of calling my old
bank and going
hi where the [ __ ] is my
$25 and you know you can't swear at them
these days uh if you do they will hang
up on you which is
ridiculous that's never solved
anything right I've never been hung up
on and gone oh my
gosh I have really got to re evaluate
how I talk to
[Laughter]
people no you hang up on me you get one
reaction and one only especially if I
was already pissed you get oh oh did
that oh you did holy [ __ ] you thought I
was mad before
oh oh this is my new day
job it's to talk to your supervisor
using my nice
words I can't believe that they won't
let you swear at them my new bank lets
me swear at them which is good because
for me swearing in banking go hand in
hand uh I am now with the militaries
Credit Union they're the best they have
bigger fish to
fry and they know how to deal with me if
I swear at them they just go oh my
goodness Miss
Wood I can't use that word you just
said cuz I'm I'm at
work but hold on just one minute let's
see if we can't figure out where the F
your money is just one
minute that's a true
story I was talking to one of them about
my bank loan and I was like wait what's
this $20 she's like that's cuz you were
late I'm like I paid that bill she's
like you didn't pay that bill I'm like
well [ __ ] and she goes that's okay Miss
Wood that's a technical term okay
perfect doesn't bother me none and I
know they care I know that it's so
wonderful to know that they care like
they called me up one day freaking out
they called me which is always weird you
know they go oh my goodness Miss Wood we
are so glad you answered the
phone me me too um how can I help
you they go we think crackheads have
your debit
card and we are so sorry we are doing an
investigation we're going to lock your
account down we don't know how this
happened but we think it's crackheads
cuz they are going from Pharmacy to
Pharmacy to Pharmacy in Stockton
California trying to get something
that's 50
bucks we think it's
SX well yeah thank you so much please do
your investigation and uh if you find
them tell them all go Hales on it with
them I tried to get Xanax with that card
it didn't work and I had ID I think they
deserve a shot let's see how good they
are