[Music]
good go are we good to go here we go
okay ladies and gentlemen just real
quick for the studio audience um uh we
don't have an opening comic for you uh
we called in all our favors also folks
this is a live show um so we're going to
want your help with a little bit of
Applause when it's time and a little bit
of laughter when it's time okay folks um
but uh without further Ado let's put
your hands together for our host
Amber prester oh wow that's me that's me
that's me I'm here I'm here uh welcome
to uh sparkly Parts the album release
party we have such an exciting uh show
this is the magic of Zoom live streaming
I maybe I'm streaming to multiple
platforms I I've tried we're trying
we're trying oh things are happening it
is streaming on YouTube and if you are
watching this on Instagram live it may
or may not be working I can only learn
so much Tech in quarantine okay this is
so strange and uh the the time should I
be looking at the camera somebody I've
been getting text are you looking at
your phone well sometimes yes I am
because trying to make sure things are
happening uh I have an opening segment I
also scratched my eyeball yesterday
morning so you know quarantine going
great uh I don't have any jokes like
some talk show hosts have at the top of
a show because I uh am numb to the
outside world but um I do have some
letters from home uh it's nice to get
back to those like old school basics of
writing a letter to someone and I've
received some letters uh from my home so
here's the first one uh dear Amber oh
that's nice uh please wash me okay uh
contrary to popular belief I do need to
be cleaned with soap and water I am not
the cast iron skillet but I am just as
important EXO EXO the coffee pot oh well
that isn't that sweet that was nice of
the coffee pot to send me a letter okay
great ah there's one we got two more
here uh there another nice letter I've
received from home uh to my beloved
Amber how are you it's been so long and
I miss you terribly oh this is a
touching letter seems like we used to do
everything together did I do something
wrong is there someone else you can tell
me we were so close Once Upon a Time
surely that Love Remains please dear
Amber please come back to me I love you
and miss you eternally yours the good
bra oh that's so sweet of my bra to have
written me a letter oh gosh okay and one
last letter from home and Amber okay
well that's a cold uh opening Amber uh
please go away I'm sick of you shut the
door regards the refrigerator okay you
know what that was those were three
different uh feelings happening in our
house our household right now uh it is
now time uh to welcome our first guest
get your sign ready oh yeah this is a
professional show this is harder than a
live show you know him uh from Grayson
Frankie and Mystery Science Theater um
he's just like an all-around um super
duper great guy and really excited that
he's here you guys please make some
noise for Baron vau
everybody oh oh am I on you're on hey
Baron thank you so much for joining us
in the virtual
realm I am joining us uh
us I'm joining you from the great state
of worry no uh I'm in California I
wanted to invite you on to the show
because I think you're a gosh Dar
Delight people need entertainment and
they need some education you are a
parent that is correct yes I have two
little children one's two and a half one
is 10 months well I want to do a little
uh little game with you so this is an
activ a game we're calling yay or nay or
are you out of your mind that is not
happening in this house and these are
some um suggestions I found online just
like just like like make a schedule just
like you know like here's like 17 things
to do with your kids schooling and all
that jazz so just let me know I'm gonna
pitch something to you and then you let
me know if you think it's reasonable or
not okay uh so here's here's a tip uh if
you especially if you need to get some
work done try asking your toddler for
help with work and do simple computer
tasks like emails and make a plan for
what you need to do do you think that
would po that for a um that
is technically a yay okay and I say
technically because you don't want to
give them any anything real that they
can get their sticky little peanut
butter hands on little ones are like yes
yes I got to get those likes I have a
tweet they copy you but he likes to play
the game of I'm an adult I've got jobs
you know I like to play that game too
I'm playing I'm making a TV show right
now okay here's another activity collect
rocks I thought someone someone was
trying to hit a word count on that blog
and they were like I need one more
activity that sounds like an insult that
sounds like what a old school like kid
from the 20s like a b boy would say
they're like why don't you go collect
rocks you know like that's
this doesn't sound like a fun activity
at all here's the one I really liked uh
let your kids practice
boredom do not y or an A or no thank you
please let your kids practice boredom I
mean I I'd say yay to that I I you know
like because they do need to kind of
figure out sometimes how to be by
themselves and you know not have you in
their face all the time like be
self-sufficient apparently kids always
need some like me time you know even
babies have the idea of your cheer
that's like listen Dad I just
like I love I love this energy you're
bringing to the to this table of
collecting rocks dad but I just need
some me time seriously my my son my
toddler he I sing a lot and he has
started going like no song No song I was
singing along to a song and he was
trying to turn it off and then I was
singing without it he's like song's over
song is over he like okay I get it I get
it my my third grade teacher I get it
right does he like to sing or he just
want he just likes a little quiet time
he does sing a little bit but he he
doesn't like the way I sing no I'm more
of a female vocalist can we get some
lizo up in here and then uh lizo not not
even joking Beyonce and lizo he that's
his that's his Jam he likes there's two
Beyonce songs and two lizo songs that he
specifically likes to hear over and over
again you say no song practice being
boys I'm like let me listen to some
bootsy baby come on a little oh our
wedding song was Gucci Collins so that
was fun um i' rather yeah that's a good
wedding song it's a sweet jam and then
the last uh tip you told me if it's a
yay or a nay is just have a real
conversation I do actually like to have
a real conversation with them I I you
know I heard this thing about baby talk
apparently developmentally a child
figures out how to get you to say the
word that they want you to say so you
say like you want your bottle and they
go Baba and then at some point you go
Baba too because you've heard them say
that and it's how they learn but really
it's Master manipulation when it comes
it's like a Jedi trick that is brilliant
I'm going to train the people around me
which right now is only one person
so that doesn't quite work out um well
Baron I I know you have to get back to
little ones and I really do um
appreciate you taking some time to just
chat with us uh on this um silly goose
Funtime show and give us some parenting
advice let's clap for Baron everybody oh
the Applause
oh thank you yes sparkly Parts out
tonight at midnight our next guest I'm
super excited get your sign ready um so
former labor organizer turn stand-up
comedian writer actor she was a writer
and performer on uh the El late night
talk show busy tonight with byy Phillips
and she currently writes on Fox The Fox
comedy Last Man Standing please make
some noise for Jenny
yay Jenny you were you are as the kids
say killing the game um you were Jenny
was just in the Hollywood quarter Fancy
Pants mag oh oh there it is there it is
look at this
glamazon I like wherever I go we both
love a runny egg yes we love a little
yoke porn is the situation yes and I
want you to tell me what the picture
which former presidential candidate
would correspond to which egg comes oh
wow okay this is okay here we go this is
challenging this is uh this oh over easy
EG egg over easy egg I feel like I feel
like that's um Corey Booker Cory Booker
Cory Booker is an ere easy egg because
he he just wants to be easy you know he
doesn't want any fuss right he's like I
get along with everyone I want you to
like me Pride hard broken Yol oh my God
that literally looks like Trump it's so
gross we got a little hardboiled who
would be hardboiled I think Bernie is
hardboiled Bernie's hardboiled cuz he
you know he's he he's good he's
versatile he's like he's a little
crotchety you know what I mean you can
mush them up and make a good little egg
salad raw egg like dropped it on the
floor maybe yeah um God who is that
that's marann Williamson Maryann
Williamson defies boundaries you know
what I'm saying she's like I'm [ __ ] the
show you know she runs all over the
place you don't know where she's going
to go it's unpredictable it's
unpredictable it's like oh it's
like you know you can't hold it like oh
there is there I like that part and then
yeah that a mess let's get and then
finally um we have a poach EG oh here we
go a PO know it's on a little avocado
toast Pete Budaj because this is a very
beautiful brunch item and yes I said
brunch because he is gay these are all
stereotypes that I just wanted to bring
up and I somehow managed to do it with
eggs with eggs that's how good you can
make connections and uh that's why we
love you uh well that I named I named
this game that's excitement with Jenny
Yang that's uh so silly thank you I love
this game I just play this game forever
oh great great we'll talk well there's
always room for egg talk I thank you
thank you so much for agreeing to do
this and helping me celebrate my album
release here in the virtual world oh my
God I'm so honored Amber you're so funny
and amazing and it's just so awesome I'm
going to be I'm going to download and
buy your pre-order your album now oh
that sounds great thank you sparkly
Parts comes out at midnight thank you so
much Jenny I'm gonna kick it over to our
next guest you guys Jenny Yang
yeah I'm so excited I uh am from
Minneapolis I started standing up in
Minneapolis and lived there a long time
ago and uh there was a good chunk oh
there he is a good chunk of my youth
where I spend every Wednesday night at a
place um called uh Glicks and listen to
uh sweet tunes and became a huge fan of
our next uh performer um he's just the
best and uh you guys please welcome to
the show Alex Rossy everybody yeah yeah
yeah yeah D love thank you for thank you
for being on my album release party show
virtual thank you time for thinking of
me uh I I mean I thought it's a I'm not
I'm not limited to just stand-ups or
people that live in my city
uh you can't say no because I know that
you're stuck at home so you got me there
I got we go way back I've known you now
I don't know like 15 years I feel like
yeah at least uh that can't that's so
long ago um well uh would you be so kind
as to play little diddy for us I would
love to yeah right on I'm gonna I'm
gonna minimize myself and mute myself
and you guys enjoy the music
Alexy all right thank you for having me
here
uh all the way out here in California
and I appreciate
it little song I called
R&B all right I said's
[Music]
hold now I
about
[Music]
bre without hands how they about
Rance
every every I get l
all I do is play it hurts all I
ever
Pirates got
[Music]
brother father bad mother with
theone mind my body and Bon my to
[Music]
[Applause]
well Alex thank you so much I really
appreciate you com on you guys uh find
Alex Rossy Alex find me damn it find him
r o SSI on all the things and you guys
clap for him thank you Alex okay you
guys um oh wait I don't want him to see
you yet I just want him to see me um our
next guest holy buckets uh what a treat
we are about to have uh just a real real
fun egg uh dear friend who had if he had
said no to this I would have been
devastated and instead I feel like a a
success uh why are we here celebrating
my album that comes out at midnight
sparkly Parts uh you can find it there
where I thought this would also be
streaming I thought a lot of things I
thought you couldn't he Us in the
beginning of this but that's fine you
know what we're all doing our best like
uh like uh like trying to with our eyes
say to our producer like I know that
part's not working it's fine you guys
please welcome to the show Chad
Daniels oh my gosh hi Chad welcome to
the show thank you thank you for having
me yes you look great where where oh you
did you sprued up at your Tech rehearsal
uh I wasn't so sure
uh about what was going to happen and
you brought your aame but I just
switched hats I had a stocking cap on
and I put my baseball cap on I know it
looks great it looks great thank you and
where are you joining us from I'm
joining you I have my computer propped
up on my kitchen island and behind me
you see my dining room where but like
what city where are you call where are
you oh thought you I'm very specific
during quarantine could you tell me
which do you have three stools and are
you on the middle stool yes uh I am in
Fergus Falls Minnesota
Minnesota oh there you are hey now well
you are living it up I tell you what
yeah we're listen we're doing we're
getting through it well we're trying
you're the best you're really funny
you're streaming non-stop on all of the
comedy platforms don't you you take this
compliment I okay thank you I have a fun
game for you to play so it's no secret
uh that you were maybe you're not maybe
the biggest fan of Los Angeles you you
you prefer Minnesota I enjoy the weather
in Los Angeles a lot you know the only
thing I don't like about it is that when
people come to comedy shows
there there there's a chance Brad Pitt's
gonna show up to do some time and so
when you when you're doing your jokes
and they've never heard of you it's just
uh you know it's not it's not fun it's
not fun I will say the last time you
were in La I had the pleasure of opening
for you and it was sold out months
before the show so you can eat it uh
they love you the fans they do love well
that was very fun that show was very fun
yes we're going to play a game uh called
uh La Orno uh Los Angeles or no and um I
just found a couple a few um but it's
also Chicago because uh because why not
um I found some phrases that were
overheard in either Los Angeles or
Minneapolis okay or Chicago okay so
you're I'm going to read one and then
you tell me if it's la or no Minnesota
or Chicago okay okay all right uh so the
first one is uh first phrase is uh I
wasn't actually saying words I was just
saying
things it seems very that seems very Los
Angeles to me it seems like the
beginning of a podcast that has to do
with True
Crime right to making my husband laugh
hasn't laughed once this whole time
probably because I yelled at him when we
were live and I have 17 text messages
about people saying we can hear you
great wasn't looking at my
phone uh no that was Minneapolis was it
that was Minneapolis I mean are you
gonna give me context to any of this
like where where you heard it oh I
didn't hear them I just found them on
like very reliable Twitter and Instagram
pages okay do do we know if the person
had traveled from Minneapolis to
Minneapolis from Los Angeles we don't
but I did look like some of them I found
I was like oh that's a funny tweet and I
was like okay this is a retweet is this
person really from Minneapolis or
Chicago or LA because I didn't want that
area because I knew you would bring up
that point I'm just being a baby because
I got it wrong let's we can keep going
great uh the next one uh let's try
having sex first before we rush into
dating Chicago Minneapolis or Los
Angeles I mean these are all big
cities lot of a lot of big cities you
don't you don't hear that in rural
Minnesota much you hear like I saw it
the Dairy Queen and then I asked you to
marry me and now we're going to have
nine kids um I'm going to go again with
Los Angeles okay nope that was Chicago
there's another one Yelp is like white
women
pornhub that was overheard in what city
Yelp is like white women
pornhub I mean I'm at a loss just pick
one there's three I'm gonna pick Los
Angeles again I'm gonna keep picking Los
Angeles no Chicago do you spend any time
in Los Angeles Amber quit yelling at me
even though it's not my fault you're
losing this game I'm three I always
forget how filling broth is Los Angeles
yeah you nailed it you nailed it I I
thought you'd get that one I don't I'm
keeping track as if there's something at
stake here there's not okay I've never
played around in a meadow before but I
know it's
amazing Chicago nope that's
Minnesota my husband I mean my producer
just handed me a note and when we were
running through this game because I
thought they were a bit too obvious he
wanted me to let you know that he only
got one of them right so you guys are on
track you think you thought they were
obvious because you saw the tweets and
made the game yep yep okay all right
pretty great pretty great I also we
could we should play Chad wins after
this you'll love
it okay nope it's my show I can mute you
and unmute you this is my show um I'll
yell at you as we all know from the
beginning of this production okay um
okay here's one other one I can make
your hands smell like chicken
nuggets what city was that over
herden I mean that has to be Minnesota
you'd think but it was La I did try to
find tricky La
once why would you say that can you
think of a scenario where you would say
I can make your hands smell like chicken
nuggets yeah I bet if someone said uh I
bet you can't make my hands smell like
chicken
nuggets you got me there you get a few
extra points for that one oh thank God
okay I care where my food comes from
that's why I always shop at Whole
Foods again that could be any of the you
picked three major metropolitan
areas it's fun it's that's hey that's
like a real that was that was uh that
was Minneapolis this is like a real
light night talk show like you can't win
but you can because we're opening the
door for you to be charming and I'm
silly like right isn't that how TV works
and Well Chad you got you you w you won
the hearts and minds of the viewers I
don't know if that's right but now I
have one for you you ready Los
Angeles Minneapolis or
Chicago I'm going to download sparkly
Parts at
midnight uh I'm gonna say all all of
them that was a trick question you're
right it's all of them yes yes yes yes
yes thank you yes moose moose
moose moves moves moves well thank you
so much Chad I really appreciate you
coming on and and chatting and
celebrating this little silly album
released with me um uh check out dad
chanels on Amazon and YouTube and uh
thank you so much you're the best check
out sparkly Parts I've seen the I've
seen the set and it's great applause
applause applause boy do we have a treat
for you our final guest of the evening
she's the best I know I said that about
everyone else but they are no longer
listening our final guest is uh real
cool real great real funny you've seen
her on her own television show Playing
House so good you guys go find it and
watch it you've seen her on V you've
seen her on Curb Your Enthusiasm and I
dare say she is the star of bless this
mess on ABC you guys please make some
noise for Lennon Fara
here oh wow wow Hollywood did somebody
say that the parts needed to be
sparkly oh oh you're so sparkly and are
those sunglasses shaped like lips that's
right Bren I don't know I I don't
actually
know they're they're beauti I wanted to
honor you I'm gonna be you'll see this
is good this is good this is you're just
many glasses I like it
um Lennon thank you so much hi
Amber you're doing great this is great I
love it you look beautiful it's Charming
every each guest better than the last
it's wonderful it's real silly you know
I really did have a plan for doing a fun
live show and then you know you and
you've succeeded and you've succeeded
and I can every once in a while I get a
little wink of Peter's elbow and I just
want to nibble nibble there it is there
it
is want a nibble
nibble I like that hair cut PS less for
less for Co to latch on to right I mean
how excited am I to get back out and
tell jokes into a spongy wet no you're
gonna need to bring a mic mask let's get
to the game um the okay I have a game
for you okay let me sorry I got to put
on my game glass
yeah oh I'm so glad that I scratched my
eye and I also had to wear glasses
tonight is it so gross oh only in the
corner when you pull it down like that I
I won't do that anymore so this is a
game okay I'm gonna share the screen so
you can see it this game is
called the first one oh let me I'm not
a did you see it
yeah hip patters oh son of a gun oh well
that was how we don't play that game
okay that's the worst name I've ever
heard in my life this is from your Etsy
all your all your eBay searches right
for terrible do you remember the one
time that that the you were so excited
to get the casserole recipes and it got
lifted someone stole it off your porch
and they and they got home and they were
like it's an iPad it's an antique book
of recipes it was two it was one book
that was cooking with cottage
cheese remember so vividly and the other
book was like the North Dakota Bean
counters assoc Bean Association recipe
book they got what they deserve yeah
they did okay but that's worse than that
one that explodes glitter in your car
okay here's the next one okay so this
one I don't know if you can see it it's
got about 202 pitted cooked prun you can
buy them in cans though hun see that you
can buy them in cans Okay so we've got a
couple of options here for what this is
can I pitch one can I guess can I guess
blind before we okay I'm gonna call this
the the raw dookie
daddy the raw dookie daddy ra dooky
daddy that's not what it's called oh oh
a puffy prune whip ah ah puffy prip I'm
seeing the direction that this is going
the nuts are optional on this one you
okay it's not a nut bar pour into a pan
sprinkle with nuts if desired they're
not telling you what to surely doesn't
give a [ __ ] what you do with the nuts
but if you want them put them in preheat
be frank you know what to be frank she
should have put preheat oven at the top
of this recipe that's already you're
already behind the aall but anyway bake
a about 30 minutes 9 by 13 inch pan
freezes well yeah I bet it does shirle
great to know yeah okay any pictures on
what this one's
called get it
moving get it moving okay well this one
is I me seriously all of these would get
that dooky moving right you threw the
Shirley's bars in there to throw me I'm
gonna call them the good sugarless bars
Gooding dinging ding yes yes yes yes do
you make these Amber though do you make
these recipes or you just collect them I
do like I like to read them they're kind
of like history books I've made some of
them or I'll I'll compare notes like to
try to make recipes that my mom has made
okay so here's the last one oh okay okay
this one is H Marsha pel oh in memory of
Loretta oh there's cream cheese in this
one that's good this one sounds good
actually I'm gonna make this for our
next gathering in 2022 I hope you do for
our next dungeon and Dragons yes well
your choices are next best thing to Paul
Newman is a option b is next best thing
to Robert Redford or uh next best thing
to James Khan what do we think
Mar it's got to be Paul Newman right I
mean it could be Redford but I would say
Paul Newman I'll say Paul Newman I'll
say that her friend Loretta passed away
in a Loveless
marriage pining for Cool Hand Luke but
let's see what it is oh James con oh
Robert red Robert Redford uh that was it
was silly fun but you won the game um
and you
win you win some stickers I will give to
you that have my face on them how about
that oh yes please you know I love a
sticker have you gone through all your
glasses no I still have two more this is
kind of a Diane Katon Vibe I'm giving
these are kind of boring but they have
like a sensible solid ear rest oh yeah
okay and these are the ones that my
daughter was wearing earlier yeah that I
got at a wedding oh
I now yeah I had well I wore the clear
ones to try to not open up your face
it's your signature look I I really
can't thank you enough for taking time
um away from your family tonight uh to
so proud of you and celebrate the album
coming out and uh and I know you
pre-ordered so I thank you for that yes
yes yes get it tonight ladies and
gentlemen listen to this lady she's so
funny oh you're the best you're the best
you guys clap it up for lenon pm thank
you so much lenon I'mma kick you out and
thank you so much I love you I love
you just cut her off this has been
ridiculous uh a ridiculous Endeavor uh
when I had this idea I thought it would
be kind of fun and silly and I've done a
few Zoom shows and I know how to do Zoom
so much work uh more than I thought most
important thing I can tell you is to not
scratch your eyeball the day before and
to learn where the mute button is this
is a really a party show to celebrate um
I made recorded my first standup comedy
album a little while ago and it is now
available for people to purchase and
listen and one more time the album is
sparkly Parts I can't thank you enough
for watching thank you so much for
coming to this uh experiment and this is
uh my producer and husband uh Peter Jane
uh thanks for helping us out and um I
guess uh we're done now thank you guys
have a good night