obviously this isn't my natural
climate I had to actually take six
inches off of my beard just to
survive the weather this week so I'm a
standup comic actually up in he said
Fargo and that's true but I spent most
of my time on the Minnesota side I'm a
stand up comic in Northwestern Minnesota
which essentially means I'm desperate
for stage
time perform for a lot of
deer so so much so that last year I did
five minutes at my day job company's
Christmas
party as part of a talent competition
that I did not
win funny part for me though is the day
before the show got an email from the
woman in human resources and she was
like hey Adam because that's how she
sounds in her email voice in my
head she said hey Adam do you think at
the show you could keep it like a PG13
set
that's no good but then I went online
looked up what PG-13 meant found myself
some
leway yeah because apparently when
something is PG-13 you can be partially
nude remember I said I did not win that
competition it's not a nude Christmas
winner another funny thing about my day
job I used to be in the training
department in my day job which in case
you didn't know means sometimes you got
to go out and meet with other people who
work in other training departments and
other day jobs because dreams don't come
true oh yeah that that that probably
doesn't go over too well in
paradise usually it's like nobody laughs
and I just think I'm performing for a
room full of astronauts and princesses
it's like oh a lot of success stories
good well pretend you've failed at most
things you've ever tried
and you'll enjoy the next 10 minutes of
my set a lot more quite
frankly want to be
relatable got to be relatable so I was
at one of these meetings last May and
the woman who organized the meeting was
like all right everybody let's do an ice
breaker how about we go around the room
and why don't you say your name and uh
where you work and oh just for
F why don't you tell us if you played
any April Fool's pranks this year
D I may have imagined that sound in
context I don't know she actually said
that they liked itting back good enough
for
[Laughter]
me now I'm second in line you
guys lady in front of me pulls this
little number number on the room she
says oh on April
fools I was just calling people and
begging them to play pranks on me
because April fools meant so much to me
and my
dad he passed away this last year and I
just thought it might be nice to
experience some APR fools in his
I was looking at the organizer of the
meeting going what the
[ __ ] that should be pretty safe right
did you play any April Fool's pranks
this year that shouldn't conjure up any
daddy death
issues plus I'm a
comedian which means to some degree my
brain is a
douchebag so when it was my turn I was
just like oh April
fools yeah I'll tell you what it was
great
I played all these pranks with my
Dad we just prank it up on April Fool's
Day they call us the pranksters we've
got jerseys made and everything it's
great he's just
so
alive something he does cuz he loves me
so much