oh man you guys so I know I look like a
badass up here I've got this beard it's
a great beard sometimes get a random
compliment on my beard sometimes it's
from a lady what
up not just gay men tapping out codes in
airport bathroom stalls
that I had to learn the tap code for no
thank you
Senator that's a Minnesota joke and you
guys got it all the way down
here good for you
keeping up on all the perves we've got
up there in Congress um so I was in a
Subway sandwich shop right there I'm
excited getting ready to dominate my $5
foot long
and there was this
beautiful albeit dreadlocked and pachuli
stinking girls standing behind me in
line and these weren't like the
sexy Dave
Matthews fan dreadlocks this look like a
[ __ ] spider
Hive like spiders just said you know
what bees have the right idea we're
doing
hives we're going on the
road so she looks at me and she says I
love your beard and I was like thanks I
love it too what's
up shit's about to get real at
Subway and then she says if you came to
the bars that I go
to with that
beard you would have so many
girlfriends I was just like
lady what kind of [ __ ] up underbridge
troll bars are you going
to do you have to incorrectly answer
three questions from a wizard to get
banished to the bars where you
go is that what's happening because I'll
go