this is like the truest thing that I say
on stage so please uh don't be afraid of
me um I don't know if this ever happened
to you where you like meet a new person
and I don't even mean like a romantic
thing you just meet a new human being in
your life and then you immediately [ __ ]
it up and overshare and make it
weird have any it happens to me daily
it's been happening to me for the last
12 minutes with you lovely people
tonight quite frankly
so I met this guy
Stephen and I was like oh it's great to
meet you
Stephen so Stephen you ever just wake up
and wonder what's the
point you ever get anxiety
Stephen you ever worry that maybe
someday your anxiety is going to become
so powerful that it's going to manifest
itself in some extreme metaphysical
event like it's going to transport you
to the bottom of the deepest in the
middle of the ocean and you're going to
realize what's happening for a split
second before you're crushed by the
pressure in the Darkness at the bottom
of the
ocean that ever happen to you
Stephen you ever worry that maybe
someday your anxiety is going to become
so strong that it'll teleport you to the
dwarf planet formerly known as Pluto and
you look out at our galaxy unfolding in
front of you you'll see our sun just a
blue Speck in the distance as your blood
vessels freeze and your lungs collapse
and you're crushed by the pressure in
the darkness in the vacuum of space you
can relate to that right stepen
it's just regular human [ __ ] you
know you ever worry that maybe someday
you're going to wake up but instead of
being your bed you're going to be in a
tiny hole in the center of the earth and
it's pitch black and 150° you can just
barely squirm for an inch before you
feel a Tremor and you're crushed by the
pressure in the darkness in the center
of the
earth only instead of like I don't
know becoming a
diamond you just just stop existing
forever you ever think about suicide
Stephen yeah I'll take two McDoubles
with no
onions and a McChicken with extra mayo
Stephen let this be the one buddy take
me home to the angels hey thank you so
much I'm Adam quel