it's
ridiculous I did do Zumba though and uh
if you've never tried it Zumba is maybe
the most fun and humiliating way to lose
weight all in the same
millisecond CU they don't explain
anything to
you right you just walk in there some
girl two feet tall pure
muscle fake boobs chipper
chipper you know like she doesn't have a
stripper name like a fruit or a
spice but it's next
door it's still something ridiculous
like Tammy 1em one ey heart you know and
um she is so happy that you were there
which is disgusting you know what I mean
she say good morning is anybody new any
um anybody new
is anybody new to
me okay well if you get confused just
move
something and that's it that's all the
instructions you
get there is no more help a
common then they start the music and
then everybody's Grandma's air humping
better than you ever
will enjoy that reality check
[Laughter]
I can't prove it but I believe that the
Zumba Corporation pays senior citizens
to master
it and it's a brilliant marketing
strategy when you see an
octogenarian Drop It Like It's
Hot and you cannot do
it oh it Sparks a fire you got that's it
that is [ __ ] it beatus hold my spot
if Mabel can do it I can do it I'll see
you in gertude tomorrow we are going to
lock this [ __ ]
down I'm going to be in a rap video by
next
quarter and I'll tell you a lot of
propaganda in Zumba too like oh you can
burn five 600 calories an hour doing
Zumba and that's
[ __ ] yeah I burned four
[Music]
calories you can't burn calories while
you're confused
confused that's
physics I also don't appreciate that
zumba has copywritten or trademarked or
registered tm' whatever you want to call
it an exclamation point into the
title that is
[ __ ] this is America don't tell me
how to say my word
words one of my favorite things to do
though is whenever someone's like what
are you doing tomorrow I'm going to go
to a zumba class and
uh
Zumba so anyways no I quit Zumba and now
my new exercise method is Spanx and um
yeah have you tried
spanks they're wonderful
[Laughter]
I don't know if you know this but uh
they just came out with a study in
January this year spanks cause internal
damage to your
organs for
sure does anybody
care
no no one is throwing away their Spanx
right they're like what is that kidney
weight who gives a [ __ ] put them on