[Music]
get the bad guy every time wearing
diapers soling crimes he's a baby he's a
cop he's Baby
[Music]
Cop you tell me baby cop what would you
do if you were a my shoes if you had an
officer who was taking nappies on the JW
botching a bre coming stumbling in the
morning wreaking of breast
milk I'm done giving
warnings the da and the downtown brass
are all over my butt for that stunt you
pulled spitting up on a suspect in the
interrogation
room till further
notice you're on unpaid
leave I'm going to have to have your
badge Don't make me say it twice
[Music]
get the hell out of here
you're looking well baby cup listen I
got a special assignment Deep
Cover no one can know you're back on
duty
[Music]
interested Baby
Cop don't make we say it twice yeah
let's let's just say it twice right yeah
it's I'm not asking right that's the
whole
point cool okay everyone good okay
and action goes