get the bad guy every time wearing
diapers soling cries he's a baby he's a
cop he's Baby
[Music]
Cop uhhuh what you tell the chief
that hey why don't you come out with the
Miss and I tonight she's bringing her
sister the one I've been telling you
about you know the
pediatrician I think you'll like her
oh come on man you got to live your life
you can't just let this job take
over she might pick you up
Giggle plus I heard she likes to
[Music]
tickle
uhuh that's what I'm talking about all
right all right all right he's Baby Cop
hello
baby you want to go get some criminals
baby yeah you want you want to go put
your people in jail you want to go pull
people over huh
[Music]