[Music]
get the bad guy every time wearing
diapers soling crimes he's a baby he's a
cop
he's you know not a lot of people take
pride in their work like you do you know
man I appre A lot of people are like I'm
here to sell drugs and you're like
you're here you're here to sell an art
and I love that I'd like to put a little
uh extra into what I do we should take a
drug
selfie or like let's just do it like
we're excited about the drugs I mean cuz
we
are yeah nice that's probably Johnny
yeah go go get Johnny I'm going to I'm
going to put this on
Instagram it's Baby Cop Baby
[Music]
Cop well it's Baby Cop for you he is a
great
cop wait to go baby
[Music]
cup he's
baby baby put these cuffs on tight
[Music]