[Music]
get the bad guy every time wearing
diapers soling crimes he's a baby he's a
cop he's Baby
[Music]
Cop I don't care how they did things in
Detroit Baby Cop we do things a little
differently
here you got to play by the rules we
don't go around blowing up buildings
just to flush out B B guys I know you're
a loose
kid but you going have to tighten things
up if you want to work in this Precinct
you hear me you got to play by the rules
around here cuz if you don't I will have
your badge quicker than you can ask for
your
mommy wipe that smile off your face you
think I haven't read your
files I know your history I want you to
know that that stuff just will not fly
here I think you'll be all right with me
sir all really Hendrickson you think you
can control baby cup baby cup makes his
own rules but I'll be damned if he
doesn't get
results now get out of here they're both
of you go catch me some criminals oh one
more thing and I don't know which one of
you two did it but the next time you're
in my office you do not make a
poopy yes sir dismissed
[Music]
baby you remember when we pulled that
guy
over he never paid his
ticket all right
well you want to take a
nap you want to take a nap
together all right let's take a nap
all right here we
go my partner
[Music]