hey everybody this is part three of the
bird feeder
[Music]
Chronicles how you doing this is Ian um
I'm standing outside my house right
underneath the bird
feeder I'm happy today I'm not I'm not
sure why yesterday was really hard for
me as you might have noticed I didn't
have an update yesterday it was tough um
I was going through some hard times ran
around put up all these
Flyers that was a lot of work and I
don't have much of a work at in the
first place so went up and down all the
alleys in my neighborhood put up some
flyers and I
got big goose egg right there zero
return which uh kind of ticked me off
and um made me a little sad made me a
little introspective um I actually made
a video for yesterday um I just didn't
bother putting it up um just in full
disclosure since this is like a video
blog thing and I'm kind of like a diary
put my insides on the outside um here's
a clip of uh what I did yesterday that I
decided not to upload
[Music]
[Applause]
okay well see that's what I'm talking
about right there I didn't want to put
it up because I don't know the quality
was kind of mediocre and it doesn't
really reflect well on me as a person so
I decided let's just skip it let's take
a day off come back today you know well
refreshed that's exactly what I did now
the bird Peter's been up there for about
6 days I think I don't know I'm kind of
iffy of math but in the spirit of Web
2.0 I have decided to be a little
interactive and take some suggestions
from you the viewer got some right here
now uh my friend hap from Texas she had
a really good idea she said hey Ian why
don't you sprinkle some seed outside
underneath the bird feeder so that's
precisely what I'm gonna do right
here yet again got the Scott song bird
selection going reach in here throw a
little bit
around pretty good amount too might as
well be liberal with it otherwise it's
not going to get used at all you
know so we got some nice piles of uh
Millet and stuff sitting around
hopefully for the birdies to enjoy throw
some around here
too um my friend Stephanie from New York
um she wrote in not technically a a
suggestion but she used the phrase bird
banal in her response um and that's a
colorful use of alliteration Stephanie
so um that degree being put to good use
thanks for the comment keep them coming
uh Lori from right here in Minneapolis
Minnesota suggested patience so
um guess we give that a shot
Keith K died ni
David kerine David kerine Keith kerine I
think still
alive died in the Thai hotel room kind
of
for for
[Music]
[Applause]
all right so that was patience uh giving
that one a shot
um still buckus sorry who's that Lori
yeah no dice on that one Lori um so I
decided to go for something that's
worked time and time again for me oh and
by the way the air conditioner is
generally on the fan settings so there's
no hot air coming out of there but
thanks for the suggestions on that one
10 people who said something about it um
all right so I decided to try something
else that I've known has worked in the
past I have up there a bottle of wine
and a glass right there next to the
cedar sign um hopefully that will get
some people out uh get some of our bird
friends to make an appearance um and
it's there it's there for the taking um
the glass is uh pretty well full I mean
that's a lot for a bird and I left the
cork on there kind of loose just in case
you know maybe hey you know if they run
out you know middle of the night make a
run over here hey why not you know it's
good time
so
anyway that is the bird feeder
Chronicles for today this again is part
three uh we'll be back um I presume on
Monday with part four so stay tuned
[Music]