[Music]
hey everybody this is Ian um all right
so here's the deal I'm here in my
bedroom and it's now been a week or so
since we've actually since I've hung the
bird feeder and we still have yet to
have ner a single bird show up so I have
decided to do what many other failed
Ventures have done I have decided to do
an open mic night here in my bedroom
kind of get some excitement here and it
is my pleasure it is my utmost Duty
ladies and gentlemen to welcome up the
one and the only Patrick
[Applause]
Bower how's going how's going I uh
thanks I just flew in here from Toledo
and uh much like every other thing that
uh flies I failed to stop by the
feater I was saying now at weddings
apparently uh instead of rice they're
throwing out bird seed because uh rice
makes uh pigeons explode and um
apparently the government is not
throwing R everywhere on my block um the
add a benefit I guess to throwing bird
seed at the wedding is that you no
longer have to decorate the car that the
bride and groom drive drive off
[Laughter]
in and you know I've seen things like uh
misspelled wedding invitations uh wrong
color napkins the DJ plays the wrong
song if you've never seen a wedding
dress with pigeon [ __ ] on it you have
not seen a woman cry her
hardest until you've slapped her because
really if you're not getting your
money's worth out of that dress I say
you aren't living my
[Laughter]
friend grle sounds weird
an old standard for everyone this one is
not mine but you know it's an old Street
joke whatever I just I feel like closing
on it cuz I'm uh doing a comedy contest
and Deluth
um you know what you get when you [ __ ] a
canary
chirpies Sly it's uh
untweet Patrick B everyone have a great
night it
ladies and gentlemen Patrick
Bower going on a tour of the
subcontinent very soon up next we have
another very funny man who also uh head
headlines every Wednesday at grumpy for
the Minneapolis quami death squad
everybody oh my God oh my God oh my
God ladies and gentlemen Chris M oh my
God
Chris thank you Ian and thank you
everybody please keep keep your feathers
on but anyway I used to date a bird once
uh very funny she thought everything I
did was gross gross she was always like
yuck yuck yuck yuck e ew
ew gross
gross
hey Fe or not you like that joke it was
excellent you know I had a dream last
night and uh well it was about uh well
I'm a little shamed but well I was
eating out a chicken for quite a
while luckily it was just a
[Laughter]
dream thank you very much everybody
thank
you ladies and gentlemen a very funny
man the water and only charismatic
everybody round of applause keep it
going
all right now this Open Mic thing can't
go on for much longer here to close us
out everybody you've heard about him
you've seen them on television and
abroad ladies and gentlemen billly
y all right all
right thank you all for coming out I'd
like to thank the
[Laughter]
birds I can go
on um hey I have a joke about birds um
ducks
um so hopefully some will come to the
theater uh I was watching a hunting show
and this guy's duck hunting he's got all
this really expensive stuff he's got
like a $300 Duck Blind and like Duck
whistles and duck decoys and duck urine
I don't know if he need that stuff
um I don't know if you need that cuz uh
um I've never been hunting before but
I'm pretty sure all you need is a loaf
of bread in a hammer uh cuz I was at the
park last week and holy [ __ ] right like
I had to fight them off I'm like one at
a time and they're just like quack which
I guess means bread and
like you know I they're like I need bird
jokes and now I just feel like I'm
rubbing it in just like I can't get the
birds off of me I didn't know about the
theme until I got here so um I I'm
sorry
sorry ladies and gent Billy
[Applause]
Young all right well welcome yeah thanks
for stopping by my bedroom tonight
you'll find comment cards underneath all
of your seats um if you if you like if
you didn't like it tell us sign up for
our mailing list if you did like it of
course uh tell some birds about it so
one more time for all of our comedians
here
tonight all right that is uh yet another
installment of the birdh house
Chronicles thanks for watching hopefully
you enjoyed
[Music]
it Tick
T tick tock