this is Ian talking to you right now
this is part one of what I'm calling the
bird feeder
[Music]
Chronicles now it's not that good of a
name but this is only the first part
really I mean yesterday was kind of like
the introduction to the bird feeder
chronic so if you have a better idea
post it on a message on the Facebook or
whatever and you know we'll we'll take
it into consideration and by we I mean
me but I only if you have a better idea
I mean come on seriously so anyway um
the if you watched yesterday you know
that I've had a bird feeder then for 4
days and I had yet to have a single bird
well it is my unfortunate job to tell
you now that today is day five still yet
to have a single bird show up and just
depressing to me cuz I've been you know
you know I've been doing stuff around
town for quite a while and you know I
have a pretty good reputation people
generally show up to my stuff and I I
like I like to know that and I even
charge cover charge but I'm giving away
a big pile of food and the birds they
just aren't interested yet so I'm trying
I'm thinking to myself I've given this
much thought much pondering and I'm like
okay well where are these birds from
well they're from Uptown well what do
they do in uptown well these birds they
hang out on telephone wires and kind of
hang out so I have decided to put
together a gorilla marketing campaign
aimed at today's bird my clientele so
I've come up with a name for my bird
feeder it's no longer just my bird
feeder now it is known as the cedy right
there so check it out right there pretty
cool huh I even did a logo for it and
everything it's not the best logo but
yet again we're early on this maybe
we'll s snaz it up later maybe I'll talk
to Olsson and Company or some
advertising agency if this really takes
off so I've come up with a couple ideas
here so check it out now this is stop
hanging around so that's what they do
and this is on a telephone poll so
trying to get right to them so stop
hanging around fly over to the cedar see
I've got a bird up there on a telephone
wire was thinking of Goldie Han Mel
Gibson thing but I decided against it
cuz that's kind of high brow for birds
and um always what you want to do when
you're advertising your wares what are
your wares well right here check it out
we have featuring today you know and I'm
trying to you know add urgency to that
so maybe tomorrow it'll be different
maybe we won't have as good of stuff
tomorrow we have sunflower chips white
Millet peanuts red millet and Canary
seed we have two different kinds of
millet I know and I even came up with a
little slogan seed is good H yeah see
maybe they remember Wall Street and you
know I'm generally kind of against word
playing stuff like that but you know
maybe birds are for it you know cuz dumb
people like puns a lot so you know birds
have little tiny brains so maybe they'll
be into seed is good that's the hope you
know I mean yet again stuff's free we're
giving it away I'm just kind of trying
to raise awareness for these birds cuz
these are hip up town birds like I'm
telling you man they got to know what's
going on so we're coming right to them
coming to my clientele now my clientele
might include different kinds of birds
and this is something I've have already
considered in addition to the two
different kinds of millet I have two
different kinds of advertising campaign
check this one out right here
this one tweet [ __ ] this is for our
gay birds in the neighborhood so you see
we have a rainbow flag underneath what I
believe to be a finch yet again
advertising the two different kinds of
millet we've got and yet again seed is
good so tweet [ __ ] if you're a gay
Finch perhaps a by curious pigeon hey
we've got what you need cuz let's face
facts today's active pigeon they're
hungry you know they've got better
things to do than sit around stand in
line man and there is no waiting at the
cedar now let's check out the location
shall we here we are right here behind
my house now let's take a look up there
now you see okay there's the sign for
the cedar I'm a little out of focus but
you can kind of get the idea I hope and
up there is the bird feeder the cedy
this is it this is our local this is our
location so birds get with it here we
are day five still no birds but now we
have a very aggressive advertising
campaign that I think speaks to today's
bird and uh by the way yesterday I did
the uh I posted the video on Facebook
didn't help attendance at all so maybe
they're still on MySpace maybe they're
still on Friendster see Ste you can even
hear them mocking me right now but I
don't know so maybe they're but they're
out there they're doing something but
they're not checking Facebook so if you
have any sort of uh Aven thing you're
trying to put out there Facebook not a
good solution but hopefully Gorilla
Marketing is so we're going to check in
tomorrow and see how it works see you
then
[Music]
[Applause]