hey everybody this is Ian um I'm talking
to you right now from my messy bedroom
here in Minneapolis Minnesota doing a
video blog thing which is I don't really
like doing cuz I think it's kind of
trendy well it was trendy a couple years
ago now it's just kind of I missed the
boat and I was lazy then and I had
better [ __ ] going on and well now I
don't unfortunately and the the gimmick
Still Remains so here I am anyway so um
about 4 days ago I decided um that I
wanted to get a bird feeder now that
might seem stupid to you Ian you're
probably saying to yourself you seem
like a somewhat together with it Guy
bird feeders are for the elderly well
you're right and um unfortunately I'm
not getting a younger myself but I'm
bored a lot of times so you know I sit
around I I do a lot of work in my room
in my messy bedroom that's why we're
here right now um you know I do stuff
you know I'm editing you know blah blah
blah and look at me I'm working right
now I actually have a Final Cut Pro open
uh was doing some editing but if you
notice right above that um I have a nice
window I actually kind of set this up to
uh you know my little editing area to to
uh be right by the windows so I can look
out you know like so it doesn't seem
like I totally wasted the day away and
every now and again I'm lucky enough to
get a couple Birds just to kind of hang
out there and they look at me and they
say hey in how you doing and I go hey
Tweet Tweet back at you little bird
friends but you know and then they then
they leave and then they got bird things
going on so finally after living here
for about 4 years I decided Well you
know what would be awesome why don't I
get a bird feeder and that is precisely
what I did about 4 days ago right over
here in this window right behind me
above my dirty air conditioner and this
was going to be great this was going to
be you know like it's not like you know
exactly my raison Detro not my reason to
live but I thought it would be you know
something new I could look at while I
wild the hours what precious gift of
Life Away um but but so far um I've had
a problem that problem being that I have
not had a a single [ __ ] bird show up
now it's been 4 days now I don't know
about you but if I if there was a big
pile of hamburgers sitting around my you
know neighborhood it wouldn't take me 4
days to find it I I would know pretty
damn quick that like holy [ __ ] there's a
big pile of free food for the taking now
something I haven't told you is that I'm
I've been you know I'm 32 years old and
I've had I've had a multitude of jobs in
my life not the least of which is
graphic design done a lot of PR work too
in the past um and I honestly kind of
feel like a failure because I'm giving
away free food right there free food for
taking and there's a moth but that moth
isn't going to eat any but I'm giving
away free food to basically this uh bums
to Indigent hobo birds that really don't
have any better options in life at all
so I I'm being altruistic look at me I'm
cool look at me I'm a bleeding heart
liberal I got a [ __ ] bird feeder for
some [ __ ] birds birds don't want it
so I am setting up this video blog to
see what I need to do using my years and
years of
research and knowledge of uh public
relations um trying to get birds to show
up to this bird feeder I even bought
good food I don't want to think that I
like I skimped on this I didn't look I
got some Scots song bird mix now I'm
already regretting that because as you
might have ascertained you don't really
you might not know me very well but I
not a morning person so if I do get
birds here it might not last very long
so the last thing I [ __ ] want are a
bunch of loud birds but what I'm trying
to illustrate to you is that I actually
spent the money to get real seed from
our friends Menards who aren't
sponsoring this of course cuz why the
[ __ ] would they anyway but yeah so this
is a video blog Illustrated on what do I
need to do to get birds to show up to
this bird feeder thank you for watching
hopefully this will be good