[Music]
all right hey it's me um with was it
is
6:52 in the
morning I'm
not enjoying this this is the loudest be
Birds ever
now all right so I don't know throughout
my life I guess I've learned to
ignore the sounds of wordss generally
it's just depressing it means you know
it's time to time to go home go to
bed well now I'm home in my bed the
sounds of birds following
me well anyway I guess
um he uh congratulations is an order uh
to The Comedians I think they apparently
that was the missing link to get birds
to show up to the
feeder um I'd like to thank them like to
thank everybody who uh wrote in with
suggestions and I would like to thank
you for
watching stay tuned for part two of the
bird feeder
Chronicles when I uh ditch this damn
bird feeder in some jerk's
yard it's been a fun
experiment now it is
over we have happy birds happy loud
birds thank you for watching good
morning hello darkness my old
friend I've come to talk with you
again because a vision softly
creeping left its seats while I was
sleeping and the
vision that was planted in my
brain Still
Remains within the
sell of Silence
[Music]