speaking of uh eating standing up like a
maniac my my wife really is into those
food
trucks she really likes that if you if
you've never been to a food truck it's
uh it's like the same fine dining
Cuisine you know you'd get at a nice
sitdown restaurant except you get to eat
it standing up with no plate while you
Huff exhaust
fumes it's great it's spend my entire
childhood being told not to take candy
from strange cars well what if it's an
Asian fusion
Taco what's the rule on that cuz I
really want to try this chicken curry
burrito out of a decommission
U-Haul I think I'm going to give it a
whirl so we went we went to this food
truck festival this summer and uh the
longest line for all the food trucks was
for this place uh called Eli's donut
Burgers yeah what that is it's a
hamburger patty with mayonnaise and
cheese served between two grilled glazed
donuts the first time I saw that was the
first time that I realized I I kind of
understood the mindset of people who are
against gay
marriage it's like you can't put that in
there those don't belong
together like I just got irrationally
angry like look I know you're not going
to make me eat it and your sandwich in
no way affects my sandwich but it's just
not right