good I am hecton Klein vone documentary
filmmaker perhaps you Americans are
somewhat familiar with some of my films
including my latest award winning film
Holocaust what Holocaust which was very
well received in Iran about a year ago I
received a package anonymously through
the mail which contained five video
cassettes and a note Written in Blood
which simply read tell the people but
these tapes contained chilled me to my
very core and became the inspiration for
vacha about to see the footage
Chronicles a TV host attempting to make
sense of a yearly event known as
bachfest a drunken bakanal of such
staggering proportions that it makes
Carnival in Rio look like a school girl
slumber party I must warn you what you
are about to witness should not be seen
by the faint of heart the very young the
very old most women and some men you may
vomit in fear you may be driven insane
you may even abandon your God such is
the power of my films but one thing is
certain you will not be able to tear
your eyes
away here now is the tragic story of
drinking visan at B
Fest
drink with you
all
F we're in lovely new Minnesota where's
my beer here's mying beer give it to
me this drinking with the end live on
location of Bo Fest in lovely new all
Minnesota it's being put on
by our friends at the Shell's Brewery
and judging by the sheer outpouring of
Jack acidness around me I assume these
people have already been
drinking it's like I'm waiting for Al
Roker to come out any second now but
we're going to walk around we're going
to talk to people we're going to drink
someing beer do you people like
beer it seemed a simple enough task to
undertake perhaps Ian was optimistic he
might find some Pearls of Wisdom or vity
banter from these cheerful beer soft
party people but it soon became clear
that something more Sinister was a foot
for you see the bar beer does not
lie you guys sisters
C that's kind of hot thanks anyway is
this your first time here at B Fest
absolutely definitely are you enjoying
yourself we are hey ask where we're from
so you guys are having a good time so
far Fargo definitely yeah so where are
you from I hang on I'm from Fargo North
Dakota I'm from South
Dakota that question sucks I'm going
back to Iraq in June so I'm here to
party it up drink it up I'm glad you got
all your killing out of here somewhere
else because it's not me tonight swear
no you can swear on my
show everybody let's say all
at hey I just had a staff member grab my
ass that's a special time isn't it I got
the implants I got the
implants so hey so you're a staff member
here huh yes I am how how'd that happen
I there are actually people who work
here I thought this was just a bunch of
people stormed the place and stole beer
have you been to B Fest before Jo yes
sir second year dude do you have any
words of wisdom for the people at home
you know what here's my words of wisdom
I went to a cake this morning at 6: a.m.
I don't suggest that cuz it's dumb you
know I mean like if you're going to
drink at 6:00 a.m. and then come to this
it's stupid we should probably just come
here and drink you know what I'm saying
I I you needed life wisdom to teach you
that you didn't think hey there's a
dayong drinking Fest it I'm going to do
some cake stands before I show up this
footage went on for hours but Ian was
not alone in his Venture he brought his
friend for the most dangerous part of
bfast
a man called
Madu M here for drinking with I I'm
going to be doing the B hun don't know
what the hell that is but we're going to
find out come with
me hi just a normal customer here
wondering what this boach Hunt is here
at new alms bachfest well they're cut
out out of plywood Bo heads goat heads
and uh different sizes and each size
brings a different price it's all cash
money and you find one you bring it up
here and uh you'll get the price are
they actual size no they're not they're
smaller hi Chris MW out here in the
field hunting for box with fellow boach
hunters from new home yes yes yes see
told you so uh have you read the clues
um sort of yeah just just glance over
them thought we' take a peek at the map
see how the clues combine with the map
you know see if we could find any points
to start at looked at the map it doesn't
show you where they are hey Chris MW in
the field here with a guy with a keg of
beer on his back and a girl that's right
yeah see you have the girl do is this
the only day of the year you have a keg
on your back no no which other days a
couple of times yeah it's not any
specific day but usually a couple of
times a year I have a kick on my back do
you usually have to walk far before
people uh cost you for the beer well
we've only G about 100 yards so far and
more than that yeah we haven't made it
down all the way down the hill so
usually about 100 yards in we our kegs
empty yeah could could I have some beer
could you have some beer please well you
can have a beer only but you're going to
have to shle for us you know how to shle
I not I forgot how you don't hey Tom he
doesn't know how to shun a long time I
do you don't know how to Shunk not I
forgot can you a little bit Yeah well
shle is kind of a dance you're arm
in-arm with people and you kind of sway
back and forth and I think we like sh I
don't know but we'll try it ready is
this like this like this are we shunlin
well you guys are probably going to need
lessons it's time to find some bhe
heads and with these simple words medu
went off in search of the bachhe heads
drunk with passion and a lot of beer he
became like a Savage man stocking his
prey how ever what began as a B hunt
soon became a fight for survival in an
unforgiving
Wilderness unable to rely on his vits
and very nearly sober medu became what
is known as a
b you're just suck on it oh thank
you you getting any that's Bach beer
right there so this is what real men do
in the woods this suck on each other's B
now fully the property of these mountain
men Madu was taken away to their Forest
Lair their perhaps unspeakable Acts were
performed upon him there goes Chris
we're only going to find his skull and
his penis M has never heard from again
until now yeah that reminds me drinking
with Ian isn't drinking with Ian without
the shot of the night let's go to via
satellite we have an Uplink right now do
doly how you doing
hey kids how you doing you know it' be
really nice if uh the producer drinking
with you and would keep me up to speed
on what the hell we're doing but no I
didn't get a phone call I didn't get an
email I didn't get a text message saying
hey we're not shooting
tonight so in honor of that tonight's
shot is called throat punch the producer
and I make throat punch the
producer you take a
shot of Philips vodka
vodka a [ __ ] it you take two shots of
Philip
vodka vodka you take a
shot of triple
sec and you take a shot shot of Red Bull
bull add a little ice ice shake it
up strain
it and that's what I call throat punch
the producer shots on the
house so really Ian next time seriously
man give me a [ __ ] phone call text me
you've got I mean we're Myspace friends
Jesus send me an email smoke signals I
don't care just let you know all right I
think our ups going out uh thanks olly
all right now back to more bockfest
action Ian could not have anticipated
how much action there would actually be
this zeach beer flowing like beer there
was no end to the silliness of the day
I'm glad somebody else dressed up for
this somebody else who really gets the
occasion of course I do yeah I mean so
are your stable of hoes around here or
is it just
you anyway so what's your name my name's
Laura Laura are you enjoying B Fest so
far I am I like it here this your first
year this my first year and so you're
you're being def flowered on camera
right now so I know it's racy so yeah so
there's a lot of people here are would
you would you consider this an
attractive crowd looking at
you I'm blushing I'm
blushing yeah so anyway we're going to
walk around we're going to talk to
people we're going to find every
douchebag with a B we can find and we're
going to get them on TV one by one trust
me on this this is going to be a great
television show don't go anywhere isn't
that right yeah
exactly how much of this dunken Foolery
could one man sustain d as it turns out
Ian is not so different from these boozy
masses we spoke with someone close to
him to know
more you know Ian and I go back a long
way and I don't know if a lot of people
know this but Ian and I actually met in
jail and I knew that I was going to hit
it off with Ian right away he was the
only other guy in a clown suit and
despite the fact that he was a happy
clown I was a sad clown
that never became a wedge between us we
have been Fast Friends really ever since
and when I found out that Ian was going
to
bachfest I have to admit some alarm
Bells went off when you take a bathtub
full of free beer various delicious
spicy sausages a free hotel room it's a
recipe for
disaster so if you see Ian in your
travels see somebody who looks like Ian
please give him this message that All Is
Forgiven he'll know what I mean I do
have a ha cou for Ian at this
time and it goes like
this Ian at
bachfest suckling the teeth of free
beer
someday he'll come home
while watching this grown man cry I
debated with myself over whether I
should use this footage or if it was
simply Shameless
exploitation just look at him weeping
like a heartbroken little girl yes cry
you little baby you weepy VY little
Namby pamby
man and now we go to
commercial you'll save money and time
you'll get the best of merchandise and
service when you patronize these good
neighbors no beer in the midwest has a
grander brewing tradition than grain Bel
for over 100 years grain Bel has been
the beer that fathers have passed on to
sons and friends have passed amongst
each other at local bars and watering
holes it is a beer with tradition that
spans Generations which is why it has
become legendary both here and across
the country next time you go out ask for
a premium triple calf draft energy drink
is made for the night life and not for
sport triple calf draft energy drink is
only available at establishment selling
Spirits mix Triple C with your favorite
intoxicant and you will come to
appreciate the lasting effects of the
world's first draft energy drink Triple
cap tap one off and Spike
it if there's one thing we like better
than booze it's cheap booze and that's
why we chose Merwin Liquors as the
official drinking withian liquor store
great deals a huge selection they even
have a contest where customers can win
free drinks for a year Merwin Liquors is
hard to beat yeah it's a bit ghetto but
up your street cred and Save A Buck or
two stop in at Merwin liquers at Lindale
and West Broadway in North Minneapolis
just two blocks west of 94 or visit
Merwin lick.com
drinking with Ian is proud to be
sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV Vodka
no matter if it's UV blue raspberry UV
red cherry UV green apple UV Ivory
vanilla or UV orange vodka UV flavored
vodkas offer a premium product without
the high price tag please visit UV
vodka.com for additional information and
recipes a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest news source and the AV club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at news stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at theonion.com
and avclub.com pizza luche proudly
supports drinking with Ian free delivery
until 2:30 a.m. weekdays and 3:30 a.m.
weekends download our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with thean is
nothing without our sponsors please
support
them one Pearl two honey put down your
stupid knitting because I just got
drinking with Ian season 1 on
DVD I've been waiting forever for
this hey how's it going I'm Ian you got
here man you guys got craft tasting
music
drink how long does this go
on it says here it goes on for five
whole hours including commentary by the
cast and crew hey you like mailboxes I
just wrote a ton of killer hiu about
mailboxes this is really starting to get
weird honey do something I can take you
off I'm trying it won't come out of the
DVD player make it stop make it stop
drinking with Ian season one on DVD
including commentary and bonus footage
it's like a home invasion except we
shoot you in the head with entertainment
pikao I can see
you and now you are back you have seen
the Carnage and you have seen the Mayhem
that is B
Fest and you may ask yourself as one
might why would such a man subject
himself to this torture leave his
comfortable home to go out into the
middle of the
Wilderness surrounded by drunken Savages
who fear the pelts of animals they have
killed the answer is simple
sponsorship for you see the bond between
a television show and its sponsor is
stronger than the strongest
superglue and even more powerful than
Love by now you would think that Ian had
had enough and like these stupid
Americans you are you would be
wrong are we are we from an important
newscast Place yeah yeah no well then
what the hell are you doing here for
well that's why we're here we're
important newscast people you're
tricking me this doesn't even work does
no this is this is full of candy oh for
the love of God eat
it yeah do we know where the orgies are
tonight so are you guys like
vegans Channel 6 of course Channel all
right so you guys have like a team name
or something no remember OFA people
eating goats
again all right so are you afraid being
are you afraid being like the only woman
here a little bit cuz there's a lot of
men and animal they're running around
it's kind of scary but I'm getting over
it after I think I think they've been
drinking yeah that's even more scary but
I'm drinking too so I know I need to get
on that I got to hold this microphone
and yeah anyway so is this your first
year it is and I'm enjoying myself very
much that was my follow-up question now
now we're ruining
everything did your cat piss you off
what happened I shot this but this
here's the
grandfather Dan seriously so what's your
name my name's Allison Allison I'm glad
to see you here this is great can I have
some beer oh have a chug should we count
for him one two three four five okay
stop that's my beer
Channel 6 kcv
9521 or
what as the Oompa band played their
rendition of Ring of Fire like an
endless loop Ian began to feel the
claustrophobia brought on by the crowd
of
thousands desperate for some peace he
wanded the spacious crowns of the
Shell's room
there smaller groups CED in the
woods Jesus Christ um I had to get away
from these people I need a brief respit
in the woods a brief
constitutional I hate large groups of
people um especially when there large
groups of people from Southern Minnesota
uh so I'm out here uh drinking Fe having
a fine time with me and our friends
Denson and young thankfully are here as
well oh hi there hi there hey
it's good to seeing you guys yes uh yeah
we were just out here uh doing a concert
for some close friends you know honing
up on our skills and uh well actually we
have a new song off of our new album
dreams and such the wishing sessions if
uh if you want to stick around we can
play for all right yeah we'll just play
this new song it's actually called oh
are you sick I'm sorry oh no I I have
allergies oh you should try drinking
some orange juice orange juice it's an
old world grity that one ju yeah but uh
all right well all right let's do the
song and get you out of here you some
rest some rest yeah all right two three
four everything made of
RSD and the trees and and I
said sorry sorry are you all right like
I mean is it son's perfume or cologne I
mean should we move you like such places
no I'm fine it's uh I'm not large
perfume anyway I'm cool let's just uh
let's do this okay all right from Top
sorry sorry okay two three four
everything is made of rainow the birds
and the trees and you and everything is
okay seriously well we just move you
like I no get you away from whatever
you're allergic to and then we can
finish the song all right I'm really
sorry about this fine I don't I don't
think it'd be better anywhere else
either all right let's just do this is
it mold what oh my cousin's allergic to
mold one time you had a bad piece of
cheese boom coma three months is that
even no no true story it's not mold you
know I i' I'd really rather not talk
about it all right I I don't want to
make anybody uncomfortable okay all
right well let's sorry the top sorry
sorry everything is made of rainbows the
bird and the trees and you and me I said
everything is seriously what the I'm
sorry I'm sorry why you just tell me
what you're allergic to we can get away
from you and then we can finish the God
song we can't finish the song If You're
sneezing every 30 seconds it's it's not
that easy all right it's not just tell
me all right I don't want you to make a
big deal about it okay I'm not going to
make a big deal about it all right I'm
sorry I yelled okay went to the doctor
and he said I'm a I'm I'm allergic to uh
fat
people you're allergic to fat people
yeah fat fat
people okay I get it all right did Bob
put you up to this Bob where is he is he
is he over there Bob take a little po
little F old husky bres you tell Bob
he's no Bean pole either Bob Bob's been
missing for weeks his wife is worried
sick no I really am allergic to fat
people all right I can't control it oh
my God like wait it's just it's not nice
to make fun of somebody because of how
big they are like all obesity is an
epidemic it's a disease like Teddy
Roosevelt hey no I know overweight I'm
not trying to make fun of you or anybody
else or Teddy Roosevelt he's National
Treasure all right I really am allergic
to fat people I can't control it and
gravy for some reason I don't I don't
know you just can't be allergic to how
big somebody is that's not how it works
okay that's not how allergies Work bill
it's a real thing trust me all right did
you know overweight people produce twice
as much lonin as regular people yeah
there are over 23 Americans who are
laros intolerant okay listen if you're
just trying to be mean to me mean to you
mean to you I'm the one with the serious
Affliction here all right you know what
I I can't go to the State Fair without
my respirator I tried to go to an all
you can eat buffet last week I almost
collaps I'll probably never get to see
the city of Chicago oh my God that must
be horrible it is it is you know I wish
I wish that once just once I could walk
into a Dunkin' Donuts hold my head up
high and order a jelly
fil that's my
dream this is my nightmare oh my God I
had no idea how could you is there
something I can do can I lose weight I
can lose weight sweet Bill if the answer
were that simple you're kind of taking
over Bill you've got your sugar lobbyist
on Capitol Hill you've got a SE for each
ass cheek sitting next to us on the
airplanes you've even managed to take
complete control of the public transit
systems mine's a Dying Breed Bill one of
these days I'll accidentally wander into
a taping of the view and that'll be
it Candle in the Wind there's got to be
something I can do I'm afraid the only
thing we could do right now is continue
the song when I have my oxygen
tank
Bill tell them about
me um well dening and young um Everybody
are just just young thank you Jesus man
what the hell are you allergic to fat
people too no I'm I'm allergic to bald
people oh
God zud only serve to confuse Ian
further so to feed his already bloated
ego Ian threw himself back into the
throngs of bck Fest to follow in his own
hubris so you got any questions yeah
where where are the orgies tonight
anyway uh you know I heard there was one
going on one of the Biffy out back but
it got a little stank so man man Biffy
ories what am I I'm in my 30s now I've
moved up to full on okay so you need
like the men's restroom perhaps in the
will Coleman there's a mansion here I
figur they have to have a grotto all
Mansions have Gros and Playmates right
you can have like a low-key heft thing
going or something like that extremely
lowkey so all right so so far today I've
been uh I got a Buddy Holly I got uh I
David Bowie uh and I got Wolf Blitzer
amazingly enough this is the first man
who's actually recognized me and what's
your name my name is Ian exactly we're
drinking with Ian dude holy we're
drinking with I that's good to he he's
got to protective home uh so yeah is
this your first box Fest this is my
first box Fest now are you a fan of
seducing beer cuz they say beer is like
a woman do you what you what's what's
your come on techniques for beer Ian
well you got to get the nose right in
there sniff around a little bit and then
you know good bouquet is very important
taste it swirl it around and then just
dive
in wait oh wait a second oh this is your
first year at bfast this is my very
first year at bfast are you enjoying
yourself I'm ABS absolutely enjoying
myself sorry about that I should swear
have you SE there's a lot of Germans
around here does that scare you like it
scares me I I have a lot of French
ancestry I'm in Terror the entire time
I've been here I feel I'm going to be
conquered at some point this isn't beer
on ground this is urine uh it's not only
urine but French blood yeah and a little
bit of regret a little bit a little bit
of regret a little bit you know but you
know that's what life is made of you
know a few regrets and a few triumphs
and and you're an in French blood and
you're an INF French blood and really
you can't have regret without both no
you know French blood that's like I
don't know that's the groundwork for
most uh failures and wonderful things
you got any words of wisdom uh if you're
GNA drink drink in new home during BR
fast if for no other reason then it's
relatively cheap yeah exactly it's
highly
affordable the be villain and drunken
Tom fery did not end this B Fest the
masses Spilled Out into new filling the
bars of Main Street Ian was sweat up in
the Rivalry finally passing out in a
mobile
laboratory Ving early the next morning
in a sanitation yard he started the long
journey home
all right that was the bo Fest edition
of drinking with thean I hope you
enjoyed it as much as we enjoyed making
it for you it's like 8 in the morning
we're still here at new home we're going
back to
Minneapolis I'm confused still kind of
drunk I don't know what the hell
happened I don't even know what that
means but anyway it was a good time we
we had a great time we drank a lot of
beer we met a lot of interesting people
and to everybody in new all I just want
to say I love you but I'm going back to
indanapolis screw this
Ian was never heard from
again what became of him it is hot to
say there are rumors he was picked up by
a random truck driver ripped and eaten
but the locals tells the story of a man
who stalks the wooded CRS of the Shell's
Brewery subsisting on acorns and his own
Ur eagerly awaiting the next B Fest
so what is to be learned from this
probably nothing but if you are
considering the journey to new to attend
BF Fest hug your children tightly make
passionate love to your wife for you may
never
return good night and thank you for
watching
sit ubu sit good dog