[Music]
standup records proudly presents Cory
Adam
jokes I don't know if you can tell by
all this but I'm
single thank
you it's weird too like I was in an open
relationship and we broke up right and
like that's super awkward cuz when you
break up with an open
relationship it just feels like you got
into a more open
relationship it's like sit down honey I
think it's time we see even more other
people and the moment I became single
all my friends had all kinds of tips and
advice for me right and it's always the
people in the worst relationships that
have the most advice like I'm on the
phone with a buddy of mine he's like
Corey you got to hang in there love is
amazing it's
I'm on the [ __ ]
phone you don't see get out of here I'm
on the
phone no Cory you just hang in there
it's
great and I got to this weird point
where I got convinced it was my fault
right my fault I was single like it's me
right shot
up like I had a buddy of mine tell me
that I wasn't putting myself out there
and
he made me sign up for Plenty of
Fish yeah that website should be called
seriously dude not nearly enough
fish I had one girl message me she's
like I like Stephen King's misery too
let's get married I'm like no I'm out
uh-uh read that book keep moving I'm
out and a 36 years old dating is weird
like I don't like it right like I'm too
bitter for dating I get it let's lie to
each other till we're comfortable to be
ourselves dating
woohoo but at 36 I'm too bitter for it
the only joy I get out of dating is by
making the date as awkward for her as
humanly
possible my favorite place to take a
lady out on a first date is out looking
at
houses really rais a family here let's
go check out the family burial plots
what do you
say that's Cory Adam jokes now available
from standup records
[Music]