uh hi everyone my name is Chad Daniels I
supposed to say this isn't comic
Spotlight yep Chad Daniels hi comic
Spotlight for for
myself it's pretty good intro hi
normally I don't dress like a uh
skateboarder going to a golf course but
uh I didn't know I was going to be doing
a set tonight how are
you I was at a bar one time and this guy
wanted to fight me but he looked at me
and he goes you probably fight like a
girl so I had sex with his best
friend because that is how girls
fight yeah that's right look around look
around find a man that isn't smiling
he's been cheated on look around go
ahead I'll give you a
second because girls think they use
vaginas they use their vaginas like it's
the hottest commodity on the earth and
it would be if only one of you had it
but you all have vaginas and some of you
are [ __ ] and that brings the value down
of the other
ones right when women are like if you
want some of this W don't you mow the
lawn cuz other girls have Apartments
[Laughter]
that's why they don't have to mow the
lawn there they have people that do that
for
them never made just don't hold your
vagina hostage because I don't negotiate
with
terrorists it's very American policy but
I stick with it I uh I started doing
standup a long time ago right here on
this stage and uh what happened was I
was working for Xerox The Copy Company
and was let go or fired and I got a
six-month severance package and I threw
myself a retirement party cuz I was 23 I
didn't need all that money right uh then
we came down here and some of my friends
signed me up for Open Mic without me
knowing about it that was my awesome
first experience with standup comedy so
uh not a lot of laughter and then I
thought well I know what I'll do I'll
just write some stuff and come back next
week and it'll be way better and so
that's what I did and then it was not
way better do you remember any of the
first
jokes uh yeah the first joke I ever told
was uh about a uh yeast c commercial was
a monat 7 commercial and this lady comes
out all cocky she's like hi I'm trying
monat 7 cuz I've tried all the other
store brands hey whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa I think I was using both hands whoa
to make it dramatic whoa whoa whoa
probably yelling you know I can't
remember exactly how it goes but it ends
with if your puppy won't sit on your lap
anymore you have to go to the doctor so
that's that was my sensibility when I
started I was uh born and raised in
Fergus Falls Minnesota and spent 20
years the first 20 years of my life
trying to get out of that town and then
I had two kids and uh moved back just to
get them closer to home and watch them
uh try to get out I think was probably
my strategy there it's it's funny
because you listen to all my albums um
back to back and you can almost hear my
kids growing up I had someone from Acme
a crowd member come up to me after a
show last time I was here and they said
you know uh we started coming here 10
years ago so we feel like your son has
grown up in our family and so that was
kind of cool to
hear uh the album natural selection I
actually wanted to call it uh TI rabbit
or remote Miss um but then the guy
that's recording the album he was
listening to it and I say natural
selection on it twice and that's kind of
a theme throughout throughout the album
uh it's a lot about it's a lot of my
kids stuff you know it's crazy because
I called a Booker one time and they said
oh kids kill comedy careers and I have
to tell you I don't know if I'd still be
doing comedy if I didn't have kids
because a I get a lot of material about
them I love talking about them I love
talking about the struggles that come
with
parenting uh I found a my son is 14 and
he has his own bathroom and I found a
ruler in
there
and 15 minutes later when I was done
laughing I went to him and I knocked on
his door
and I said hey I found the ruler in your
bathroom and he's 14 so he responded
yeah but and then we what about I don't
where's mom can't breathe why are you
the last thing he said was I was doing
math while I was pooping that's the last
thing that he said to
me and I said 6X equal 36 what is X and
he goes what and I go you weren't
[ __ ] doing math don't lie to
me so he came upstairs a half hour later
and he goes hey Dad have you you ever
measured and I said I grew up with two
women of course I
have but not with a ruler like a [ __ ]
[Laughter]
hillbilly I laid down on my back and I
made a pencil mark on the door frame
like a goddamn
gentleman that way you can see your
progress and nobody finds your ruler
like an [ __ ]
and he said is that why Grandma Karen
told me Smurfs live in her house and I
said probably but the album um made it
to number seven on the Billboard charts
and number two on iTunes and uh we're
all very happy about that Pandora I
don't know who likes me there but
someone does and they put me on all the
stations and so then people start are
starting stations of mine and I hand out
little cards that have the same picture
on it that the album cover is after my
shows um and people are always like oh
that's the album that comes up on
Pandora so it's it's uh it's getting a
lot of play and it's uh I'm happy about
it I recorded a special here about two
and a half years ago uh I listen I don't
do a lot of things first but I really do
feel like this special was uh the first
one to be shot in a club since probably
the 80s everyone was doing big theaters
and stuff I feel at home here I feel
very comfortable on the stage uh and it
was great you know I called it Asis
because um it really was what you were
getting when you came to a show it
wasn't you know you hear people all the
time that are on TV shows and then the
people that come to see them do comedy
are expecting that character and it's
not them uh so I wanted people that
watch that special to realize that if
you bought a ticket this is what you're
getting and I did some impr I mean came
up with some stuff off the top of my
head I was goofing around um and just
kind of having fun with it and the
crowds were great and the staff here was
so so cool you guys can enjoy my past
work and then there'll be when you're
all caught up there'll be another one
waiting for you kind of like the Harry
Potter series so I'm not exactly sure if
that one
second
hello hey I'm doing an interview thing
right
now okay yeah I can help you with that
all right my daughter has homework I
need to I need to
leave for