[Music]
okay here we go come on Cody come on
come on come on hold hand hold your
brother's hand come on okay dear
heavenly father thank you for this
Bountiful meal we're about to receive
and thank you for hocky and that one
time that Cody had a breakaway goal and
he scored a hockey goal against for
letting uh hockey be such a part of our
life and for letting there be hockey
tomorrow night at s and the bus broke
down but Cody had a pocket knife and was
able to help fix the electrical cords on
the battery of the hockey bus and then
Cody fell in the ice and went under the
ice and that dog happened to be there
and from helping me make bars for after
hockey to share with Debbie and Sandra
over at the hockey Center and thank
hooked him up to the dog and the dog
pulled him out and Cody was okay and
then thank you for that time that the
bus broke down on the way to Regionals
and all the guys had push the bus over
to bigi and take the bus into that one
place where they got it fixed and thank
you for
[Music]