oh hey This song is called little stiffy
[Music]
I never believed in the one till I met
you I didn't know peace could come to
me and love could be so
true it never even seemed to matter that
in inches you were only
two then you
died and it broke me
boohoo boohoo
The Moment I
Saw
the slip from your
eyes all gang in the world would have
silen my cries I
was to Madness even to me was a
surprise I would never stop loving you
there's only so much time till you're
gone
little we got to do it quick cuz the
cops
find when your in me
my are much more
prol let's get her done before you die
for good little stiffy
I changed the sheets took off your
clothes and I lay you
down let a scent candle put on my
m i bed it like a
Bronco Rory clown you were dead you
still are and I still love love
you and I know this is how you
it even if you wasn't
[Music]
there your fingers woven in my
hair while I try to keep you stiff with
it I'm cting on your r
or to finally break the
you're still dead and now your stiffy
dying going to miss you in your 2 in sck
little we got to do it quick the cops
find you're almost there don't you worry
I'll be in
a keep it hard for me and the after
little
stiffy keep it hard for me in the after
life little
[Music]
stiffy
y yeah