goodness gracious are we up to headline
time
already oh my God who's G give me give
me some noise if you've seen charismatic
before come on let's hear it beautiful
that's what the whole field advantage is
all about so ladies and Gentlemen let's
keep this going as we move on to our
headliner for the rest of the belongs to
Mr Chris
[Applause]
mic here we go for G
everybody and all the rest of the comics
you've seen
tonight he laughed out you laugh out no
okay cheers I'm going have a asian beer
hey asian beer I'm not driving I tried
that didn't work
ever drinking and D between my wife and
I we have three DUIs man she doesn't
have any
know
fing I live I live with my
wife she's a piercer at a tattoo shop
when I met her she Pier you if you want
not if you don't want I I respected that
but if uh if
pierces everything on people right
pierces like dude's wangs even some Wang
sorry it's how old am I [ __ ] it's slang
for
dong but she'll do it not this one I had
some work done as an
infant that was it I don't know why I
didn't they didn't ask I didn't sign off
on it I don't
remember they oh god he's perfect oh
except for that part
doctor fing we got to cut part of his
dick
off why I don't
know other people have I don't I don't
[ __ ] know why we do it we're doing it
though that's what you do how much do
you want to do the Lord will tell
us cut it off
I don't know I uh uh I never want to get
in a fight with one of those guys though
with the dong piercing what are you
going to do to him it's been done
right you make fun of him cuz he's got
to sit down to pee now which that's what
happens if you know a guy he sits to pee
it's like a lawn sprinkler after you do
that not the cool whippy kind either
it's like a low pressure kind of small
town it's like a a you don't get to do
the yes it's like a
a all
right he gets pissed you give him one in
the crotch he's
just
Exquisite
[Music]
again I quit my job a while ago I don't
I quit a job I usually get fired so it
kind of felt like a promotion
I I get fired from a lot of I got fired
from my first job when I was 14 I worked
at one of those Little Caesar's Pizzas
guy came in and said how big are your
10in
pizzas 14
in how many pieces are in
that doesn't [ __ ] matter you don't
know how big it
is there's two how about that I cut it
once there go get out get
out well there's three of
us not if you turn up
missing what' you say to him fine I'm
[Laughter]
fired that was a Pizza Shack is where I
learned to like maintain on a massive
amount of pot you know like if you've
had pizza that's Stone people make it
that's why it's so good that's what they
know pizza stone people know Pizza
hot pineapple on a pizza you think your
[ __ ] friend thought of
that I'm pretty sure I did I don't know
pretty
sure you want to get high here fill out
this application you
know like [ __ ] I don't know I work I
had a lot of uh waiter jobs and that's
like like you that makes you hate people
like on a like your waiter [ __ ] hates
you every second don't ever think your
waiter likes you your waiter is the
reason he's smiling is because in his
imagination he's got like a SAA in the
middle of your neck oo the spine's
taking a while like it's
like he hates you he hates you and you
should know what you like oh God every
smile you know CU you go home and it's
just it it's so traumatic you go home
and you'll watch the news and it'll be
like yeah a couple was stabbed to death
on a lake while they were just trying to
take a job and you're like they're
probably dicks anyway they probably
didn't tip they probably [ __ ] them [ __ ]
them you know they probably wanted no
ice they probably wanted no ice I have
no ice oh [ __ ] you [ __ ] you [ __ ] your
mother [ __ ] the next time you see me
there's not going to be ice in there
okay that's how much I [ __ ] hate
you you have time to think about that
there's two people dead right now and
you want [ __ ] no ice [ __ ]
you you
wait you wait tables and people come out
Valentine's Day let's all go out on the
same day and have a [ __ ] romantic
night let's all go out at the same time
that'll be good let's we have to go on
Valentine's Day we're going on
Valentine's Day and that time we're
going on that time we're going to have a
[ __ ] romantic night we're planning
it that no that never happens you know
you go up and then you know the
reservations aren't
ready well [ __ ] a it's Valentine's
Day and everybody's out we get guess
what you don't get to sit down right
away well who loves you anyway look at
you you're a [ __ ] you suck you know
like and then okay okay come to your
[ __ ] here's your table here's your
table we wanted a
booth we wanted a
booth oh you got problems there's two
people dead okay here let's [ __ ]
let's ask the homeless man staring at
the window he wants some food we got to
clear the frost off though it's February
it's very
hey homeless man did mental illness make
it incapable for you to take care of
yourself well do [ __ ] it bad cuz she
doesn't have a
booth like oh you want to come in are
you cold get in here man you want a
blanket like yeah put him in a
blanket is that better
yeah sit down man you want some food
yeah here just sit at this table do you
have a
booth whatever [ __ ]
happen dude's got perspective but
I work at Jimmy
John's right now uh because that's what
you do when you don't have a job and you
work at Jimmy johnes but
uh and I performed at the orway uh also
so [ __ ] I mean the orway if you don't
know was a beautiful 2000 the SE theater
in St Paul made out of extinct Honduran
wood modeled after old Opera Houses in
Europe and 2,000 people I performed them
but I worked at Jimmy Johns and did that
in the same day
pretty sure I'm the only guy to [ __ ]
do that ever okay thank you everyone
knows thank you but
but I delivered a sandwich to uh this
apartment building where um I thought I
I knew I hung out in the apartment
building but I wasn't sure which
apartment it was um and I it was last
summer and then I knew I went to a big
New Year's party there it was my
friend's house and then he moved out in
April and so but I went there in summer
and then this couple answered and I
wasn't sure if it was the same apartment
that I've been in so many times and
especially on that New Year's party
and uh so I went you know they answered
this couple aners the door and they're
like you know and I give him the
sandwich and then they're like you know
and I go hey when did you move in by the
way and they're like oh in
May I was like they're like why and I
was like oh I just just cuz I did Coke
in your bathroom I did Coke in your
bathroom Coke in your
bathroom they were looking at me looking
at each other
like he did cocing bathroom he did Coke
a it's good they were
good [ __ ] I don't know but I just want
to be a comedian I don't know I mean i'
ra rather be a you know an a band more
[ __ ] but um comedians kind of get the
drgs but it's better than poetry uh
it like if if if comedy was
skateboarding poetry would be
rollerblading right like you might be
talented but no one wants to watch and
no one wants to [ __ ] you that's for sure
like they you might want to they might
you might get a girl to make love to but
that's gayer than [ __ ] a dude
like
I I travel to exotic places like North
Dakota North
Dakota North Dakota is proof that God is
not exactly everywhere
um there's you can't you can tell I'm
not from North Dakota when I go there I
got this look in my face it's like a
hope you can't look like this and be
from North Dakota like it's like
a that's what it's
like it's not a tolerant Place either I
was in a bathroom in North Dakota
someone carved swastikas into the wall
carved them they carved kill [ __ ]
someone busted in the bathroom I jumped
put my scratching tools
away it wasn't like that I was
scratching out kill and writing
tolerate but I didn't want anyone to
know you don't want to get caught
tolerant in North
Dakota I go to Wisconsin a lot too
Wisconsin is proof that you can get
pregnant from sex I truly believe
that
you and it's a spillover but it's the
center you
know fing some dumb people it's
Milwaukee is kind of the oo it's a
terrible place it's like uh I don't know
I mean they're they're not tolerant
either like their biggest problem with
Jeffrey dmer is that he was gay like you
know
like like yeah killed a bunch of guys
that's [ __ ] up he [ __ ] them first a
come on
man I I want to think about
it I used to have a lesbian sister and
then but then she changed into my uh
straight brother and um I'm bless
blessed with a transsexual brother you
know uh and he told me you know when he
told me like I'm not Lyn and he had a
sex change and I'm not Lynn anymore I'm
lonus I was disgusted not by the sex
change but lonus that's what the [ __ ] is
that like you want it's your middle name
Fester like come on take me seriously
now I'm
[Music]
lonus he did it when I was 27 why can he
do a 10 years earlier I got away with
everything Chris got a
tattoo Lynn got a
dick going
out I go
out parents are like you got a dick
you're going to hell let we snip the end
off come
here get you to
heaven in Wisconsin no they have the um
they they I went to the Packer Stadium
they have they pray they have literally
they they have green and gold rosaries
with NFL players numbers on them they
have Packer rosaries that they pray on
they pray for the Packers to win the
game oh dear Lord please let find it in
your Divine Mercy to play isn't your
[ __ ] kid in Iraq the [ __ ] are you
doing you're praying for the football
game this
it's Christians so they're the only
religion that advertises you know like I
saw I saw on a bus bench it was like Hey
kids like they're trying to be hit for
the kids like hey kids rebel against
your parents go to
church I actually saw one there was a
guy rock climbing and it was like did
the do now do the
Pew they're hip they're totally hip no
other religion would ever do that like
forget what you've been doing man start
H doing
like
start you know some Buddha on a
billboard like please come
on but that does marketing that the next
step is they're just going to [ __ ]
tie you up and kill you again that's the
next step because I want you they want
you you know they do they never see a
Buddhist with you know just like [ __ ]
find inner peace find it find it open
your [ __ ] eyes find it find the
moment find the [ __ ] moment open your
[ __ ] eyes you know you never well you
might I don't know have
you sounds like you have there these
Mormons I bumped into these Mormons as
we all will but they you know they
riding their bikes it's like June with
the wool pants and the shirt and Jesus
says my name is Mark and they're wearing
helmets and you know the Mormons the two
guys and
I I ran into them and there you know I
it's going to go by but then I was like
hey I might get a story so I went back
and they were like hey have you accept
there was one guy there was Mark and
then there was like this
like really young guy he was like 18 and
midb brainwash and he just he had
nothing to say but Mark was he said have
you have you taken Jesus into your life
and I was like yeah and that [ __ ] him
up you know
really um good like I'm just kidding I
haven't give me the thing give me the
thing and you
know and he's like
he's like until you take Jesus into your
life you're going to be miserable I was
like when man it's like 80 I got a new
girlfriend I'm getting laid you should
try that getting laid you should try
that that's good you
know when am I going to be miserable you
know it's so you know he's talking about
like you know God did this he did that
he did that I was like oh cuz God's a
man this is the only time the guy like
actually looked like he was like talked
like a person he's like
yeah of course I'm sorry I'm sorry God's
man
duhh but what makes him a man I asked
you know and he's just like what and I
was like well does he have a hairy chest
does he does he have testicles that
would make him a man wouldn't it quote
he said I guess God would have some sort
of genital
region spreading truth on nickeled it's
just like he said he was going to like
you know God's got balls sure I was fine
with it you know imagine this like
wrathful deity in the Lotus position you
know 17 testicles hovering around or
whatever and God took one testicle and
created the
Sun and L it was good and big who dude
who
huge and God took many more testicles
and created the planets all of varying
sizes which is
normal for a Godlike deity now he's got
two like a dude
like dude how do you know God's a man
right you know it's like come on like
who I mean because I had to tell him
like what what does he have balls
for okay
Mormon they're for [ __ ] that's all
they're for man who's God [ __ ] who's
God gonna date that's a lot of baggage
right it's like you
know you said you take me out tonight
like I brought the Sun up and I put it
down let me have a scotch
[Applause]
[Music]
you
know so I was like seriously where did
you find this out who told you this is
it Gordon who Okay Gordon's the head of
the Mormon church now who told him
Joseph Smith duh okay Joseph Smith well
who told Joseph Smith well Joseph Smith
was uh lived in the 1800s and he went
out into the woods and the guy said to
me that two beings of light he saw two
beings of light came down from the sky
and I couldn't help it I was like God's
testicles and the little guy was like
you watch your mouth boy I mean I swear
I was old older but he's watch your
mouth boy now I wish a story could end
in a fight with two Mormons but there's
a lot of problems with fighting a guy in
a helmet in public
um obvious one he looks [ __ ] and he
might be able to prove it in court he's
Mormon what was I going to do to him
anyway I was just like I might get the
fear of God in Me and I'm railing head
on the curb and nothing's
happening the power of Christ compels
him you know something I don't know plus
I'm a
pacifist
um but so I don't know I went to Oregon
and uh not Portland though way different
uh Oregon wow I was there was a little
bar and I was doing comedy and a guy was
in the front and he had swastika tattoos
but it wasn't a big deal to me he was a
guy with [ __ ] swastika tattoos there
he was Jeff and
uh Jeff liked your show [ __ ] uh no like
but I if you've been to Oregon like it's
you know that's I can see where that
would happen because it's beautiful and
it's just you know you're like wow look
at the streams and the and the stars and
the sunrise all the nature look at the
mountains smell that Mountain Air man
man I hate black people man that's what
happens to you it just happens it's a
natural thing he can't be blamed
there's more did you hear about that guy
this year that got
uh uh he tried to get the cake from the
he's suing a bakery because he named his
kid Adolf
Hitler who has a kid named Adolf Hitler
well just Adolf
Hitler he had this guy had a kid named
Adolf Hitler and uh I I assume he named
him he didn't have him but he he had a
kid and then he he's suing the bakery
because he wouldn't for the kids like
third or fourth birthday wouldn't put
the bakery wouldn't put Happy Birthday
Adolf Hitler on the cake and he's suing
the guys like in Pennsylvania and but
then the best part is that he went to
Walmart because they had done it for him
two years before but here's the deal
Walmart didn't they didn't have to
special order it Walmart already had
them um I just had
him like yeah Jeff's over there he's
going to get them all get over
there but
uh I don't know this and we you know my
friends like like uh Patrick who's on
there before me we have a video called
Clan brand where it's just like this
video that's about uh the clucks clan
that has a breakfast cereal and it's a
little comedy deal we did right you
should look it up but uh we went to this
like you know this is why I like to do
these shows here because you can say
whatever you want and you guys get it
but like go to go to like a hotel that
has a comedy club in it and it always
sucks it's just like this the hotel club
owner was just like can we play Clan
brand it's funny he's like yeah right
people from Tennessee stay here yeah
like come on man like you're not a
racist okay but you simp you know like
he's a he's a he doesn't want to offend
the racists that's all they got money
like yeah come on
man the clan is
right down shut
up but they know it's that's what I
think you know should be uh you know you
should keep uh art dangerous I guess cuz
you know be safe in the real life you
know no one gets hurt when Art's
dangerous and that's you know it sucks
when it's not listen to the radio you
know have you ever listened to KQ for
it's like Groundhogs Day man it's like
every [ __ ] day oh they're playing
[ __ ] You Shook Me All Night Long I
love that song oh they're playing You
Shook Me on that long I love that song
oh they're playing I thought they
weren't going to play it forever a
second but then they played it w Shook
Me All not long it's a conspiracy it's a
music conspiracy man they want to make
you apathetic toward music man I swear
to God they don't you know she like
whatever is all F me all You Shook Me
All Night Long all night long and every
day every day I want to hear that song
never gets old don't have any other ones
[ __ ] it
right everything sucks man like there's
the like the don't [ __ ] buy any the
80s music deal either go don't go to any
80s music parties you know yeah hey man
80s music man it's F funny it's like no
it sucks it's like rat and poison those
two just went on tour together again and
they didn't even call it the rat poison
tour that how that's how much they
suck they're D know it's so funny no it
sucks I know crank
it what I know every deaf leopard song
we all do none of us ever wanted to know
one cuz they suck they're a karoki b you
should sing Pour some sugar at me at
karoke get drunk should wake up and go
ow that sucked and I should do something
else with my life you know they're there
to teach you something don't get me
wrong but it's not to listen to you know
I can prove to you that de leopard sucks
right now with
words their drummer lost an arm and it
didn't make a
difference okay an arm should make a
[ __ ] difference in a four piece I
don't care okay hey cut the singer's
head off whatever they sound fine it's
just that LE bird you know
I saw on VH1 the the drummer if you
didn't know the drummer from De le has
one arm used to have two ended up with
one uh because he flipped his car off a
road in England and then this they had I
watch his VH1 thing uh shut up and
uh they he flipped his car off and he
off the side of the road and they he
lost his arm and then they had the
elderly couple on the show uh that um so
that found him and then he this is what
they said that he said when they found
him we saw a young man and he said could
you help me I'm a famous rock drummer
and I've lost me
arm that's what yeah like if it was any
of us like could you help me I've lost
my arm I'll tell you the rest on the way
to the
hospital this a you know the most
important part of the story right now we
can go chat on the way like like what
this [ __ ] like let's
go could you help me I'm a rock drummer
okay let's go but in due time
I play in the style of rock and roll and
I'm quite popular dude your arm it's
gone I've asked you
twice don't you care about your arm I
only play for de
leopard oh good point let's stroll a bit
it is a nice
night [ __ ] there's a lot this is bad
it's bad
music John Cougar melon camps got that
album It's called The greatest hits
album called the best that I could do I
mean come on even he knows
it
right here's my life's work
sorry it's not very cougar like
title small
town that's a cougar no you
know called my Uncle the other day we
got a lot of good local music out here
in San Francisco go it's like yeah you
do Primus the merman lots of [ __ ] he's
like yeah Counting Crows holy [ __ ]
people like them it's like Counting
Crows they're that band they go they go
Mr Jones and me tell each other fairy
tales those guys those guys he actually
goes in the song he goes man I wish I
was
beautiful you look fine dude shut the
[ __ ] up right you you know you look fine
shut up if if I want to hear a woman cry
I'd punch my wife that's right that's
what I'd
do I would never do that though my
wife's pretty tough I mean if I ever hit
her she goes so nuts like i' I'd
probably have to hit her again I'm just
saying I don't really want to get into
it all all the
time I did that joke in Wyoming there
was girl she was so mad at me she had
her glow stick necklace on cuz it was
her birthday
um is it your third
birthday [ __ ] out of my face why are you
talking to me you
know I mean she thought that I beat my
wife and so she thought she'd come and
threaten me she is what she said she
like you don't you should you can't joke
about hitting women I had to punch you
in the
face that's not nice either you
know it's like if you plus like think if
you actually think that I'd hit my wife
what the [ __ ] you think I'll do to you I
love her think about
it she was like this
tall here's your money back no no give
me that no re
no money
back bad music out there man I don't
know so I'm a poor guy I'm really poor
um I take a lot of vacations for a guy
with like no money though I got a cabin
way out of the way it's it's actually
only accessible by uh
mushrooms I go there a few times a year
just saying it's not in this state
exactly
um my wife and I did this stuff ecstasy
once not once we do it all the time but
we did it once and have you ever done an
ecstasy man
[ __ ] good not don't do it it's bad I
mean what here's what happened is like I
mean we got totally
naked we're married
whoa oh thought this was church it's
happened it's
happened but now we got naked and we
just like made out for hours then we
just ended up telling each other like
exactly how we feel about each other
remembering to say the stuff all you
always forget to say you know
remembering not to take each other for
granted see it's this drug that was
legal up until the 80s that they Ed for
like uh couples counseling marriage
counseling they also use it for regress
memories cuz what it does is it it it it
really helps you have like an step back
from all your petty problems just kind
of fall away and you just like feel this
unconditional love for yourself and the
people you care about so it sucks don't
do it and uh so what and and then and
it's not like tripping because you have
like a control over it and um basically
you uh like what it did for me recently
is um you know it made me realize that I
was kind of addicted to these negative
emotions all the time and and my I don't
know and so I've been able to like get a
perspective on stuff and like my my
life's been just INF itely better so it
it just sucks don't do it stick to booze
okay do what they tell you and uh I'm
not looking down either because I drink
a lot I mean what happens when you drink
though you get arrested you get
hangovers you you cry in front of people
you don't want to cry in front of you
get in fights you [ __ ] try comedy it
sucks you do dumb [ __ ] is what I'm
saying worst thing that ever happened
and my wife and I we did ecstasy she
ended up with a hickey on her boob which
is trashy don't get me wrong cuz you
just look used you know you [ __ ] you
don't if you're going to let someone
suck on you until there's a bruise you
you know you're not trying the expensive
cheese at the grocery store the [ __ ]
wine you know it's [ __ ] Carlo rosi
and velv baby suck on my titty you know
it's the way you look but you know I had
leverage on everything for like two
[ __ ] weeks is all I'm saying you know
like you're supposed to take a left
there like yeah nice TI
[Music]
hickey someone doesn't want to get blown
again like you couldn't get a chick with
a TI hickey to blow you I mean I'm
saying if anyone's going to do it it's
going to be the [ __ ] notched up rag
doll standing in front of you when the
lights come up at the bar at 2 a.m. the
ti hickey you're like okay that's where
I go you don't even have to say anything
you just knock her around the head like
we're going let's
go are you a photographer like yeah I'm
famous give me some gas money I'm going
to your place
it's cool you should be able to just do
drugs you know don't you should do drugs
to yourself not other people so I've
worked at a bar and people have been
roofied you know like they give Mickey
you know they rofy them and the girls
pass out and they can [ __ ] them but they
haven't that that seems so like that's a
lot of process like you could just have
her over for turkey dinner have you been
to Thanksgiving everyone falls asleep
anyway so have a girl over for turkey
dinner you know that's why you know when
I'm at a bar I see a girl drinking I
just stick a turkey leg in her gin and
tonic and
wait I figure if you're drinking a drink
that has a turkey leg sticking out of it
you deserve whatever happens to
you any
opposition I know I want to be a drug
dealer when I was a kid my dad said
no what do you want to do I was like I
want to get a bunch of pot and divvy it
up and sell it to everyone in town and
keep all the money like no you can't do
that get a job like fine so I was a
bartender you
know my bartender Dad what's that well I
sell alcohol cigarettes and Red Bull to
everyone in town and keep none of the
money sometimes people give me a
dollar proud of you
son can't do that forever though okay
I'm going to be a
[Applause]
pharmacist hm
I don't know I figured this out uh cops
have to as part of their training they
have to get maed in the face before they
can become a police officer so they're
not willy-nilly Mason people in the face
all the time I think that's good that
makes them legit right by that same
token I think a police officer should
have to do every drug before he can
arrest you for that
drug what do you
think yeah that be better [ __ ]
[ __ ] cop pulls you over with a big
light in your face like what the hell is
the matter with you
boy
[Laughter]
nothing what the hell is the matter with
you I'm sorry I took a bunch of ecy and
I lost my friends and I just thought I
could make it home and I just went to I
think I'm fine but I I don't know I'm
sorry right on
how's that feel rubbing your head huh
how's that feel huh feel good drinking
plenty of water drink water all right
now get out of here and go tell your
friends how much I really love
them ecstasy where did he get that [ __ ]
man save my
[Laughter]
marriage drugs I mean everyone does
drugs astronauts got busted getting
drunk and going up into space space
apparently space isn't cool enough on
its own
right you ever been to
space
yeah have you ever done it
wasted here try a space beer it's from
the
future so weird to me you know like we
had 20 space bear up there
dude how'd you get home I have no no
idea we thought we were getting pulled
over it was
Mars totally spaced
dude and leave Willie
alone [ __ ] Willie got arrested this
year again Willie Nelson come on man
Willie Nelson who's the [ __ ] rookie
cop I hope he gets tons of [ __ ] for that
he busted Willie like even the dog is
like dude it's Willie come on man we all
smell Willie all the time it's like a
white noise to us leave it alone it's
Willie he doesn't hurt anybody you know
like Who's the rookie cop I goes back to
the station they're all just like Bravo
wow you caught Willie what tipped you
off oh you're going to make
detective just made him late for his
show poor
Willie leave him
alone so uh was any did anyone see me
out thereo protesting at the uh Planned
Parenthood last week um I wasn't well I
was there I wasn't protesting I was with
the protesters but I was actually in the
I was the guy in the short shorts and
the Jersey old school basketball kind of
goggles wristbands high tops playing
defense on the Christians handing out
pamphlets good luck
today it's a good handoff you had last
week that was [ __ ] awesome man [ __ ]
yeah man good handoff come on come
on what it's
abortion it's the word that's the just
don't call it abortion wacky
birth change
everything having a wacky birth today
[ __ ] can I have one be awesome I used to
have a girlfriend that worked at an
abortion clinic wo awesome free
abortions we just went nuts two three a
week didn't matter four you need four
let's go they're free woo got a tip
though got a tip
[Laughter]
um abortion is hard I mean don't get me
wrong I've had one I had a girl that I
mean I had a girl I don't know I tried
to do it myself I mean I I knocked a
girl up so I figured you know equal and
opposite reaction I knock her
down doesn't work doesn't work that way
but there abortion is a very hard thing
to do right you got to [ __ ] you know
you got to get up in the morning
generally uh you got to wave through a
sea a Christians handing out pamphlets
you know get in there fill out tons of
paperwork you take a life
um you got to get [ __ ] for two weeks
cuz you can't be [ __ ]
her that's what she said I don't know
like Chris we can't have sex for two
weeks I was like ah you
can't that's what kind of guy I am
speaking of abortion how's the show
[Applause]
going
than I don't know Michael Vick's getting
out of prison this week awesome he's
suing to get his
um payment from the Falcons his signing
bonus cuz he feels so bad for killing
all the dogs
I mean he's getting out of prison suing
for the money must feel
bad I mean he found they found over 30
dogs mutilated tortured and buried in
his backyard then when they called him
he said I made some wrong decisions and
some poor
judgments CU that's a decision we've all
had to
make H should I cut this dog's head off
and bury it in my backyard
or feed it I don't know I don't
know don't rush
me you know what cross my fingers I'm
cutting his head
off I only hope I'm making the right
decision Michael Vic what's up man you
seem distant man yo man remember when we
buried them dogs up to their neck in the
backyard ran them over with the Escalade
with the PlayStation 2 up in that
[ __ ]
yeah I'm not sure we use proper judgment
on that
man hold on brother what was we supposed
to do man not train dogs to kill each
other maybe use that millions of dollars
that you make for throwing a [ __ ]
ball around to help people of the world
[Applause]
you come correct brother thank you for
putting that perspective thank you you
okay you okay HH come on we got a lot
more dogs to kill let's
[Laughter]
go I don't
know so uh I don't know where the
Segways went but I get blown a lot um
did you
settle don't settle get
blown that's what my set's about get
your face in there okay I mean both
sexist but talking about me
tonight get blown make sure you're
getting blown was that how quiet gets
it's not exactly silence it's just like
a bunch of couples stopping holding
hands like
I don't understand what the [ __ ] deal
is just get blown I mean oh yeah oh
you're talking dirty oh yeah that sounds
sexy
right blown I get blown all the time get
blown quit being
dirty anyway I was getting blown one
time and uh I had the uh remote control
in my hand and uh it cuz love doesn't
come on Valentine's Day spontaneous and
uh I thought it'd be really funny if I
just started changing channels
um but then I realized that if I did
that I probably wouldn't get you know
blown for a while and uh that's not a
funny enough thing to do while getting
blown to Warrant not getting
blown you know then I was thinking like
what is a funny enough thing to do like
you know put a plate of nachos on her
head or something you
know make a noise maker like a new years
I don't know just yell booya when you do
it booah you know then it Dawns on me
right I'll wake her up and uh totally
worth it totally worth it uh it's been a
while but
uh we get
along uh I live here in Minneapolis a
lot of vegetarians um you know yeah they
try to get vegetarians are a vegetarian
is a person if you live like in
Minneapolis a vegetarian is a person who
does not eat meat for no other reason
than that they're dumb and
um but then there's vegans and if you
don't know what a vegan is a vegan is
like like a vegetarian's like we don't
eat meat and then a vegan's like you
don't eat meat well check this [ __ ] out
we're not going to eat
anything cuz if you're a vegan you don't
eat meat you don't eat cheese you don't
eat dairy you don't eat any animal
products all you don't even eat honey
cuz it comes from bees who I swear to
God are making it anyway it doesn't
[ __ ] matter eat the [ __ ] honey
they're just doing it just eat it like
what are you going to do you're going to
see a bee in the afterlife like what you
think of that honey I made
man I didn't eat any
brother well I was making it anyway you
probably should have eaten
it plus we're in heaven we're all eating
honey just eat the [ __ ]
honey yeah
my sister sponsors a starving child from
a third world country which I guess she
sends him 89 cents a month and then the
kid has to wear her logo or something I
don't not sure he sponsored but um she
doesn't even think it's funny that she
keeps his picture on the
[Music]
refrigerator dear Pablo my kids think of
you every time they can't decide what to
eat here's 89 [ __ ] cents
oh no that's a lot of money in invero
Heights
Minnesota love Chris's sister you know
it's I mean that kid Pablo is he's vegan
too actually but in his language it's
pronounced starving
um dear Pablo I am a vegan from America
Daddy what is a vegan they're from
America they have food but they don't
eat their food that's [ __ ] up I know I
want their food me too man want some
[ __ ]
food daddy will the vegan send us the
food nope they'd rather throw away a
dead chicken than send it to you talk to
Peter about that I don't know
they that's [ __ ] up I
know Daddy are the vegans the
Taliban
yes in a way it's weird I don't know we
can talk about it over dinner there is
dinner no
[Music]
Pablo we do this one every
night Daddy what is this accent we have
what accent okay never mind
uh how long does this go sometimes too
long
know I just think I think eating meat
gives you a sense of humor what do you
think because I've worked at a
vegetarian restaurant right and uh
Joanne did not think I was funny and I
should stop using her real name because
check this story out
um this girl right real hippie like to
eat salsa with her
fingers uh you know she like this chick
she's like well I got pregnant
accidentally she volunteered that
information I was like okay well that
sucks do you mind asking me how did that
happen she's like well we don't like to
use condoms fair
enough but uh I don't mean to go bowling
at the obvious Lanes but
uh why don't you pull
out that would ruin the moment
Chris wow are we from different
planets that is the
moment booah you
know am I from a different planet I
don't know sometimes I think I am
because later that day in the kitchen
these girls are telling a story about
like she's the girl said it like three
times she's like who five times even she
didn't even know who doesn't know this
one you know she's like my husband
didn't want me to toss his salad you I
said you want me to toss your own salad
you want to toss your salad I don't
think he remembers how to toss salad
being so
want I was like
[Laughter]
[Applause]
so I said I said I was like maybe he's
not tossing
yours everyone looks at me she's like
well who else would be cooking for him
oh my God what am I from planet Earth or
am I what that's
funny I was like I wanted I thought a
guy with a rusty trombone for sale was
going to walk in the room Rusty
trombones for sale who' like a rusty
trombo I'd love one oh what's your name
Carl hot in here isn't it it is hot Carl
it
is this is my boy Sanchez he's just
playing in the dirt what a dirty little
Sanchez he oh got something right here
son by the way uh where you from Carl
Cleveland oo steamy down there isn't it
it's a bit steamy down in Cleveland what
do you do down in Cleveland I go
motorboating I go motorboating down in
Cleveland there's a sports caster from
this town named Randy shaver and nobody
bats a [ __ ]
eye it's me is it [ __ ] here's Randy
shaver with
sports I am randy shaver with sports
sports come on man they had a vegetarian
sloppy joe on that menu it was called a
sloppy Jane that was in print [ __ ] it
I'm the dick I'm the dick got it got
it how could how could I not how's your
sloppy Jane Chris like don't say it dude
you got to work with these people you
remember what happened at the last job
delicious sloppy seconds please I had to
I had
to I like you know metal you know it's
just like there's that everywhere you go
if you just have the radio in your car
you're [ __ ] man 93X rocks dude and
anywhere you go like here it's 93X rocks
it's the weasel Nick and Josh 93X rocks
dude totally rocks rocks
now and it's been a while since I could
hold my head
up you know it's just it's not even like
wimpy but it's just like it's weird
culture of [ __ ] like spray tan and
eyebrow rings and you know like you know
frosted tips and dudes are like
infliction shirts just like a dude this
dude's got so much inner pain it's all
they think about is inner
pain oh dude that guy's got to have like
four eyebrow rings that guy's crazy man
like that's what the kids are rebelling
to right now ooh
whatever dad you don't even why your
life I'm out of
here you don't know nothing
about I'm going here old man something
you don't know
about I'm
gone I'm going to be way too tan for
March you'll
see and you go anywhere they're all the
same because they're all owned by Disney
these are not horns these are Mickey's
ears now
you go to out out of town it's the 94x
with ferret James and Rick you know it's
the same thing go to Lacrosse it's true
95x with a fish check it out it's true I
worked with them
um it just sucks it's you know 93X cuz
it's extreme you know like when's that
going to end what does you know why was
the guy you know rock climbing on that
thing with do do the do why does
Mountain Dew have to do with rock
climbing or X Games or you know like
extreme everything's they don't even put
the e in anymore it's just X you know
come out to the X Games everything's X
like Mountain Dew and Red Bull and
Gatorade like something was being like
advertised in my house and the TV in the
other room I heard it is like fully
loaded and extreme like what now you
know I go in the other room they're
advertising
soup Campbell's Chunky as a matter of
fact Donovan's mom was on the [ __ ]
commercial like what is soups not
extreme soups would you eat when you're
see
and unless you're skateboarding with a
really hot bowl of soup and a new shirt
right like whoa you know might get some
on my shirt it's kind of extreme right
maybe throw the soup off a bridge and
bungee jump after it and wow it's
extreme soup try to wrap your face
around right you know but pour the soup
in a loaded shotgun and just try to pour
it in your mouth who and see what happen
have donovic with Na's mom just shoot it
in your face and like oh my God he blew
Campbell's Chunky out of the back of his
head
radical oh my God it's like suicide bomb
your
hunger soap get it in you get it [ __ ]
in
you everything Mountain Dew Red Bull
Gatorade it's like rape your thirst just
rape it pin it down and [ __ ] it and
leave it crying in the shower with its
clothes on and mascara running down its
face shaving its head in the mirror like
jod Foster of the movie oh God I should
have never [ __ ] with this thirst it's
so [ __ ] extreme oh my God yeah just
slay your thirst throat and [ __ ] the
wound man
yeah be it in your backyard and do it
like Ed G and [ __ ] put in boxes all
over your house make a belt and a
lampshade out of your [ __ ] thirst
[ __ ] do it your thirst [ __ ] thirst
man just find your thirst in a parking
lot knock it out and Bam make a dress
out of its skin and fing [ __ ] the pile
of Flesh it left why you raping yourself
why you raping yourself yeah yeah bite
holes out of its back you [ __ ] your I
mean it's just soup that's all I'm say
there a
[Applause]
soup oh Ren
[Music]
[Applause]
Ren thanks everyone for coming out man
seriously um
[Applause]
I think they can edit something out of
this uh I'm going to a lot of um
comedians would tell you about how
[ __ ] up TV has gotten not me I think
TV's gotten all the better ever since a
couple years ago they had that show the
swan on and that's where I thought we
were yeah that was that show where they
had it was a show about um it was a
makeover show Extreme Makeover the show
though what they did was they took um
like surgery and stuff with women they
took two women who weren't good
enough they showed them to you and uh
Fox had this dream team of like plastic
surgeons for her face dentist for her
teeth therapist even for her ugly mind
right they had everything like right and
the game was this was the game for three
months these women weren't allowed to
see themselves in a mirror their friends
and family weren't allowed to see them
they and and then they would just hack
away at these Brads you know they'd even
work out a little and um like you know
they just want to look totally different
and then like just surgery and then
after the 3 months was up they were
revealed live on camera boom in front of
their families in the mirror for the
first time as this new like hot Franken
Fox she looked nothing like she used to
she just come out like [ __ ]
me you
know they look really hot before they
melted or like they had a kid and then
the guy was like what the [ __ ] is this
thing she's like it used to be ugly and
I thought it was a beautiful show you
know it's
like good for you you know I always knew
you were a beautiful deep deep deep deep
deep deep down inside all it took to to
bring out your beauty was a modest team
of surgeons and dentists doctors
therapists knives Forks cork screws get
rid of those wrinkle lines shave that
unibrow little eye lift a cheek lift a
nose lift a nose job a boob job boob
lift little lipos suction suck the fat
out of your ass stuff it in your chin
burn the warts off your face knock the
teeth out of your head Fick the bugs off
you shave your back sew up that blown
out fish pocket looks like [ __ ]
drapes made of bacon so I can look at
you for two [ __ ] seconds without
vomiting soft poop out you look good
baby that's all I meant to say that's
all I meant to say you look so good now
that you look nothing like the way God
Made You and uh you know it's a
beautiful show the best part about that
show too is there's two contestants
every show and then uh uh but at the end
of the show only one of them is uh voted
uh to be in the swan beauty pageant
that's going to be held at the end of
the season so after all that one of them
still isn't good
enough throwing in the did all we could
pile we like this one over backroll we
like this one over
back God Bless America
hey folks I've been Chris and this has
been the best that I could do thank you
very much good
night keep it coming forismatic
[Applause]
in
in in
[Applause]