you know the best part of being you know
a hockey mom is that it's just all about
the kids hockey hockey hockey it's all
we do my name is Connie Dugan and this
is my husband Donnie Dugan we're just so
happy we got uh Cody and donor they're
such good kids and they're going to go
off and be hockey Superstars I just love
everything about those kids Connor's had
a little setback he got
uh he got H in the head with his dick
and uh it was his own his own stick
Connor let's go we got to stop at
Rainbow to get hot dogs and orange
drink
God con think she miss the
train she's out
back it's a lifestyle it's a privilege
it's an honor
this if they want to do hockey I want to
take them to do hockey that's what this
is about
[Music]