[Music]
you know hockey is a gift but it's not
it's not free so you got to pay for it
somehow and that's why you fund
ra you got to believe in what you sell
and you are what you sell you know it's
a cheddar bacon almond log and if you
don't like that here's a a Cajun style
snack basket and that comes with the
three zesty uh pretzel dips and each
come in like a cozy country Croc we just
bought frozen pizzas from deborn did
however on
Tanner oh well they do have the Gopher
Valley Farms cold pack combo that has
the the garlic and herb the horseradish
and the white cheddar cheese
spreads is it is it real cheese oh yeah
it says cold pack spreadable cheese food
so that's
that's real cheese I mean that's they're
not going to lie on
that it's goer Valley you know it's not
like they're some Fly by Night cheese
spread operation they're going to have a
real cheese in their cheese spread I'm
so sorry I think we're going to have to
pass Rhonda Wagner told me that she's
been selling a lot of the uh it's like
the hot cocoa baskets and with the
little gifts and stuff hey who is this
hey how are you hey what are you guys
doing we're just doing some
fundraising well I'm uh I'm Connie Dugan
yeah I know who you are Connie are you
are you Debbie yep okay well you know we
do a lot of fundraising in this
neighborhood kind of we have a lot of
friends this is where we do a lot of our
fundraising oh
great yeah so what are you selling
selling uh old Wisconsin frozen
pizzas the 100% real mozzarella
cheese Dam it as far as I'm concerned
Debbie borad Halverson can munch on my
vacuum packed jalapeno horseradish
cheddar beef log cuz it's not about
money at this point it's about respect
[Music]