[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast the year is 1969 we think the
album is hello seal it's me the artist
is Betty Walker my guest is Jackie C
hello I enjoy the small we think yeah
because Cliff nesteroff who wrote a book
that I haven't read about the history of
Comedy um did you read it no yeah there
you go I need to get it it's the way to
go it's the way to go I say uh cuz uh we
hear about it and it'll be fine
absolutely we're living in the moment I
he doesn't need my help Mel Brooks loved
it like he got you know he got all the
praise of the good people right yeah so
it's probably a very good book the thing
is is people whenever anybody writes a
book that's supposedly like the history
of Comedy you're
like how about the of some comedy right
and that's inevitable and it's
inevitable and it's it's there's no
there's no way to to make it it be
everything to everybody so um I wanted
it to have more than one line about
Carol brunett but that's me you know uh
so who knows and so I picked uh an album
off of your list yes because I am Jackie
K and I never listened to stand-up
comedy um never did as a child that's
been established the only album I ever
bought we did it last time yes Lenny
Bruce yeah that was a and that was a fun
album to talk about too um yeah cuz it
was his best album we went with in my
opinion cuz I I bought a bunch of other
ones and threw them away okay I just
kept the one and then when I got rid of
my record player I got rid of that album
as well for the for the love of God I'm
not I'm not a I'm not a hoarder by any
stretch of the imagination me neither
wait a minute we are surrounded by items
know you're
I have no
idea yeah and this is one of them this
is one of those that I just told you I
bought in cazoo Michigan because I was
there for a wedding and of course I went
to a record shop of course you did hello
seal it's me Betty Walker now Cliff
nesteroff said that this came out in '
69 yes it is essentially her on the
phone we're just listening to her talk
to supposedly her friend seal MH and
that's the whole bit that's the shtick
yep for 45 minutes for 40 45 minutes now
now who does that sound like Mr Bob
newart course sure I thought I was going
to be able to Hannibal burus Bob newart
and huge reveal that he stole a Zach
from Betty Walker but nope that is not
happening and um because this came out
in 69 and his came out in ' 61 MH this
is a
premise that I don't approve of you
don't approve I do not approve of half
of a phone call being your
stick uh you you can you can in my it's
not for me right right this was pretty
funny sure a pretty funny album Bob
newart very funny guy yeah
um just tell The Joke Man uh I
don't I don't I don't mean to get all
lety Bruce in your head in your face but
uh Mor Saul I he brought the newspaper
up sure guess what you why don't you
read the newspaper write some jokes
about it leave the newspaper back at
your table
so your thought is Betty Betty Betty's
literally phoning it in oh my gosh Betty
and Bob both phoning it in but and this
thing like literally literally or I
don't I've never use that word correctly
hi
guys are you listening uh so this is
actually a very funny album but it's
it's kind of
um it's sticky and it very much
some of it doesn't it doesn't you know
what I was going to say it doesn't hold
up but it actually does for exactly what
it is it's good for exactly what it is
yeah but being like one note is kind of
difficult for you is that the thing yeah
it's 40 minutes of one note and this
woman Betty Walker if she is portraying
herself you're like you're a mess lady
and but I did watch Rod Sterling had a
um uh a game show you sent this to me I
had no idea that exist uhhuh and then he
redid it with a well somebody else redid
it as a host in um in 74 okay and she
worked on both of them and it looked
like a golden opportunity to probably
make 250 cash right right right hardcore
uh sort of like the at midnight of of
our current uh Administration you know
it's a great way to make a grand and uh
and the youth are watching it yep so
maybe it'll drive some people to a show
sure and and she's a comic so
but I think she mostly like I think it
was sort of like Charles Nelson Riley in
the end where she was just doing that
and then maybe some standup but not like
she wasn't really acting she only acted
I think in the 50s a little bit in the
interesting see that's interesting to me
this is yeah clearly honestly if we'
have looked at the cover I guess we
probably could have guessed 69 pretty
easily it looks pretty groovy I mean
maybe yeah
maybe she's got a Paisley shirt on God I
want it to be 59 yeah I understand
believe me I just it's not that I don't
like Bob new but how great would it be
if we had a huge reveal mhm this came
out two years before nope nope it did
not well Shelley burman's convinced that
Bob newart stole it or was convinced at
one point that he stole his act but then
again uh what's his name uh George
Jessel was doing that act in the 20s and
30s so but who's to say there wasn't a
woman doing it it would be interesting
to know if there are other women who did
the phone bit how great would it be if
someone was doing a telegraph thing in
the 1860s
seal hello seal yeah no I'm just calling
to tell you that can I borrow some money
anyway and no is it okay and uh so and
some of the tropes are are just you know
she's essentially a housewife right yeah
and that's she's portraying a housewife
whose husband controls all the money and
she is hiding debt she's hiding uh
shitty uh life choices she doesn't have
any money yeah and so Mr tupperman uh
who's a first name I've forgotten yeah
me too and maybe Howard uh but whatever
her husband um who I think at one point
she refers to as Mr tupperman does feels
romantic and
um but he's um he's he's all the things
that it's sort of a I mean it's a little
it's it's a little hacky but it's only
hacky because it been done sure it's
been done so much since then mhm and it
wasn't they were some of some of the
lines were actually quite funny and
um I wish I would have taken notes yeah
no I wish I'd done the same thing but I
I had the same exact feeling although it
feels like 1969 feels like the last time
you could have done it and I don't know
why she would still be you know like
even The Brady Bunch was like was out of
step with what Middle America was and
this just seems so already dat women's
Li yeah yeah it feels very dated
remember um women couldn't have their
own credit cards until
74 and so I mean there was like and I
read this book I read this amazing weird
book about romance novels because I
inadvertently admitted during a uh
probably I I think my last album hor
Crux that I read romance novels and
since then I you um you're never alone
you guys so people are constantly
handing me and uh which by the way you
can't buy other people's porn so stop
handing me romance weird I've even
gotten Maria banford to stop buying them
cuz she'll go to like a Walgreens or
something and she's like what about this
one look at his chest and you're like
stop buying them for me and um but the
um but I did get this non-fiction book
called
um uh dangerous books for girls MH and
it was about the history of romance
novels and it was that's interesting
lightly researched it felt a little bit
like a romance novel in the fact that it
was a lightly historical romance the
history pretty light yeah
um by Maya Rodell rodale whatever her
name is anyway but one of the things she
pointed out was that the reason romance
novels were sold in grocery stores is
because women could buy them using the
grocery budget interesting and so their
fellas their husbands didn't know they
were like oh there's an extra two three
bucks on the grocery list well it's a
romance novel that's fascinating yeah it
was kind of fascinating holy [ __ ] the
just a subterfuge to go through just to
feel human to get a book written by a
woman for a women for women about women
and even if it's some weird rape fantasy
where you're like any fantasy that makes
me not make meatloaf on a Wednesday
night you know and because I remember
when I first started reading them some
of them were really old at the library
and it was just one horrible he you know
Luke and Laura from General Hospital
where he rapes her and she falls in love
with them and then you're like that
seems wildly unlikely yep and uh but you
do whatever you got to do lady you need
to get laid uh you need to check out
okay it's on between you and your God oh
my God the fact that that art existed I
think the assumption is that we're on a
weird track right now but like the
assumption is always that those these
power fantasies are more for men but the
fact that they were made for women and
that it and they sold like hoty
yeah it's so but you you again if you
have no other choices what are you going
to right right it was it was sort of the
definition of those power fantasies were
the power fantasies and so women are
like all right well that's the fantasy
yeah yeah maybe in the end he falls for
her anyway right it's not that he wants
to just beat her up and rape her he also
he wants to beat her up and rape her but
then get this he also wants to shower
her with diamonds and take her out to
dinner weird you guys totally weird I
know makes you want to weep but um so
this I mean so this lady in 69 yeah I
think and plus she was remember I think
she was probably 35 years old in 1974 MH
so she wasn't like a 16-year-old in 1969
sure bringing it right um but I will say
but it's okay so perfect couple mhm do
you remember that one uh if you remind
me what it is I'm sure I will I can't I
can't remind you Warren's flu I remember
they really really run in together the
one I remember specifically is the the
bank and the horse those are the two I
remember oh the horse yeah the horse was
actually really funny I thought so
because it was a the call from the bank
mhm and I think the horse thing was at
the end of the of the bank thing cuz she
wanted to borrow the money because she
lost the money um it was well we bought
a horse and you're like well the kasta
group went and looked at the horse and
uh you're like well you know and uh and
what's the horse's name so I was the
only one with the checkbook that's the
check I issued in
Pennsylvania the name of the
horse listen sale let me come
over and make out the check for 400 just
in case I forgot to add in a few other
huh the name of the horse why is the
name of the horse important to you sale
listen let me huh if I tell you the name
of the horse swear you're still going to
give me the
money the name of the
horse the name of the
horse is Seal's
mouth I told you you were de man no it's
not my fault Tony Rosen said we should
name it that she said girls if this
horse could ever run as fast as seal
talks we got to win
so hello seal SE Seal's mouth which run
it runs like Seal's mouth right so it's
a fast running horse that's what and and
then seal hangs up on her right spoiler
alert you guys uh from this album 37
years ago oh boy yeah yeah uh so what
tracks do you remember that I'm
completely forgetting you you said you
remembered another one we like 47 mil
years by the way so um
like the ones that yeah guess who's
getting married I Warren's flu was was
one I did not like because it was just
about how he had the flu and how he
didn't she didn't like him right and it
was irritating so um like I
like I I uh if I remember correctly 4:00
in the morning was pretty good MH
um yeah I don't know they were um
the what there was social commentary in
it obviously but it was very much
um it was it was I mean the the things
that stuck with me is that she didn't
have her own money and she had to hide
this money business and uh she wasn't
very good at it and then what there was
another
one it
was it's not helpful this is not helpful
at all wish I had listened to it right
but unfortunately I listened to it a
couple of days ago yeah yeah yeah no but
I mean that's that's enough that it
stood out to me is it do you think it's
better that there seems to be a clearly
it's not a romantic relationship left at
all between her and her husband is it is
is it funnier that that's like super
true or would it been have been more of
a a better album to you if if they there
was a little hint of like sweet old
American love between them would have
been awesome if if this album had turned
into how much she and and I've talked
about this a couple of times on
different podcasts about how it's so
much work to write negative comedy and
it can be done very well obviously right
um there's some seriously grumpy Comics
who are super broken that write some
hilarious comedy but for me I like the
idea of being happy and doing the work
to write jokes about that happiness
that's work too yeah but then get this
if you're negative you live this
horrible negative life you write these
great jokes about your horrible negative
life and then you relive it every time
you tell that damn joke I would rather
be happy do the hard work of writing
jokes about being happy and then get to
relive that happiness every time I do
that joke it's just as much work in my
opinion but I get to be happy yeah so um
that would have been amazing if Betty
Walker um but I I don't know that there
were any like and nobody ever did jokes
about how much they love their husbands
and wife of course of course did Phyllis
Diller I remember Fang have you heard
any of the Fang jokes yes I have and
they were all pretty grumpy right yeah
yeah yeah yeah actually there's a
project online it's I think it's still
going through the Smithsonian yeah
through Smithsonian her joke files being
transcribed and I went through and I
transcribed a few of them and you can
correct other people's transcriptions
like just as [ __ ] shitload Wikipedia
kind of thing basically basically but
like basically you pull up a scan of a
card with one of her jokes on it you
type on the type in the date type the
subject matter and then you know
whatever the shitty joke was and I say
shitty just like you know they're just
dumb they're great though Phil s's
fantastic but like just a dumb joke that
it was it's so weird when people keep it
like that you know like Joan Rivers had
those filing cabins yeah and
um D fan used to talk about uh but uh
files that he had online and Eliza
slesinger has some sort of of uh Excel
document and um I have Stacks and stacks
of of notebooks sure I've kept all my
notebooks yeah for why we don't know I
think Mark Maron said it best when he
said I picture when I'm dead everyone
just going oh my god let's read all this
and nobody's going to read it they're
just they're going to light it on fire
well yeah yeah that's exactly right yeah
yeah and so I remember the first time I
ever saw Maria throw bford friend of
mine right so we've been doing stand up
together since '92 993 and um the first
time I ever saw her throw a notebook out
was probably seven or eight years ago
and I was like wait what are you doing
she said I'm done with the notebook I'm
throwing it away and I was
like oh my I I could keep them and sell
them on eBay and she was like watch this
and she threw it away in front of me and
I was like okay your notebook you get to
do whatever you want that's going to
that is going to be a piece of legend
that is going to be one of those things
that people are not going to believe in
30 years uh because yeah it's it's it's
yeah that's I I I it's disappointing cuz
you're like cuz I want to see the
Doodles I want to see the weird like
like magazine articles she cuz she is
always counting Out magazine articles
and gluing them into her notebook you're
like what's happening in this notebook
because my notebook is all just it's
just writing just me scribbling so wow
well at the end of The Comedy is so
different now from let's take let's take
you and then let's take Phyllis Diller
Phyllis Diller needed a stack cuz I
think I I'm assuming it's just like oh
maybe there's some [ __ ] I can refer to
go pull all the stuff I got about
weddings I got to go do a thing right
right I mean what if you so she's doing
she's doing events right and she's
separated them in these card cataloges
by topic right is that what's happening
they are they're they're almost
exclusively Topic at Le they're they're
by date and then I assume they're by
topic first but yeah like it's like
celebrities is the topic and then
celebrities uh this obscure celebrity
whose name I've never [ __ ] heard and
I typed up 10 jokes about this person uh
so it's it's so weird to but I mean have
you done corporate gigs in there I've
done some corporates and I'm not
particularly good at them mostly because
I don't like them yeah I bet um
they're I mean it's
it's the best people who do corporates
write to the corporation sure they write
to the business uh they write jokes to
to that topic mhm um the boss the the
the work
MH the city that they're in you know and
I do none of that I'm like do you want
to see my ACT okay I will come and
perform it for you wow and then you will
pay me and that is something that is not
a
corporate I'm I'm shocked that anybody
would let you do I like I didn't know
that that it ever went that way I always
assumed it had to be customized to the
oh no no no it's mostly yeah it's mostly
just normal they just want to
fascinating okay and the only the only
thing like when I do corporates you know
they'll say a couple of things about
corporates is uh first of all um you
should always get paid depending on the
amount of credits you have a buck per
person attending mhm okay and if you
have credits five bucks per person
attending okay and if it's 200 people uh
you should get a lot of money yeah and
um so like there was a guy uh several
years ago who and ended up doing like
the the LA County Sheriff's luncheon MH
that they hired but didn't pay and then
he ended up doing some jokes that had
the n-word in them and swearing a lot
and it was a luncheon for cops and uh
there was a big expose about it and they
were like look at this horrible thing
that happened well was because they
didn't pay them yeah if you're paying a
comic in lunch they're going to do their
set for themselves of course but if you
pay me $3,000 uhhuh I my brain's
attached to my mouth of course I won't
and all you got to do is tell me don't
swear yep try not to do your weird
abortion chunk I don't have a weird
abortion chunk but if I did um you could
tell me not to do it cuz you were paying
me enough money to tell me what to do
and what not to do CU standup comedy is
so I mean in general it's super Loosey
Goosey you do whatever you want right
you write the jokes that you write and
you tell the jokes that you want to tell
right and when it when it comes to a
corporate or um
colleges they because they supposedly
pay better MH they get to tell you what
you what you can and cannot do makes
sense and some clubs are actually like
that too where you'll walk in and
they're like hey um keep it together and
uh and you're like fair enough you've
hired me this is the this is the club I
want to work so and and yeah I mean the
weirdest thing I I I auditioned for a
cruise ship one time and they didn't
like my outfit and he's like hey I'm a
dressy Bessie I can take this outfit off
put on whatever outfit you want right
did you want me to work your cruise they
did not it turns out cuz they didn't get
back to me about that I didn't even say
I was a dressy Bessie I tried to keep it
polite I said well obviously I can wear
whatever you want me to wear you me to
wear a ball gown and do standup comedy
and that's that's interesting because
she is wearing I think a dress in this
thing is yeah kind of it certainly looks
yeah it's a [ __ ] Paisley Crazy Pink
PA number that is uh yeah that is a
polyester nightmare which is not my
phrase I don't remember where I got it
from but she yeah it's a little scary
but she could something like this it
couldn't work now right there's no way I
think it could do I mean when you think
about um some of the comedy that comes
out there's there's a lot of there's a
lot of um themed comedy now okay because
we have like this the the the internet
creates these Niche groups you know true
and it's so great for dorks right it's
like oh I want to talk to everybody who
builds uh Star Wars Lego right those are
the people there's a hundred people in
the world or there's 3,000 and then you
all go to Vienna in July you've saved up
and you meet in a in a in a in a in a
Hampton Inn in in Vienna and you have
the time of your lives because you met
over the internet and everyone someone
comes from South Korea
people are from Australia people are
from Indiana and and and and it's
beautiful so there are people who want
like sort of squeaky clean Christian
Comedy sure sure grumpy Christian Comedy
I mean there's different ways of because
there are plenty of comics who are
Christians who are not they don't have
mean jesuses right they're just they're
just telling jokes and uh I I knew a guy
who was like he got asked to do this
Christian comedy thing and he was like
yeah I'm a Christian but I don't think I
can do your thing because your thing is
weird he's like I I don't know what kind
of Christian you need me to be right
right right and he's like I'm just a
normal hey I hope it all works out for
you kind of Christian you know and
um I don't care about other people's
religion I just I just I just want to do
my thing and uh it's very American old
school American and but I so I think
that there are probably
people I know that there are like what
do you think maybe the promisekeepers
maybe those guys would love a housewife
comedian yeah who would just talk about
real stereotypical housewifey kind of
stuff I guess so yeah I get I mean I I
mean I like that there's I like her
attitude a lot I like her I mean there
there's a modern version of this this is
a more positive spinoff there's a modern
version of
this that now granted I have not seen
this woman's the woman I'm about to say
her long set in probably seven or eight
years but Debbie Gutierrez is uh Latino
mommy comedy MH is essentially what she
called it she says yeah I pretty much do
Latino mommy comedy okay and Latino
mommy comedy is sort of this talking
about her kids talking about her husband
talking about uh her friends uh Debbie
Gutierrez just tells the joke she's not
on the phone which I I I don't know that
the phone thing would ever go you see
that's what I'm wondering that was I
guess that's my is because it's such a
like a it would work as a sketch in a
thing you could do that as a sketch you
could totally maybe a web series yeah
absolutely that I want to do a web
series of Beyonce's weird white ant yeah
just checking in checking in on with
Jackie Cas and Beyonce's weird white ant
I love that I love that I don't know how
to write it though because I don't know
anything about Beyonce right right hello
hello s oh am I glad I got you s have I
got something to tell you do you
remember that big wedding I went to you
remember I told you beautiful wedding
perfect couple the perfect couple are
going to be an
old yeah no wait a minute you will not
believe this story seal dear they had a
beautiful wedding there was no fights
the honeymoon no fights even the two
mothers agreed where they should
go they came home from the
honeymoon they both went to the little
love nest wait a minute
they got up in the morning you
hear he went to work she went to work
and from
work he went to his mother's house for
supper no he forgot he was
married well I mean honestly like even
Bob newart I saw him live he doesn't he
did one phone bit as a nod like bit of
nostalgia for everybody oh there you go
yeah and then he did the rest of his act
to the people yeah mostly Street Jokes
which is the weirdest thing in the world
Bob newart does Street jokes
now I'm not kidding I got some quiet
time now in my head yep yep it's very
strange it's unusual I don't even know
where to go with it I don't know where
go there's nowhere to go with that
except for stop doing that uh how about
it was I saw um Jack klugman's oneman
show what what yeah which I would
recommend I mean he's dead now but um it
was amazing yeah I would prefer to see
Bob new hard's oneman show I would
prefer Bob newart to just tell stories
about how great uh his life has been or
how weird it has been and how bad it
there there were bits of that in there
for sure and they were easily my
favorite parts right especially when the
I don't know if I'm supposed to say this
on microphone when especially when the
street jokes got a little more colorful
we'll just say colorful um the yeah when
he's talking about his life great stuff
uh turns out Bob new racist or do you
let's say racially insensitive I won't
say racist because it's not like I hate
nword you know but it's like Street
jokes straight up Street jokes some of
which have a racial tinge to them yes
I'm giving an old white man a break and
I probably shouldn't be I really but
he's still not Bill Cosby and that's a
horrible low standard to have but Bill
Cosby I think about Bill I've seen Bill
Cosby twice have you seen have you ever
seen Bill Cosby okay this about six
years ago it was before the big sure and
um the big reveal on Bill cos big reveal
the big reveal and um so I saw once then
a year and a half later I saw him again
okay and he had an entirely new hour 15
except one joke he did a GPS joke both
times okay and the GPS joke the first
time I saw it was the was the first GPS
joke I had heard okay so I it was great
and he's a great comic he genuinely is
of course and
um and I think about him I think about
him almost every week I think about Bill
Cosby cuz he doesn't get to go up
anymore but he's a comic so you know
he's still writing and I'm wondering
what jokes is he writing besides my wife
doesn't talk to me right whatever and uh
but you wonder what because I remember
he did very much Slice of Life he still
writing kind of guy not like not like
what you're saying Bill Bob newart ising
where he's just he's telling stories
about what it's like to be super famous
yeah uh not talking about getting laid
or raping people uh but but we like
going out to dinner with his family sure
and it's his birthday and his wife is
like well bring your wallet he said I
should I bring my wallet she's like are
we going out to dinner and he's like
yeah but it's my birthday it's nobody
buying and it's a very it was a very
funny joke yeah um but I think about him
and I think about
um how great that is and um that's what
I want Bob newart to do sure and also
Jay Leno I saw Jay Leno probably a year
ago maybe last okay maybe more whatever
uh he did 15 minutes and about five or
six of it were those monologue jokes
okay and it was a lot and I was just
like no there he is there's those
monologue jokes who cares and then but
then the other nine minutes were these
fascinating sort of Slice of Life kind
of stuff I bet about his life and I was
like oh please tell me more about that
yeah and they had punchlines they were
they were set up you know I always
thought he was a funny dude as a standup
whenever I saw him on TV I just hated
him as a host of The Tonight Show
definitively he was one of the best
stand-ups of the 80s yeah right and just
I mean he had it was observational but
it was personal it was interesting it
was smart it was silly it had all the
good things going for he got great
[ __ ] Personality yeah except for when
it comes to business apparently you know
like everything else he [ __ ] great on
stage yeah so um so I want I I would
love to see more of that you know so I
think that and she really did but Walker
she was clearly successful because of
her personality because of she was super
likable and like you watch her on that
game show and you could tell that all
the guys like her you know she's very
much one of the guys and
um the material isn't bad the jokes are
fine they're they're just jokes about
weird husbande kind of and that have
been covered yeah of and are being
covered to this day you know people are
still talking about you know uh [ __ ]
man what are you going to
do it's uh you know my wife is does this
or I don't like my boyfriend or he's uh
I I hate my wife I hate my girlfriend
and you and I always whenever I hear
that premise I'm like please break up
please stop hanging out with that person
right uh you're actually hurting my
feelings uh cuz uh there's someone that
will love them if you [ __ ] let them
go and if your wife is mean to you or if
your boyfriend is mean to you oh my god
I heard some weird joke the other night
at a at a just a showcasing show here in
LA and it was this woman talking about
her uh fiance MH and she said um she did
this stuff about knew her stuff about
how she was engaged and then she did
this older she what was clearly an older
joke about her boyfriend and she said
well I suppose I should tell
that's my fiance and it was about how um
he had asked if he could poop on her and
I was like oh my God don't marry that
guy uhuh uh that guy has uh serious
control issues and wants to poop on you
and uh and um you're fetish you want to
get pooped on and but she didn't want to
get pooped on yeah right like I mean if
they were both into it 100% you got to
have the two same Lego pieces to go yeah
right you have to be a person that
literally wants to be [ __ ] upon yep with
a guy that wants to [ __ ] on his
girlfriend and you're like I hate both
of you and neither of you are invited
over for the barbecue um but because I
you both would make me sad at my house
oh that's so disturbing so it's super
disturbing but comedy is so personal now
that's probably me oh but comedy is so
personal now
MH
that where you have to go to make it
more
interesting because we can't do these
jokes at Betty Walker was doing right we
have to go down this weird Rabbit Hole I
mean Louis CK is a perfect example right
that guy talk about unwanted thought
Centrum that guy will address the
creepiest thoughts that he has but
there's no one I don't
know I kind of love Louis CK and the
fact that
he's his standup he has more empathy
sure like he he has a way of describing
somebody's bad decisions own bad
decisions and just sort of revealing in
himself these sort of not great parts of
his
personality and how he's kind of working
on it or how he's not working on it and
that is also very funny though a little
more disappointing because you'd like
him to work on it did you see that SNL
uh set the other night I did not I've
there's too many don't worry so he did
this bit about um you know he he
previously he has done sort of white
privilege kind of jokes right and now he
is not just White Privilege but like the
1% white privileged guy right and so
he's in this situation where he's in
let's say a Four Seasons or Ritz and he
call and he's called down because his
laundry is supposed to be 24 hours as he
calls down and he's talking to this
woman and he talks about how he's
clearly a white man and she isn't and so
he should be getting better service and
you're like that is a disaster of a
premise you are a dick and he's like
yeah it's a glimpse into who I might
really be sometimes it isn't okay and
it's a wonderful kind of angle on it
absolutely yeah but and it turns out of
course that he has forgotten to give
them his laundry and but and and the
best part of the joke is actually how he
talks about how you can complain at a
Ritz Carlton but 15 years ago 20 years
ago when he was on the road mhm you're
not going to complain at a motel not
even a super eight just called Motel who
are you going to call hey there's
cigarette Burns in the in the in the in
the in the uh sheet and you're like yeah
what do you want me to do about it
you're paying $25 a night thanks exactly
what are you right and so he he would
never complain in those situations but
now because he's in this expectations
are so much higher yeah but at the end
of the joke what I didn't like and he
doesn't can't possibly care but what I
would like is sort of not a solution
MH because in this case the admission
was yeah I'm kind of a dick M and you're
like oh I going to want you to work on
that and uh CU I have this new bit that
doesn't have an end either right you
know and the end is is the premise is
that I always
thought that
I sometimes I think to myself if I die
an [ __ ] but I was right that'll be
fine oh believe me seal if you could
only have hold on one second what did
you just say
Warren what do you mean by that
waren what do you mean I'm lucky that I
don't want to wear minis
scope hold on S Mr Superman don't ever
tell me that if I ever wore one I Would
Walk
Alone hold on M hold on Mr tman can I
tell you something and I want you to
know this now and forever that for as
long as I'm married to you whether I'm
Pro or anti- Min spur I'll never shut up
sail I'll never shut up
sail I will never will you shut up and
stop crying
S I will never walk
alone I'll kill myself I just woke up my
bird and nobody why is that okay
I mean there's nothing worse quite
honestly for me than what I'm right that
self-righteousness manifests itself in
the
grumpiest just a raging jackass you
don't want to be around me and if I'm
right
Jesus I was at the grocery and I've told
this I don't know I did it on my own
podcast the Dork Forest but um I was at
the grocery store a month ago we're
living in different times MH I'm walking
out of the the grocery store there's an
old man 80 I push an old man in this
story it isn't okay 80-year-old dude not
crazy not homeless khakis belt polo
shirt loaf of French bread he's walking
in front of me out of this thing
80-year-old white guy and he starts
yelling at the rent a cop and he says
the n-word and he calls him a Haitian
and he tells him he screws monkeys and
that's why there's a and it goes on like
that for 40 50 seconds and 10 years ago
I probably would have just looked at the
red deop and gone the hell's it matter
with that guy yeah yeah and I might have
yelled something at the guy but that
would have been it but those days are
done and Jackie wants to be a white lady
meat Shield or I can't stop myself right
except for that I have to stop myself
because I want to be of some use sure
and me getting in the face of an
80-year-old man isn't necessarily the
best use of my my my life so I get in
his face and I'm yelling at him and the
only good thing I yelled at him and I
was like is there anything you wanted to
say about women to a middle-aged white
lady and uh and he was like and he was
like what are you talking I said you
can't talk to him like that it isn't
okay and you can't say those things cuz
they're horrible and you're an idiot and
I'm just yell and I'm swearing and I'm
doing all these things and finally
80-year-old white guy says to me I don't
there's nothing to do with you there's
none of your business and I said it has
everything to do with me because this is
America and you're horrible and it isn't
okay and he says America p and I turn
into a country music song and I push a
80-year-old man I don't push him down
but I push him and I push him into some
carts anyway he doesn't fall it doesn't
it isn't okay none of it's okay it's not
and uh I'll tell you what the hero
doesn't do the hero doesn't go sit in
her car and cry that's not what Captain
America does after uh he's done he's
fought the
Nazis he doesn't take three days to tell
his husband uh that he was D jackass at
which point my husband was like you know
who carries guns 80-year-old white guys
that is a good point so uh how about you
keep it together and you don't hurt the
elderly yeah and I was like okay he said
you can yell at the guy you could say
things but there's no yeah keep it
together is I want to be of some use but
that isn't anyway so that story is
essentially I don't want to die an
[ __ ] uhhuh and me pushing an
80-year-old man is me being an [ __ ]
sure and so I realized in that moment
that even if I'm right I still die an
[ __ ] so I don't want I don't want
to right and Alive are both super super
helpful right and
not as bad as the person that I'm
fighting exactly I don't want to turn
into that guy yeah no that's the fear we
all have I think
right and yeah I don't know if I should
be laughing at it or not but it is
really funny funny hopefully there's a
bit there cuz I wasn't there that's why
it's funny that's why Comedy Works oh my
God yeah yeah the
way remove
distance could now I don't know I'm just
the more I think about Betty Walker I'm
I'm again I enjoyed it yeah it is but it
is one note and it's so hard again I
don't know how she suspends 40 minutes
maybe she doesn't maybe it's not 40
minutes of of of worth it uh but I I
don't know what else she ever did but it
also seems like that is the perfect kind
of person to I mean she did on the phone
what you again Phil Siler was a good
example I mean that was all housewife
stuff I mean that was all like what it
was like I actually like there's some
people who I like Joan Rivers who it's
actually really hard to talk about what
Joan how she evolved as a comic because
she released two albums in her whole
lifetime because she didn't need to
bother you know so it's hard to say like
she goes from like this album and then
17 years later like super [ __ ] famous
Joan Rivers rich off her ass still
really funny right really funny but an
entirely different kind of comic exactly
but then the beauty of this of of of a
career where you put out an album you
know and like if you listen that's why
it's I mean Doug Stan hope puts out an
album like every year every year and a
half right it's but if you listen to my
albums and by God you ought to
absolutely uh you can you get the
evolution and plus to some extent uh
especially with my albums because
they're they tend to be more about my
dad my parents and my siblings and my in
my life so you get the story of my life
and so like if you go the first album I
did I did it and it is if you find it oh
my God rip it quick because it'll
disintegrate around you because it was
one of those those ones where I burned
it on my computer yeah it's called cake
it's not my downfall and a lot of the
material that's on that album is on
bread okay but um circus people is the
first sort of professional album I ever
did and that's on CD Baby and it's on my
it of course but it's available you can
listen to it for free on all the things
okay um but if you listen I don't like
that album very much um
because it's sort of no longer in
sequence because cake is not my downfall
uh is out of print and will never be in
print uh and Mo and the best of that
material is on bread okay it's sort of
out of order so you should get bread and
then listen to Circus people and
there'll be some overlap of the of the
jokes quite honestly and that's fine um
and the one guy who emailed me and said
why are there the same jokes on two
albums you can [ __ ] off uh quite
honestly there are believe me one of my
favorite comedians is Rusty Warren who
mostly because I think she's fantastic
and adorable she signed that for me
lucky me The Woman released about 15
albums and she overlaps on every album
oh every album every album I mean cuz
she was a club comic and she was a club
comic who had a bit she did she had
songs she did every time songs she mixed
up the intro to the songs was the same
but she was Charming as [ __ ] so it's
okay right and it um when did she work
uh okay Rusty her last album I could be
full of [ __ ] 76 or 78 late 7s but she's
early 60s to late 7s okay and she had a
Vegas stretch in there too like she but
she could never get on Carson cuz she
was dirty even though listen to Joan
River well I don't think she was that
dirty she probably Listen to George
Carlin exactly right believe me believe
me I I'm just with just the reason cuz
Johnny Carson love lovely as he might
have been was a giant sexist and a
homophobe I mean it's it's we're allowed
to say that right I think I'm allowed to
say that yeah I don't think I don't
think you're breaking any ground right
saying that uh I and and if you think
that Johnny Carson wasn't a bit of a
sexist watch any of the sketches watch
any of them absolutely any of the
sketches with the booby ladies and him
tripping and accidentally grouping one
of them you big weirdo and it's grossu
but um yeah mhm so there we go there's
that but yeah I mean but again like
again who gives there's overlap that's
fine but but if you but if you listen
like Brad Brad was my first I
think I mean circus people has some good
fun stuff on it it's
fine but bread and then horcrux and then
this new one hero is
um those three I'm super proud of all of
them and I am a different comic on each
of them yeah yeah and so it's it's
fascinating um if I listen to more
comedy I bet you'd find that with other
Comics you guys you should totally do
that with Pat and Oswalt absolutely you
should actually and I could tell why
later but yeah you should it would be
neat to just to follow somebody's career
like if you listen to like Maria Bamford
oh yeah uh let's talk about her again
yeah um just because like I help her
with her merch I was just helping her
and she has she had three albums we were
selling in Phoenix last weekend and um I
believe she has a total of five albums
out okay and talk about like The Burning
Bridges tour I think is the first album
how to win uh is second album um I don't
know if unwanted thought syndrome is
third but what and then 20% just came
out yeah and uh there might be one
another one in there but if you were to
listen to each of those albums you would
see you would you would actually get the
Arc of a person MH kind of healing
themselves using comedy absolutely which
is a neat thing to hear MH and
um I don't know it's it's why when I've
hear that like Aaron Jackson or Wendy
leedman um or
um uh any number of comics that I know
don't have albums and you're like well
Wendy Leeman not having an album is a
crime against uh Humanity I think she
has a DVD out that's it and I'm like oh
my God because she could be on
television doing 5 minutes and never
repeat herself every night for a year
right right right right okay because
she's a damn genius and those jokes are
perfect for five
minutes and um so I don't know why she's
not on all of the it'd be great if she
did a different how great would like a
four-day week where she did like Monday
on Fallon Tuesday on colar Wednesday on
Conan Thursday it would just be it' be
fun for me I would I I would love yeah I
mean it really drives me crazy when
people don't have albums obviously but I
don't giv you have a podcast exactly but
I don't know if I've ever heard other
than going to see Maria record her last
album the one she did at UCB which is
that the 20% is that 20% no um maybe
yeah maybe okay so I saw that and that
was amazing but I don't know her I just
went cuz I'm a huge fan right yeah but I
didn't I haven't heard her other albums
all I knew of her growing up was seeing
her on TV oh that's the voice lady
that's all I knew yeah yeah you know and
then eventually she gets personal and
[ __ ] I wish I to other albums well an
attainable goal holy smokes talk about U
like on my Pandora station you know how
you can make a Pandora station and so I
made mine and so my Al my albums are on
there but it's just it'll go to like
Rachel Feinstein or Jen Kirkman or Maria
Bamford or any you know gronowski or or
any anybody's
and it's always you know if you've been
doing standup like as long as I've been
doing standup my first album that cake
album probably I think i' printed it in
'98 okay but my but circus people came
out I think in 2000 or 2001 and then
bread was in 2003 or four and
um that's not right who cares well but
there's they're like literally I've done
four albums in the last 10 years or or
and it's really it's for the and I've
been doing standup comedy for about 27
28 years yeah those first
years I'm not I'm not sad that I don't
have those albums because that that
standup is going to be very different
sure I mean circus people is brutal
enough for me so uh but I know Comics
like I always encourage like the
features because I do the road of fair
amount that's what I do right and so I
headline the road the opener uh there's
no money in featuring in doing the
middle spot on the road so as soon as
you have or 40 minutes get an album out
right because and it'll be fascinating
and irritating to you um 20 years from
now if you keep doing it yeah because
you know especially if you could like I
like to come out with an album every two
and a half to three years yeah because I
want the jokes to be done sure and um
that's why the first 10 12 minutes of
hero is so um fascinating to me to some
extent because those some of those jokes
are I've only done them a half a dozen
times really oh [ __ ] handful of times
doesn't feel that way well that's good
um cuz but they have a couple of them
have better punch lines now okay okay
all right but
um but they're
so and but I'll tell you what some of
them couple of them have better punch
lines but a couple of them aren't as
good as they were those first six times
because I wasn't as emotional about all
right okay and sometimes that emotion
will add another layer to the stand up
Scorpio
Rising don't say that s it's very
logical listen to me she explained it to
me she said look a Scorpio Rising is a
fixed water sign I am a pure Leo no that
means that I am complete fire complete
now she says Mrs tman what happens when
you mix fire and water when you mix Fire
and Water you get
Steam and steam is the story of my
marriage yeah no she gave me a little
hope no she said to me that uh she said
your husband can be a wonderful man she
said he's wonderful when Jupiter hits
his natal
house this happens once in 12
years and I missed it both
times oh I yeah I agree I mean there's a
bit on there that isn't even a joke that
kind of made me tear up a little bit the
genocide thing uh was just what the [ __ ]
was the line it was like how exactly did
you put it nobody gets on the trains is
that how' you say it yeah yeah yeah yeah
I was like I was like oh [ __ ] that got
real and it was great it was perfect it
was a perfect moment for it that's
that's how that should work I but I also
like the idea of every two and a half
three years you're doing it rather than
every year because you can't hear the
evolution from one album to another you
have to hear a gap yeah for me anyway
like it's it's like if it's every year
cool if that's good for you and your
people are going to buy it [ __ ] great
you're going to make the money but for
me yeah I'd rather hear well that's why
I like as much as I I truly enjoy Louis
I like watching him
um but it's when he was putting out an
album or a new special every year I
remember watching him because I'm I also
don't listen to albums or watch specials
but I'd see the set or I'd see something
I'd see him perform and I'd think oh my
God how great will that be that joke be
in another six months yeah yeah yeah
yeah because if he if he came out every
18 months instead of every year and I've
heard actually that he said he's done
with the every year thing because he
doesn't his plate is too full and he
can't finish the jokes in tou sure and
so yeah yeah let them marinate man just
think about how great they'll be if they
marinate and uh because you'll come up
with another another punchline or two I
did the political stuff because I
thought we'd all be dead and for some
reason I thought well let the aliens
find it yeah and uh you
know well and that I mean the crazy
thing is like when I hear I mean you
actually call yourself out on it at the
beginning of the album wait let's say to
the name of the album before we keep
talking about I not the hero of the
story thank you not the ER of the story
is my new album it came out at the
beginning of March 2017 and it did
things that none of my other albums did
which was it was number one on Amazon
and iTunes uh for sales and then number
three on Billboard number three on
Billboard without a bullet you guys it
opened at three then that was it okay
but it had never made billboard so I'm
excited that's awesome yeah now all
that's left is for at the end of the
year it to be critically acclaimed and
on those lists of course uh CU those are
the lists I also enjoy of course of
course you
person but that I mean but that's it
like you call yourself out for like uh
you know not normally being political
but feeling it as a necessity you don't
often like I find myself having to
listen back again I'm listening trying
to listen to a comedy album every day
this year oh wow it's a pain in the ass
I'm 20 albums behind already because
it's so hard to Duke with all my other
[ __ ] yeah but when you listen to stuff
you and I who was I I think it was when
I was interviewing Tommy Chong the other
day I was like hey I know I'm going to
overe examine this cuz I have my head up
my ass like I admitted it I'm like cuz I
just just how it goes like so you find
yourself picking apart like maybe they
meant this like you get super way too
intellectual about it sometimes it
really really helps when somebody does
that and says I don't normally get
political now I'm getting political
enjoy or don't like it it is actually
kind of helpful to have that as a as an
earmark you know well it's
um it's funny because I did that I
recorded them at Acme in Minneapolis
where I've done all my albums it's my
home club and that audience is trained
and standup comedy audiences live
standup comedy audiences are more
tolerant than any any just normal people
like if you go to a very conservative
State like I'm going to Birmingham next
month and um Alabama and but I'm I'm
performing for standup comedy audiences
sure who will sit there and go well I
don't agree with your politics but that
was a funny joke yeah and that's what
they'll do they'll sit there and do that
I was in Poria and um I started in I was
did some of the I have new political
jokes because I I'm I'm having a hard
time writing anything but because it's
on my brain and I don't want to some
woman came up to me the other I was in
Phoenix and this or Tucson this woman
comes up and she goes you know this is
the third time I've seen you and I think
the political stuff is your Forte I
think that's going to be your thing and
I said I don't want it to be my thing
because I'm angry and I don't want to be
angry and what I'd like to be is happy
and then write those down I think that's
been established anyway so um but I was
in PUO and I started in on this
political chunk and and um and I don't
say president psychos uh name uh in any
of my material appreciate that as well
and yeah I don't want to talk about uh
I'm not a reality TV person either so uh
but the
uh but I started talking about the
present the current Administration and
um I just start getting this glare from
this dude like the second row and I go
you know you can hate me all you want
man but I'm getting walked in my car so
[ __ ] off you know I'm like it doesn't
I'm going to talk about this if you
don't like it you can bail it's hardly I
don't know what you what else you want
me to I mean I'd love to talk about dogs
of course of course if I could write a
puppy bit we'd all win well I mean
Carlin got start don't get me wrong I
love early George Carlin way more than I
like later Carlin much as I appreciate
the art of what he did as an angry man
on stage even though like if you saw him
off stage he was less angry seeming uh I
think a lot of people like him got
started on those I'm not saying you're
going to become a political comedian
especially if you don't want to be but
like reticence is always a huge part of
it I don't want to be reticence is a is
a is a part of it if you're like
willingly angry about everything that's
either boring or somehow really
fascinating if it's Lewis Black but like
you know uh or I guess to some people
Kenn it's it's a short it it it it's a
tiny part of the spectrum yeah and if
you can rock it rock it sure but
otherwise I don't even want to ex I I
did Kelly Carlin's show on XM and
um I admitted that I had not heard any
of her dad and she was like ah thank God
finally the person who doesn't know who
the hell he is and she's like I loved
him but Jesus I can't take the
canonization or whatever right yeah and
I it was interesting because I had done
two XM series one with Jay Thomas M who
played a right-wing blowhard on Murphy
Brown and then Ria butcher rightwing
blow hard husband on Cheers and it turns
out that was a typ casting cuz he's got
a radio show on XM serious and the first
thing and the thing about shock jock
radio dudes is there's only one way is
to shock them into shutting up of course
of course and but at the end of it do
you feel like you won no right but it
who because I don't want to play yeah
and uh the only it's very war games uh
would you like to play some chess uh
because want to it was the his first
question he says you one of these
[ __ ] feminists and I said yes yes and
a [ __ ] so if you want to play shut it
and then at the end of the interview he
goes hey you were pretty great let's
have you on again and I was like yeah
we'll we'll talk about it God damn it
like I want to be I I don't necessarily
need his fan base to care about me are
you one of the oh my good god yes I'm
alive so I'm going to be in favor know
that you don't think that women should
have control of their own bodies cuz
it's on the platform but I'm going to be
against that cuz I don't tell you what
hand to jerk off with right I'm like
you're a lefty you knock yourself out
you're righty it's it's you between you
and your God it's uh but you want to
tell me what to do with my body let uh I
don't want to talk to
you I don't know why I'm having this Joe
pesy moment I don't know but I like it I
like it very
much well if they do the Home Alone
reboot I hope they hire I hope they hire
you as the pesy character CU that would
be fantastic I got I got the I want to
call it hard target and it would be me
and like Wanda SES and we both work at a
Target and then uh either bank robbers
or terrorists break into the Target
right at closing time and so we are
trapped somewhere in the toy department
and we use toys and found objects in
Target to stop the bad guys in a home
alone like moment I love this idea very
much it's a buddy movie and then she
could be like in love with the
pharmacist okay or I could or two actors
that are neither of us and I would like
to sell this idea I love this idea and
uh I'm stealing it no but I love this
idea let's put Ricky and uh Kate manucci
or whatever sure sure sure garun lot
buddy movie done it's a good idea two
two more skinny white girls on on camera
that's a very good idea let's do this um
in their 20s early 30s let's do it yeah
um okay so let's do this because yeah
are we at an hour we're just about at an
hour I'm a little sniffly I'm sorry how
dare you how dare you be sniffly uh okay
so let's talk about Betty Walker's album
because the only reason we didn't have a
ton to say about it is cuz it might not
it was funny but it's like it's funny
there's not as much to say about it cuz
it's it doesn't age well Soul CH
changing at all exactly right it was I
was glad that I picked it though sure me
too 100% because um I never heard of her
MH and I was like oh I wonder what she
was doing and some of it was great and
it was interest and she was interesting
through the whole thing yeah and look at
those eyes man man she looks like she's
smarter than the average bear right look
like like like super smart and really
funny and I
think if she were alive today like if
she were doing standup now that it would
be much more updated and much more she
would roll with it I absolutely and I
actually think it might have fit right
it would have been fun to watch her do
it maybe that might have been more of
what people were laughing at too I want
to know I don't know oh right cuz it's
best with comedy the way it goes for me
I like to see it live MH then I like to
listen to it on audio okay that's the
next step all right uh and then video
okay because video there's that
separation of screen least favorite way
to watch standup comedy when it is part
of a plot of a TV show o yeah sure it's
a sure or a movie AA your punch lines
are your uh Julie Kushner Julie whatever
polka dot uh movie about uh a standup
comic anyway her hook was that she wore
polka dots oh okay I see that's that's
just good writing yeah oh abut but
there's a new there's a new a new TV
show that I I admit to being interested
in it's with Al madal on Showtime called
I'm dying up here oh is it the one about
the backstage of Carson [ __ ] it's like
uh I think so 70s early 70s and he's
supposed to play like a Freddy Prince
like character the man guy okay and
um so that could I mean the weird thing
is is the standup you just you can't no
one's willing to give away their a
material no of course so
there's no way to portray stand-up
comedy as funny as it is yeah when it's
like on an episode of Bones and someone
has been killed and uh then you got to
watch a standup comic he's like well
he's got reason to kill and the worst
part is they hire a [ __ ] standup
comic to do it and then you've got to
look like you don't know how to be a
standup right but there's no but you
don't say no cuz everyone needs $1,000
of course not yeah why would you not
okay I don't know when this is going to
come out so I apologize for that if you
have specific time you let me know
otherwise let's go over where they can
find you what they should purchase well
all right my name is Jackie K it's k a h
i a an and if you go to jackie.com all
the things will be revealed I have two
podcasts I have a podcast called the
Dork Forest which you have been on yes
uh talking about uh and we should have
just stuck with Legos because uh um
because then we had Matthew on yes and
uh and he went more in detail because he
can because he can and and he will
requested or not vice presidents are on
the brain with that guy yes and Legos
are on the brain with you yes and so the
Dork Forest I interview people about
they love a lot that's what they dork
out about like this week it's some
musicals with Rebecca sugar uh who
created a a cartoon called Steven
Universe oh okay anyway so um it could
be anything that's the Dork Forest I
also have another podcast just about
standup comedy so if people who listen
to this MH I do a podcast with Lori Kil
Martin on the nerd Channel called The
Jackie and Lori show where Lori and I
literally real time [ __ ] about standup
comedy great so good times for there if
you like that and we're exhausted
because we work really hard all the time
and the scheduling of getting us on both
in front of a microphone uh is the
hardest part so it's usually midnight
and we're exhausted so we hit an hour
and we're like goodbye yeah and so we
talk we talk we talk and then Kyle tells
us it's an hour and we're like and run
so you can get as much sleep as possible
my flight's at 5:00 in the morning so um
the that's super fun and then I have I
am not the hero of the story is my album
Jack at Jackie on all the all the things
uh Instagram uh Snapchat Twitter uh dork
Forest uh the Dork Forest on Facebook
but the
um I'm on the road all the time doing
wherever town you people live the most
exciting places I'm doing standup is at
the end of July I'm doing it in Dublin
Ireland whoa and then Iceland ruic
awesome so uh figure out how to get to
see those things and then other than
that I'll be in Bloomington you guys
anything Indiana okay so that I mean if
it comes out the next month or so but
otherwise just go to jackie.com and go
to my schedule and look that's awesome
and I opened for Maria Bamford and I
opened for Brian Regan so [ __ ] those are
two very different Comics two very
different Comics but like that's
impressive it's a Well I am very
versatile mhm and then I also had line
my own beeswax so uh come and see me do
stand up if you if you want and if not
no no harm no fall that's so good it's
all good do you have to tailor your
comedy for Brian Regan just because he's
clean yeah yeah yeah yeah and and for
Maria yeah because the thing is is like
if I'm just doing my the greatest thing
about working with Maria is Maria wants
me to go as weird and she's the one
who's constantly saying do the genocide
bit I'm like the genocide bit is
emotionally draining of course it is so
to do it is I have to gird my loins
essentially and then bring up the
Armenian Genocide right you know how
good that stuff was though I almost went
and told you oh you know what I recently
heard about that and I was about to do
your bit back to you that's how much it
stuck in my head so like yeah it's it's
so much fun um Everybody yes listen to
her album follow her listen to all her
damn podcasts all too they it's not it's
not it's not it's not a full PL it's
it's easy to listen to every week um and
uh throughout this year I'm doing comedy
album a day so go to youtube.com/ comdy
onvinyl you'll see uh my reviews I'm way
behind by when time this comes out I
should be caught up plus some my next
movie is coming out sometime Jackie's in
it she plays herself oh my God that was
so fun that was a ton of fun I have to
figure out how I'm going to integrate
all those blogs and still make the movie
look good like it's going to be weird uh
but you just you just helped me out so
much by doing that it was a ton of fun
um and that's about it so thank you guys
for listening and as always always have
a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
five-star rating and a nice review you
can find us on facebook.com / comedy
onvinyl Twitter at comedy onvinyl and
find everything else at comedyon
vinyl.com a major portion of Comedy
onvinyl has been underwritten by standup
records please visit standup records.com
for all your comedy needs and tune in to
the new standup channel available on the
Roku where you can also find select
episodes of this podcast
[Music]