[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast the year is 1969 the album is
Tad poles the band is a bonser do dudah
band my guest is Jeffrey Weissman uh
thank you for inviting me into well your
friends home um my pleasure this is fun
this is fun so we met through I did the
million McFly March last year and you do
all kinds of Back to the Future related
Charities yes because I took over the
role of George McFly in part two and
part three I thought how can I give back
to the amazing International fan base
and these movies uh so I produced a
fundraiser for Michael's charity uh
under the ospice of Team Fox produced a
cruise to uh raise money and put a band
together made up of uh former cast
members of Back to the Future films and
we raised about eight grand our first at
our first try and about a thousand for
we spark for which is Wendy Joe bber who
played Linda McFly who's passed away but
she set up a cancer support center here
in Los Angeles yeah that's so good that
cruise looked like so much fun I was so
jealous every time I looked at the blast
well you mentioned that you had gone to
uh sites that back future movies were
were uh shot at and the day you did your
Milli million McFly March was the uh I
think we're into the fifth or sixth day
of a another fundraiser for for the
Parkinson's foundation called we're
going back yes Ken Kowski out of Canada
Joel waler out of La uh produced this
event where all these I think they had
250 fans every day going to each one of
the locations that we shot the original
scenes at awesome from all over the
world they were thrilled they were sort
of orgasmic for these Back to the Future
nerds it was just delightful because we
would have cast members crew members at
those locations to tell behind the
scenes stories or sign autographs or
that we took over the town of Filmore
and you could
hoverboard uh the flux capacitors played
it was it was really a lot of fun that's
awesome it was so then through there H
after sort of realiz I mean to be fair
you showed up to give me some you were
kind enough to give me some things for
the McFly March yeah it was totally cool
that you were doing it you showed up
dressed as Charlie Chaplain I'm like
this is a guy I want to talk to on my
podcast I'm like holy not only like you
drove over just in full regalia and I'm
hoping maybe not in the floppy shoes but
I could be wrong yeah I well I I try not
to D drive in those shoes but sometimes
I do it's a little dangerous for the
others on the road I'm okay still uh but
I I guess I had just come from a gig
yeah yeah yeah and so you picked a band
that I've wanted to do forever in fact
like a good friend of mine has all their
albums and he's like why haven't you
talked about the bonso on the show
before and and I'm what's up with that
nobody's brought it up you brought it up
so well I originally wanted you said
well something that you loved and I
immediately went through the oh my God
the Maze of albums through my childhood
I remember having a a 78 of Bill Cosby
because he played at my dad's Club his
uh you know where he's a football player
and his skin gets stuck to the seat and
his jersey gets into the game that was
it was great I had a demo vers that
hadn't even been released yet dad got
from Bill at the at his club uh and uh
inherited from my parents collection or
my older brother and sisters I had
examining doctors by May Nichols so I
was like oh let's do mik Nichols and
elae May and I can't even find my copy
of examining doctors now oh no and uh so
I you said well what other you know and
well there's you know I went to the
committee 50-year reunion got Gary
goodro uh who just passed away to sign
the the Broadway album wow here Alan
Myerson was there and Howard hman all
these greates I was like I could do that
or but I I don't you know I love the
bonser dog man I was in
73 visiting the original Renaissance
Fair up in Aura mhm and there were these
guys who used to have this game called
tulsy [ __ ] okay where you get on a log
with someone else and that you have a
basically a big pillow but it's pretty
heavy and you try to knock each other
off off the lock right and was a Doug
Doug and Mike I can't even remember
their names but they were you know
hippies but uh really sweet guys who um
produced a Fantasy Fair I remember in
Hollywood at the Palladium it was the
first Fantasy Fair the first time you'd
see a laser being bounced off uh the
next building over from the parking lot
and they had Bulgarian female choir and
this unusual band called The Mystic
nights of the Oingo Boingo um that's so
good all these really great bands at
this Fantasy Fair and and they were they
were truly unique fellows and because I
lived at the ferite for a while as a
gypsy myself uh I would see them often
and one day they were walking down the
the dirt path and were singing this song
uh oh the Parson's eyes are glistening
and the children are all listening for
the stor has brought a son and daughter
for Mr and Mrs Mickey Mouse Pluto's
throwing a party but before the fun
begins he'll award a gold Madonna to the
father of the twins hooray hooray it's a
public holiday a million million people
are happy bright and gay bells are
ringing in the steeple but is that
public holiday so the stor is brought a
son and daughter for Mr and Mrs Mickey
Mouse I was like well what is that they
looked at each other you don't know the
bonso dog doah I said no and then they
went in and started riffing on shirts oh
my God shirts here comes a little
strange little lady with with a kangaroo
o mam what do you think of sh oh I don't
know so much about that they were they
knew all these lyrics of these avantgard
irreverent songs and comedy sketches I
was like what is the bonso dog B and
over the years I got to pick up some
records after hearing Urban Spacemen on
the radio and and uh getting to know
them and then researched them and found
that they had
been the house band on an early Tv show
uh don't don't touch that dial not adust
do not adjust your television Jesus
Christ I have it written down pardon my
friend that had uh three of the Monty
Python MERS not adjust your set there do
not adjust yourself Terry Jones Eric
Idol pal Michael Palin yeah and uh you
know they had this sort of
officious uh beginning of like many
great bands like the talking heads and
uh so many others dvo that came out of
art school they were all in art school
Together the Beatles were in art school
together and uh they formed this they
weren't skiffle they were more I think
Dixie Land type right Jazz they were a
Jazz Ensemble which is so weird to me
yes well then they found with jazz you
learn the elements of Comedy
improvisation that's true right right
right and their irreverent
leader uh Vivien
stanel had such a dry tongue and cheek
uh you know attitude in his voice was
like uh oh everything's also roll and
everything and and you hear him one of
my favorite cuts of all theirs is the
intro and the outro you listen to that I
have not and you mentioned it and I just
read about it it's so magnificent
because it's all it is from start to
finish is uh introductions of the band
members and there's everyone from Roy
Rogers on trigger to count B Bassy and
his orchestra on triangle you know and
and they get a little EXA Eric Clapton
on ukulele and oh that's wild Eric you
know it's this real wait a minute now I
think I might have heard
cuz I mean in the early days of being of
thinking it was okay to steal MP3s I
stole a lot of bonso dog stuff and so
but then I lost it so I know I've heard
that now there's Instant Karma for you
for stealing yeah believe me believe me
but now I mean what do you you got to
you can find them in the used record bin
for for very little now most of my
albums are 50 cents it's normally how
cheap I get them because I don't you
know God bless the Goodwill in the
Salvation Army so true uh though you
know to find them in mint condition uh
it's you're starting to pay10 $15 a yeah
sure sure but they're so wonderful and
you can find most of the songs now on
YouTube they've been posted I even named
my home after one of their songs uh they
did a cover of a song I believe was
originally from the 20s called jolly
farmh and uh it's basically uh just a
uptempo kind of fox
trotty uh Happy song you know all the
all the cats meow all the dogs bowwow
here on jol farm and uh there's couple
different versions on YouTube you can
find and and that's that's just it's
delightful music It's A celebratory and
then often irreverent and so absurdly
funny uh kind of makes it go crossy so
through through the years not only
becoming a fan but I I DJ too and a
Gentleman uh that I know up in Northern
California who was a Pirate Radio on a
barge off of the uh UK off English Coast
um has a radio show up there and he
invited me on knowing what a fan I am
because he got Roger Ruskin spear on the
phone oh that's so good and we did we
were on the phone with him for over an
hour that's awesome and was reminiscing
uh up the yingang uh he had just been
touring starting to tour with three
bonso and a piano uhuh and his uh his
follow-up record is uh has even the
sequel to shirts really yes called
shirts
2010 hello well that was the sound of
Roger ww rabbits you heard them eating
on there that's very cheap at this time
of the year but now here in Wilston
green yes it is a bit chilly but no
matter because here comes a gentleman
and we're going to talk to him about
shirts excuse me sir would you mind
talking to us about shirts do what about
shirts shirts yes we got plenty of
town good
grief and here comes a lady with an
enchanting little
kangaroo and I'm going to ask her
something about shirs no I'm not because
she's given me rather a valgar
sign would you excuse me would you mind
we're talking about shirts huh about
shirts shirt yes the problem of shirts
the kind of um you know are they
necessary
shirts there it is where it is yes where
is Shir I don't know I don't know and a
lot of the songs are very similar even
though we don't have Vivian stanel
anymore Roger Ruskin spear who had this
whole concept of having a wardrobe
Orchestra uhuh you'll see one of their
the bonso's tunes is called the trouser
press uhuh and he would build these Rob
bots in his garage and often they were
made out of I don't know dry cleaning uh
machines or you know press trouser press
he actually made the trouser press into
a musical instrument uh that's amazing
yeah well they were art students you
know and and uh he'd get calls he had
these wonderful stories in fact I'll
I'll share the the show with you and you
can use excerpts if you like oh great
yeah uh where he would be opening for
rock bands You Know Matha Hoople or or
uh slate or whoever you know back in the
day and he would have his robots on
stage just doing their strange things
and uh it's their avangard music and you
know most of the hippies back then were
probably really Stoner on acid and it
was just perfect for them yeah what the
[ __ ] am I see watching
it uh twist the brain and and you know
the the renaissance fair that I spoke
about where I learned about the bonso
there was was pretty big drug culture so
it was perfect for those guys to be
discovering bonso dog ban because the
the renfair is very Anglo Centric sure
and uh you know here in the states for
the hippies and comedy it was fire sign
theater sure Dave Osman came out of the
early Renaissance Fairs yeah you said
that that's interesting Phil Proctor was
around then and uh the the uh so the
natural kind of progression since it was
Elizabeth in England is after hours well
let's get some contemporary English fun
in here and uh you know Beyond The
Fringe and other English humor was you
know was good but it seemed to a little
too conservative whereas these guys were
hippies and irreverent yeah so it made
sense it all in the equation what's
crazy is later today I'm going to be
talking about some of the more
conservative English music and even
maybe some of the more State English
comedy with the album we picked this is
a perfect um position thank you there's
the word that I couldn't think of or is
it just a position just here's one
there's one there's a nice gesture and
listening to it I was just like well
first of all you telling me that I'm
like that's just amazing that they might
have been hurting nerd's brains just a
little bit before Monty Python that they
might have just been needling our brains
before well if you were like a liberal
or
Democratic or or uh rebelling
conservative teen in the mid to late 60s
you know and the flower power was coming
on and the hippie movement was evolving
or you stayed in your bedroom until you
were old enough to run away from home
and become emancipated I you were
probably dropping acid or getting stoned
you know on the sly and you had you know
you're little record player what did you
have to play well some of these uh you
know trippy records that uh you know
Frank zpp and the mothers were in my
opinion doing sort of like what the bons
of dog band were doing
St side where they were just freaking
out being very creative with this
improvisational Jazz stuff that Frank
was leading them in and and it's really
you know we're only in it for the money
and freak out and Suzie cream cheese all
those early records are trippy as hell
and if you are were buzzed and listening
to it or late at night you know looking
for entertainment where you didn't have
to go to mainstream television and watch
The Beverly Hillbillies or uh you know
you had this outlet and so for the
English kids Lonzo dog band for the
American Kids the Frank Za and the mo
mothers and I don't know this is I'm
just kind of figuring it all out and
retrospect well it's crazy too that
these guys were the connection between
the Beatles and Monty Python essentially
too because Urban Spaceman which is
probably the first bonso song I ever
heard and loved it didn't get it because
I was a little too young to get it I
think I still don't think I entirely get
it but that was half produced by Paul
McCartney because he liked the Bonzo dog
band right and then George Harrison
connected with mon Python and producing
their films and then it all comes
together in Rutland weekend television
it's just like this just it's very
incestuous but like three wonderful
things that are like I guess making love
that's gross um but you know what I'm
saying you you get my point as said love
fast it's all relative and the whole
time I'm listening to this I'm like wait
did you get that it's inest it's all Rel
come back up I should have given it more
credit than I did the listening to it
I'm like okay so was new vaille bandn
before or after and I did not know that
they're basically about the the same
time and that they almost became the new
vaille band but then the new vaille band
apparently stole their entire look and
their all the like the design of their
oh I didn't realize it yeah I just had
read that so the guy who who who who
made the new volb band album with
session session musicians apparently
came to Neil L and the rest of them said
would you guys like to perform when they
said no he stole their look and then
just put together another well it's it's
a compliment you know there's always Ste
imitation is a form of flattery yeah
that's what it is steal from the greats
that's what you find
and so were new vodvil band were they
the ones that did wi C the whole album
is that though boy there's no variety
stop holding your nose and singing
exactly that's all
yes but what uh the bonso did though I
grew up very much uh you know kind of
writing on my parents' tastes and they
had besides Herb Albert and uh you know
The Singing Nun and things like this you
know growing up they also had uh the
firehouse 5 dixyland band and if you
listen to bonso's stuff they're doing
hello Central give me Dr Jazz with a
more wacka whacka kind of feel to it
right and so I was like oh well I know
this music already that's perfect yeah
it was It was kind of cool fun so it's
kind of conservative you know respecting
our elders sure but then breaking ground
new territory rock and roll because they
did get into the Rock and Roll bent on
it and had fun with that and it sort of
still burlesquing yeah yeah yeah Vivian
stanel was just amazing apparently he
was terribly tortured and really had a
bad end Etc but uh but you know a lot of
Genius said Barrett with Pink Floyd you
know they they had uh their demons and
such
uh Vivian I guess just couldn't uh I
don't know there is a great book out
apparently on Vivian stanel and the
bonso that oh really that uh I I
recommend people seek it out because I
hear it's a great read that's awesome um
okay so you did mention earlier and I
didn't want to let this go that your
father had a club so yeah nightclub
Comedy Club both what are we talking
about uh it was a sort of a private
gambling Club really yeah uh uh if he
had either co-owned or managed various
clubs the LA City Club he had his own
club on Santa Monica in West Hollywood
at lanica called The Regency and then up
on the Sunset Strip the boy which later
became the Cavendish West which I think
is still extant uh up on the strip and
he was co-owners uh with Lauren Green
really on that one or one of the others
and then uh when I was a kid I'd go
visit the club and I remember I got
kidnapped once by czecho Marx's
Widow hid under the table for hours they
didn't know where little Jeffrey was um
and I I would meet Omar Sharif uh Don
Adams you know a lot of you know Stars
would go and sure play bridge or back
Amon and yeah and you know one time I
think the club got raided by the da his
the da Bert Bert Pines Mom Ruth Pines
was part of the gang that got arrested
so you know everyone got released and
all the charges dropped cuz the DA's
mother was part of the uh the Patty
Wagon Gang anyway so they you know it
was u a business that he got in and my
dad was always trying to get out of that
business uh because of seeing actors
drinking gambling and all he didn't want
me to become an actor at all yeah yeah
yeah and and he would ask he came home
one day and said Jeffrey uh I asked Don
Adams some advice for you since you say
you want to be an actor and and he said
w-e tell him to forget about it it's a
90% luck and 10% of you know talent and
who you know you know whatever yeah yeah
yeah and uh so this
needless to say I I I couldn't get
acting out of my system and I continued
and and I became very proud first of my
dad for going back to school and getting
his Masters in Psychology and becoming
PS a psychologist and and then he became
very proud of me when he saw my name and
the first movie I co-starred in I think
Twilight Zone movie with John Lithgow on
uh George Miller's segment and then
other films and so then later in his
life he became a drama therapist as well
really and I'd go down and Coach him you
improvisation and and his scene work and
he would take uh drama therapy and
Shakespeare and and Theater into
jails and help treat inmates you know
rehabing them with Arts with the
dramatic arts and such well I think he
only got caught in one or two lockdowns
that's good that's good that's a good
record oh my God that's fascinating to
me hey I've been fascinated too I had a
righted here on the arm I scratched and
got
infected so the uh I guess the
introduction to Comedy on vinyl came I
guess through my dad uh he not only had
comedians play at his clubs and such but
uh he would regil me with with stories
of going to see uh uh what's his name uh
wab buy a duck uh Joe B not Joe besser
he was in the studs uh I I'll look at
I'll think about it his name but he who
used to play on the Sunset Strip a lot
and Don Adams was his standup uh you
turned me on to Bob newart you know all
the the stand-ups that made it into
television you know uh and and I would
have this awareness you know red fox I
know came from stand up but his albums
are like
[Music]
filthy baby I've got
speed I've got everything I
[Music]
need I'm the spaceman baby I can fly I'm
a
[Music]
personic
gu I don't need pleasure I don't feel
pain if you were to knock me down I'd
just get up
again I'm the spaceman baby I'm making
out I'm all about
[Applause]
[Music]
I wake up every morning with a smile
upon my face my natural exuberance
spills out all over the my mother also
was a Bailbonds woman MH before she uh
switched careers and she bailed Lenny
Bruce out of jail twice holy and uh as
well as Winston vir's daughter you know
for pot charges anyway uh
so so the second time Lenny uh and my
dad's best friend Burton marks was his
attorney and uh we got Lenny out of jail
um my sister and I were in the car and
Lenny I go score some [ __ ] you know and
because he swore in front of the
children she would never bail him out
again you know so she had her standards
you know I love it oh my God but I so I
grew up I guess with this Mystique
around you know who's Lenny Bruce as
soon as I was old enough to go listen to
some of his recording like wow and then
Justin Hoffman movie you know came out
it really uh was fun for me to sort of
get a little inkling and uh preview of
The Adult World of comedy and then you
know because I've been performing in
comedy I was in the Laugh Factory
All-Star improv Jam for better part of a
year and a half uh a lot of those folk
that we that I jammed with uh Brad
Sherwood from Whose Line Is It Anyway uh
Dan Connor who's now with impro theater
we okay we helped start Los Angeles
theater Sports 20 years ago and uh now
they're still performing but what
they'll do now is take one suggestion
and do a three-hour Jane Austin or
Tennessee Williams or Twilight Zone or
Steven S High Musical and they are just
amazing wow they've honed their crap so
beautifully and it all comes out of this
sort of standup but improvisation family
that these albums are are based on you
know the Nicholls and may it so funny I
was shooting a film uh kind of a grad
student film one day and Sandy Baron
shows up on set I was like name uh he
was on Seinfeld as the angry neighbor
stand up comedian for years and I like
and and you know he's he's on oxygen by
this time you know he's got tank with
him I was like Sandy bear what are you
doing here he goes oh you got a cute
producer I met her at the the
deli let me come with you to your film
set maybe I can coach some of these kids
I was like my God and I told him about
my idea of doing a documentary on the
family tree of improvisation yeah and he
went on a rave he was
like [ __ ] the May Nichols Lenny Bruce I
was doing improv in the clubs years
before any of them the committee I I
outdated them I predated them as jerks
stole it from me I I wish I had one of
these recorders to get this interview of
Sandy Baron going through all that it
was so funny to hear his anger you know
I should get the credit it's like you
know uh ramling Jack Elliott saying Bob
Dylan stole his whole act and got famous
the same type of thing sure sure it's
all incestuous but so this improvisation
thing now you know I'm teaching it at
University mhm and it's taught in
schools when I went to Australia uh 15
20 years ago in junior high in the high
schools the the Keith johnstonian impro
uh the theater Sports type improv was
being taught in the schools wow it was
very cool and they had their own TV
shows before who Whose Line Is It Anyway
brought it to popularity first the UK
and then the states and it really is uh
a great tool now
because I know facilitators and trainers
who are taking it to these companies
from high-tech through sales and
training people how to listen because
that's the key to Great improv it's just
how do you listen and then add logically
to the storytelling and it's really
incredible tools and and now these guys
like Dan O Conor and and Brian lman who
I sort of weaned on improv with are now
doing the Ted X talks really on
improvisation and such really it's fun
that's crazy it's interesting too that
it's all then based on I mean there's
there's a reward system of laughter no
laughter versus silence too and that
everybody must respond to that then if
it's working well it's it's uh there's
different forms of it and I try to stay
away from the gag proov or bar bar proov
where the
laughter uh you're not going for the
laugh but rather more of the
storytelling because ultimately even if
it's a dramatic piece it can be so
fulfilling sure can be so incredibly
rewarding and it takes a lot of trust
because our natural tendencies across
the board are insecure and we want to
please and if you're doing it for
someone someone else you're shooting
yourself in the foot you have to do it
for yourself and listen to the integrity
and and be respectful of the story is
number one and working at the top of
your intelligence is exhausting yes it's
very hard and and doing all the things
it's a juggling act and But ultimately
if you look at the early committee work
mhm actually not the early but all
through the Committees they were working
at the top of their intelligence really
bright wonderful people and they laid
the groundwork by and set the bar high
at the same time and that's why I can't
wait for uh Jamie Wright who runs the
San Francisco Improv Festival is doing a
documentary on the the committee oh
awesome and he got all the members that
were alive and attending the 50-year
reunion up there to do interviews and
then uh mixing it with the archive
footage it's going to be brilliant when
it comes out great that's so good you
know and the funny thing is I don't and
again I don't know you you know the
bonso come out of this improv Jazz thing
which great we didn't even mention is
that there are actual there just
sketches I mean shirts is a sketch yes
and it's fantastic and assuming I'm
assuming it's improv it is and it's
pretty much a man on the street in proov
they took it to the street and and what
you hear is what they got and it's so
incredible the responses from people on
the
street I I hope you'll play it yeah yeah
yeah I I will even though is it on tple
I think on TES yeah yeah yeah it's it's
an interesting mix this album then
listen to uh shirts
2010 I'm excited to hear that so okay
but you also said you know because
unfortunately I had to force you to pick
one album so this is the one we're like
all right let's do this cuz also is the
only one that I could find in terms of
the mp3s that I have um so but there
there's some other I mean urban Spaceman
was one that you that you're a big fan
of is is there one well Urban Spaceman
for them was their big hit mhm here stat
side at least and and it has a lot of uh
political statement in it and is Up
Tempo and it's a little rock and roll
it's where they're actually shifting a
little out of the Jazz and into the
rocking part part and it's very witty
and clever and such and thus it got
AirPlay and you know here's hippie
comedy music and so we don't only have
the the Mothers of Invention which don't
fit into any am or FM playlist format
right uh so they I think Urban Spaceman
because it's sort of a their pop hit uh
most people would know yeah so you you
first heard of them through these people
quoting them at you what did did you
just go out immediately and buy an album
like what was your no I was pretty poor
I you did say you were you're living
yeah I was doing a gypsy kind of life
doing those renfair days so I kept I
sort of filed it away and whenever I
would come across then years later uh a
bonso dog doah band record uh or I heard
him on Dr Demento or whatever wherever
uh I would pay close attention and
finally became obsessed with finding Mr
and Miss um son and daughter for Mr and
Mrs Mickey Mouse and then uh discovered
jolly farm and discovered uh you know
various other tunes that uh I had either
heard of or heard parts of or were filed
in my my subconscious so on on Tad
polles uh it wasn't really until a
couple years ago that I relistened to
and rediscovered hunting Tigers uh in
ninja and I had never heard that till
today so and have you seen the video no
oh go go to YouTube and see the video
now you'll see Viv Vivian stanel is the
star of it mhm and I suspect I think the
original version or the version you'll
see on YouTube is from uh the the TV
show okay okay don't adjust your TV what
do not adjust your set do not adjust
your set there we go and so it is kind
of like a kid show sketch yeah yeah but
it's fun as can be it's really lovely
and you know they're in all pit helmet
and being completely British and going
out and hunting tigers in Africa or I
mean inja and and you'll see it's just
camp and silly fun and and delightful
right so it is yes a kids show but it's
also adult like you know George of the
Jungle you know it was was a a cartoon
for kids but it had adult stuff in it if
you look closely there's a lot of uh
great humor in uh a lot of those those
cartoons that were kid oriented but very
adult so uh so hunting ERS out in ninja
shirts let's see tubas in the Moonlight
Dr jazz is like I mentioned the Dixie
Land thing that I I was familiar with
Monster Mash and always yeah they cover
the Monster Mash it's great
[Music]
I was working in my lab late one night
when my eyes beheld an eerie sight my
monster from the slab began to rise
suddenly to my surprise he did the MH he
did the Monster Mash monst Mas it was a
graveyard smash smash it caught on in a
flasher Mash he did the Monster Mash
from the Hall of Gore in the castle East
to the master bedroom where the vamp 's
Feast the ghouls all came from their
humble abodes to get a jol from my
electrod they did the monster and I
almost brought it I uh I have uh zachar
L's version mhm uh that he signed for me
at uh the show in New Jersey in parcion
um what do they call it Chiller theater
one of these fan cons that's awesome
yeah it was I mean he's is he still
alive I he's probably about 98 now wow
wow
yeah you do have a lot of their albums
sitting here though you did bring a lot
of them yeah I I well I have Gorilla
which I was hoping the one was the one
that we were going to do oh shoot well
then that's my fault well no it's no no
worries but it has Jolly Farm because
that's what I call my home uh it's a a
natural favorite and it's so sweet it's
just a really sweet little uh Left My
Heart in San Francisco look out there's
a monster
coming uh is very
strange monster coming just just uh and
the song Death Cab for Cutie is on this
record yeah which as we know is a band
name right uh so they obviously in that
band uh pay homage to the bonso I but
the intro and outros on this one too oh
okay see that's all right and I feel
like I have heard them and I did look up
Mickey's son and daughter based on your
recommendation which is great and then
they do their little I'm
bored on as opposed to Iggy pops I'm
bored which is pretty good song too um
Sound of Music on there anyway gorilla
is uh just a fun fun one and then this
Urban
Spaceman is different than tadpoles so
strange that that I would have this and
I I like uh well I have Urban Spaceman
but I don't have Tad how did that happen
and it has a whole Sloop other songs and
then there there's this sort of uh let's
let's make up and be friendly which was
obviously an American compilation of
probably tracks that just didn't have a
home yeah like rollinson and you know uh
turkey's King of the Scruff waiting for
the Wardrobe it's got to be a Roger
Ruskin spear you know uh really fun
stuff I recommend once again seek out
find their book and get the history uh
and you'll see you know Neil Enz of
course after the rutles I don't think
did but maybe one of the bonso reunions
oh really because he's got his own thing
going you know and he tours as Neil inis
and and is very popular successful and
whereas Roger Ruskin spear will get
Larry leg Smith and uh a couple of the
other bonso who may still be alive I
think several of them have have kicked
but uh we'll do these little reunions
and like I mentioned three bonso and a
piano which I hope you play a cut of
okay yeah all right I will I will you
can download you can upload maybe yeah
that be good so as you can see also
Roger Ruskin spe has solo stuff
out it's an insane cover and these are
the robots those are the robots wow holy
crap that's fantastic um man okay so you
that that's what's so funny to me though
is that it stuck with you for so long
before you actually heard it for real
for it was actually fin yeah because I
was at a a point where I was sort of
you know rebelling from my parents so I
was out living on this Fair site and and
looking for mentoring or guidance and
all and all of a sudden he these hippie
guys singing this ridiculous music that
was really quite charming and and there
was you could tell there was a lot of
reverence and uh play and I was like Wow
and that stuck with me yeah and and then
I saw what these guys were doing with
their Fantasy Fair and that stuck with
me and and so then I would
seek out the Mystic Knights of the Oingo
Boingo and find that they as you know
Oingo boingo's music is just fun as can
be yeah and uh the whole Danny Elfman
soundtrack stuff uh you know it's even
though once again he steals from
everyone you hear Nino Rota from felini
films and you hear all these different
places that he's stolen from steal from
the great and and imitate and celebrate
uh the the Cinematic feel so these
albums if you're
a an adolescent and you're in your
bedroom and you can't get along with the
folks and you have these albums that are
like little movies in your brain you can
watch you know the thing with chich Chin
chong you know with with creating these
scenes each each one you can
cinematically see them as they're being
told or acted out the fire sign theater
stuff Nick danger you know it's uh you
got these visuals when you know TV is
just commercial garbage and and you had
these escapes right
what's great too about this is I I
noticed on the back this it says da da
for now apparently they they were
originally going to be called the bonso
dog da da band like just be liter
literal yeah yeah but then they went to
dudah apparently originally daada though
it was one apparent this is this is it's
a very hotly contested amongst the
members of the group even so but I just
like that it's not just improv it's also
just like Tristan Zara it's just insane
it's just they're not just playing
they're not just doing Tri it's not just
like tribute jazz music it's not just
one thing it's very it's it is we have
not done it justice by talking about it
you can't explain it it's very I I don't
think I I cannot find a way like you
could say hey kind of sounds like he's
doing Winchester Cathedral there but
also it sounds like a Monty Python
version of that you know and it's prey
python so you know it's yeah it's very
hard to do justice and it's funny
because you have sort of the sound that
uh in America we might expect to hear in
a shaki's pizza when they used to have
musicians you know banjo player Dixie
you
know combined with Monty Python it was
just like no well is that interesting
have you met anybody from the band other
than the the radio interview yeah no I
haven't I wish yeah yeah yeah I would
like that uhuh um did this lead you down
other paths that we haven't talked about
like did the bonso dog pan leave you
elsewhere Lead You elsewhere in terms of
like other other comedy to seek out or
even other music to seek out or is it is
it its own thing uh it's sort of its own
thing I I uh have though these wacky
tastes that it has
encouraged uh and and there are
contemporary bands that have this kind
of fun I in fact had um what were they
called the the space Spacemen from the
planet so and so uh on my my radio show
I'd have uh bands that were usually
young folk who had humor in their music
yet good musicianship combination that
that Thrills me um like I said you know
I'm a a Frank Zappa fan yeah I'm
surprised nobody's picked it for the
show honestly it's not strictly comedy
of course but but there's so much
irreverent humor you know uh from
titties and beer to uh a a Jewish
princess to uh you know Disco Boy
there's there's comedy all through
Frank's stuff yeah plus incredible
musicianship yeah my friend Dave he said
when he auditioned for Frank it was one
of the hardest auditions he ever had and
Frank you know he kept up so he was
offered the the to be in the band but
shortly before Frank called him back
Ambrosia called him back so Dave ended
up in ambrosia but uh people that you
meet or or you can even find like Ruth
Underwood who played the The Vibes for
Zappa she'll talk about Franken then
demonstrate some of the complicated you
know St alonso's pancake breakfast
xylophone solo for you and it's insane
it's insane but so fun yeah it takes you
on a trip and and an adventure and has a
story to tell as well uh Frank's just
you know as everyone knows is is
Legend and I think his huge influences
were were the 12
atonal uh Records that his father had in
his collection he was like what is this
complicated stuff and grew to understand
it and bring it into his playing and
like the bonso have this improvisational
Jazz sort of foundation yeah and
everyone had to be great musicians
whether they
played a an iron press or uh uh the
washboard you know it just all these
strange instruments came into play is it
I and I don't know if you since you not
only are an artist but you teach artists
or you teach art there is that thing
that you're talking about with Frank's
zaa where there's this desire to pick
this stuff apart to figure it out I mean
is there something like for acting was
that was it acting for you were you're
just like I want to pick out these bits
and piece or was there any one
particular thing for you or is it just
that way for art for you gosh that's a
little complex and also a little muddled
but but but you know it's inspiring
though it I look because I teach film
acting mhm
and there really is no one technique
that works for everyone yeah so you need
to have uh the ability to create the
stimuli to get the emotional marks that
a character May demand and for one
person that stimuli may come from
Meisner fantasy charging uh for someone
else it's got to be actions and also
another person that takes sense memories
or emotional recall you know you have
the Stella Adler you have the the uh lee
strawberg you have the Meers some people
like the the uh Asian a martial art of
acting that Suzuki is has created or
some like an Bogart and Tina landow's
viewpoints version there's all these
different techniques that work
externally some are internally some are
very Zen oriented you just let the
character take over if the writing's
good and and it's interesting because
with great music it's the same way
there's some who have taught themselves
how to play and others who have spent
six hours a day slaving and learning
excruciatingly how to play their
instruments and then uh some who can
only read the music and others who can
improvise right uh so it's I see in your
question this profundity for me to uh
you know Co you know I I can't say that
I have the ability to uh make all these
magical things happen that these
musicians can but it is really fun to
see example in my uh improvisational
teachings that we just finished the
semester up at Sonoma State the uh
students have Revelations that yes I
have to be truthful in how I'm feeling
and start with that real energy than
rather than coming from something fake
or uh you know I give them tools
hopefully that they will learn not only
just how to do improv but take into
their lives sure and live a a sort of
deeper whatever they do deepen and and
uh yeah boy talk about
[Music]
tangent with big hungry Tiger's table
manners have no place dear dear dear de
dear de dear de
dear after they have eaten you they
never say their Grace dear
de hunting tigers can be ripping fun
like fre blind might see the Hunters Run
hunting Tigers out in IND
out in out in out in
India you all know how beastly tigers
are out him out him out in India they
bite they scratch they make an awful
fuss it's no use stroking them and
saying
puss but you know what's funny is like I
I lied when I said I'm not going to ask
you about back to the future and here's
why uh we're talking about this band
that is doing this very familiar thing I
think that most people at least when
they came out you're familiar with
that's the crap your parents listen to
right so this this imitation thing as
something of an okay mimic myself I mean
I would first have been aware of your
work as having to imitate a pretty
famous piece of film history and you're
doing it behind layers of makeup first
right right yeah so like I don't know
like I I do want to know where your
brain was when you're doing that and
like what the challenge was well the
first of all uh I I knew crisen the year
before he got the first back the future
really yeah I did a film with him up at
AFI and I found him a very compelling
really interesting actor I loved it and
I got his number and tried to stay in
touch and when the first film came out I
was like I know that guy he's knocking
it out of the park he was really great
and as uh time progressed uh followed
his career through River's Edge and The
Doors movie and all the other stuff dead
man great great work usually uh High
Caliber almost every every thing I saw
him in yeah and then when I came into
the opportunity to be his photo double
standin as I was told I was thrilled and
I even called him I said you know say a
good word for me I need to get my
medical so so my uh wife at the time
could have our second kid get our
medical coverage and he never called
back and I was going for these uh itic
fittings these uh basically mask these
makeup sessions
and uh when I had to do a screen test in
the young George meup I was like wow I I
guess they're going to have to have us
him at one place and me at the other
place on the camera at the same time
because I wasn't told Jack and it was
actually after the screen test was over
uh zamus turned to the cinematographer
dean Cy and says what do you think I
think we got Chrisman without the
trouble I was like what and and then I
heard from my makeup artist that chrisen
was not coming back I was like I
couldn't fathom how they were going to
do this film without him yeah now if you
look through history there's always been
imitators like Billy West was a famous
Charlie Chaplain imitator who uh I'm not
talking about Billy West from W talk not
know this yeah Billy West from I'm
talking the early 20th century he made
Charlie Chaplain movies as the Trap and
I don't know if Charlie sued him or not
for that brand new to me the studios may
have but there were other chaplain
imitators Larry Simmon I think did some
chaplain films and uh if you look look
back you know Darren on bewitch got
replaced and they got an actor who look
similar uh you know the studios either
by uh death or other obligations or
handcuffing with negotiations whatever
have from time to time had to replace
actors uh and you can look at it as a
tribute
to that great work of that actor you
could look at it as cashing in uh and
and abusing or you could look it as to
what they were in the back future case
is they had negotiations break down you
know chrisin wanted script approval wow
all right I don't think they were going
to give that even to Michael J fox sure
yeah uh then I'd heard he wanted the
same money as Michael and then uh they
offered him I think a 100,000 and he
counted with a million and and uh you
know so the as as it went you know the
first film was George's Story the second
film was Marty's story and the third
film was Doc's story so George was kind
of relegated to a support player yeah
and although had he come back for part
three he would have played Sheamus you
know the Michael as if Michael didn't
have enough to do already they gave it
to him so uh it was odd you know at
times I was like am I a scab here this
is weird because the first time Michael
saw me in the makeup he was like
Christman ain't going to like this and
and often the director even referred to
me as crisen and Leah at one point
introduced me to her mom after we shot
the film and here's the the actor who
played Crispen you know it's oh God what
am I doing oh Jesus luckily you know
this is 26 years ago now it's all of
course of course but and the and the
studio had announced all the original
actors were coming back to reprise their
roles and so they want to keep me a
secret and I could not forward my career
by advertising I everything that I tried
to do to promote myself the plug got
pulled mysteriously on or I got blocked
or took me more than uh 6 months just to
get photos uh from from the studio so it
was a a nasty kind of scene you know
thank you Spielberg and Company but uh
you know it's kind of water under the
bridge now there's a lot of distance and
yet there's still this Feud it's very
strange that chrisen and Bob Gail still
have this Feud Hatfield and McCoy and
I'm like you guys get over it seriously
do some reunions make it a fundraiser
for Michael's charity yeah yeah yeah and
the fans would love it too to see him I
would freak out with Tom Wilson you know
with with everyone from the cast doing
some big tributes yeah yeah yeah you
know I don't know how much longer Chris
Lloyd's going to last right sure uh
Francis Lee McCain you know we're we're
all you know the the young leads now are
all in their late 50s sure so it's it
would be good to celebrate with the fans
now in public and and keep raising money
for the Parkinson's Foundation cuz
really if it comes down to it it's all
about Michael they wanted Michael for
for U Marty McFly from the day one
basically but he wasn't available
because of family and so they forced
Eric stz down their throats because he
had just come off being a hit on mask
you
know poor kid yeah but he was good he's
a good actor very good method actor but
he wasn't doing the comedy that they
needed Michael's Michael's got this
great formula for comedy it's just
brilliant one of the few times you ever
see an actor call
cut it's like wow you know generally as
an acting coach I I tell my students
never cut yourself never call cut his
gold to be mind after the dialogue ends
yeah and and he said cut can we do it
over I and and believe it myself and
when Michael who knows his craft inside
and out says that the director has no
choice but say absolutely Michael let's
get it let's get it the way you want it
yeah you know because he really is is
great and is very smart hire competent
Talent both on your crew and your cast
and just sit back and solve problems of
course yeah yeah what did you do to I
mean was it just all right I'm going to
watch some stuff or I'm just going to
how did you just do it did you just know
the impression well I I because it's not
that simple it's not as simple as ah
here's an algorithm I've got the voice I
study I when I first started playing
Stan Laurel at Universal Studios if you
went to Universal between ' 87 and 2001
and you had your photo with Laurel and
Hardy Charlie Chapman Grouch marks
chances are it was with me that's great
and I was in between TV and film roles
and I got the opportunity to audition to
play Stanley and I remembered seeing
Laurel and Hardy as a kid but I didn't
remember very well I was doing
everything very silly I needed the work
though and I think I don't remember if I
would wore my underwear on the outside
or my bowler I'm sure was too big anyway
the actor playing Oliver Hardy knew my
work from a production where I played
mutio in Romeo and juli in Hollywood and
he says to the boss he says I know this
guy he's got talent I'll train him MH
and within two weeks I was doing a
passable Stan Laurel awesome and through
that it opened such uh a great place for
me of reverence for Stan Laurel's uh
talent because he often not only wrote
but he also edited he sometimes directed
H roach would only give him one credit
and that would be the starring credit
sure but he was uh weaned on theater uh
I became friends with Tony hos who was
the Grand Puba of the sons of the desert
the Laural and Hardy fan club that Chuck
mccan and Jim MC George
and Orson Bean and Charles MC jam mcab
oh gosh what's his name anyway they
started this International fan club
that's still thriving and uh Lois let me
look through Lois Laurel Stanley's
daughter let me look through his
scrapbooks wow and there's a photo in
there that I hope one day the public is
to see it's magnificent uh his father uh
Stanley Jefferson's father
was a theater producer and he built the
children a stage in the backyard and
there's a shot of Stanley he must be
about 10 years old directing his
brothers and sisters on this stage so he
grew up with this amazing honing craft
and even stole his father's suit uh tux
to perform the first time uh up in
Alston or laner wherever and his father
unbeknownst to Stanley was in the
audience and you know really give him a
good uh speaking to afterwards you know
what are you doing on the boards lad
anyway uh
so putting together Stan Laurel to do an
accurate and respectful portrayal took a
lot of doing and studying then about a
year later because the the actor God
bless him the little Tunisian man who
played Charlie Chaplain up at Universal
for many years who was a political
hire just to get him away from chason's
I think uh was just doing Charlie no no
great service he had stolen a a mime
from Marine World Marine lands uh act
you know tickling people behind the ear
with the straw and and was in shorts and
a bad no makeup except a mustache and
darken the eyebrows and and it was
infuriating me because Charlie needed to
be uhuh respected so we finally got the
uh the managers up there to get this guy
and make him in a proper costume and and
his Charlie got better uh and then put
chaplain together and and would replace
him on days off with other actors like
Billy Scutter who played Charlie for IBM
for many
years and then put together doing grouo
and I even got a a grouo chicko and a
Harpo and I remember one of our first
big gigs was for City of Hope a tribute
to the Marx family where Robert Marx
zeppo son and uh Harpo's son bill was on
piano
uh Gilda Robert's wife was being
honored anyway it was we got incredible
feedback from the marks Brothers family
that's awesome that was awesome that was
very nice and and in more recent years I
put a three stoes team together wow as
you can see my hair is just right for
playing Larry now so we'll do these gigs
uh that you know basically party gigs or
sometimes stage stuff uh but through
that work I learned to answer your
question such a long roundabout way
fascinating I love this stuff how to try
to find as Michael COV who was one of
stanislavski's star
students uh his theory of acting is to
find the character gesture okay find the
essence of that character through a
gesture and so chrisen you know had this
this forward this forward uh uh
gravitational pull pulling him forward
hello I'm leading with my forehead and I
have these gestures and and then the
voice is a placement hey you get your
damn hand
bi oh you know and so he has this very
uh singular energy and and feel and
character gesture that's is his Essence
he has this stuff going on in uh his
core that it took a while to get
grounded but it wasn't impossible to
find and that's why when I'm playing
George age 17 M I had found that stuff
and most people see George going to the
car in the background and picking the
fight with Biff again and kissing
Lorraine on the dance floor and I have
that Essence that crisen does so well
yeah and I like to look at it as more of
a tribute than a freaking ripoff people
you know chrisen fans God bless them I I
am a fan too but they'll they hate me
it's terrible things on I know for the
longest time I did a uh Reddit ask me
anything uhoh I'm Sor and most of the
folk were very lovely and friendly and
asking and other people were like you
piece of so and so and I'm like oh
brother oh my but you know it's and and
you're not alone a lot of people didn't
know I I had I still have people I'd say
about 35% of the folk out there that I
meet at fanc cons were like you weren't
George oh yeah I was in two and three
uhhuh and uh you
know it's it's it is what it is it's
kind of weird and uh uh I'm very happy
that I'm a part of the family and and
they're really lovely people across the
board I I don't care what Bob Gail or
chrisen Glover say about each other I
think they're both lovely people they
just you know are at each other and uh I
hope they get over it is there any truth
that chrisen Glover collected eyeballs
at one point that the story Tom Wilson
has told I don't doubt it didn't he
bring I think he brought that collection
on Letterman did he really okay there we
go that makes sense and I think they
were glass eyeballs okay okay well
that's fine I don't think they were real
ones that would say because that would
be a little strange though his you know
if you look at his books you know the
rat catching books that he's sort of
reinterpreted from uh the 19th century
and uh his music you know there's an
album for your show yeah that's a good
call he's supposed to be
walking he's a cook and you know he's I
don't uh pity him you know he he still
whines a lot but you know he's got a
castle I think in Romania or somewhere
and I think a home in Utah and probably
still has apartment in in Hollywood
anyway he's he's had a great career
makes a lot of money because of my work
on the film you know he settled out of
court when he said it's not fair that
you made another actor up to look like
me and misled people and used my footage
without giving me very much money right
so he got you know his three4 a million
dollars where I got maybe over the 26
years with residuals I I don't know if I
got a 100,000 Jesus Christ you know all
right that's fun yeah I I don't have
to anyway I celebrate actually the fans
in the movies I mean those are great
great stories you're do great things
with it though like like that's the only
way to do it justice I think because
other you know like just performing is
one thing but like if you're actually
doing something for charity that's
that's positive yeah I mean I still have
to put food on the table so I I can't
give everything but usually every
ComicCon I go to I I try to give a good
chunk back awesome to either
Michael's charity or Wendy Joe's charity
we spark do you have uh first of all
okay let's let's talk about Tad PES and
you should come back on we'll talk about
another album I we'll talk about I don't
give a [ __ ] what we do but what's a good
reason to listen to Tad poles uh if you
haven't heard it before oh well uh the
fun the the the
uh I'm the urban Spaceman of course the
pop hit on it is very catchy it really
is and uh the satire and the politics
and the social climb is referred to then
in that one hunting Tigers out in India
is very
silly English fun uh shirts is
irreverent silly yeah it's it is a lot
lot Monster Bash if you don't know the
original this is a good introduction Dr
Jazz Jazzy uh tubis in the Moonlight
silly fun the uh laughing Blues mhm I I
oh yeah uh was very happy to hear this
tune because I've uh as you may gather
I'm a a audio file and an archist of
early sound the actor who played Oliver
Hardy used to collect cylinder records
wherever we'd do appearances I'd help
him find cylinders finally I was like I
think I'm going to start getting these a
couple years into it and so I have
amassed a nice collection of cylinder
records and a lot of the ones I lean
towards are Vaudeville and Music Hall
especially comedians you know I have me
back on and we'll do a show on Marie
drer yeah I love Marie dressler's stuff
very a lot of it of course is based in
menaly which is derogatory now but some
of my favorite songs that come out of
mist Z are laughing songs uh uh an
actual known freed slave George W
Johnson late in his life recorded these
great laughing songs now they they don't
have titles that you you're going to
like but they're really lovely fun
things and they're all
you know and they go on and this sort of
thing so laughing Blues is a bit of a
laughing song and I have you know also
discs of various laughing water and the
okay laughing record and the uh you know
almost all the record labels would have
their own Laughing Song and then there's
popular jocular Dr Brown of Camden town
which is a laughing song I have all
these laughing I probably have 40 or 50
laughing songs in my collection wow
Spike Jones has a great laughing song uh
there's just so many great ones and so
to hear the bonso dog D dudah band or
daada band uh have a laughing song is is
uh very was very rewarding for me and
that's on this record it's pretty
fantastic like you can't not laugh again
that's the whole point but I mean that's
just it like it's wonderful and then you
know some of the uh the songs like by a
waterfall you know uh are kind of
psychedelic they even mention LSD in it
and canyons of your mind is definitely
psychedelic uh so it's it's it's great
for uh the trippy hippie culture that uh
hopefully will come back and get people
you know Back Into Love instead of
abusing immigrants that
be I don't want to get too political
here um I think you rest assur hopefully
most of my fans are big end of peace I
would hope so do you have anything where
can people find you online if anywhere
and B what do you have to promote I
don't know when this is coming out might
yeah well I've uh I've got my website
Jeffrey weissman.com which is in
desperate need of updating at least on
the news page but you can see my
different characters and everything I'm
talking about basically on one
connection one page or another look
alikes or other characters or my
teachings then I'm on Facebook I have a
fan page because my personal page has
been at 5,000 for 5 years uh and I have
to unfriend someone to add someone and I
know almost all my 5,000 friends and I
check their status every day anyway uh
so I have the fan page there and I have
a a Twitter account JF
Weisman uh and my Instagram is my name
Plus numbers and I don't know it off
hand I'm I'm still technologically
challenged somewhat uh but once again
you can uh find me uh and email me
through the homepage of my my website uh
I have a MySpace page
still do you hear crickets uh and there
there's uh also a film that I I worked
very hard on uh a lowbudget indie film
that I'm rather proud of uh I play a
very depressed epileptic widower who
befriends an adolescent girl who's being
abused in the foster care system and by
the local gang and uh it's like a
modern-day Shakespearean tragedy it's uh
sounds awesome it is pretty awesome it's
very very heavy uh called savior of none
and that's currently just started
streaming on on amazon.com there's that
word heavy again sorry I had to so sorry
why is what what's going on in the
future is there gravitational pool why
is everything's heavy and uh so there
there's uh savior of none uh I have a a
lovely part as a nefarious time traveler
in a pilot for a TV series called The
Traveler so if that goes to
series cool special effects and really
great team of folk that I'm working with
on that uh I've got various projects and
de velopment that I wish I could talk
about sure have me back on maybe I can
then yes oh yeah that that that will
absolutely happen we got to talk about
cylinders um okay guys thank you guys
for listening thank you so much for
doing this this is a lot fun I know it
took a while to put it together butet
Jennifer um you guys should go to oh my
God there's there's a bunch of crap but
I don't know when this is coming out
just go to lookingforward movie.com
that's my all improvised fake
documentary I brought these other
records that we didn't talk about like
for casual Affairs this is a very hard
one to find seen seen the cover but I've
never actually SE best ofel marel I
can't believe that exists that oh yeah
and there's absolutely nothing on it
that is great anyway we bring more
records out of the AR no no that'll be
fun um go to lookingforward movie.com
that is my improvised uh fake
documentary that is going on through
November uh that's that's all I'm going
to tell you to do do that go listen to
The Dan and Jay's Comedy Hour podcast
and yeah anyway thank you guys for
listening and as always have a good
thing thank you Jason thank
[Music]
you comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clam our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen address.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
five-star rating and a nice review you
can find us on facebook.com/ Comedy
onvinyl Twitter at comdy onvinyl and
find everything else at comedyon
vinyl.com a major portion of comedy on
vinyl has been underwritten by standup
records please visit standup records.com
for all your comedy needs and tune in to
the new standup channel available on the
Roku where you can also find select
episodes of this podcast
[Music]