[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast the year is 1995 the album is
shame based man the artist Bruce McCulla
and my guest live from New York why did
I say live that's stupid Ray Harington
it's Saturday night
Ray Harrington is with me thank you so
much for uh doing the show Absolutely
it's a it's a pleasure um I've I've been
uh nerding out uh listening to previous
episodes so it's it's a lot of fun to
finally be able to talk uh in part of
the
conversation well I hope you haven't
been listening to super early episodes
if you have I apologize uh you know
thoroughly oh it's podcasting that's the
world you know oh my God I mean I've
been doing it for almost six years now
but it's a world of difference I mean
you know but it's uh you you I sound
like a child at the beginning I'm like I
just we have no idea what we're doing um
and we've luckily uh this this episode
can go up a lot quicker because I don't
have to edit it because we have done
this album before but it's been a while
since we've talked about it and I it'd
be fun to get your fresh perspective on
it but before we do that you do have
something to promote so let's get that
out of the way I like to get that out of
the way uh if if people have a time
sensitive stuff so oh sure uh I am
starting a Kickstarter because I would
like to put
a moon
base on Jupiter oh wow I haven't figured
everything out yet sure um yeah but that
that's my plan is to build a base on the
moon may I suggest then take that to
Jupiter oh okay see that was going to be
my next question I was like well you
would normally you might refer to that
as a Jupiter base but you have decided
specifically you want it to the specs of
the moon but then you want to transfer
it to Jupiter and see what happens
exactly okay well that's fine I'm I'm
excited to see what's your goal right
now uh$ 13 billion 13 billion okay and
when does this start with and that's
with three question marks at the
end I didn't know Kickstarter allowed
you to do that that's great it's
difficult it's difficult uh I just
coughed into the microphone uh but you
do have a movie oh yeah um that's one I
meant specifically oh all right there's
also a a a documentary film called be a
man um and that is uh coming out on uh
October 7th mhm um on iTunes Amazon and
all of the digital webscape and uh I'm
very excited it feels like it's finally
going to exist that's awesome and tell
the audience a little bit about it I and
I apologize I did not get to watch it
yet I really want to but I you know I'm
not going to lie no it's totally fine I
think I spoiled the ending with the with
the Moonbase
tease because that's what it it's
originally it was going to be called
build a moon
base and we had some uh we had some
issues with that I guess uh JJ Abrams um
already copyrighted that oh wow yeah
he's got his hands in so many different
pies yeah he he sent me an email and he
said I already mailed that to myself so
you are s o and um and I was like s so
sounds like a stepdad phrase it really
does and I am now I'm sorry I'm riffing
way too much uh so be a man uh long
story short my uh my childhood was uh
sans's men uh I I grew up with my mother
my grandmother and my great-grandmother
I never had any men in my life and then
um cut to uh being an adult uh and and
being married and having a house and
then my wife told me she was pregnant
and I had a an existential crisis um I
panicked because I didn't know how to be
a dad or what that even looks like
because I never had had one growing up
so I decided to do all of these manly
things that I thought made you a man
when I was a little kid
and um so I set out to kind of take that
journey and uh and the documentary uh
follows that Journey well see now I'm
even more excited to see it um that's
fantastic and I like that you picked an
album with man in the title I didn't
realize it until I was maybe like
halfway through Rel listening and I was
like oh this is actually there's a good
portion of this album that is um
mirroring a lot of my own internal
struggle uhhuh of masculinity and
because I I don't know I'm you know it's
2016 I am
33 um so I grew up in that era where I
was raised with um like Roseanne and and
you know Wonder Years and things like
that that's those were the men that I
saw and as I grew up it turned into like
MacGyver and Magnum
PI and so then I was stuck as a stunted
manboy trying to figure things out
before my son was born and I was like
okay so I'm going to do the fighting and
the drinking and the cars and um and
it's it's insane the the the journey was
fascinating and terrifying at the same
time um you know I thought I would do I
thought I I thought I would do funny
things you know being a comedian and and
being put in situations I was like oh
this will be funny right and then every
time it was being
confronted with uh with this weird
Middle School thing that was inside me
like this tiny little little person
inside me was like oh no all of these
things are getting dredged back up and
so I went from being you know a pacifist
to being uh just standing in a boxing
ring with Vinnie Penza five time world
champion boxer oh my God and uh and
apparently I had pissed him off by
asking him to do this and so that did
not go well and just getting to relive
some fun childhood stuff uh riding
around in a in a laan uh from the back
to the future movies that was fantastic
and and you know talk to a lot of great
comics and it's it's fun it's a love
letter to my son and and it's very funny
and um I'm excited for it to exist
that's awesome um but moon bases uhhuh
yeah yeah yeah moon bases are what's
important that is why we're here kids um
so my God so I'm looking through the
track listing again of of this album so
it's 1995 so you're you're a few years
younger than me my guess is you didn't
hear this when it was released but or am
I totally
wrong um I don't remember when it hit me
and I think that's that's probably
something that uh most people uh say I I
I want to say I think I came across this
I was in high school and um I came
across it in a in a bookstore which is I
think where you should come across like
Fringe comedy oh yeah is in a bookstore
and uh and saw the CD and it blew my
mind I was like wait this Bruce Mulla
from Kids in the Hall has an album right
and I thought it was going to be standup
right sure and so I I paid for it and I
and I went home and I was so excited to
listen to it and the first time like
from the first track I went oh this is
very
different and um and but I was hooked
like immediately I I think normally
something like that would turn me
off in what way well I think it comes
across uh oh boy like if you aren't
immediately sold on Kids in the Hall
sure okay yeah I think it can come
across incredibly precious oh definitely
definitely I I remember when somebody
first uh I think it was benac or
thrilling adventure hour he's the one
who uh first picked this for the show
and we listened to it and I'm like I
love Kids in the Hall and I especially
love Bruce McCulla but I'm like holy
[ __ ] this is just like this is a 20s
something making an album about a 20
something brain a particularly brilliant
20-some but like he's he's he's just
this is what it's like to make an art
project is what it feels like so I
completely understand what you're saying
yeah but I think I like I wasn't even in
college at the time and and so I was I
was primed to have the The Angst and the
sense of having already judged the world
and found it
wanting so I was prepared to be like yes
this is what it is this is give me more
of your reality yeah and I I do partic
I'm sorry I I do particularly like his
his point of view and and the fact that
that is mixed it's so dripping in irony
while at the same time being having this
sincere cynicism to it if that makes any
sense I think there's a
beautiful um tragedy in throughout the
whole thing I think the subtext of
everything
is I I was thinking about it earlier and
it's like it's this idea of everyone
being a victim of
circumstance from the the very very rich
to the very very poor um you're just
stuck wherever you are yeah either in a
relationship there's a lot of like
angsty break upy feeling in in the film
film in the album in the sound film and
um there's the but there's also this
this hope to it that comes across like a
like a minimum wage hero yeah like he's
going to don't worry we're all stuck in
this crappy job but you're going to
you're going to love these tiny Quiet
Moments yeah I I I I the more I think
about it and the more I W you know and
I'm always going to be comparing this to
what I see on Kids in the Hall uh just
because that was my first exposure to
him I feel like I don't know I'm I'm I'm
trying to Peg where he's going to fall
at the end of his career and what he's
going to mean to the world of Comedy
because he's somehow in one of the most
popular sketch groups of all time but
like you say Fringe is a very good word
for what this album is it's its own
thing completely yeah and from what I
understand of of like articles I've read
and and interviews and things like that
he's definitely I read his Memoir as
well um he's especially at that time he
was just running away from any semblance
of uh normal and and
expectation and so I think part of this
is is that sense of just well I'll put
something out that I only I want to hear
y yeah and then people embraced it and
he was like oh no and and then he did um
the the drunk baby project and uh and I
still love that as well yeah so I think
there's a that's a very Bruce Mulla
thing like let me oh you want to like me
then prove that you want to like me
right yeah and there and there's that
tone throughout the whole thing there's
that tone in his acting even there are
times when I feel like he is pushing me
to either not enjoy him or really
appreciate what he's doing to push me
and and that is such a struggle to be a
fan of him like I I am a tried and true
like deep in my bones fan of Bruce
McCulla I mean Kids in the Hall is my
biggest influence of uh just having a
sense of humor and what I find funny and
I always loved the um like the absurdity
of reality that Kids in the Hall showed
and and you know Finding very very tiny
mundane things and and just expanding
and expanding and expanding until the
most normal thing becomes just crazy and
uh you know I would watch Kids in the
Hall thinking oh I love this tone I love
uh what they are doing and what they are
saying and I think listening to the
album was the first time I realized oh
that that's not a tone that the show has
the show is a collection of five
different people's very specific uh
sense of humor and Bruce is is I think
it's just it's that base tone that that
everything carries through it's true
yeah that that is one reason why while
the show is still rewatchable it is I it
is one of those things that I can't
really passively watch I can passively
absorb like a Monty Python cuz I love M
python but this this if if we're going
to Kids in the Hall I it's I have to
actively watch and be ready to watch and
that could just be my brain but it is so
it's it's jarring from one sketch to the
next even if they're sort of connected
because there's all those voices there
and the fact that the guy who made this
album is also the guy with a cabbage for
a head is at this same time like it it
makes sense but it also feels like there
there's almost this thing of
specifically with a sketch like that
that is obviously making fun of a lot of
different tropes in sketch while it's
making fun of those tropes it's also I
feel like I feel like there's a part of
him as the pretentious 20-some that he
was that was like well are you laughing
at me or are you laughing at the wrong
thing like it just does feel like a test
no matter what and while I I I kind of
like that challenge personally it's I
can see why it might turn some people
off oh yeah I think I think something
like this is such a oh it's a it's a
very academic Pursuit and um I don't I
don't know why it hit me the way it did
when I first heard maybe because it was
so different um I think it I think it
fits in a different time um you know
that kind of the the spoken word um
sensibility to it I think fits in an
earlier kind of exploratory comedy World
um I'm thinking like uh like fire sign
theater like the the more theatrical
kind of Radio based comedy and then Here
Comes This Album from uh basically like
the grunge comedy
troop um that is is very unexpected yeah
no absolutely I if if uh if we're you
know i' honestly I'd never heard anybody
refer to them as grunge comedy but I do
feel like at least in terms of period
that's absolutely perfect and in terms
of aesthetic cuz they're not Punk they
they have a punk aesthetic to them in
that and probably all because of Bruce
cab but uh yeah there is definitely that
yeah I think it's gr because I think
Punk would be I think everybody in the
troop would if if they were surrounded
by like a punk kind of Ideal they'd be
like it's a little loud in here yeah
it's absolutely true it's it's that
would be too that would not be Canadian
enough this is this is absolutely
perfectly Canadian at the same time um
yeah yeah and ironically I mean you have
uh vigil on the album and you know the
it's a kind of Ode to the Seattle scene
when KK Cobain killed himself and um I
REM oh that's how I got oh my God so I
got the I got the CD and I was super
excited that I had the CD and I had my
first computer and uh cuz yeah that's
right around the right time I had my
first computer so I I burned the CD on
my computer I you know just I ripped it
there and I would listen to it on my
computer and it screwed up the track uh
listing so vigil was always the first
thing that came up and that's how I was
introduced to the album was that that
was the first track and I was like this
isn't even really funny this is right
this is just heartfelt and sad and and
it's but beautiful yeah and um and I
still listen to that and and and I'm
impressed with it and I feel like oh
this album just is a perfect sales pitch
for why Bruce McCulla needs to write um
like essay formed no like just give me
books that are just tons and tons of
short stories and n and like little uh
essays and and things like that and I
will just devour all of them yeah he
yeah and the more I'm thinking about it
I'm trying to figure out what his I I
want to know I something like that would
be perfect because I would like to know
what his evolution has been mentally as
a comedian because I mean he's even
talked about recently how he's you know
I've calmed down a bit since I was in my
20s but like has he I want to know
because he's made some real you know and
I don't mean this in an insulting way
some real pedestrian stuff since then
but it's it's money-making stuff I do
want to know I want to know creatively
where this guy's brain is at right now
like if he were to do a new album today
what is that what does that become is it
now I actually speaking of which I have
not heard drunk baby project so how does
it
compare how similar or different are
they um I think it's more musical okay
than uh than shame based man uh and
there's a couple of tracks on there that
I tend to skip okay uh because once I
think they're more once you get the the
initial joke it's like okay this was
great and then let's move on to the next
one okay but there's some stuff on there
that's really really great um uh I'm
struggling to come up with an example
because they're mostly songs sure sure
but uh yeah there's some fantastic stuff
on there and um it's still great it's
still very good um but like I did some
reading and uh I guess sham based man
kind of went on a print and fans were
asking Bruce where they could get uh
shame based man he's like I don't know I
can't even get it myself so he released
uh drunk baby project on his own wow you
know in answer to that well here now you
can get this that's great so yeah
there's that sense of and I think with
something like a shame based man or a
drunk baby project they're
so they're so uh just in a passing
moment they're so tied to a very
specific moment in his life in the
listener's life and and you know you're
creating these these collections of
little sketches or songs or you know
poems whatever um I think that I think
each one of those albums would be compl
completely different even 6 months
later yeah like oh I really like this
part but I had I had a better thing come
into my head you know a week later yeah
that's a good point um do you so in
relising to I don't know how recently
you relisten to it but do you have you
probably don't even need to do you have
a favorite track off of the whole thing
uh I I did relisten to it last night and
um I I do it occasionally I feel like I
need to there are moments where I'm like
I need to get back to certain comedy
things in my life um I will rewatch
Roseanne from time to time uhhuh because
it's uh a phenomenal sitcom like it's in
my mind it is the that's the top of the
of that particular Mountain so I like to
revisit that and then I have you know
comedy films I'm like okay those are the
ones that I aspired to um so this album
is is easy for me to revisit as a
comedian as a a standup because I don't
feel um the fear of of something rubbing
off the wrong the wrong way okay the way
I would if I was listening to a standup
album like uh you know Kyle Kain I think
is a fantastic stand-up comedian I'm
that's like the last big fan moment I
had before I was too far into comedy to
be like Oh I'm a
fan um as an audience member yeah um but
even now if I go back and listen to like
death of the party or something it's I
listening to it in a very different way
and kind of pushed back a littleit a
little bit just because I don't want
something to get into my mind and then
I'm writing a joke that's too similar or
my voice starts to sound that way yeah
um so with this I can just I can just
wallow in it yeah no yeah and not worry
about that I I I have the the luxury of
not being a standup at least for that
that uh that part of it um but I I I I
completely get that do you think we this
is going to go off on a tangent a bit
but do you think that fear is unfounded
do you think it's just our own paranoia
cuz I have it with other things not
stand up particularly but do you think
it's do you think it actually would
affect you if if you if you dug
deeper um I
think I think in any creative form I
think you get nervous that you're just
going to I think it's a sense of being
found out yeah yep and feeling like a
fraud uh like if somebody looks too
closely it's like oh know you're going
to see my influences right right um
because there's a difference between
influence and and just outright oh
you're doing that person sure you know
um I think with standup it's a little
harder because like you can watch a
sketch and go I can feel their influence
here clearly whoever wrote this loves
you know XYZ whatever sketch troop or or
you know you can I mean you can look at
a sketch and go oh this person liked
this era of NL right um but it's not
coming through in a sense of oh that
person just sounds like that that writer
right um with standup because it's just
a singular thing it's just a voice and
and you're talking and you're you're
telling a joke there are rhythms and
cadences that can come I mean they can
just be ripped whole cloth from somebody
else and when a comedian is starting
it's like you can you can look at
somebody on stage and go oh okay here
are the two comedians they like the most
because they sound exactly like them
right yeah I mean and you you kind of
let it become your own um you have less
to mask you if it is just you and your
voice and a microphone yeah and it
worries me because I mean so many times
comedians will come up with a joke and
or a structured thing uh where there's
like a punch right here and then you'll
see uh you know an established National
comic like on television or in a special
or something like that and they they do
that same same exact thing and you go oh
and it's like you're mentally just
crossing it off the list all right don't
do that anymore um because comedy's a
finite thing and and the way you
structure a joke is just going to be
there's only so many ways you can do it
uh when you can't use editing or visuals
or anything else um so yeah I think
there is a a guarded sense there at the
same time I think as creatives we all
tend to get a little too worried about
that M and
uh you know I went through a phase as a
standup where I was like
I'm uh I'm throwing away so much
material because I'm afraid that even
the topic has been touched before right
right and it took me a a little while
for me to finally just just go I mean
everything's been talked about yeah
there isn't a single topic in the world
that hasn't been dealt with in standup
in some capacity sure so you know you
just have to make it your own you have
to talk about it from your perspective
and and not worry about that um but yeah
I think there is a little more safety
because I don't want I don't want my
inner monologue to start to carry the
rhythms that another comedian has I get
that I get that and that that does make
sense and luckily the bonus here with
with a Bruce McCulla I don't think
anybody ever could even try to mimic
what he does there's no I mean and I've
I've tried to do an impression of the
man it just doesn't you can't it's not
he is otherworldly in that way to the
point where yeah I feel like you can
absorb this I mean he's he's dealing
with again some classic themes like you
say no nothing hasn't been touched on
but he does it in these ways where you
have no you have zero idea what he's
actually talking about um right but
there's some beautiful thing uh I mean
your original question was uh you is
there a track that's like my favorite
track on the album I think it's uh when
you're fat I think it's the name
it um
because on its surface it could be seen
as a you know I think if I saw the the
track title on a lot of different
comedians albums my I my eyes would just
roll right in the back of my head yeah
um but it's this sad modlin song about
this poor woman who is
alone and and feeling very alone on her
birthday and just H everything's it's
just a sad depressing Moment In This
Woman's life and it is
so funny because it's it's it's it takes
away all you know um drama it's just a
person's life and there's a line in it
uh and I'm not going to do it justice I
can't remember it exactly but it's like
you you know your hand slips under the
cover she's laying in bed your hands
your hand slips under the covers and you
you know you climax and then you roll
over and think about your student
loans and I ruined the Cadence of it the
Rhythm everything but that moment I
remember even back in high school
hearing that and being like Oh my God
that's so normal you know it's so
overwhelmingly normal and then as I grew
up I went through college and I really
liked you know this the idea of this you
know hyp
specific uh normal reality being
completely absurd and now I think about
it as a 33 old with a kid and you know
crushing student loan debt I'm like oh
yeah I know you I I know you yeah yeah
so it's just a beautiful
moment uh yeah I think that's there's
there's so much of that in his in his
albums and Kids in the Hall and I think
anybody that is a fan of Kids in the
Hall can watch the show and a sketch
will pop up and you just kind of
inherently know who that's coming from
yeah that's true that is true it's
it's that that is the challenging thing
about his work and about their work
where you know there are a lot of comedi
I I
interview you know every few weeks I
interview somebody new and everybody's
got their own perspective most of them
are standups or at least actors but most
of them are stand-ups and you know you
will frequently get and I won't
necessarily try and I won't go out of my
way to disagree with it but there are
people who are of the opinion that well
whatever makes people laugh is that
that's comedy then that's that's all it
is but this is a thinker to the point of
frustration and and is it who would you
do you is this the kind of thing you
would recommend to just any comic or do
you have to feel it out and just say oh
this is your you know if they've never
heard of it oh this is your taste maybe
you'd like this like is this an album
that you've gone out of your way to
recommend to
people uh when I was younger I I would
you know scream it from the hilltops I I
would I would sing it is it sing it from
the hilltops and then shout it from the
rooftops it's broadcast it from the
Moonbase I would broadcast it from the
moon that thank you and we need to get
that movement happening um I would tell
everybody about it but it was in that
very uh College vein of just look what I
found yeah and and I'm aren't aren't I
the best for having found this before
you um but I think now I've gotten I
don't know if it's jaded or cynical of
me to think it I think no I think it's
just more understanding that comedy is
incredibly subjective and there are
whole worlds of Comedy that are for
different people and not at all for
others and I think I think this I think
shame based man is one of those secret
slided across the table kind of moments
where you go I think this might be for
you
right um I certainly wouldn't recommend
it to everybody sure have you connected
to other Comics over I mean have you
ever had a discussion about this with
with another standup or other comedians
of any stripe yes a couple um I think
it's a It's tricky because you tend to
meet uh it like if somebody's a big fan
of Bruce McCulla and shame based man
they are automatically a fan of Kids in
the Hall I think it's a thing I don't
think the ven diagram of somebody who is
a lover of Shame based man and not at
all a fan of Kids in the Hall May
there's one person and it might be
Bruce but I yeah so I've had the
conversation with people and I love you
know waxing philosophical about the
entire uh the entire UA right um but uh
like my one of my closest friends uh is
a huge huge Kids in the Hall fan a big
fan of Bruce and this album was actually
one of those things that we originally
connected on we were working at a movie
theater and um we were both
projectionists and and this is how we
came and found each other which sounds
like a perfect uh track that would be on
a Bruce album right these two
projectionists these lonely men in the
in the night finding each other in the
flickering Celluloid right like that's
just something that he would do and we
we just loved talking about it and and
you know quoting things back like people
like normal people do with the Simpsons
that's what we were doing with this and
um and uh and then there's an immediate
shame washing over me because we uh uh
so long story short I had the
opportunity to open for uh Kevin
McDonald um a couple years ago and I was
so excited and and very happy to do it
and we hit it off like immediately I
love Kevin Kevin's great and um we were
like best buds for the weekend it was
just it was wonderful and so the next
time um uh the the troop was getting
together to do a
tour Uh Kevin hooked me up with some
tickets and I was so excited and we went
and we watched the show and I had this
beautiful you know Middle School moment
in the in the crowd that and I could
watch the show and it was great they
were fantastic they were nothing was
lost it it was still just as sharp mhm
and um uh and there the bite was still
there like it it still hurt a little bit
which was great that's awesome and uh
and so afterwards uh we went backstage
and and I tried to compose myself and I
brought Tom My my friend Tom with me the
the projectionist and uh he was very
excited and he can be cool in a moment
and I a way I can't um because I'm too
in my own head sure and so we we met
everybody and everybody was fantastic
overwhelmingly normal and inviting and I
just kind of stood there uncomfortable
and all of these feelings of like I I
need to tell Bruce McCulla these things
uhhuh right but I don't want to be that
person sure especially around a guy who
is kind of just he he exudes a sense of
not wanting that right right and I made
it through most of the the time we were
all hanging out and right at the end I
just kind of let everything fall out my
mouth and I was just like I just think
you're great and you've been a bit of
inspiration for me and I have both of
your albums and you should really write
a book and I was just getting like
ushered out of the room by Tom I wasn't
getting kicked out but my friend Tom was
like pushing me out of the room like
just get out of here um and it it that
will eat away at me for the rest of my
life I don't know I feel like that's
that's the experience you're going to
get with Bruce Mulla I yeah is there
ever a moment where you can be like oh
yeah it was totally cool and he was no
he was super cash no that's and if you
if you want to go based off of the
character he portrays I was just
thinking about it he's like a more
slightly more approachable Andy calman
character uh and I never say calman I
don't know where that came from he is I
feel like he lives for the theater of
life to the extent that he's perfectly
happy knowing that other people are
awkward in his presence and that might
be in that way you made it perfect for
him so therefore you did have the
perfect Bruce McCall experience
yeah I think you're right I think you're
absolutely right because he does there's
a very short list of people that would
terrify me if I knew they were watching
my set right just like to the Bone like
oh I don't know if I could go out there
and the the list is like two people MH
and it's Bruce McCulla and the other one
is Stuart Lee but I mean that's that's a
whole different story but yeah um yeah
cuz there's a sense of even if you were
getting along with him and everything
was great and and you knew each other
fairly well at that point there I feel
like at any moment he could just turn
and it would it would all crumble in
front of you like you're both he strikes
me as the type that you're both laughing
at a thing that just happened and then
he just abruptly stops and goes now why
do you find that funny yeah that is that
is there needs to be a word for that I'm
sure the Germans do have one but that is
absolutely correct that is exactly you
get that from just his presence just
from just from looking at him and you
get that from if you look at a photo of
him from 1992 to a photo of him
yesterday there and I and I've heard him
interviewed he's a perfectly nice
congenial fellow however there is
something about him that scares you and
that's okay I mean I think that's kind
of cool but at the same time it's just
like why how did he accomplish that why
do I feel this way what does it say
about me uh but I completely relate to
it I I think you and I are both on the
same wavelength about we feel about him
the same way although you I mean you got
to me I don't I wouldn't have even
gotten those words out I don't know how
you manage that that's oh and please
please don't don't take that as me like
name dropping in anyway I'm sure he
would not remember a second of that
interaction but I will never be able to
forget it of course cuz it will always
be a regret like I should like I'm going
to replay that over and over like how
could I have been
cool how could I have done it and I
think that feeds into the grunge
mentality Bruce McCulla is this is going
to sound ridicul I think he is the KK
Cobain of sketch
comedy I'll take it I I think I I think
that's that's not imperfect that is that
that is a very uh that's really great I
guess we're just lucky that uh you know
uh we still got him you know I'll take
that um my God you know if if I ever get
him on the podcast I I won't necessarily
say who told me that unless you want me
to but I feel like I should be like
somebody once told me that they think
you're the H com and then I want to see
his reaction was he a big man in flannel
you know it was him it was him and this
feeds into my uh weird uh you know like
we were talking about at the beginning
um you know I didn't have a dad growing
up I have I understand and deal with the
fact that I have um daddy issues right
and they're going to come out in in this
sense of you know working with people I
admire sure um especially in comedy and
and and so all of that stuff is just
feeding into me with a guy like Bruce
McCulla where it's like oh you're
detached you're emotionally unavailable
and you hide your feelings like this is
a this is a perfect magnetic connection
where whatever isms he has perfectly
match like another Lego piece to these
isms and I'm like yeah you can go ahead
and absolutely emotionally wreck me go
ahead I will clean your car I I like
that in terms of uh what that probably
does to your your brain specifically
your brain in terms of its receptiveness
to different types of Comedy there are
people who I've had to force myself to
be interested in certain comedy uh I've
had to really push myself I I wonder if
it's the same for you is is there do you
find any kind of Comedy completely out
of reach for you or are you pretty open
to listening to new [ __ ] um I mean there
was a period of time uh like my my late
College days and my early standup days
kind of overlap a little bit and in that
time I was definitely in that that vein
of uh oh I've already figured out what's
good and what's bad yeah right and let
me tell you who's bad you know um I
think as I've gotten older and more
experienced in comedy I think is more
the the more important part of it um I
can appreciate the craft of just about
any standup or sketch or anything like
that I think when it drifts towards
more uh being more absent
of passion or or you know somebody
really loving what they're doing there
um I think it's easy to see that and
that's when I tend to go I I oh it's
homework you know there and there are
things that feel like homework um some
seasons of Saturday Night Live feel like
homework when I'm in it and I'm watching
and and my wife jokes about it and she's
like no I get why you have to watch it I
just really don't want to right now sure
yeah and uh but then there's moments
where it's magical and I'm happy and and
and I love that it's there but I like
that you attribute that idea of it
feeling like homework to being more of a
lack of passion than your uh
unwillingness to give something a shot
because it does seem like you're pretty
open-minded when it comes to this stuff
sure and and I mean on a good day that's
how I want to that's how I want to be at
least uh portrayed I I at least want my
external image to be that um I mean
inter there yeah if it's like if it's
super hacky kind of stuff I'm just like
I don't I have no interest into this
this is not for me yeah um but I think
that comes with just really believing
that there's comedy for everyone
everyone is going to have a certain type
of Comedy that's because everybody's
sense of humor is different sure and it
depends on how you're broken yeah it
absolutely you know what way are you
broken you'll probably laugh at
something in a different way it's
absolutely true um I and and I I really
want I I don't know enough about here's
the here's where I here's where I piss
off those annoying commenters and I say
oh I don't know such and such and then
they get angry uh but I really don't
know enough about his his backstory I
feel like I can infer a ton from his
material but I also feel like I can
maybe infer nothing from it because he
also could be playing the character of
this broken man you know it that's
that's what's so damn challenging about
it I'm sure he's dealt with some of this
stuff the addiction thing I know has
been he's talked about before I know
that there there is addiction in his
past in bits and pieces of that kind of
a broken childhood um but I don't know
the specifics I don't know if I want to
um but that's that's part of where the
challenge comes from yeah I think I'm
okay with not knowing his his past um I
think my my interest is definitely more
in how the troop works and and worked in
the past how they found each other I
know they've all talked about it you
know um over and over and over
especially especially
especially H oh
no you caught yourself I did it you
caught yourself I'll see myself C out
um but especially since uh the Advent of
of podcasting I think they've probably
had to talk about it so much sure uh
that they they really do need to just
make the book just write the Kids in the
Hall book and and get it done um because
I am fascinated with it I think because
they are so different and and you know
there's definitely been a lot of you
know infighting with them and but the
fact that they're still kind of a family
and come together that's interesting you
know how these very different voices
work together is is a fascinating thing
I think the individual
story um yeah not I'm not as interested
because I think that that part is more
personal than maybe I'd care to get with
them oh for sure yeah I mean you you
it's a thin line to watch but you're
absolutely right in terms of in terms of
just the fact that they stay together is
kind of shocking and like you say there
that if you can still uh put together
brilliantly biting satire that's just I
don't know I don't get that I don't get
how you do it I think that's great that
they still do it but uh that's but maybe
that's part of the because like you and
I are both are in sort of in that world
of comedy and maybe that's why we're
we're uninterested
or or less interested
in you know the more like childhood kind
of experience and growing up and and you
know becoming fully fleshed human beings
sure than we are in uh when things
started to happen like any any of the
SNL um Memoirs and things like that if
someone could just just like rip the
book in half yeah where it starts when
they got a phone call from you know a
casting agent or something like that
that's where it gets interesting for me
because that is such a
machine that I want to know more about
that it's like I don't need to know if
you were molested you know I I
appreciate it I understand but it's just
so cliche
uh that's awful I feel
[Laughter]
terrible oh my God yeah well you know
I'm actually hoping no well now I'm just
gonna I I don't want to I don't want to
say that this is definitely going to
happen but I might have a pretty good
like SNL half of the SNL or Story coming
up on the podcast in a few months is
what is what I'm hoping so oh that's
awesome yeah I fingers not as not you
know it's not going to be Lauren
Michaels or anything but my my my hopes
are that we're going to have a at least
half of the story um and I'll tell a
little tell you a little bit about some
of the stuff that we've already
discussed when we stop recording because
I can't again either way but yeah you're
absolutely right that that that is one
of those stories that hasn't been
properly told it has been definitely
told from certain perspectives but you
don't
picture and you know his written by
winners ET ET Etc so um yeah I uh yeah
I'm excited to do you should tell me any
questions you've got regarding the
history of SNL because you might
actually have some more intelligent
questions than I do I wouldn't doubt it
um oh my gosh that's yeah now I don't
have to do that right now do I yeah
absolutely right now 100% okay so uh
start with the the molesting question I
think that start there and then just see
where that goes just ask everybody that
I regardless of who it is that comes on
the show I just assume that that's
happened um right just I think either
that or start a new
podcast and you have guests on and the
all you do is ask one question right at
the beginning MH uh have you been
molested and what was that like and then
just leave it I really didn't want to
talk about this I'm so sorry I we're
getting wildly off topic for my Moonbase
discussion I know I where did where the
hell did the Moonbase go I All I'm gonna
say is
this uh the money will come with the
moon base it's just going to take The
Upfront cost uh sports teams are going
to pay a
mint if you think basketball is
interesting
now wait until they have less gravity
and slam dunks become a three minute
event you guys you guys got to get on
top of this second this thing goes live
you guys got to make sure you're giving
what kind of uh so I'm assuming you got
some like postcards and stuff people get
for putting giving you money post oh
yeah we have a whole tiered system on
Kickstarter for gift packages um uh some
of the solid stuff is in the middle
brackets show
$150,000 um you can actually name uh the
the NBA team oh that's great um and it's
it's fairly simple you get to you don't
get to name it just whatever you want
you have to pick from a list um it's all
the existing NBA teams but instead of
the um town or city in which they're
based it's just
Moon so it's like the moon hornets and
the moon
bulls and I like it because it just it
turns them all into terrifying creatures
it really does that's absolutely true
yeah like Chicago Bulls oh yeah that's
the NBA team uh Chicago or sorry Moon
blls and you're like okay well we need
to fix that
problem much more for formidable at that
point um yeah oh and to to get back to
what you asked about like listening to
Comedians and and being afraid of
letting them creep into your voice I
went on a nor McDonald YouTube binge
last night and now I'm terrified that
this is starting to creep into nor
McDonald territory you should just
embrace it my my buddy Allan on my other
podcast was just doing nor McDonald on
the show the other day like he was just
doing an impression of him just he's
like let's let's try this out for 5
minutes and it was uh it was it was
relaxing but I understand you you've got
a rep to protect I get that oh what
little rep I
have okay
so why listen to shame based man if you
haven't heard it before if you are a fan
of Kids in the Hall what's a good reason
well then I mean if you're if you are a
fan of Kids in the Hall you've kind of
already answered that question right
it's another thing that they did um
because again keeping in that Grunge
mentality uh it's like when that band
was doing their thing and then they
break off and then you're just left with
Eddie veter you know and you're like oh
man I I I wonder what the the old basist
is doing you know nothing it's just
Eddie that's your only choice um uh so I
think people tend to seek out those
things I've done it I'm guilty of it um
I've I've think I've I think I have
ingested every single media thing that
exists that they've done uh as offshoot
projects yeah um but for for Shan Bas
man the the S the recommendation comes
from I mean just how singularly Bruce
Mulla it
is and listening to Sham Bas man feels
like you're getting a a
concentrated like pitch meeting for uh
an entire season of the show
right like here are all of this is where
his sense of humor lives and you get to
experience that for a while and um and
some of it is fantastic and other parts
you're like I don't know if I'm maybe
I'm not keeping up with this or maybe
he's not telling me the in the best way
but there is a miscommunication
happening somewhere but that's a that's
a beautiful part of it because then like
a line will hit you I think his writing
is phenomenal yeah his writing makes me
want to chop off my
hands and I don't know why I would do
that I think you could chop one off and
then you're just kind of stuck holding a
like holding a Cleaver with the other
one going I didn't think this
through cuz how am I going to get this
other one it's so true so but no yeah
his writing is fantastic and I think
having such a unique kind of Spoken Word
album allows that to shine and don't
listen to it expecting like a a
beautiful voice to be singing right yeah
I that was the other thing I forgot to
bring up is that like that's not yeah
that's absolutely not what you're
getting but it's also at the same time
very satisfying that that is the voice
that's coming out because you that's
that's the voice you hope Bruce would
have I think um I it's like I'm I'm
reminded of a a sketch that was on I I
don't know if it was on the US uh airing
but um I found it forever ago and it's
it's just Bruce McCulla walking out onto
the stage um uh you know in the Kids in
the Hall uh studio and he turns on a
boom box and it's just like a very
simple like drum beat happening and he
just starts slowly and very awkwardly
dancing to it like with like a Todd the
way a toddler would dance almost and
then the beat would drop and he'll like
freeze for a second and then it'll come
back in and then there's just a close-up
of his face the the the Beat Drops and
he goes check it out and then it goes
right back into it if like that's a
that's a litmus test for somebody's
sense of humor if you laugh at that
that's the type of Comedy for you and if
you and but I completely understand why
meanwhile I'm laughing my ass off at it
but I completely understand why somebody
would go what is this and why why are
people laughing right yeah
100% that's that's that's a perfect uh
condensing of of why to listen to this
thing and why it's kind of beautiful um
um so all right Ray Harrington where can
people find you online where can people
find your movie you go from there okay
uh I am on Twitter Ray Harrington uh on
Facebook uh whatever the weird URL is uh
just Ray Harrington and I'm on rayh
Harrington comedy.com uh and you can
find be a man it will be on iTunes
Amazon and all the other places uh just
uh type in be a man and it'll be there
um you go to be a manthe film.com I I
really am excited for the the movie to
come out I know it's a like oh this is
when I'm supposed to plug it but um it's
the it's the most personal and funniest
thing I've done so I'm really excited
for it to exist and of course go to uh
buildthe b.org
and that is uh that has all the
information about the Moonbase we have
some fantastic uh blueprints uh and some
soil sample information there as well
we're going to build a pool cuz we just
just have no idea how that's even going
to feel sure to swim in less gravity
that's that's super exciting to to be
inside of a pool while it's surround
like a sphere like it sounds like it be
a sphere pool a spherical floating pool
boy I'm I'm getting more and more
excited it feel about this as we go yeah
that's
uh I don't know if that's creepy
build.or build the b.org please please
make sure I mean the movie sure I mean
of course we want but we're going to do
screen of the movie on the Bas it's
going to be a great thing oh well see
that's that's even more exciting so guys
this is going to be the first movie
played on the moon that's I think it's
going to be the second actually oh
what's going to be the first one oh I
think they already they've they've
played a few movies I feel like they've
done that haven't they have they tried
to project a is this what you're telling
me that they projected a movie onto the
the moon I was I was going to I was
going to yes and this to death I really
was and then the the the very real
question of have any movies been played
on the moon now I need to know that I
can't imagine they can get any light
projecting device to successful I could
be I I know [ __ ] about [ __ ] when it
comes to space but that said if they
haven't this is this is but what about
the like just what about in the capsule
oh I see what you're saying so so could
they have possibly brought some sort of
media watching device with them and did
they in fact watch perhaps a feature or
maybe even a short film did they did
they riff a movie on the moon because
that's uh boy oh boy boy yeah cuz I I
feel like if it were today it it
wouldn't it would be a non-starter that
question it's like yeah iPad Mini you
got it it's all set right right right uh
but then I mean watching a movie on the
moon that's that's a to-do it's
absolutely true boy oh boy well guys
they played golf it's true why not watch
a
movie and then the question is what
movie should it be yeah I that's oh boy
that's really oh boy I can't even I
can't even improvise a really good joke
about
that why don't we say brain candy let's
see oh [ __ ] I love that movie I know I
know people sometimes don't like it I
love it I really like that who doesn't
like it I want their names don't like I
I've heard that some of the kids in the
hall themselves don't really oh they are
unhappy but they made the whole movie
when everything was breaking apart sure
and wow this is this is the fear of
being a Kids in the Hall fan as it
becomes part gossip show yeah right
right where it's like well I heard you
know Dave didn't want to do the movie
well when I have one of to practically
threaten to sue him to do the movie and
that's why he's not in it a
lot well once I have one of tons of ton
of questions asked them if they wanted
to be played on the moon that is going
to be question number two well I'm going
to give you my um contact for for one of
them I won't say who and and yeah for
sure because that would be a fantastic
conversation oh I agree um well Ray
thank you so much for doing this uh
you're wel thank you for having me
sincerely this was fun anytime uh I
don't know if you're ever in LA
performing or just visiting but feel
free come back on the show this was a
ton of fun uh please guys uh go to the
we the website again the actual website
again oh uh banthe film.com banthe
film.com uh guys check us out you know
where to find us we're at comedy on
vinyl everywhere go to lookingforward
mov.com which is my movie that's coming
out one blog at a time throughout 2016
uh through November and uh it's [ __ ]
weird we're at eight hours now eight
plus hours at this point and at some
point it'll be into a watchable single
piece of something um so yeah thank you
guys for listening Ray thank you again
for doing the show sincerely thank you
and as always have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen address.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
festar rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook.com/ Comedy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedyon vinyl.com a
major portion of comedy on vinyl has
been underwritten by standup records
please visit standup records.com for all
your comedy needs and tune in to the new
standup channel available on the Roku
where you can also find select episodes
of this podcast
[Music]