[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast so I'm great with numbers but
luckily it don't really doesn't really
come into it that much but yeah most
what's your favorite number my favorite
number that's a very good question uh
h no that's a stupid question let me let
me ask question any number if it's got a
seven in it yeah M let me ask you a
better question
yes um you have to guess I'm I'm going
to think of a number between one and 10
and you have to guess if I'm really
thinking of a number between 1 and 10 or
if I'm just pretending that I'm thinking
a of a number between one and
10 okay so I bet I bet let you on the
show it's your show that's fine that's
fine but uh it's you know feel free to
interrupt that's kind of the point of
the show you know uh so we'll start out
when are you ready to go I'm ready to go
yeah I think we're going um so the year
is 1965 the album is in one head and out
the other and in parenthesis the new
emerging bigot the artists Burns and
shriber Avery Avery shriber and Jack
Burns and my guest my guest is Jonathan
Katz thank you for being here well thank
you for inviting me what a pleas so you
picked this album And while I might be
Loosely familiar with Burns and triber
i' had never heard this album which by
the way very short album unexpectedly
short yeah uh less than 25 minutes I
think uh really yeah and I I was I was
actually quite shocked uh it's got a
great cover uh because it's it's it's
the cab driver uh sketch on the
cover I think that's the routine with
which they're most associated is the
right right
it and it's it's a great bit it's a long
both basically the album is two bits
except for the make a song at the very
end it's the cab driver and the
conventioneer on one side one whole side
is a 13-minute track where did you first
hear this
album I think it was um you know I was
into comedy with through my my cousin
Paul and I were got into comedy together
Lenny Bruce and burns and Tre ber uh and
then my sister introduced me to music
musical comedy like uh Tom L sure
um but Burns and triber also the first
time I ever got on stage was in New York
City at a club called hillies uhhuh
where I think you know was in the West
Village in New York and David mammo and
I got on stage and tried to do burns and
triber cuz we didn't have any mat of our
own and we lasted about 30
seconds 30 seconds before you realize
you couldn't do it anymore 30 seconds
before they booed you off stage no I
think I I think David probably could
have gone a minute M cuz he was better
better prepared than me but I as as soon
as I realized that I had to remember
stuff right I was
done what were you try did you try and
do this bit do you remember the bit you
triying to do I think we tried to do the
Cap taxi
cap um but uh the re the one of the
reasons I love them in retrospect is
that they cut each other
off that I'm sure they
were they had a real I doubt that they
work with the script but they but they
were such an amazing team sure yeah and
um I think the
the track that I really fell in love
with was the one about the faith healer
because so many comedians have done that
including Robin Williams yeah and I
don't think anyone's done it this well
right yeah and it's uh it's layered uh
to say the least and the idea that I
mean you you talk about uh be I mean I
it seems like something it's so
conversational that you would think yeah
sure I could memorize this and do it
I've got this in my head and then I
think the second you realize how comp
complex this is even if it's born out of
improv how complex this is is kind of
overwhelming but you could Jason you
could call up right now my cousin Paul
and David mammed and asked them to make
the sound of the Communist
frog and both of them would say boodoo
relap my
friends it's just such an insane
sound and the idea that there were
communist frogs living in was it
supposed to be happening in Florida I
think that's I think so yeah yeah
yeah um so I guess they
were this was set in a time when it was
not very hi hip to be a communist
right and oddly not both of my parents
were really yeah my parents were both uh
subpoenaed by the house on American
Activities
Committee and they both both pled the
fifth that is more than upsetting so so
I I mean neither of them believed in the
Communist
frog but um yeah so it means means a lot
to me on a bunch of different levels but
mostly comedically is so
funny is there uh so I'm guessing I'm
guessing Jason that this is this is
going to be interp interspersed with
some of the the album itself yeah I
normally uh throughout the episode every
10 minutes or so I'll throw a clip of 30
seconds to a minute in so that people
can get an idea of what we're talking
about including like you know esec
especially if there's a specific beat or
a specific uh you know character moment
that that you like I always like to
point that out to people so they can
hear what you're talking
about uh I think the one thing that that
that stood out uh or at least is is in
my memory is the one thing that my
mother always used to quote which was
just the you know the yeah you know the
cutting off of one another just as a bit
just that that was in that that could be
a bit is kind of kind of wonderful and
you definitely see a little a lot of um
makes me think of just about anything
that uh Christopher gueston and and uh
Billy Crystal did on SNL they they they
really took a lot from this which is
fine but uh right you can you can hear
that influence pretty clearly
too yeah and also they were based in
Chicago I think they Jack Burns and a sh
right think that they came out of Second
City yes that's right um so you know I
was also around the time listening to
Nicholls and may sure
um uh
Jerry Stiller and an
Mira and I got to work with Jerry
Stiller I made a movie with him that's a
that's see that's amazing a wonderful
movie called The Independent where
Janine garao was my love interest
although she would say it was just a bad
date that's fantastic that you should
try to see that movie if you ever can
because it's he portrays a guy who made
really bad movies ah and knew
it and he and somebody offered to buy
his entire entire catalog and pay him by
the
pound um
and you could see a scene from that on
my website I'm I'm going to have to look
that up I'm surprised I haven't seen it
um I there there's a point where I
watched everything Janine Garo was in uh
so I'm surprised I haven't seen it
um is you know that is the the cab
driver I'm sure I've heard it before but
I had never obviously heard the entire
thing do you is is there something
specific not necessarily about this bit
but about this album that made you pick
it was I mean how how many how many
albums did you listen to before you
heard
this I want an exact number yeah
43 um what kind of stuff were you
listening to before did this change the
kind of Comedy you listen to or was this
the kind of stuff you were listening to
at the time I think Lenny Bruce was the
first comedy album I listened to L Lenny
Bruce live at Carnegie H some people
think it's one of his worst but I I
happen to love it and um
and then I guess I don't think I had
discovered Woody Allen at that
point
um but and then it's a kid I listen to
funny songs the songs that my sister
thought was funny like there was a song
about the railroad goes to the middle of
my house which you probably don't know I
do not know that one yeah and um
I guess jeez
I you know I was a kid in the 50s
mhm
and you I was listening to a podcast
with do your podcast with Dr Demento who
I think is a little bit older than me
uhhuh
yeah but I did recognize some of his
references sure scares
me um well I mean Spike Jones you you
there was a good 20 25 year period where
you couldn't not know who he was and
then oddly fell off the map for the rest
of us I was aware of him I I was trying
to convince my wife that she would love
Spike Jones that was not a
success she does love me however well
see there you go that's at least nothing
changed yeah God God cannot win this
battle against the atheistic communistic
conspiracy without your help God needs
your financial aid in this struggle
against the Communists God needs your
help God knows God needs your
help my friends my program the word of
Truth is broadcast in 150 stations
throughout the United States and Canada
and of course I need your financial aid
to continue this battle against the
atheistic communistic conspiracy so we
ask you to send whatever you can be it a
penny a dime or a dollar to kill aami
for Christ box 224
224 Tulsa
Oklahoma you do it today you'll feel
better for it tomorrow here my friend
love you my friends we have with us this
week as we do every week many Poor
Unfortunate handicapped individual
Christian Brothers good Lord has seen
fit good Lord has seen fit to strike
them down during Passover why we do not
know that's it he is I wouldn't
necessarily say an acquired taste but a
taste for a certain type of mind I do
think you have to be either a comedy
lover or of the period or both in order
to appreciate it maybe I I could be
wrong I could be wrong but that's what
it felt like to me because it took me a
second to to get into what it was and
and to understand them but you know
that's that's kind of what I but this
this guy that I introduced you to Jeff
martyr is that his name yes I believe so
he also when I when I did stand up with
him on the
road anytime we had any time off he
would go looking for flea markets that
sell with old I guess they weren't that
old at the time well in the 80s 33s were
pretty uh scarce of Comedy
right and I I found Woody Woodbury which
I tried to listen to and I couldn't and
then I heard Phil is it Phil Kendry or
Henry Phil Henry yeah he said he was
talking about how wonderful he was yeah
it's it's such a it's such a mixed bag
when you when you interview people the
kind of stuff that they're going to love
and not I mean uh that's why I'm not a I
used to be a real big snob about
highbrow and low brow and then sort of
realize that that doesn't really that's
a useless definition at least for me it
doesn't help anymore I did discover
through your podcast that I have so much
in common with that guy with Phil hry
yeah oh he's wonderful just in terms of
a really loving audio
and comedy and but I was amazed to hear
that he does his podcast in real time
and he does all all the voices himself
with no editing It's upsetting and and
to watch him do it cuz you can watch him
do it online just the speed with which
he does it the fluidity with which he
does it the seeming ease but obviously
you know there's there's no way that uh
there's no way it's not complex for him
still but just it does not seem to be
and it's it's good God and that it's all
improvised I don't know how he does it
at all
yeah hey Jason do you do any accents
yourself uh on occasion if it's called
for can you do a British accent for me
uh what would I be saying and and what
what part ofland am I from just if you
can say uh um this is uh if you can
introduce me with a British accent that
would be great or or just or just tell
me your name with a British accent is
even better oh okay sure hello this is
Jason Clum with the comedy on vinyl
podcast here with me today is Jonathan
Catz and what about a French accent my
French accent is for garbage it would
sound exactly the same as the English
well do it then
no um can you do other any other accents
H H reliably uh I'm trying to think I am
from upstate New York but if you do an
Upstate New York accent it's like oh
it's it's like every other you know
every other strip along the Apple agents
what town in Upstate New York Lauren New
York near Onana near Cooper toown oh you
know this town scan atus yes I do you
know it's a hot bed of Comedy Talent
this is what I'm told yeah Bobcat goth
Barry
KMS Tom Kenny mhm they all grew up there
so weird I keep waiting to get them on
the show as well because yeah at the
it's it you don't find a lot of Upstate
names in in the comedy world at least
not as many as I would expect it's not
the you know it's not the 30s anymore so
uh there's not as lot a lot of people in
upstate doing comedy but uh yeah those
those two guys are hilarious let's go
back to Burns and Trev too easily
distracted
um I'm trying to
remember I think oh uh they on Columbia
Records this one that I'm looking at is
a Colombia record yes this one is that's
how it happened because my uncle my
cousin Paul's father was an art director
at Columbia really and he would bring
home uh real TOS of Nat King
Cole and uh he did the artwork for Dylan
wow and brought home the burns and
triber album one
day and he found me he loved me but he
found me so
annoying
um and and the fact that my cousin Paul
and I were borrowing his real toore tape
recorder just to Pretend We're Burns and
triber drove him
nuts and we also recorded scenes from
Mad
Magazine that's fantastic yeah I had my
whole life on audio which is just in
case you ever want to know what I
sounded like as when I was eight can I
tell you I I absolutely do and I'm the
exact same way uh I've been doing these
same things since I was a I have an
entire podcast dedicated to sketches I
was doing when I was 13 with my best
friend really yeah we have like 50 VHS
tapes worth of garbage that we thought
was really funny at 13 yeah had your
voice changed not much a little bit Yeah
considerably
yeah I I think I I mean it's a different
kind of be of hoarding but it's if you
archive it online it's not so bad yeah I
know I it feels like it has more of a
purpose because you know nobody has to
come see your crap but they can if they
want yeah and also I think the sound of
someone's voice means more than their
image to me do you think it uh
emotionally or what yeah no emotionally
I think it's more
potent in in fact I I spent a year of my
life trying to find the sound of my
mother's
voice and that Journey ended up on this
American life that's amazing so going
through all of your old tapes just to
hear her somewhere yeah directly on mic
or in the
background and no it was just you know
she would play the piano and I play the
violin and whenever somebody called her
home they always thought she was Mr cats
she was a smoker uhhuh
um but she died when when I was very
young and so for me it meant a great
deal to hear her voice oddly enough the
pach that Ira
gled was more about my sister and I
going back to our homes in Brooklyn mhm
he was not interested in my mother's
voice at
all so how how much is of that whole
piece is in there any of it
uh nun
none that's too bad that's do you have
that posted online somewhere I hope that
that's on in the um This American Life
archives oh okay was called for a return
to Childhood it was a segment in
that and it was it was at least 10 years
ago or eight years ago
mhm I mean having these that's that's I
mean that's one of the purposes of this
show too I mean obviously we don't get
to there aren't LPS of uh too many
comedians when they were eight to when
they were you know in their 50s 60s 70s
' 80s but there is it it always means
something to us at the time is there
something that this correlates with in
your life or I mean I could be jumping
to conclusions there but is there
anything that this reminds you of is it
remind you of uh getting on stage with
David mammo or does it remind you of
being a a you know just your friendship
as a
kid you talking about Burns and triber
mhm yeah it does it does remind me of my
connection to my uncle Abe my cousin
Paul to David to Comedy um and I think
even to Dr Katz because one of the
things about Dr Katz which was fun was
that we were allowed to interrupt each
other yeah you know no there was no no
uh
no conceit to manners you know it's just
totally people talking over each other
and occasionally stop you would stop
talking talking because you were
laughing so
hard
um
but yeah I'm sorry
I'm I apologize for the silence I know
it doesn't play well no it's okay I mean
you're thinking I mean I I hope people
understand that what I'm I I actually
Panic whenever I pause on this show and
I just try and cover it with speaking
and then forget what I was talking about
so worry not do you do you edit the
audio yourself I do I do I don't edit a
whole lot uh unless there's something
where somebody really doesn't want
something in there so if you know if any
racial epithets come out of either one
of us I'll try and cut them out yeah are
are you married I am uh if if you could
just remove this from the broadcast mhm
I slept with your wife oh oh I will make
sure to definitely remove I'll I'll
bring should I bring it up with her or
should we just leave it as it happened
but I I actually slept oh I I was
exhausted do you have kids I do not oh
how long have you been married uh let's
see uh
two uh two and a few months two years
and a few months oh can you say that
with a German German accent no no I'm
kidding I'm asking too much of
you you know the reason I'm asking about
these accents is because in in my next
podcast I'm going to portray a guy that
has a voiceover agency uhhuh so this is
going to come in very handy was the
blood of a
lamb that's that's we don't do it it
sounds good once in a while you'll get a
not that's all right hold it up there
now as long as you believe that's the
bottom all right all
right oh Lord Oh Lord look at here oh
Lord he has a twisted left hand Lord he
is sorry oh Lord I believe he is sorry
and penitent and Lord I ask you now to
please in front of all my Witnesses Lord
to please make that one hand like the
other Lord I beg if you make that one
hand like the other Lord please make
that one hand like the other Lord
something oh my God he
did wait a minute you got the wrong hand
here a little more f a little more Move
Along Move Along Move Along put some
money in the pot there in the way out
move along Move Along there
son I'll tell you that bugs me when that
happens
I come on Lord shape up I feel like when
I first watched Dr cats to me the idea
of uh uh stepping on one another's lines
and apparent improv seemed obviously
groundbreaking to me cuz I'd never
really heard that before it's it's it's
good to know know where obviously at
this point having gone to college and
done some studying myself I know that
while your show didn't invent it it
certainly perfected it at the time for
me it's it's great to listen to that oh
no this is kind of where it came from
for you I love I love having that like I
had Billy West on the show a couple
weeks ago that that podcast hasn't aired
yet and he he told me about oh yeah well
you know this not just the three stoes
were the source of uh Ren and Stimpy but
this particular Three Stooges little
yellow plastic album was the the root
for it that's where I discovered it
those little bits and pieces those are
what's kind of fun to
discover now you're not old enough to
know about going into
a into a little booth and it sounds like
it could go very dark the story but go
going into a little booth in Grand
Central Station and recording your
voice that is something that they still
exist in a few places just you know for
hipsters but uh yeah I've always
regretted that I didn't live in a period
of time when I could just
go to a booth and pay a couple bucks and
yeah
H I'm I'm assuming you have one you must
have one that you recorded or more uh
I'm looking around the room I don't but
I have so many forms of of audio
recording that are obsolete M I have a
machine called the El cassette recorder
uhhuh and that's a format that did not
catch
on what is different from the cassette I
would think of it's much bigger than
much bigger
it's
it's like it was a step it was like
trying to go from the cassette to the
real toore with an extra step oh boy
that was the El
cassette I but I I kind of I've almost
bought a few of those old not
necessarily that but I've I've almost
bought an Edison uh you know a cylinder
recorder I I I held back because it was
expensive uh and then an Edison wire
recorder which would have sounded like
garbage but still would have been
fascinating oh my God that that would be
amazing to own that I know I almost and
I pretty sure it was at an estate sale I
would have gotten it for less than $50
and it still had you know unused you
know G yeah I and I love that stuff I
don't know why I I couldn't I couldn't
begin to tell you why but it's just
fascinating to
me well I have all these still photos of
movie of movie studios and the thing I
like the most is looking at the audio
equipment that they
used and there's also photos of Ginger
Rogers and Fred the stair which is cool
but I I go with the
equipment have you always been obsessed
with
that I well it was happening with my
father who uh at the time was working as
a synagogue administrator in New
York and brought home a Wallen sack real
toore mhm and that became my favorite
toy
for the next 10 years
sure and then I graduated to
a t stereo machine then a t for
track but I've always and then at when I
was in college I learned how to
bounce from one stereo machine to
another one to do multitrack
recording and in fact I'm next week I'm
going to Vermont to get my honorary
doctorate degree that's from from Gard
college and that was my senior study
was a recording of three Blind
Mice that's fantastic yeah did now were
you originally I'm assuming your early
stuff that you were recording and being
obsessed with your own voice I only say
that because I I understand the I
understand the realities of being
obsessed with your own voice but uh were
they you're just being goofy with
yourself and your friends and eventually
I mean were you musical from I mean
maybe I don't know how many people know
like what a musician you are but you're
a musician uh as well as a comedian so
how how early I guess did music enter
into your
recording I would say by by
age 12 makes sense maybe even earlier
because my cousin Paul and I wrote some
of the worst songs ever really bad I
think that's one of the reasons my uncle
hated me he didn't hate me that's too
strong but he did die of a heart attack
listening to me
singing no um what kind of stuff are you
writing die uncle
[Laughter]
die what a horrible child yeah no we
wrote a song called the
eigor he's so cruel he brings his monkey
to school it was really terrible
stuff um and then I wrote One Sweet song
as a sort of a 12-year-old uh sing a
tiny bit of
it hey there miss lovely can can I talk
can I talk to you I'm going to send you
audio sorry I can't I can't even but I
did write some really good songs and I
even got one recorded commercially by
Buzz
KAS do you know that name I don't and I
and I feel bad that I don't well he
wrote the song Everlasting Love sure in
the
70s Everlasting Love which was recorded
by a lot of different people mhm and on
the and my song no place for a lady
written under the pseudonym Johnny
trevit was a bside and one of
his songs holy crap people don't even
know bides yeah I know I know it's not
an issue anymore you pick what you want
wow see that's that's fascinating to me
so wait what year is this that we're
talking uh this is in the I guess the
60s I I signed with a publisher music
publisher in the' 60s uh mhm and I gave
the rights away to so many songs
thinking that was a good thing right oh
my God I thought it was in Show Business
yeah yeah I mean that's that's the thing
that's the draw I I often wonder too
like if if I would have stuck with
comedy if if I hadn't been better at
something else necessarily but you it's
interesting to me that you know as
wellknown as you are for comedy that you
got into it spec with with well what
kind of music was it that's that's my
question it was mostly original music
Anda a few cover songs and the songs
were written by me and I was the front
man for the
bandh uh couple of songs one song I
wrote with David mammo called This Heart
Is Clos for
alterations and Robin Williams sang it
on Mor and Mindy my goodness
um
and we did a cover song cover songs a
lot of R&B cover
songs uh but most of the songs original
and I had
a a very beautiful young woman play bass
her boyfriend was a great sax player
mhm it was a five-piece band and a good
on a good night we made
$500 and we never had a good
[Laughter]
night oh finally a joke
finally hey don't expect anything from
me cuz uh you know I I let every I I
save that for for my other podcasts
which are garbage admittedly um do
you so at this time was comedy even a in
your world other than you enjoyed it and
you were probably funny on your own with
friends I mean when did you start doing
I remember my first joke and I feel like
I'm dropping another name here but my
best friend in in elementary school was
Josh Mell the son of zero Mell holy cow
yeah sure and he once said to me me and
he was a very large kid M and he said to
me your bats in the
belfrey and I said to him thinking this
was funny and your fats in the belly
that was my first joke oh my
God but
um but I did get to say go to see him on
Broadway and sit stand the Wings and
watch half naked women walk out on stage
of course
and that would have been in Fiddler on
the
Roof a very risque production of Fiddler
on the Roof I guess that was a a funny
thing that happened on the Way to the
Forum I would hope so who was was Phil
Silvers ever in the actual stage show of
that am I just misremembering I know
he's in the film no I think he just the
film zero mustell was and Jack Guilford
were in the stage show okay okay my
goodness I I can't imagine seeing Zero
mustell live that just just wow yeah and
he also my parents knew him through
their days as lefties mhm and he too was
subpoena you know people anybody who was
sort of a nice guy was subpoena yeah
they figure you're going to bend I
assume yeah my god wow I think Woody
Allen did a movie about The Blacklist
maybe it was called The Blacklist I wish
I knew I wish I knew his his his
material better I only know I I know the
stuff that people don't respect as much
I really love Take the Money and Run oh
I love that too it's such a good movie
yeah
taxi
cab taxi taxi cab
yeah here we are where to friend going
the hotel a room
518 they stopped me on the fourth
floor oh
yeah I got you I got you I got
you that's quite a city you got out
there what you call your New
York yeah that's what we call it yeah
yeah I bet you there are 8 million
stories out there that's probably the
crossroad of a million private lives
broken heart for every light bulb of the
Great White Wave I like really goofy
stuff which is actually which is another
reason to bring it back to this album
one of the reasons I really enjoyed this
because it is very goofy and light in
tone except the stuff it's dealing with
is boy oh boy like so racially charged
in in such a great way
yeah um like I said the the subtitle
sort of is the new emerging bigot that's
I mean that's that's that's most of this
is uh that's underlying in all of this
it's just it it's this interesting Fu to
a time that they wish would go away I
feel like what do you mean by an
interesting Fu uh uh I should have just
said an interesting [__] you uh instead
of uh yeah instead of shortening it
that's that's okay you know what word
really drives me nuts is Fran frig does
that bother you I I think it's so uh
without emotion sure oh I agree there's
there's no K we can start there there's
no k
sound I get it I understand about
censorship but
sure
um I'm just trying to think of if there
was anything
else around the time of Lenny Bruce and
Burns and Shor that was funny for
me did you ever have you ever met Jack
Burns did you ever meet Avery Shor
before live um but I did I don't know if
this is a song you've ever heard of that
a song that Bob Dylan you should play
this on your show cuz it's
um it's an obscure song of Bob Dylan's
called Lenny Bruce is dead you know
people have brought that up a few times
on the show and like an idiot I've never
looked it up yeah I'll try to send you
Rob can you remind me to send Jason that
song
um it's another thing that arrived home
by way of my uncle
mhm see that's that's a that's a fun
thing like it it's it's it's a mixed bag
when I talk to comedians of uh did your
parents bring comedy into the house or
were you introduced to it through
friends you had it just this a great
industry connection where I guess every
once in a while you'd get comedy also I
hear my mother was very funny I hear
this from my friends I I just found her
was wondering why she was hanging out
with me and my friends embarrassing
me my dad W loved my comedy mhm if he
saw other people his age
laughing but this is his best joke my
father's best joke uh hey Jason did you
hear about the fight at the bakery I
didn't what happened two roll got
fresh oh my God yeah that's what I was
up
against I had to find peace in that
world
oh but what's interesting to me though
is like you not you weren't just oh I
tried music first you didn't just try
music you did it and and you did it well
what when did comedy
happen comedy well this is the short
explanation when I sang people
talked and when I talked people listened
mhm and when I danced people
left so that's that's pretty that's the
an abbreviated version of my transition
from music to
Comedy but that seems then I mean you
could have potentially then made your
career as songwriter only if you'd had
done that but you needed to perform I
have to assume
yeah and I also could not write a hit
song I guess that would also change
things yeah the closest I came was a
song called the local motion oh wow well
there we go which which I wrote for
Little Eva uhhuh uh-huh uh but other
people deny that sure the guys who
actually wrote the
song you wrote a lot of leadbellies
tunes too didn't didn't you if I'm not
mistaken yeah in fact I call I was the
first guy to call him Leadbelly wow he
just went by lead better for a while and
you're like listen
yeah that's not going to catch
[Laughter]
on uh my other familial connection to
the music business was my father was
going to marry Woody
guth's ex-wife after he passed
away but she didn't like my father's
kids meaning me and my
sister so that didn't work out that's un
Arla Guth was could have been my half
brother I it became good friends with
with Nora Guthrie his sister mhm and
Jord Guthrie his
brother would you get half price tickets
if you went to the Guthrie in Minnesota
just curious if that were to happen if
that had gone through I did I did
perform at that theater you did with
with Robin Williams I toured with Robin
Williams
M that's another thing I was playing two
songs on tour with Robin
Williams um
born to be punished and this heart is
closed for alterations
uhhuh and he sang them both
and as only he
can when was this CU I I see online that
you're credited as musical director for
his 1979 tour is this after what you're
talking about now or what what are we
talking about the tour was in 78 and was
one of the worst credits ever because
he's not a musician he's a comedian yeah
it be likeing be like um being
the uh in charge of Comedy for Isaac
Stern right
right to do all his Woody quips between
sonatas so see that's so were you okay
so this is what's what's hurting my
brain is the idea of him performing
music and that is something that would
not have occurred to
me well it here's how that happened is
that he his first
wife uh a woman named
Valerie uh was my girlfriend in
college
and many years later she introduced us
and she said Jonathan I married this
very funny guy and he should do your
songs and I said
okay yeah I mean who are you to turn
that down but wow that's and was it just
for this one tour then that this
happened I mean we we we remained
friends and we became fathers around the
same time so our my oldest daughter hung
out with his baby boy wow what is okay
so and be my apologies for not knowing
what album did an album come from that
tour I have to imagine reality what a
concept okay okay I thought so and I
think I have a credit on the album I
don't have a song however but you do
have a credit on the album itself yeah
cuz I played acoustic guitar
with a
um his opening act was this act called
Rick and Ruby okay one wonderful act
from San Francisco and they played
electric guitar and she sang and there
was a Pianist named Josh Brody who was
wonderful MH but they they were very
quirky
and I actually like I could watch their
act night after night and Robin I could
only watch a couple of times
because uh his energy scared me I can
completely understand that yeah yeah I
mean that's a I mean it
was it's a it's a trite comparison but
what it must have been like to be around
Jonathan Winters except maybe again
including the drugs it had to have been
it its own thing yeah wow I once sold a
vial of his urine for $500 to someone of
his
fans and it wasn't even
broke but um no this is he was so hot in
78 off off of Mor Mor and Mindy
mhm but
he was an amazing talent he really
was um and as an actor as well as a
comedian well sure yeah of course I mean
that's it's it's it's so hard
to that energy can be so like you said
it can be scary maybe to some
off-putting uh we just did a tribute
episode to him a few weeks ago a live
episode that was a tribute to Robin and
uh I mean that's one of those things we
talk about where some people don't
necessarily appreciate the skill that
went into being that crazy on stage uh
you know and uh like to be in front of
it I can again maybe again not
necessarily even intimidating but
definitely it's like where theck is this
coming from that it would make me
anxious I know the person I am I can
tell that would make me incredibly
anxious to be around but
fascinating yeah the last time I saw
Robin was at at the Four Seasons in
Boston mhm and I told him a joke and it
just he was such a generous laugher mhm
and I told him I had seen a production
of The Vagina Monologues with Senor
Wes and
um he would turn a joke into like a half
hour bit
Yeah but
um he was an amazing guy Dave's a ladies
man he's what we call your ladies man I
say Dave you're a nut get out of here
Dave I say that to him a lot get out of
here I don't mean that you know I just
say that to him get out of here Dave
Dave's a you know what Dave did you got
a minute listen to this Dave brings this
he brings this tie with to the
convention it shines in the dark yeah
that's funny huh that's funny that's
funny huh that's funny all right all
right that's only half now listen on one
side on one side of the tie it says win
with wilky see you turn it over on the
other side it says screw you buddy what
a jeez we had him up there last night in
the hotel room for 3 hours in the dark
looking at that tie what a night that
was that
this guy sounds like a hot ticker
oh you kidding me you're going to start
telling me how funny Dave pronin is
don't start telling me about Dave crin
for God's sakes Dave and I go back for
years you're going to start telling me
about Dave don't start telling me about
Dave my friend don't have a thought with
me about davein sorry I brought it up
all
right and here we go yes I do see your
credit they probably the audience would
have heard me pulling this out of the
sleeve but yes you are credited as a
musician on that album yeah third
musician it doesn't say third musician
but you are the third not that not that
the credit order matters I'm just saying
I I I'm surprised I never noticed it I
have listened to this a number of times
I'm I'm shocked that I've never noticed
your name that's that's kind of the
interesting thing too is a lot of names
that I'll interview on the show or we'll
talk about we'll weave in and out of
other people's projects and people are
usually they don't always mention that
they were involved in a sideways way in
somebody else's somebody else's project
did you ever Okay so we've got a lot of
I'm getting another call and it's going
to stop making that beep in a sound in a
second okay okay you you can take the
call and record it if you want no no um
but I was going to
mention another connection I had to The
credibility gap oh yeah who who I think
I forget who's talking about that um
yeah Greg Benson uh hilarious guy a
YouTube personality we were talking
about I met David Lander who the
wonderful world of Ms oh for sure yeah
cuz and this is this is a trick question
in my home I have an Emmy
Award a cable Ace
award an award an award from the MS
Society called The Gift of laughter
award which was presented by David
Lander to me and which of those three
Awards do you think mean the most to
me the assumption is number three
but you're Jonathan C
so I want to know your actual
answer come on take a guess I'm going to
say number
three which one was that the the MS
award no it's the Emy because I'm an
[__] like everybody
else that's fine that's that's you know
what I you're you were more than free to
admit it I mean like you've you've been
a gentleman so far to me but I'll I'll
you know no but David Lander and I had
such a great time at this
convention because I discovered that
what people do with these conventions is
they get high I had no
idea it makes sense uh you've earned it
yeah that that is a guy that is a guy
who I
would he's another guy whose involvement
in the comedy that I love I feel like
was underrated until you know I
discovered the credibility gap years ago
when I first grabbed one of their albums
and uh you know in my head he was just
from Le and Shirley until oh crap oh
crap this guy's a brilliant brilliant
genius and uh wow yeah I have you ever
talked to him about that uh the world of
that kind of Comedy since you do really
enjoy audio comedy you know when he was
in in Boston once he came to my home and
we recorded together um and it was about
he played a sports
announcer named Brian
ASU which is
just just the name itself is such a
wonderful setup for a bit but he I'm
sure he you know he lives in La I'm sure
he would be happy to do your show that
would be great I I have reached out to
him and uh that would be something uh
that would be fantastic I don't know
what kind of physical shape he's in
cuz it takes a different course in
everybody yeah
um but
uh trying to think of who else has a
connection to Comedy in those
days did you ever get Lenny Bruce's
daughter on the show that's another
person I've reached out to I've tried to
get her on the show a few times and
that's something we've interviewed you
know the the Sons and Daughters of of
some of my favorite comedians and we
hope to do more of that also but uh
every once in a while I I'll find out a
few of them are friends already so I
like for instance Kelly Carlin and and
Rob newart I'm going to try and get them
both on the same episode to talk about
Richard prior because I think that would
be a lot of
fun this is just a what what we used to
call a coincidence is that Richard PRI
and I have the same birthday and the
same and the same illness that he had
not was not his biggest medical problem
but he did have MS sure um and it's the
same birthday it's shared by Woody Allen
and Sarah
Silverman that's interesting and then
also a guy named ed
Hawkin that is also that is equally
interesting even though I don't know the
name Ed Hawkin is a financial planner
who couldn't make it in
comedy jeez I'm so
predictable do do you have a favorite
line off of this album I had to write
down some of mine that that kind of
stuck
out I'm just trying to think there was
something about it might be in the cab
thing
about
uh I guess Jack Burns is talking
about uh what was what it's like at
conventions he goes to uhhuh and he say
I was up there all night with this guy
we had we had win with wilky
ties um it puts talks about putting a
lampshade on his head which is a big
deal in those
days uh I never quite saw the appeal of
that but um let me see about in the um
in the faith healer
one uh I
think um they do say kakami for Christ
which is one of my favorite yeah lines
in that and also um
the reverend's name is is Moly yeah so
he says holy moly so ridiculous but I
love it
um they just were nuts those guys that
were great
um the sound of the Communist frog I
mentioned that already yes right right
right I'm going to do my impression of a
communist frog and then you can then you
can uh play theirs this this is this is
how I would portray a communist
frog
ribbed um and they have a totally
different approach they certainly do
yeah I'm trying to think of what else I
could do that with
there there is a bit where he's asking
one gentleman about it and uh his accent
seems to reveal quite a bit to the to
the Reverend I'm a convite yeah and also
one of my favorite lines is um he the
first time he's trying to be healed is
he he's portraying a guy with with a
immobile thumb yes and and Jack burn
says immobility immobility immobility
how many times have I heard that
tiresome
phrase three
[Laughter]
times yeah that's was Avery shriber who
said three times mhm well listen the
years go by they forget your veterans
now you go into a barro you see a girl
you say I'm a veteran you know what they
say forget it yeah that's it so what
they say but in them days it was
something else oh listen I put on a few
pounds I admit it the years go by they
roll by they go by they're gone they're
gone but in them days they were all over
me I
will Hey listen buddy if you like I can
make a little stop before you go back to
your hotel
room I can wait till I get back to the
hotel
I don't think we're talking about the
same
thing oh I know you're talking about
what your women huh yeah yeah yeahuh
yeah women women I'm talking about the
women not for my friend pass El Paso on
that no no I don't I don't go that n
yeah well you know don't take it as an
insult yeah it's my job yeah well here
you are buddy huh here oh that's a buck
yeah so what do you uh you drive a cab
huh yes sometimes yeah you're lucky you
caught me when I
was it's this it's this interesting mix
of like obviously these guys come from
uh this new emerging not all that new I
guess in 19 what do we say 19 197 no
this is 1965 so it's it's newer this
this this form of uh of improv but
there's also there's always this uh
temptation to go a little sticky which
is fine because that's I love that kind
of Comedy but it is funny listening to
that mix because you don't find it as
much in in improv where people are
taking it a lot I guess more seriously
for whatever reason um so you don't find
like the temptation to go shticky as you
as you might then you know you said
you've said the word shticky yep should
I say it again which makes me feel like
you should book Andy Kindler on your
podcast he he is already booked and I I
don't know when that's going to happen
but I I am so excited for whenever that
is yeah he's so wonderful absolutely he
is and when I when I when I when he's in
therapy with me on stage which you which
you've been doing lately he says Dr cats
are you doing shtick
he's wonderful IND oh God it's a genius
uh and there's there there only certain
types of comedians who can keep alive a
certain type of humor without it seeming
uh like a hack move like you can still
build on these older forms of Comedy I
mean otherwise improv wouldn't still be
alive either because it's just a tool
it's a fun tool that you can use you
know
um you know when we before we did Dr K I
go out to to see live improv with with
my friend Tom snd the co-creator of the
show and we decided we didn't like it
that much CU they should just do the
funny parts right which is why editing
became so valuable
sure I mean that's and that that's
another huge huge thing too is there is
there are a couple examples in that
period U of when Dr cats came out uh of
stuff that's
that feels improvised uh and usually is
but also has the benefit of editing
yours has more the benefit of editing
than a Christopher Guest documentary but
there these these things that may not
that you're responsible for this but
these things that made everybody think
they could
improvise and uh a lot of people are
trying to recapture the magic of again
Dr cats or any Christ one of those
people is Larry David on Curb Your
Enthusiasm sure who who asked Tom Snider
how we could possibly get such a natural
sound
mhm he would
never uh he's not big with the
attribution Larry David that happens
that'll happen yeah in this in this in
this
business
uh is that where we have to leave it I
feel like we have to leave that that I
think so I mean he married he married my
ex-manager so our lives became sort of
intermingled for a while there that is
interesting I don't know what to make of
that well I think the the what I made of
it is that she didn't really find me
attractive that's oh that's been
Mar I gave him his own ringtone that's
you're so generous yeah
[Music]
um let's see if they left a message was
coming from 213 which is your
neighborhood that is true van lives
right down the street
yeah um do you remember is there just
because I really do like this cover do
you
remember are there any particular albums
in terms of album art since you seems
like you got brought home a lot of stuff
was there anything in particular stood
out I wanted to decorate the basement of
my home with album
artwork but my
wife uh had other
plans yeah that'll happen so I mean I
did throw out some amazing album covers
most of them were music I don't think
any were
comedy see that's that's the thing about
like I mean I I think by I just have to
because I do this podcast I do have one
at least half of a wall are a lot of
album covers that I particularly love
but there's never enough room for all
the ones that I especially I just keep
discovering newer and newer ones or
getting signed ones on occasion like
from fire sign theater or Rusty Warren
uh I I love having those as a reminder
they're nice I mean the these bits of
art I actually have a friend who I think
he just said he's going to be framing
he's got enough copies of this one fire
sign album that he's cut it in half so
he can frame the entire piece as one
long one long piece of art which is kind
of great I have to revisit Fire Sun
theater
cuz I I was in a little too distracted
at the time they came out mhm understand
understandable a lot a lot of people
were I feel like that's that's why that
that's one of the reasons why they're
not as they're not given nearly as much
credit as as as they they deserve um you
know uh for breaking a lot of a lot of
new ground or a lot of ground that might
have been being broken at the same time
by other people who were then more
recognized recognized for you got a you
got a long back catalog to go through
but there's a lot of great stuff in
there yeah well the good news is that uh
I have all all the time in the world no
I don't I wish I
did but I think tell me when you feel
like we are have a comfortable amount of
material for you to work with yeah I was
actually just about to ask you if you're
going to recommend this album for people
to listen to if they don't know who
burns and shriber are or even if they do
and they're not familiar with this type
of material what's a good reason to
listen to this album and give this one a
listen as their first bit of exposure to
them well I'm just I just I'm missing
another call which is Okay the reason
the reason to listen to Burns and triber
is because they're
silly they're
incredibly well rehearsed mhm
they are almost like a a musical on
uh they're very there's a lot of
musicality in their act with the
exception of Avery shriber playing the
guitar which I don't think is
necessary right um but just the way
their
voices work together and the way they
step on each other's lines and it's that
wonderful thing where they cut each
other off in a comedic
way
um and I think it's it's just
politically potent it's a really
wonderful picture of what life was like
at that
time yeah I mean it's not even
necessarily the hippie aesthetic it's
its own thing and I like that that we
can find something from uh this period
that's got its own feeling to it I mean
it's these two guys that are doing all
making all their commentary through very
seemingly silly sketches that underneath
them are a lot deeper yeah you know they
they they had their own show for after
that and they were appeared on The Dean
Martin Show which is a credit I don't
have unfortunately
um but uh you know you were talking
about Robin's genius and backtracking a
little
bit he had the same gift that Letterman
had was to make things appear
spontaneous sure and that's such an
amazing
talent yeah I mean the idea of
retreading something like even like this
it starts out in as Improv and making it
again to be able to interrupt somebody
and and act as though you made that
decision or to act like you're being
interrupted for the first time that's
there's an awful lot of skill there
yeah my dad went to came to see me on
Letterman one night and he the first he
asked a producer who was Bob Morton at
the time mhm he said to him do you
really need all these
people he couldn't believe how many
people were involved in making a a half
hour of
Comedy that's fantastic the size of the
crew but
um I think we should
maybe take a break for a few years no I
mean maybe maybe stop now and where can
people follow you online Twitter on
Twitter you can follow me on Twitter I
don't know how you do that how do you
follow me on Twitter you just search for
Jonathan cats yeah you search for my
name easy enough my Twitter handle is I
think Jonathan Jonathan cats yeah
Jonathan cats
okay yeah I think that's that's the best
place to find me sounds good habitual
Twitter Twitter so go go follow Jonathan
Kats on Twitter go watch him live thank
you guys for listening and thank you for
being here thank you for doing the show
I really do appreciate it it was a lot
of fun Jason my pleasure and as always
have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
fstar rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook. /c comedy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedyon vinyl.com
[Music]