[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast the year is 1973 the album is
2013 the artist Carl Reiner and Mel
Brooks That should be noted Carl riner's
listed first on most of these my guest
is Greg Fitz Simmons
but it's we're also using his equipment
which is very nice of him so thank you
it's very kind of you well it's um I
don't know about lend it's a lease it's
a lease program sure and uh you know you
don't have to pay it all at once okay
just every time somebody downloads they
just send me a penny Okay that's a good
idea yeah well you will take a while to
get your money uh I apologize sincerely
um PayPal will take a cut of each penny
well of course they got to wet their
beak and then of course Spotify they
going to want a little bit up front yeah
um you know there's there's a lot of
Jewish people that they're going to get
in the way
here uh say it's your equipment so you
can make that joke yes that's fine I'm
not can I before we get into it I'm
noticing a dog Town sticker on your
laptop and may I ask why uh lived in
Venice for about 15 years and um love
the dog down okay yeah makes sense have
you seen the movie oh I love yeah yeah
yeah I I'm I mean I my first documentary
is a sort of parody not a parody it's
not but it's like it's a parody in that
like the sport I'm talking about is so
stupid and so far removed from something
as cool as skateboarding that I had to
call it Lords of soap town so oh that's
hilarious long story but as to why it's
called soap town but yeah yeah yeah I
love those movies can I see that on
Netflix not yet I'm I I just signed a
thing to get it released on DVD good so
waiting for Netflix to come knocking I
think I have to knock at their door yeah
there's a lot of uh
buzzers and knocking and texts with
Netflix yeah yeah they're very busy
these days yeah yeah seems like it um
developing good shows um okay so why did
you pick this album because it's common
La last few months people have been
picking a lot of these a lot of Mel
Brooks and car r specifically these
albums yeah like I'm having to turn
people away well I think I think Mel
Brooks and Carl Rin are both having this
sort of Renaissance with people I don't
know if you call a Renaissance as much
is an appreciation of them uh Mel Brooks
and they they did an HBO special
together and um I think it all started
actually a while ago maybe maybe seven
or eight years ago when
um uh what's his name who's a sports
caster
um I'm gonna be no help he did a show on
HB Bob Costas it is Bob he did an
interview with them and and uh with Mel
Brooks and it just went on and on it was
supposed to be 1 hour special and he by
the end everybody in the studios nearby
had had collected in this one Studio
Sound Stage and he went for hours and
they released it as like a three-part
special or something um so I I don't
know if it started there but then um you
know they they just have done stuff
together I saw I saw Mel Brooks do a
oneman show in uh in Beverly Hills at
the David geffin theater and he'd never
done a man show before and he got on
stage I don't know how the hell we got
tickets like KPCC announced that there
were okay that there was a show and my
wife called in and got like we got the
last two tickets we were like in the
back row in the corner but it's a small
theater okay and he got up on stage and
uh you know in a tuxedo and he just had
a glass of water on a stool and a
microphone and he basically went through
his entire life from being from his
parents' life to being born to Childhood
in Brooklyn to being a young writer on
your show of shows all the way through
the movies he's directed and
interspersed he would sing you know he
wrote all those songs yeah Springtime
for Hitler and so he would sing the
songs as he told his stories my God and
I mean this guy did not miss a beat for
he he did 45 minutes and then said I
have to pee left the stage came back
five minutes later and did another 45
minutes so good and it was like you know
it was probably like a collection of
every story he's ever told on a talk
show on The Tonight Show or a panels or
wherever and so they just were all beat
it out and they were all full of funny
stories and jokes but heartfelt at the
same time and and Carl Riner was out in
the audience and they they did some
2,000 year old man back and forth and it
was just a really magic night wow so I
think there there's been a bunch of
things like that and then they've each
gone out and done some podcasts which I
had Carl Riner on mine probably the
biggest thrill of any podcast I bet
guest that I've ever had and um and then
I know that Mel Brooks has done uh Chris
Hardwick I believe he's done Marin yeah
I'd like to get him on mine but I'm I'm
afraid to
ask he's such a hero to me sure no I
know I have yeah I I would say I'm just
as a I've sent the emails uh oh yeah
repeated repeated to no response whereas
Carl Riner I have gotten at least
responses you know but he's a he's
melbrooks he's a busy man he's a god
what are you going to do I had a dream
about him I guess because of this
podcast but two nights ago I had a dream
and I was um with Mel Brooks I forget
the context of the dream but I was
making him laugh and he really saw me as
like the best version of me like I felt
like this is what a perfect parent would
make you feel like it was definely a
father thing and I was young I was like
a little boy and he kissed me on the
nose and he hugged me that's amazing
yeah that's so good it was like
everything I dreamed that parenting
would be and that I never
got I I I mean I'd always wish my
parents were Jewish if that counts I I'd
go for that too that'd be fine yeah oh
yeah we'd all be a lot funnier with
Jewish parents yeah I think so yeah
what's your heritage uh uh man you know
what I've been researching that a lot
lately uh found out just super German
which is what we expected my last name
is German yeah Eng super super Anglo on
one side and then I'm like three4 German
one quarter Anglo that's mostly it okay
with a little other stuff thrown in that
I'm interested in but there's no proof
or yeah documentation just rumors yeah I
like those rumors it's fun but it well
you know I got on ancestry.com recently
me and Dave kachner kachner got
convinced that he and I are related
because we're so similar and so uh we
both sent out for the ancestry.com kit
and then you can once you do it you can
cross reference oh yeah your DNA and you
can see if you're related in any way I'm
still waiting for the results I should
do that I should my mom did the DNA
thing I want my dad to do it I mean I
hope they don't turn out to be related
but you understand I just want to know
my backround right I like the idea
though cross referencing you and a
friend who you think or hope you know
that's great I love that that's
fantastic um
so when did you first hear this
particular album and you you picked it
you said because it's all 2,000 year old
man whereas the other stuff is a mix of
just other interview stuff yes well I've
got um my well my initial connection to
this is growing up my father was a huge
Mel Brooks fan and so we we watched all
of his movies together growing up and
the producers was always his favorite
movie of all time which was amazing that
it turned into a Broadway show that got
so popular because it was kind of a
sleeper hit for him you know it wasn't
his well most wellknown but he we always
just felt like it was the most perfect
premise and the execution and the
casting and so I always had this very
emotional connection to Mel Brooks
through my father and then when I was
um I guess I was about 12 or 13 he
bought me the 2,000 year old man
collection which is three or four albums
from from the collection and uh just you
know wore them down listening to them
and then as I got older and my dad
passed away I started playing the albums
for my son we'd play back Amon when he
was probably about nine or 10 MH and we
play back Amon we listen to 2000 year
old man and it it landed squarely on him
he did nothing was missed I mean he it
is just so purely funny you can't
explain why all you just can stand back
in in awe and say this is a man who is
represents and embodies funny yeah and
you know when he talks about a nectarine
being the perfect fruit you know it's
the right temperature and I take a
rotten nectarine over a a fresh pear and
you know he would just repeat that and
uh and so he was he would repeat the
album and then uh one Halloween you know
again he's like 10 years old and we're
out in Venice Beach and we're
trick-or-treating and uh I go oh and
it's Mel Brooks and he goes somebody
dressed up as Mel Brooks I said no it's
Mel
Brooks and he turns around and there he
is and he's out trick-or-treating
because his son lives in my neighborhood
and so he was going out to trick or
treat with his grandkids
and my son said uh Mel Brooks he goes
it's so nice to meet you my name my son
I used to call him the mayor of Venice
introduces himself to everybody and he
says uh I you know he goes I love the
2,000 year old man and he goes 2000 he
goes what are you doing listening to the
2000- year old man you're 5 years old
and he just was so playful and they
talked back and forth we took a picture
I'll give you the picture so you can put
it on your uh podcast and uh it was just
such a thrill and he was everything that
we hoped he'd be and uh and so um when
it came time to pick an album I I went
back through my albums and I wanted to I
wanted the one that had cuz some of them
have sketches that are brilliant also
sure but this is the one that was just
purely 2,000 year- old man you knew
Shakespeare told you know heedy cat with
a beard how how did how did the word
shower shower come to be shower most
voice came are because of an poetica you
mean they sound like what they are they
sound exactly shower doesn't exactly
sound well list you going to shower and
you
hear but that's not shower well when
they added the hot water then you walked
in you went out
so very good okay see that's how we got
shower simple simple you mean all words
you think are Anam poetically B
basically come from the sound of well
how about the word egg egg doesn't sound
like an egg watch that chicken look at
that chicken study that chicken very
very very very closely yes I do I don't
see as produces an egg and you you
listen to it you'll you'll see the
chicken
goes that's that's that's and they they
pulled together different parts that had
some of them had appeared on other
albums I believe I think so and pulled
them all together and this is the
complete uh I don't know it's got to be
like 20 tracks yeah 20 uh 25 I think
yeah which is a a which actually
concerned me cuz I'm like wait how long
is this album I mean I don't care I love
it I'll listen to it all day but I was
like oh God I have to prepare how many
times I get to listen to it but it's so
fast y so incredibly fast and maybe you
know and I again people always expect
that I know everything about the album
we listen to it but like I don't know
how much of this is improv it does feel
it feels like 100% because he's so
Lively maybe he's got some stuff in his
back pocket I mean do you know enough
about it yeah
well the whole concept started out as
you know there was a
time in New York back in like the
1960s where people got together for
cocktail parties and they dressed up and
it was Lively conversation it was
intelligent and then people that were
funny would sort of just just take the
stage I mean you going you go back to
like darthy Parker but this whole idea
of you know reparte and dinner parties
and it turned into the first standup
comedy in a sense Bob newart who you
know his I'm sure you know you know
everything about these comedy albums but
you know he had never done stand-up
comedy when he recorded Bob newart
himself and it went won a Grammy and it
was a best-selling album and um so that
was the same thing it developed as a a
living room kind of a monologue and this
was the two of them at parties would
just make people laugh and it started
out as a 5-minute bit mhm and then um
and it might have actually started in
the writer's room yeah the Genesis of it
was it was they were in The Writer's
room for your show of shows and uh they
would just always [ __ ] off and so at one
point Carl Riner just says to Mel Brooks
so you're 2,000 years old what's that
like and he just made this noise and
that made everybody laugh was like this
sigh and uh and then from there they
started doing it at dinner parties and
it just grew and grew and grew and then
they put it out on an album and so when
they did tape it in front of an
audience uh from what I understand it
was probably about
75% you know they had the they had the
jokes sure yeah and then the rest was uh
you can tell the points where it's
something quick
because to me what what's so endearing
and compelling about the album is it's a
bunch of things but when you go past the
jokes and the material and the then the
character it's the playfulness and the
relationship that comes through you hear
two friends that are enjoying making
each other laugh and and who
are making each other funnier together
sure yeah and who don't step on each
other their rhythm is
impeccable and the respect that Carl
Riner shows Mel Brook in setting him up
and then getting out getting out of the
way he's the best straight man
ever it's true I which is funny too
because Carl Riner as he's one of my
favorite sitcom actors of all time and
playing Alan Brady is one of the hamiest
crazy but to be able to do that and also
be this guy this interviewer who is you
know I mean he's not he's not Bland
necessarily but he like you say he steps
out of the way a second he needs to
right uh I do like the moments when he
breaks so those are some of my favorite
moments on the whole thing you can tell
like he got thrown I love that so so
much and he still has that I mean when I
saw them at that show together and when
I've seen them on TV together he's just
enamored he's got a crush on Mel Brooks
it's beautiful and they get together uh
at night I guess three or four nights a
week they get together and they watch TV
they're very current on comedians that
are out there right now they love Sarah
Silverman and SC that's great yeah and
so they they have ice cream and they
watch TV and awesome yeah it's just
beautiful friendship and it's very sad I
mean they both talk like I had calll
Riner on my podcast and he said um most
of his friends are gone yeah you know
the guy's 90 years old at this point 91
yeah something like that I think Mel
Brooks is like 88 89 right it's crazy
and neither of them have their wives
anymore so now it's it's I mean if it's
going to be just them it's good that
it's those two yeah you know that's
great I mean for me I it's very selfish
like I love the idea of that I'm like I
hope I have that when I'm 90 [ __ ]
years old although it' be great to have
my wife too I'm not you know you guys
understand she doesn't listen to the
podcast no of course she does what is
she stupid uh yeah so it it's funny
because I own this album I have this one
framed on my wall because mostly yeah
because but more because Mel and and
Carl are both on it and I love the 2000-
year old man and then I realized when I
listen I'm like [ __ ] I haven't heard
most of these bits I've heard variations
on the other albums cuz I have the same
three album set that you probably got
with the two of them nose to nose
so and that's fantas but this one I
don't know there is something pure about
just 40 minutes of them just
bullshitting on this same character over
and the jokes are so dumb and that's
what's so delightful about it yeah do
you have a favorite bit on the whole
album or several bits or well I guess
the nectarine thing always makes me f
makes me laugh um I like uh I like the
silly stuff like when he says uh he asks
him about his pubic hair and he says no
my public hair he's talking about like
the hair on his head and his arms and uh
it's just
um you know it's it's the moments you
know um when he talks about like what is
the uh great mystery of the universe and
all the years you've been alive what is
the one thing that has always befuddled
you and given you wonder and he goes you
know when you eat asparagus and then you
make a number one what is that smell
and that's another one where you hear
Carl kind of like bend over a little bit
it's so oh there's you know it's funny
too is like it's it's kind of a it's a
pretty like it's a formula yeah it's a
great formula but somehow it works every
time he has so what was the name of the
first blahy blah and it's always like
Murray or Saul and somehow that joke
lands every time and I don't know why
yeah he goes uh he he goes did you know
Jesus and so he talks about knowing
Jesus and then he goes and what about
the apostles he goes yeah yeah the uh I
I I know the apostles it was uh Josh and
Lee and Barry and uh and and he goes
those were not the apostles he goes oh
my mistake that was William
Morris oh God it's so silly it's so it's
it's another two another sorry it's
another example of around the same era
of like um Alan Sherman and stuff where
Jewish
culture regardless of whether it's is
over the top is like an Alan Sherman
where he's just singing yish in a lot of
stuff uh where it's it's just appealing
to mainstream America and there probably
though a lot of them laughing and not
being sure why the same like same reason
I might have laughed at it when I was a
kid cuz I didn't know but it sounded
super funny to me um do do you think
there was like what do you think why do
you think it might have resonated so
well as it just the characters well the
Jewish thing really is is a big part of
it there's a very yish Rhythm to it
there's the you know it's like the old
Catskill comedian Rhythm but with really
intelligent stuff yeah and it is inside
but it's always accessible Mel Brooks
manages to always sort of Co-op that um
that that Insider feel of this language
that isn't even a language it's a pigeon
language that is as associated with
comedy as French is with with love and
you know uh German is with attacking
other countries and you know but he uses
yish in a way that lets you in you
always know what he means by the Yiddish
word sure yeah yeah and yet it's full of
it and it's like I was a member of the
I've been a member of the friar Club
since
1993 really and been around these guys
and I've picked up a pretty good
vocabulary of Yiddish over the years and
so for me to uh to hear him it's like I
feel like I'm back at the friers club
and I feel like he's part of that that
Spirit of these guys that I've come to
respect so much who went to the cat
skills not there was no comedy industry
back then you know that was a comedian
was being uh there was a job where you
went table to table while people ate and
you tried to crack them up yeah that was
your job and you did it for four hours a
day and then maybe during the day you
were you got to wear your towboy at the
pool on top of being I forget the name
of it but it's there was a job
description for this guy and they all
did it and they they developed chops and
balls and thick skin and this this this
there's something so um confident about
that Rhythm because it's
saying and here's where you laugh right
right and you needed that because you
had people that were eating dinner or
talking amongst themselves and you had
to announce in a way here's the joke
yeah you know and and so um so I think
the way he he takes that together with
um again just the the quick mind and uh
which you didn't see with Catskills
comedy that was the same guys doing the
same jokes forever sure and here was a
guy who was inventing brand new
character and uh and and situations on
the spot yeah and then throwing it into
movies that you would you know BL a
western right a western a yish western
essentially like there's I mean he even
has an you know the Indian chief
speaking yish which is one of my
favorite parts of that whole yeah that's
right that's right Lo and gain oh my God
the new sheriff
svat God sorry I I got to be careful
last time we talked just a couple weeks
ago we did uh 2001 years and we ended up
spending H 75% of it talking about
Blazing Saddles because it turned out my
guest was equally as big a fan as I am
who was your guest uh travels Travis
mroy from my brother my brother and me
and uh great guest a lot of fun turns
out he's seen the movie a thousand times
no kidding like he's kept track it's one
of those things I'm like oh well [ __ ] I
no competition here but we loved it just
as
much do you is there something about
this I mean again you're you're a
standup you're an actor but like is
this is any uh like The rhythms or any
of melbrooks like in you like you can
sort of feel it coming out when you do
when you're being funny or do you not
notice it it's just a part of you so
inherently that I think it definitely
comes out when I do crowd work because I
realized that what's funny like you said
with Mel Brooks is that it's it's quick
it's not necessarily the first word he
says is funny it's that his rhythm of
answering
immediately is is just it just makes you
laugh and I think when I do crowd work I
do that I'm going tell you the truth
about all the Jewish Mothers and Fathers
and the Jewish in-laws you're talking
about mine and all yes this is the truth
about them they all are prideful yes and
spiteful yes and they all for instance
me when I was a kid when I got married
it was in caves caves you lived in a
cave cave you were living in a cave and
your we made dinner we said pop M come
over come over for dinner and you know
the Jewish Mothers and Fathers they came
over with a terrible rainstorm they're
standing outside the cave I said come in
p no I'm all right here you mean he was
standing outside the cave I'm fine I'm
fine he was standing outside the cave I
said I said P training my training on
you no we all
right we all right we don't have to come
in we just want to look at you dangerous
out here
I mean they were they're nuts so finally
what what what brought them into we
pushed them in can we take your Cod let
me take your no it's all right I'll kick
my coat oh they wouldn't even give you
their coat sit down no standing is good
and oh sit down we made dinner for you
no we ate we ate on the dinosaur on the
way over you know I asked people
questions then I I react to them and the
the quality of the joke is inversely
proportional to the speed at which you
get it out and and so speed is of the
essence and uh and so you know you I I
think I I definitely pick up on that and
I and I think I also pick up on the
structure of you know he was one of the
first great improvers I mean this was I
guess at a time when Second City was
just coming up sure and uh you know he
was definitely um you know at the same
level as these guys were in terms of
just the basics of accept you know MH
even and I but I'll also give him credit
cuz he that son of a [ __ ] can deny
better than anybody else too if he has
to you know he can do it in such a way
oh that's true yeah he's not when I
guess when I say except maybe except
that the bit is going to keep going oh I
see what you mean oh okay okay okay okay
yeah but but not the not the
improvisational yes and as
okay but to extend things okay I see
what you're saying to to to go blindly
forward with a bit even when you don't
necessarily know where it's going or
what you have oh man cuz there the one
or two genuinely felt like curveballs
cuz even Carl's like I'm trip you up
like I'm going to trip you up why is a
nose called a nose and he comes up with
what are you going to do blow your eyes
yeah so stupid but again that's exactly
that is one of the fastest bits on it
and it feels so off the cuff that I have
trouble believing that was a bit already
right maybe he even had notes he's like
all right here's where I'm going to [ __ ]
with him yeah like I don't know but oh
man I'm trying to also picture what kind
of what kind of an audience we're
dealing with here too because they're
going nuts I can't tell the size but I
can't remember if they did it in a I
think they did it on like a recording
studio Sound Stage okay okay um I think
they did a series of nights and then
they pull together the best stuff makes
sense don't quote me on that but I
believe that's what it was you know you
should have I have a thing on my podcast
where it's called Fitz dog fiction and
when I say something that's not true
people email me and then I read the
corrections on the next episode see I
you know what that actually is probably
a better way to do it than wait for
people to get pissy with me which by the
way does not happen a lot I have a very
cool audience like gen genuinely very
cool I've gotten one one comment where
this guy was so pissy about me not
knowing something and I emailed him back
yeah I had I kept a cool head and I just
said listen I don't know everything but
I like this idea of just inviting it I
think if you invite it people aren't
going to be dicks about it no they love
it okay so you know what uh that 100%
people go ahead email me jasonc comedyon
vinyl.com and is that your personal
email or you have like a that is one of
yeah that's my that's my that's my uh
podcast one yeah yeah I mean there's
also Jason stoland dress.com you feel
free to email me whatever you want no
pictures of your genitals thank you so
much send those to fitzdog radi
gmail.com I'm sorry your gental uh what
am I saying it's all the it's so silly
like these little bits so is this one of
the albums did you play all the albums
for you for your son oh yeah yeah so
good and uh and then we watch blazing I
don't want to get to Blazing Saddles but
but I showed him Blazing Saddles
probably younger than I should have
right but um cuz there there is you know
the whole thing about uh the hooker
[ __ ] the black sheriff and the size
of his penis there's a lot of stuff that
would there a little but I just figured
you know who gives a [ __ ] yeah yeah and
so but I I haven't shown on the
producers yet maybe I'll do that when he
he's away but when he gets back might
one of the best things about having uh a
child is waiting and then sharing a
movie with them that that's special to
you I bet I bet something that so but
then it's so hard with Blazing Saddles
because there's so much irony to Wade
through but it just he's he's good to go
like I guess if he's raised with a
comedian dad I you know maybe it's
easier to I think so and and you know
even though some of the stuff they they
are references he's not going to get it
doesn't matter because it's it's there's
a music to it that you just get into
yeah my parents wouldn't let me watch it
no no I don't think I saw till I 16 and
then it changed my life really yeah like
everything became about doing what he
was doing with that movie and then
getting really pretentious about it too
I had that stage um man the prod did you
like the producers musical we're going
to go down this path just for a minute I
didn't did I see it I don't I don't
think I saw okay the problem is I would
just say listen to the soundtrack rather
than see the movie version really I
don't like the movie version nothing
against anybody in it oh the movie
version M sorry the movie version of the
play yes the original movies Fant yeah
it's not it's not it's not fun the
musical's great I just don't there's a
few things in life that you just say you
know leave it alone they just nailed it
yeah you know like I remember hearing
like Shia Twain redo Wild Nights by Van
Morrison and just like you're oh you're
GNA do it better than Van Morrison are
you you gonna take one of his most magic
upbeat songs ever right a song that
people [ __ ] floss and do their hair
to while they get excited about going
out into the night to discover Bliss the
soundtrack of Joy you're going to take
that you [ __ ] dumb [ __ ] can I curse
on your show you certainly can oh my God
I got and you know what it wasn't Shania
Twain I'm I'm gonna look it up because I
don't want your listeners emailing you
sure sure well they again they can
correct you uh that's fine they can send
those corrections to you that's okay uh
if anybody hears us you know
uh oh John Cougar melon Camp covered it
that's oh yeah that's oh yeah I remember
that and that's just he made it whiter
than was necessary oh my God he watered
it down and oh and then the worst thing
is then you meet young people who don't
know about the original version
yeah yeah I mean that's they've talked
about like a Blazing Saddles musical too
and I don't know why that would I first
of all you I we talked about this last
time you can't say the N word on on a
Broadway state alth do they ever say it
or does the Bell go off cover a ton they
a ton yeah just you might not think
about it though like because the movie
is so silly and cartoonish that I you
know um well let's get back to the the
the let's get off Blazing Saddles sorry
it'll it'll happen um so did you uh have
you heard did you hear when they did the
2000-year old man in the year 2000 which
was like the last one they did what do
you think of that one I loved it yeah I
loved it you know it was
like it was it felt like two masters
just doing an overview you know it
didn't feel like they were
necessarily breaking tons of new ground
but they were going through it again and
and it was showing that Mel Brooks was
as sharp as ever and is you know what
sharp means is
IQ plus guts yeah yeah you know comedy
is really about risk reward and can you
go for a joke that's silly mhm and not
be ashamed if it doesn't work right yeah
that's part of that is having the trust
with your partner mhm which they which
they have probably even in Spades more
more than they did before I think their
relationship is probably stronger now
than it ever was yeah so uh no it felt
you know it felt a little more Pat they
had it down but uh but he was just as
quick I think he thrives and again this
is just total conjecture but I think he
thrives
on on Variety in such because like every
time you saw him do a oneman show what
is great is if you'd seen him do it the
next night my guess is every story would
have changed a little bit because every
time I've heard him tell a story I love
them every time they change every time
I've seen them live a few times same
thing like one night totally different
to the next night just cuz you're like
yeah you know the crowd wants this or
this is what I want to hear myself say
tonight you saw Mel Brooks live a couple
times uh let's see I want to say 2007
let's say 2007 six or seven not doing a
oneman show not doing a oneman show no
but he was doing um q&a's after Young
Frankenstein Blazing Saddles and the 12
chairs those are the three I saw was it
at the the theater the god it wasn't at
the silent movie it was one it was
closer to over here somewhere in Santa
Monica yeah uh and I don't remember
where the hell it was that one man show
I saw apparently is the first and last
time he ever did had feeling cuz I had
never heard of it and I now I want to
record and he clearly rehearsed it for
nine months that's crazy yeah that's so
crazy I know but yeah like between those
three nights that I saw him and was like
five away from him and didn't get to say
anything person I was with had the guts
to say can I have a hug and he gave him
a hug he did I wish I'd have done that
yeah yeah but uh yeah I would ask for a
kiss on the nose yeah right a kiss on
the nose is fantastic from Mel Brooks
Christ H but yeah it it was different
every night and I think he thrives on
that like at the very least that just
that variety but then most Comics do am
I wrong is that or do you do you like
having a set tight and good to go like
what's important to you well there's a
gestation period for me as a comic where
I come up with a new bit and obviously
it's very loose I I don't really write
it out I find it on stage and then if
there's something there then you try to
stretch it out and push it and see how
much more you can get like I feel like
every bit every idea has a certain
yardage you can get out of it some end
up being just like on liners and some
end up being stories and some of them
end up being um just jokes that have you
know uh a lot of Beats to them and the
longer I do them the more they get to be
word for word and that's when they
usually end up getting pushed to the
closing bit once they get strong enough
and then I sort of take them out once
they once I get tired of saying them and
you sort of say when I do my next album
I'll you know it'll be a collection of
12 five minute chunks that have each
been sort of locked down Jesus oh nice
lovely thin the I yes I mean is he as
wor sandals he wor s very much as he's
pictured today in the motion pictures
that we see of him why do they made a
travesty of it you mean that Jesus
Christ throwing over the tables and
knocking over things well didn't Jesus
behave that way no he was quiet a quiet
lad he didn't do that no he came in the
store he never bought
anything you had a store oh I see you
were a merchant by the way did you know
any of the Apostles did you know the I
them all sure did you know the they came
in the store I knew them well a sure you
knew them huh absolutely
do could you tell us a little about them
who are they first of all there was Ben
myay Al Richie sa Abe no no no no that's
not the apostles wait that's the William
Mars agency
Wait no that's so it's fresh when you
feel like it it's not necessarily I do a
new hour every such and such for you no
no I'm not one of those guys you don't
mind you don't mind doing a bit if it
still works or still feels good to to do
yeah I feel like I want to give the
audience the best I can and if that
means in a on a Friday night late show
when they're really talking and a little
bit dumb and drunk that you know
something new and elegant is just going
to get [ __ ] on and it's going to make me
feel bad and lose confidence in the bit
right so I'm gonna I'm going to
downshift and do some older stuff get
through the night and know that the
Saturday night first show is going to be
all fresh new fun stuff yeah that's a
really you know for a comic that's a
really good like defense mechanism
rather than just [ __ ] on everybody
just like I'm going to do the stuff that
I know will work or like you said I
don't want it to be [ __ ] on I love that
that's great well and also I feel like I
owe them a good show like I don't blame
them for being drunk or whatever it's
like you know it's Friday night and so
my job is to make it a good experience
for me and them uh you know I don't I
don't believe that there's a bad crowd
necessarily they may not be as effusive
as you like but they're a bunch of
strangers they're not they didn't come
together together and and decide to be
shitty yeah so you know for the people
that aren't shitty you just have to give
them a good
show do you can we are we able to
there's no [ __ ] segue for this so I
apologize can we talk about can we talk
about the Cosby stuff a little bit do
you mind sure okay so I have consciously
avoided letting people talk about Cosby
on the show if they bring it up I say
fine but you know we have to talk about
such and such yeah we have to talk about
the garbage but you you've been going
out of your way to sort of reclaim his
stuff a way how what made you decide to
do it well you know the whole causby
thing came up and watching him watching
this statute of limitations thing kick
in when all these women who have
suffered are being humiliated again
first they're humiliated by being
assaulted then they're humiliated by
being called Liars by him and yet he's
still touring so while he was still
touring I said how do we hurt him and I
said well what would hurt me the most if
somebody stole my material mhm and so I
figured that's that's what I'm going to
do and I just started going out on stage
and doing Cosby bits and and you know
announcing that they were Cosby bits and
then it would always Veer into him
raping somebody in the job of course of
course you know and so and so uh I did
it and uh but I would do the bits like
word for word and then I would throw in
something rapy mhm and uh and then the
the the guardian picked it up and wrote
a story about it m and and then um NPR
did a piece on it and and then Daniel
TSH stole the bit and did it did you
hear about this no I didn't hear about
that but I'm not surprised oh is he got
a reputation for that he's just got a
reput let's move on from my opinions of
him but you can tell you've got facts to
go off well that's it he did he did the
exact bit yeah that blows yeah is it is
it considered okay would it be you
probably I'm sure you're not considering
this but would it be satire if you did
that as an album you pick your favorite
Cosby bits you do greatest hits you do
it your own way but is it I don't know
well the problem is there's a couple
problems one is you don't want it to be
seen as a celebration of you know his
Anthology yeah so I think the thing to
do would be if you got 10 comedians to
each do one bit okay and they all end in
rape yeah then that might be something
but the other thing that's difficult is
that it's very it's very hard to
duplicate his style it's very slow okay
yeah and it's physical and its facial
expressions and on the page there's not
that much to work with yeah I mean on
some of his earlier bits yeah but the
the the longer he did it the more it
became you know yeah dramatizing
something and um it's it's a tribute to
him I mean look you can't take away the
fact that the guy is one of the greatest
comedians of all time right no no so
um you know It's Tricky and I think the
other thing I was trying to get at by
doing it is whether or not like whether
it's Roman palansky or Woody Allen or
name your favorite [ __ ] NBA player
that choked his girlfriend like whether
or not you can appreciate the art of
what somebody does if you object to them
personally um so I I wasn't putting it
out as an answer to that but just as hey
here's an interesting thing to think
about sure well and that's that's the
way have to do it I mean good art is
better at asking questions than it is
giving answers I think and then in in a
case like this like it's also the only
well I won't say only because I don't
want to limit you know but it's one of
the few ways we're making a rape joke is
clearly about making fun of the rapist
right you know and and I don't know I to
me like it's it's it's a solid piece of
performance art if nothing else but it
also is a great I wish I'd have seen you
do it I mean but you're right though I
hadn't thought about the idea that it is
so him it is so expressive that it would
be hard to imitate yeah we've talked
about on the show The this idea that I
had years ago where I've wanted to do uh
a night of covers but I've asked
comedians I'm like what do you think if
10 people got up and did their favorite
Carlin bit uh would it work does that
work and some people are like great
that's a great idea but I'm also
hesitant to ask because I'm like does
that work as a thing well Jim Brewer
used to do that in New York yeah and he
would have he would like I went up and
did a Steve Martin bit and it's great
people [ __ ] love love it because what
comes through is you see comedians doing
their favorite comedian and so you kind
of see their love and passion for that
comedian come out okay in their
commitment to doing that material yeah
and you don't not everybody did it in
the same tone MH some people did perfect
Impressions sure I found that to be less
interesting than somebody who just was
kind of doing it their way a little bit
but um yeah I did a Ste I did an old
Steve Martin thing and and uh it felt
really good I enjoyed it do you know
what bit did yeah it was called what I
believe it was there was an album called
The Steve Martin Brothers yes where half
of it was banjo music and the other half
was him giving this very sincere
speech and there's this there's this um
kind of
sweeping uh patriotic music playing in
the background and he says what I
believe I believe in rainbows and puppy
dogs and Uncle Ernie who waves his
penis I believe in nine out of the Ten
Commandments and I believe that all
people should be allowed into this
country provided they speak our native
language
Apache I I can't it goes on for like six
minutes that's the one Steve Martin
album I don't own so that's why that's
also very new to me I but you know and
it's funny is for somebody like yourself
who again is like us standup whereas
Steve Martin was his own [ __ ] thing
to to for you to do what is essentially
a performance piece that's interesting
and I think that's one of the reasons
that works so well is cuz like you're
doing this very very tonally very
different thing than you would normally
do and I find that pretty yeah that's
pretty great yeah I mean I think that it
might be hard to get the rights to do
that but it seems like a good TV show
but I would talk to Brewer first yeah
yeah yeah well now that I know that he
did it I'm going to have to go into
business with him yeah yeah yeah I love
that idea that's great oh my God uh
let's see so how how how are we doing on
time I keep you
okay so uh let's see if I can find a way
to get us back to Mel Brooks positively
probably not so let's go back real quick
so after you're first introduced to Mel
Brooks and Mel Brooks becomes a part of
your life did it just make you see out
more Mel Brooks or did it inspire you to
look up certain Comics get certain
albums anything or were you just finding
what was funny or was it popular at the
time well I I probably that that first
album my first album was Steve Martin
wild and crazy
guy and then I think my dad got me this
melbrooks thing pretty soon after and
then I started collecting comedy albums
there was this record store in uh White
Plains New York that I used to it was a
head shop with records and they had a
they always had the new comedy album so
I would buy you know you got your Weird
Al Yankovic shirt on I would get Weird
Al's albums and uh you know I got I have
a lot of Bill Cosby albums all of
carin's albums and so I've got boxes of
comedy albums at my house and I think
the idea of sitting and listening to
Comedy is a really great way to ingest
it you know because nowadays everybody
has to watch it on TV and I think that I
think it takes away from um getting lost
in it as much because you're you know
maybe too many of your senses are being
being occupied I mean unless you're a
physical comedian sure you know just
listening to
somebody is just the maybe it's the
first way I was exposed to it because I
didn't see standup comedy as a kid right
I only knew it as listening to it and
watching people do five minutes on The
Tonight Show and that was a very
different that felt different than what
I was listening to on comedy albums
which was much looser and people sounded
like they were having more fun yeah and
um so I guess I got indoctrinated to to
Comedy by by listening first and the the
feeling I had with my father because we
listen to other comedy albums he loves
Steve
Martin and so I don't know that I sought
out comedians like Mel Brooks but then
when I was about uh 10 my father was a
member of the Friars Club also in New
York so he would bring me down and I
would meet all the Comedians and they
would and then my dad would take me out
to see their shows so good we would go
up to the cat skills and I remember
going I remember going to the yakers
Raceway one time which is this outdoor
it was a [ __ ] Raceway a horse track
and we go out and bro um
um uh Freddy Roman is performing in the
track but he's just got like this corner
of the bleachers with a microphone set
it was the weirdest set and Freddy of
course is wearing a tuxedo it's 1:00 in
the afternoon he's sweating and there's
people scattered all over the place it
was like the oxygen atom there was no
there was no matter near itself and so
he just went up there and to this day I
took this lesson from him he he said how
you doing folks thanks for coming out
let's all get together come on let's
move you guys hey lady in the blue blous
you look beautiful not I love the joking
around but getting them to all sit
shoulder-to-shoulder in the stands
together yeah and then he made them
laugh and he killed and I realized like
you your your job is not just to write
and perform jokes your job is to put on
a show make it a show [ __ ] produce it
yourself you need to you know if you
need to tell a the weight staff to shut
the [ __ ] up if you need to throw
somebody out if you need to you know
tell it tell them to turn up the
microphone like be present while you
perform and be in control completely and
so I I guess I got turned on to Comedy
that was similar to to Mel Brooks in the
sense that like these guys were Catskill
Comedians and I just learned so many
lessons from guys like Maly Lawrence and
Dick Capri um you know from watching
them in doing roasts at the Friars Club
yeah yeah oh boy those were those were
runchy very big invent what other
inventors beside Murr onen onen on what
did onen invent on onen discovered
himself very big invention yes yes I see
yes I think he was falling and he
grabbed onto himself and that's how he
fell in love you know I see and he
stayed with himself and he lived with
himself and was in love was he
ostracized for being that way he was
circumcised I don't know no no I mean
was he shun was he shunned for that oh
yes he was shunned because you know the
Bible it says they shall not H spill thy
SE the seed of thy fruit on the ground
you that's right and also thou Thou
shalt be fruitful and multiply and he
was fruitless and and subtracting you
want to look it that's right do you have
any of those albums no oh God those are
they're so massively collectible but
I've never I still have not heard one no
I've never seen one I've got friends who
own a bunch of them and collect them and
you know we'll pay hundreds yeah they'll
pay hundreds why didn't they make more
just cuz they're for club members
they're exclusive oh no [ __ ] yeah yeah
and then you always wonder like were
they nobody's afraid because they
obviously said [ __ ] in front of a group
of people but like I you know I lie I
might have heard one that I feel like
was I want to say it was a roast of like
Humphrey Bogart of all people and Phil
Silvers was in it and I love Phil
Silvers silv and he is tearing into him
with the most homophobic and again I
know it's all in good fun but like I was
like oh my God Sergeant Bilco what are
you saying like I had no idea what these
roasts were about and that that also has
made me more interested to hear more of
them but like yeah there you can I got I
have friends who own a bunch of them
because they're wealthier collectors
than I am yeah I'm not wealthy at all so
yeah I'm I'm curious to hear them so did
you see a bunch of them live um yeah I
would go when I was a kid my father
would take me back when it was closed
door mhm I want to say there was no
women allowed probably
the only one they let in for a long time
was uh oh my God now I'm just totally
blanking but uh there was no there was
no press there was no recordings of it
that I knew of okay so you know and they
might not they've only might have
recorded some of them then maybe it was
just yeah I mean I guess they must have
had some kind of Master tape but
certainly not like the media coming in
and recording it to play Clips or
anything like that and and people let it
out it was crazy the [ __ ] jokes and
stuff that you know became taboo as as
things evolved and then of course the
Comedy Central roast took it down an
even dirtier road but not not dirty in
the same way right back then it was
dirty in the sense that like uh you
really were trying to uh top each other
Y and ingratiate yourself to the person
that you were roasting right as opposed
to just I'm going to write the most
hardcore jokes I can possibly pay 10
other people to write for me yeah that's
the other thing too is like you're being
essentially cast to make jokes about a
person you may never have met yeah and I
feel like the friers club thing is at
least we're all the same [ __ ] idiot
we can all make the same jokes about
each other that's where that you know
camaraderie comes from which is why the
comedy they're weird have you done any
of the comedy I did the Chevy Chase
roast Chevy CH okay which I mean talk
about not knowing the guy you know he
wouldn't even Shake our hands before the
roast like people would go up and go to
shake his hand and he would literally
just turn he had sunglasses on and he
turned his back to us while we roasted
him God it was horrible oh that's rough
yeah wow but you know the reason he
didn't have anybody he knows roasting
him is nobody would come yeah he has no
friends yeah yeah this I don't know if
it's different later in life but at that
point which was probably around 2000 or
so okay okay he had didn't have enough
friends to pull together a uh de it's so
weird you know he still got this
reputation and then if you watch the
National Lampoon documentary uh drunk
Stone brilliant yeah it's so like his
are kind of heartbreaking and kind of
human and I'm like this is the first
time I've seen you be a person in so
long especially with all the [ __ ] like
that he's been rumored to have done to
Dan Harmon and stuff oh I didn't know
that oh yeah because that's why there's
so much [ __ ] on community so much
clashing and he's I know that executive
producers changed a few times during
that show yeah and Dan Haron has played
some of Chevy Chase's shitty voicemails
to him which to me though what's funny
though is when I listen to them I almost
and again I he's got the personal
experience I don't but I almost get a
friar Club Vibe like I'm going to [ __ ]
on you as hard as I can because I
respect you but I also think there's a
huge generation gap between Chevy Chase
and Dan Harmon you're saying I can go
online and find a voicemail of CH Chase
yeah I think he's put them on on a
podcast I I feel like they're on a
that's somewhere yeah yeah yeah CH Chevy
J is giving him just the Royal just the
biggest amount of [ __ ] um so can I again
I'm sorry I know we've we've gone off
the rails just a little bit but you know
we're still saying staying within your
influences so apologies for my ignorance
but your dad was a member of the was he
a comic or he was a radio personality in
New York he was one of the biggest radio
guys in New York and so he was he was
the token Irish guy at the friar club
which is almost all Jewish and so they
got a kick out of him because he'd come
in and he he'd make uh the Jewish jokes
with them and they'd make Irish jokes
and then um on St Patrick's Day he would
throw this big St Patrick's Day party at
the club where he invited all of his
friends that were mostly Irish sure but
then all the old Jews would come
wandering in and they'd have some Irish
soda bread and listen to some music and
watch some Step dancers and awesome and
they loved it it became this mixing of
Two Worlds and so he ended up becoming
on he was on the board and then he was
the Scribe which is on the you know
which is an elected office at the club
um and so he used to bring me bring me
to the club a lot I watched the OJ Chase
there really I saw the um the miracle
hockey team the Olympics in was it
1976 okay or 80 I think it might have
been 80 and um yeah so it's a very
special place in my family's that's so
cool life and then when he died they
they had a golf tournament that was a
fundraiser and they named it the Bob F
Simmons uh golf tournament that's
awesome and they've had it going for
years and then they wrapped it up a few
years ago so apologies for my appalling
ignorance I'm from New York too for [ __ ]
where you from in New York Upstate uh
I'm from uh well you wouldn't know the
village uh you may have heard of Onan
sure yeah okay that's that's my Village
my Village is right next door to on uh
you know Cooperstown area yeah so yeah
Upstate Big Time Upstate so not like New
York New York so what kind what kind of
radio so now I want to know more I'm
always fascinated with radio so what
kind of radio it was AM radio back when
am was King and it was I tell you what
not that different than a podcast he
would he would get on he'd shoot the
[ __ ] he' talk about my mom and us and he
talk about what's going on in the news
and he bring on guests mayor cot used to
call in every single morning awesome and
he would have on um you know Sinatra
would come in sometimes and it was very
uh it was very New York you know he's
he's a bronx Irish guy and he just
embodied a lot of what the what New York
was about but he was a bleeding heart
liberal and so he would get into it with
his Republican counterparts yeah and uh
and so it was it was like uh people got
to know him yeah and that's so cool and
they tuned in to hear his life so that
was obviously a huge influence on me and
I didn't know it would be because I did
just standup comedy for the first you
know 20 years of my career and it's only
in the last six six or so that I started
doing ra you know doing radio on a
podcast and it's kind of like wow was I
supposed to have started this a long
time ago right that's amazing yeah are
there archives out there of your dad's
stuff up on the Shelf there's a bunch um
but no I don't think I don't know that
you can find them online maybe I should
I should make a project out of putting
his stuff up online I don't know how
many people would really care at this
point but for the people that would yeah
I think it would be really nice well as
as as a at least amateur archist myself
it's I mostly just do it to do it I want
it to be there right with the option and
the understanding that maybe nobody will
give a
[ __ ] but I I don't know for me it's the
project in and of itself is worth it I
just I would be fascinated so many hours
to go through and some of it's unreal to
real yeah that's the hard part
especially if that [ __ ] starts to fall
apart but if you need somebody I I know
fire sign theaters
archists archivist he has access to
every possible thing that yes yeah so
let me know if you need anything um okay
so let's let's this again no Segways no
if you're gonna talk about segs are for
[ __ ] thank you thank you so much talk
yeah if you're G to recommend this album
I mean I think I know what you're gonna
say but let's say somebody either
doesn't know anything about Mel Brooks
or only knows Latter Day Mel Brooks
let's say they only know the producers
musical movie uh what's a good reason to
listen to this album
um I guess again I got to go back to the
relationship between him and Carl Riner
um I think you Marvel at his quickness
and his references is but it's like we
all wish we had a friend that we could
talk like this with yeah and I think
that's the number one thing and it's
like to to me to sit down and listen to
this is it's just a different experience
that young people don't get just make
them sit down in a room and just listen
to this album and it's almost like
they're going to experience something in
life that they never have before because
they're so used to seeing things
visually and you think of in the old
days people sitting around a radio and
it really develops Community you look at
each other yeah even more so that in a
comedy club your eyes are on the
performer you may glance at each other
sidewards once in a while like that's
you
honey but when you're when you're
listening to it like we would play
backham and you you look at each other a
lot while you're listening yeah and you
really connect on it and it's very
meaningful it's very personal and it's
almost like you're sitting in a room
with some friends that are making you
laugh yeah Ah that's perfect that kind
of condenses exact actly what the theme
of my entire podcast is so I'm glad to
hear somebody else say that way yeah I
mean I've been thinking about it
recently because I'm trying to like
write a book about it and like you just
said much more succinctly what I've been
trying to sort of I'll write the forward
for your book thank you so much uh but
that's exactly it and I love that and
this is a perfect album for that because
like you say it's two friends just
[ __ ] around but also they're super
professional and Brilliant comedians at
the same time I mean it wouldn't work if
they weren't funny people um that's
perfect do you and I I apologize unless
you have something super important
that's coming out to plug uh I don't
know when this is coming out oh just the
podcast please come check out Fitz dog
radio it comes out twice a week and it's
free MH and I get uh you know I'm lucky
enough to bump into people in comedy
clubs that'll come on and do the show
you know Jud appau and Bill bur Zack
Alanis and a lot of fun people sit in
and uh it's got the numbers have gone
crazy lately I don't I'm not sure what
happened I think I booked a bunch of
good guests or whatever but like you
know sometimes I'll go a year where my
numbers don't change that much but then
this year they've really been going up
so uh it's it's it's the podcast to
listen to now and uh and my one our
special is on Netflix it's called life
on stage oh yeah right I got watch very
proud of that it was from taped in ttwn
New York where I grew up in this theater
from built in
1860 and uh that's out there and follow
me at Greg Fitz show perfect yeah thank
you so much for doing this hey thanks
for doing this podcast I think it's an
amazing thing I think it's a real
contribution to the podcast World app
and anything that archives comedy like I
just had uh Cliff Nester off on [ __ ]
he's the best guys like you are really
important and uh I'm glad you're you're
you know putting this all down if I ever
want to make myself feel like just a
giant piece of [ __ ] I just compare
myself to Cliff n off though I will say
I do it online all the time actually in
that letter where I responded to that
dick hole I said well we can't all be
Cliff Nest off at the end because yeah
he's a [ __ ] genius so good well thank
you so much for doing this all right
thank you my friend thank you guys for
listening and as always have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
Levens
please visit stolen dress.com to listen
to our other podcasts read our blogs
read our tweets watch our videos and
read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
fstar rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook.com/ Comedy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedyon vinyl.com a
major portion of Comedy onvinyl has been
underwritten by standup records please
visit standup records.com for all your
comedy needs and tune in to the new
standup channel available on the Roku
where you can also find select episodes
of this
[Music]
podcast oh hi I'm Jason clom gaziza I'm
Alan Rickards your last name is record
and we are the hosts of dispatches from
PT awesome a News Radio podcast I this
is Jason again I host the well reputed
reputed this is Alan reputed comedy on
vinyl podcast as well as some other Alan
though I've been on some podcasts also
I'm an actor and have been for nigh on
several years the important part though
is that while we're close friends we
found a bond when we discovered that we
both love the greatest sitcom of the 9s
possibly of all time I won't refute that
the podcast will go through the entire
series from episode 1 to episode 97
we'll be talking with other fans of the
show people who worked on the show and
you that's right you can email your
questions about the show and I'm not
kidding here to freakzilla
scet that's right we'll either try to
get the answers for you ourselves or
direct from the people who put the show
together it's a dream come true you can
also call and leave a voicemail for us
at 646 801 WNY YX if it's relevant or
funny or even stupid as long as it's
news radio related you have a good
chance of it getting played on the show
dispatches from Fort awesome a News
Radio podcast all of this talk of aged
lunch me ghost has made me peckish
equally dumb closing quote damn it Alan
sorry oh that's in parenthesis I
shouldn't have actually said that please
subscribe to dispatches from Fort
awesome on iTunes give us a f-star
rating and write us a review it helps
you can find us on Facebook Twitter and
Instagram at wnyx news radio
[Music]