[Music]
the year is
1969 the uh the album is how can you be
in two places at once when you're not
anywhere at all the artist is the fire
sign theater and my guest this week is
Phil Henry thanks for being here thanks
very much Jason it's a great album and
uh when did you first hear it I guess
it's a question you know that that's
really interesting you you said it was
69 when it was released I don't think I
I don't think I listened to the whole
thing through until maybe 1970 or 71 I
was I believe out of high school maybe I
was still in high school mhm but um
fires sign theater had been on local Los
Angeles radio and they were doing a show
at night on Sunday nights on krla called
Radio free Oz Oz right yeah and uh that
group of guys that was led by Peter Berg
who I believe has since passed on um
then uh morphed into this fire sign
Theater which uh became a um a live
improv group I I or not improv a live uh
comedy theatrical group but I I always
consider them first and foremost
recording artists you know I can't even
imagine what they must have been like on
stage yeah that's one thing that's
always kind of uh even after speaking
with Phil Proctor a couple times I still
don't quite get a feel for what their
live out what their live shows were like
as compared to this because it's the
best produced outside of like and it's
it's I would say the content's more
sophisticated obviously than chich and
Chong but uh the production value is
I'll put them both at about the same
level it's really just gorgeous sounding
stuff and it's you know it's just for a
whole 28 minute sign it's it's non-stop
sound effects in atmosphere and that's
one of the great things about them yeah
and obviously they're in character and
they're doing a multitude of characters
and uh this is a a Columbia release and
Columbia Records Was the Same label as
in those days the Birds Bob Dylan they
they were very familiar with um I don't
know what you'd call you know uh
alternative rock and
roll the underground and so on so they
had the the benefit of all of that all
these guys were from LA but I'm not sure
I know where this was recorded uh was it
recorded in New York or I I was trying
to figure that out myself actually uh as
far at one point we are going to be
going down each of the pretty soon we're
going to be recording uh standalones
about each and every fire sign album
with Phil Proctor telling us what it was
like making them so I guess we'll
discover more then so that'll be fun
dude I'll look forward to that
absolutely that's be great a little side
note I I used to work at KX FM in Los
Angeles which was at Columbia square
that was at the corner of Sunset
Boulevard and Gower MH and I was told
that that was before it was the uh radio
station and and the television station
it was Columbia Records in Los Angeles
and uh that there were certain sessions
done there for Columbia artists
including uh Dylan so it's entirely
possible that these guys were you know
in La when they did them right right
yeah that that that would make the most
sense what I want to sort of get a feel
for you know again it's one of the
things that I'm going to have to ask him
about is how long this kind of stuff
took who you know and I don't know if
there were any like live sound effects
cuz it's a lot of it's way too produced
but uh except for the the Nick danger
thing is all the sound effects are kind
of obvious and intentionally kind of
stilted yeah yeah and and uh do you
think it's been a while since I've heard
the Nick danger bit but the movie that
they're satirizing which not kasablanca
I said Kaz Blanca I meant meltis Falcon
right right right um I I I wonder if
that was a comment on on how you know
ridiculously stilted all of those films
seem to all of us at the time because
there's a generation of young people
that are today reacting to the 70s and
the 80s and the '90s back then we were
reacting to a lot of the TV stuff we saw
in other words you know on Saturday
morning we get up and get our Cheerios
and the only thing that was on
television was a rerun movie and it was
generally something like cablanca or
multis falcon or or Laur and Hardy so
that was U obviously a place where you'd
mine you know your satire in those days
for sure for sure and there's this uh
obvious mix of reverence and irreverence
for the same stuff which is I think
might throw some people off nowadays if
they don't they they want to know they
want their satire to be obvious and they
don't want it to have any uh I don't
know it's you know if that makes any
sense they want their they want it to be
a little too um they don't want any gray
area where well I I I hate to sound like
the old guy you know because I I see so
much that's really funny these days
um but I I would to comment on that um
Jason I'd say that there was a time and
uh I forget where I was reading this it
might have been something to do with the
Greenwich Village where artists would
say to each other well what is he doing
now what is she doing now and they
didn't they didn't mean does he have a
deal or is he making money they meant
let's go see what crazy stuff is being
done because that's what it was all
about it didn't really matter who knew
uh it mattered are you pushing the
boundaries and
so the satire from them from then was
it's like Andy Kaufman I mean you know
people got a little irritated with him
that he wouldn't let anybody in on the
joke you know right that's what he
thought was so much fun and um today I
think uh because everything is so uh
about marketing it and uh
entrepreneurial you know efforts at at
making you know the dollar sure that
everybody wants to do whatever they can
to to make things obvious I I run into
that in my own you know way people
saying well well why don't you have on
guests and why don't you do well I I
first of all I wouldn't be very good at
it and second of all it's wouldn't be
very interesting but so I what that's a
that's a great point you make but I
that's funny though the idea that
anybody would nitpick what you're doing
is it easier for you now that you're
basically independent though are you
doing much more like that does it feel
more like art is or is that too no I'm
having more fun today than I've ever had
in my life and uh in and it's weird
because there's a lot of people who
think the high point of my my Act was
when we were fooling phone callers on
talk radio and and I suppose um yeah it
it's a wonderful thing to um EES drop in
on someone who is getting you know
Hoodwinked sure
um having to do that the actual um the
effort each day to paint that canvas was
pretty difficult and it was going
against Talk Radio in other words the
show was not going to be successful on
any talk station because you were
basically saying now that you've
listened to you know eight or nine hours
of talk radio here's a show that's
completely against it and turns it on
its head and you know it's kind of like
here's why you're a schmuck for
listening to it right yeah so I I I
think that that show is I don't know how
to put it but I think it's just sort of
contained in that moment of time what
we're doing now the Improv that I do now
and and the fact that it's not married
to any topicality necessarily and the
fact that it's completely improved and I
can do anything I want say anything I
want and the fact that we're making a
living doing it is beyond anything I
could hope so oh yeah yeah the big
difference too is I I actually I haven't
really asked anybody's perspective on
this I mean if if if you look at the 20
some albums that the fire sign guys put
out this is this is something that
you're spending I don't know how much
time with let's say at least a year
spending time writing it performing it
tweaking it recording it producing it
releasing it maybe doing a little
publicity trying to sell ity trying to
pimp it for lack of a better word you've
got all this and then at the end of the
year you've got this one thing whereas
somebody who's a podcaster or a
broadcaster of any kind you've got how
many you know how many hours a week yeah
you
know it's like doing a live it's like
doing live it's like doing comedy well
not really it's not it's not like
because it's not a even comedians will
have the set they'll have their set it's
very tight they work on it and it's the
same set and theaters the same way this
is constantly changing
so um it you you know if you're not
holding on to this stuff And archiving
it and cataloging it yeah it it goes
away and uh maybe there's a beauty in
that I don't know but fires sign getting
back to to firon theater and what you
just said is really dead on man um and
it's the very thing that I don't like
about maybe television or movies or
anything is that you have to spend all
this time waiting to see if what you did
is any good you absolutely yeah yeah and
uh how much fun is that not much I don't
think I mean I guess you just keep doing
other things you can ask Phil about that
too when you talk to him you know you
just keep doing other things and hoping
that the last thing that you did you
know one thing to mention Jason fires
sign theater came out at a time when
comedy albums uh I would say underground
comedy was getting airplay on
progressive rock what came to be known
as album rock station so when we were
kids and we flipped on an FM station and
we're hearing the music then you'd hear
drop into the middle of it in a set
you'd hear a bit from fire sign theater
you'd hear a credibility gap bit you
you'd hear bonso dog band or Frank Zappa
uh you might even hear a little um mty
python sure and and you don't that is
that isn't happening anymore anywhere as
far as I know no did you okay so have
you been in I I apologize for not
knowing have you been in LA in in Los
Angeles your whole life or did you grow
up elsewhere I I grew up in Los Angeles
I grew up in La through my early 20s
then I went down to Florida and uh was
working on construction work but I got
into radio down there and I spent the
next six years yeah and then I came back
to LA for 11 years then went back out on
the road doing talk radio and came back
most recently in 96 it's kind of like
playing baseball you know you do your
single a and double A and Triple A
before you make it to the majors so I I
only asked because did you ever listen
to or have access to KMD radio because
um I heard about it but I never did I
think that was the '90s am I right about
I think so I think cuz the the gentleman
who came on to talk about it who used to
listen to it all the time he didn't pick
an album he said I want to talk about
this radio station and it kind of that
blew my mind but it is one of those
things that might have been the last
time where comedy had really any
presence outside of a bunch of ging
hosts and that's you know what I mean
that's which is and I I don't know if
it's because it's not salale maybe
because people aren't buying comedy
albums and it's it's not a priority hi
your friends Ralph sport sport Ralph SP
Sport is the world's largest new used
and US water dealership R Spa sport
Motors here in the city of empa let's
just look at the extras on this fabulous
car wire wheel spoke fenders two-way
sneeze through wind V Star Mard sponge
CED edible steering column Chrome Fender
D and Factory air condition air from our
fully Factory air conditioned Factory
it's a beautiful car friends with doors
to match Birches Blacklist and this
automobile was stolen but for you
friends a complete price only
$500 an easy monthy payments week twice
a week and never on Sunday well I'll
take it I'll take it I can't wait to get
away from it all well okay fine let's
just take a look inside your beautiful
new home come on in thanks as you can
see this car has been fully equipped
with a complete line of xr's design with
your mind in mind here for instance in
all- weather climate control in red blue
or green with a special oxygen danger
indicator level gee whiz and here of
course your own personal remote control
picture size color TV with matching
brass knob just read above the bar and
press the button right there under the
handy laminated imitation Mason at Wild
West gunr with a Lor award for the
channel of your choice do you miss being
able to not that you can't buy a comedy
album nowadays however it's not an event
it's not the same thing it used to
be I I don't know the um I got into this
argument I got into one of the most
sopian arguments one can get into it was
a Twitter argument with some brain
surgeon who was going on and on about uh
oh I don't know employment I said well
do you realize that there has been a
massive and I mean Mass
massive
industry uh sea change as well as a
massive change in where audience is and
Workforce if you want to get down to it
so what has happened in the last 15
years is uh unprecedented since perhaps
the Industrial Revolution we have all of
these new businesses that have started
we have an industry radio which is on
the verge of Extinction right we have uh
live performance is back man I mean the
money that is being made for doing live
performance who would ever thought it's
it's it's enormous we have all of these
individual entrepreneurial uh comedians
historians news commentators actors
historians people such as yourself Jason
making a living doing these
podcasts um so the the the comedy the
the the transmission of Comedy the the
dissemination of Comedy is completely
different um do I miss the time when a a
comedy album would come out and was an
event I mean what rock and roll album
comes out anymore that's really a
[ __ ] event man you know what I'm
saying I mean they try to make it that I
mean Drake you know came out he doesn't
call it an album he called a mixtape you
know right and and and Kendrick
Lamar uh to my that's about the biggest
thing that's happened in music as far as
I'm concerned over the last uh you know
year or so and it ain't been all that
big of a deal because it's about
individual tracks individual downloads
individual events MH as opposed to you
know
um do I miss the album The Comedy album
not really um I like the five minutes
six minutes 10 minute even 20 minute hit
and run um
moment um some things don't lend
themselves to it sure like like Twitter
but anyway getting back to fire sign
yeah I I what do you have a favorite
track off of here let's let's start my
my my favorite track is I guess it's not
on there man I'm so sorry uh my favorite
track is and you can ask Phil about this
and he'll probably say Henry's stupid um
it was How the West Was lost and it is a
hysterical um uh you know retelling of
uh uh the European American landing and
and uh eventually taking over this
country but there this this land mass
but the it opens with a you know
Columbus landing on the shore and
there's a priest there holding up a
cross at to all these Indians mhm and he
says uh you know uh get on your knees
heathens do you know what this is that
I'm holding in front of you and the
Indian responds well yes that's a cross
a symbol of the division of the universe
into active and passive principles why
you
heathens uh I don't know whether that's
subtle satire or whether that's fairly
well transmitted but uh right to me
that's the intelligence of uh fire sign
theater in and of itself um we're all
both you know what it might have and
we're all uh we're all bozos on this bus
ah yep okay that that does are you
seeing there that tracks I was just
looking it up as we were talking about
it which I do have I have that album I
I'll have to give it a listen after we
do this but um that's where I messed up
dude I'm so sorry but um no I I now I
now know why I remember all Hill Marx
Lennon it's because of Nick danger okay
and Rocky roko and uh you
know all of that goofy stuff and and uh
uh Rocky roko Nick danger and I don't
even know if there was a female voice in
that or not uh some fake ones uh
definitely by the guys yeah F they're
really fantastic and kind of really
really ridiculous which is what like
they they at least they know their lack
of range when it exists you know exactly
yeah yeah and they really like to play
with that I have to ask you um given
your age and your generation and your
you know your your experience and what
you've passed through does it is that is
that funny to you listening to those
guys are they funny absolutely it is but
I I will say when I first heard him and
that was probably and it was this album
that we're sort of talking about is uh I
was God I was 13 at the time so I didn't
I mean here's I didn't get it I'll I'll
fully admit I did not get it it was
passed on to my my best friend by his
dad and I would listen to and he's like
this is great and I'm like okay I don't
understand what the hell is going on
here only only recently once I've I had
an appreciation for a production values
B I've got a little more knowledge of of
the period now now it it rings true I
mean here's the thing this I know why I
didn't get it this album is insane the
first 28 minutes is nonstop makes zero I
mean it is kind of like the speed with
which you do your show like just that
rapid fire but then add sound effects
add other dudes doing voices uh it's
it's kind of crazy it's it's and so it's
upsetting if you're 13 it's well these
guys were a major influence on me um
they were a huge influence on me by by
way of the pacing just like you said by
the reality the the reality they brought
to it uh not reality in the strictest
sense but the reality of theater sure um
and that theater of the mind I don't I I
can't say when I was a kid anybody if
they'd asked me if you know do you like
theater of the Mind well I like I like
audio I mean I I I like the idea of
being able to control all the elements
and you can only do that with with with
audio but these cats what they did um
forever more influenced how I wanted to
hear things it's like a Mad
Magazine um feel you know or or
something a bit zier than that um lots
and lots of cartoon effects and and a a
really smart kind of cartoon I guess did
you hear these guys before you knew of
Monty Python I'm just curious yes yes I
did I did see that's all feel like
because it's roughly the same time
period and the the fanaticism with which
people including myself love Mony python
fire sign gets Dr drowned out oh no
question because Monty Python was
brilliant for a very simple reason and
it's something that I've learned the
hard way but I've learned it it's far
more fun to saiz Everyday events and
everyday Oddities and everyday character
than it is to uh be smarter perhaps you
know I put that in quotes and saiz
politics the nation you know the culture
which fire sign theater was all about
that they were all about satirizing what
was happening in America at that time
was was insane you know England probably
a bit more sedate you know um and and so
Monty Python reflected that they
reflected the the the they reflected
their horror if you will at the passing
generation before them you know God Rest
God God Rest their souls you know they
came through the London blackout and and
the Nazis so we can forgive them but
yeah Monty Python still sort of mocked
you know them in their Gentle Way and
and and I think that's why they survive
because what they deal with the Bureau
of silly walks uh the Bureau of
arguments the joke that kills you this
this [ __ ] doesn't get old man no it's
just for real and just like my son Chris
my uh third oldest stepson Chris
as as soon as I turned him on to Monty
Python he got it right away man sure
just right away you know like yourself
so I I think that was that hurt me you
know as an artist man having to uh grow
up in a culture that was really hitting
the political satire hard cuz I wasn't
really good at that [ __ ] and when I got
it a talk radio that's what was really
expected because the guy before you was
just talking about what a piece of [ __ ]
Obama was or whatever and then I had to
come back in and sort of make all of
that tile that stuff together now I'm
that I'm doing what I'm doing now I'm
far more um involved in what I think
really is fun and that is the the money
python approach I'm not knocking fire
sign theater those guys those cats are
smart yeah um you know college educated
American sists but I I I think I've um
at this point in my life I've had it up
to here with you know uh looking at the
political landscape and I would much
rather take a look look at uh people you
know sure absolutely and the one thing
that struck me listening to this again
is that uh is actually the one I won't
say the one thing but one of the
strongest ties it has with Monty Python
is therefore is one of the things that
made me laugh the hardest is just making
fun of the idea of austerity because
they were kind of picking apart a lot of
the [ __ ] that their own parents had
given them but maybe not all that
specifically it's like the idea just the
idea of making fun of TV
just even in the background or anything
any of the pop culture or any of the
culture they were just tearing apart the
[ __ ] that was passed down to them the
stuff that had run downhill so it was
similar but I see what you're saying
that it's maybe it's a little more
literate or a little bit more uh like
you say a little more ivy league even
though Monty Python was ivy league they
weren't drawing from the same well yeah
Monty Python was Cambridge and super
educated and uh you know these guys uh I
I can't say specifically fire sign I
know the guy credibility Gap and and
spinal tap all those dudes are Yale guys
you
know you know and
so there was a lot America is a big
place man it it it occupies a big place
uh in the history of this world now and
so there's a lot to deal with and we all
pick the big things you know every time
we go into a a store or into a
supermarket or like oh wow there's the
watermelon and there's the big thick Ste
stakes and we go after what's big and
and and targetable uh we miss as
Americans I think the Richer subtext
just a friendly word of advice danger
yeah what don't go sticking your big
nose into Police business sure
Lieutenant is that all no don't talk
with your mouthful okay Bradshaw and
don't fidget while I talk to you and
stop tracking mud across my
nice when I hit the street the rain had
already turned La into a mud River it
was a short swim down Alvarado to my
convertible
I had to get to Santa Barbara in a big
hurry as I whipped on malland Drive the
lights were just twinkling on across the
San fernandino Valley I could barely
make them out through the driving rain
then a hard R down beat to junga Canyon
my tires squealed as I hit sa be all
right a left a left another right a left
to the body a right and into a gas
station hey Pop all right all right hold
your horses I'm
coming hey yeah where am I you can't get
there from here but I'm looking for the
same old place oh you must mean the old
same place sunny it's right out back
here's the key Jonathan winers was a
genius because he did mock the average
midwesterner um everyone loved George
Carlin for his literacy sure but I got
to be honest with you as much as I love
and respect George Carlin Jonathan wyers
is a guy that has my heart you know uh
he I I I I piss my myself listening to
Jonathan wyers and Monty and Monty
Python yeah um I used to piss myself
listening to fire sign theater anytime
they just got into those marvelous
characterizations but um the political
sists like the mort SS and cats like
that I don't know who we have now you
know um don't quite get my uh attention
anymore and I know they were way off of
fire sign theater and I no no no it's
it's thematically were there yeah I
think I think fire sign their theater on
record and live uh having not seen it
live but I'm imagine the theater that
they brought to Comedy had never been
there before man I mean they never it
the the crazy multifaceted multicar
caricature kind of of and and the
literacy of it and as you mentioned and
the um and and the subversiveness of it
had never had never really been uh done
before on a big stage and um that's more
than anything else I think what makes
them so influential especially me man I
mean I can say all this [ __ ] I want
about Monty Python but I'm far more
influenced by the presentation and the
theater of a fire sign theater well and
that's the big thing too is even if even
if the the reference actually honestly I
wouldn't even call it reference heavy
even if some of it's beyond you or uh
there's so much production that it is
it the the second half of it is an
homage to and a picking apart of like
literal r radio drama literal radio and
theater of the Mind the first half is no
this is what 1969's version of radio
ought to be doesn't exists except for on
our album but it's just it's a [ __ ]
mind [ __ ] and it makes zero sense it's a
whirlwind of borderline references uh
the satire is at the same time subtle
like literally and figuratively
sometimes you can't hear the [ __ ]
they're saying and you're like [ __ ] I
have to listen closer now yeah give me
give me a give me an example of that
first side so I can uh call it back a
little bit well it opens up with uh um
[ __ ] give me one second opens up with
the uh the car salesman whose name is
very funny hi Ralph sportsport here
Ralph Sports sportsport is that the guy
yeah Ralph sportsport yep yeah yeah he's
that's a satirization of Ralph Williams
there was a guy like that yeah bald
Ralph Williams yeah beautiful everybody
knew who Ralph Williams was everybody
just couldn't go anywhere in La without
knowing Ralph Williams yeah and the
characterization is good enough that you
don't like I didn't didn't have I I
think I read that but I didn't know it
instinctively but it still works so well
yeah yeah I I don't know the car
salesman today cats on TV
today
um are just not quite the um the
salesman the car salesman we used to
have they were colorful wacky guys and
so they made their way into it the only
guy that was left here in La was Cal
Worthington and that poor man uh is so
old now you know it's just not worth it
so that's definitely something that's
gone man and uh yeah that was fire sign
and the that's another thing too by the
way they uh didn't seem to and I like
this they didn't seem to worry that they
were being a little bit Regional there
um you know it it was in their world and
they went ahead and they commented on it
and um it's the same thing I grew up
with all kinds of New York references
when I was a kid watching TV or
listening to radio all I ever heard
about was New York sure New York this
New York that I swear of God I didn't
know anything about New York but all
these guys yeah just like done in
Brooklyn you know uh but it was funny
anyway you know the people were funny
and that Fishbowl that you were looking
at was really something else do you know
what the first thing you ever heard of
fire signs was the first thing I ever
heard of fire
sign was probably uh radio fre o when
they were on uh evenings okay okay um uh
Sunday nights on um um and I think it
had something to do with they did a lot
of stuff uh when it came to uh uh Native
Americans mhm and they were doing a bit
on how hippies were the reincar ated hi
the hippies of the day were reincarnated
Native Americans oh my God and then
sooner or later there'd be a scalping
frenzy uh somewhere in San Francisco so
you know all of this peace and love was
happening at the time and uh fire sign
was you know warning people that uh if
you think hippies are scary now uh
they're going to be wearing scalps from
their
belt yeah so yeah was that disrespectful
to Native people I don't know you know
it was more of a commentary on the um U
the any people buying into this peace
love thing that was the other thing
about the comics of the time fire sign
credibility gap whoever Lenny Bruce MH
none of them respected really respected
the so-called Peace Love ethic of the
Contemporary hippie I mean while it
sounded good and it made for great teeny
B you know bubblegum music they all uh
laughed at it sure and uh and that was
and Frank Zappa too that's guy who you
know we don't give him enough credit as
if Frank zpp I'm sure and we can we
could talk about this another day or
just something to think about Frank
Zappa great musician though he was and
he always and he wanted to be known as a
great musician he was serious as a
musician yeah his genius was the fact
that he was the sist of that era and he
was on a parallel track there was rock
and roll over there and Frank Zappa was
riding along the side just ripping it to
pieces you know just mocking
uh brutally mocking it and it was
hysterical yeah it was marvelous that's
that's one of the and we definitely
should because I'll be honest my my
experience with the Frank zap is very
limited so it would be fun to delve into
that because especially to talk about
people who are uh who represent a change
and who function as a change but don't
really get to function maybe as
themselves if if if that makes any sense
like just I'm I'm here to make a change
and let's hope that's enough great point
point because I think if Frank Zappa
were here and I did interview him once
and he was uh a wonderful guy but very
very sarcastic guy I I think he much
would have rather been known as a a
great guitar player because he he said
he said to me Point Blank you know I'm
as good a guitar player as jimmi
Hendricks and he was
serious and and uh but what he did and
did brilliantly was and there's nothing
like that now no there's no saturnist of
the current you know whatever the
Zeitgeist you know whatever the the
whether it be
hipop um maybe Tyler the Creator but I
doubt it you know um uh rock and roll
there's nobody out there that is is
looking at it pointing and laughing sure
and there should be at least one person
I think yeah that'd be nice
anyway would be it' be fun because I
mean I'm sure it exists too I mean it
does exist with comedy but at some point
I I don't know if it makes me a dick to
kind of get tired of people getting
excessively meta and it's funny to say
that talking about an album that is
pretty meta but I do get a little tired
of people picking apart comedy to the
point where they're not making comedy
anymore which uh what do you mean for
instance uh well I can't give it for for
in I would say I'm trying to think of
somebody who maybe is more of an a
modern-day Andy calman but oh I dig okay
that kind of thing and I know there are
people but I can't because I ignore them
I can't think of anybody right off I
know what I know what you're saying um I
completely agree and um I think the
Dumber the better so long as you're not
being destructive or hurtful meaning
sure uh I don't think it's funny to hey
I hear the new polio vaccine is out yeah
sure you know I I don't think that's
quite funny right but um dumb as in uh
for instance the Tom Brady deflate gate
thing MH you know that needs to be just
absolutely destroyed I who cares I do
I'm a football fan whatever I'm not
going to waste my time it's not worth my
day it's not worth 5 minutes yeah and uh
so all of that needs far more searing
than it's getting mhm um beyond that you
know the the who we are as people man I
mean human the human race especially the
American people themselves have are must
must be strangling MH on all of the
confusion and near Anarchy right now and
I'm sure that we are looking desperately
for somebody who can make some sense out
of this [ __ ] and I I think the way to do
it is to get it back to you know the
average person just what makes us uh uh
what makes us complicit in all of this
confusion how can we change that you
know and and I'm not looking to change
the world or anything but like last last
night on our show I had a character on
Don mix as a character I do and he talks
he talks a little bit like Pete McClosky
used to as a congressman from the United
State I just love this accent you know
and he likes to say this guy's from
upstate New York was hey Don how you
doing let's get a cup of coffee and Don
was talking and he's saying I think it's
very important well it turns out the way
because he talks that way he I like to
get right up close and personal and talk
to people and well it turns out his
breath is just foul you know so while
he's trying to make his point you know
and it's very important I think at this
particular time uh could you and I had
another character done could you back
off a little bit what's what's the I
don't understand well you're you know
it's really it's getting to me man what
is that gorgona I happen to like yeah I
like gorgona cheese or problem there you
know
I mean you're not you're not going to
make your point man no matter how
profound if your breath is bad and uh
you
know to me man that's that's what it's
all about that's that's the price of
admission for me so all right hold it
right where you are I'm Lieutenant
Bradshaw with a piece of advice for you
now here in the studio it's all Knuckles
and knoow but when that red light goes
off I'm just playing Harry aim citizen
weekend father now take a tip from a cop
who does radio work can be just as dirty
and exciting is hunting down Public
Enemy Number One so when I get home my
old lady knows what I need and how a
warm Heap and bowl full of loosa castor
oil Flakes with real glycerin vibo it
doesn't just wash your mouth out it
cleans the whole system right on down
the line so come on you little rookies
tell your mom to get on it and do it
every day just remember what the guys
don't at the precinct house sing Oh it
ain't no use if you ain't got the Boost
the Boost you get from Lo
Lo the all weather
breakfast and now we return you to act
three of Nick danger third
eye again fire sign still around thank
God because it's wonderful it's
wonderful stuff to listen to it is
underexposed so I do Wonder like what
about it like I I I wonder like how the
hell like I I do try and Pitch it to
other people and I the part of this is
to be like okay maybe you won't get it
at first maybe you'll feel like some of
this is over your head maybe you'll feel
like well I wasn't alive in the' 60s or
70s so it's not going to make but I I
feel like the there is there's more than
enough silly I mean they somehow pull
out of they made me laugh way too hard
at something that's so offensive and
it's not it's like because I knew how
satirical it was I mean they used every
every they use every racial slur
possible in this one song because it's
supposed to be cting America and thaty
just like oh this is beautiful this is
wonderful now obvious it's a little hard
to separate the weat from the chaff and
tell who's laughing for the right
reasons but you hope so you hope if you
expose somebody to something like that
that they get it yeah and here's the
thing play that now and there's lots and
lots of people that won't get it
absolutely and lots and lots of people
that will therefore want to have you and
me hung by our thumbs and if they can
find any of the fire sign theater that
are still alive they'll hang them too
and when you try to explain it to them
you'll find yourself talking to idiots
yep and as the fires leap around us and
as we finally go up to our ultimate
martyrdom you know we're just watching
what are we seeing from where what are
we seeing from the stake that we're
being burned at a a society that is that
is is doomed itself with its own
stupidity or are we just looking at us
at a microcosm that happened to catch us
as we were running out of the village I
don't know right right um I do know
that perception is everything we are
learning that uh and so if you want to
get through to people you have to make
it clear man um fire sign theater is
talking to a college educated or a bunch
of college students back in 1969 1970
every one of us got it we're we're
laughing our ass up we're going out
we're buying tickets to the next fire
sign theater but take that theater
beyond that take it into put it on The
Ed Sullivan Show or H or whatever was
happening then sure and now you get now
you got some problems you know now you
got some some problems in uh in
interpreting that so
I yeah you know I good
point I do hope I I do hope that there's
there's there's a way I mean here
luckily they've got a web presence and
they've got people passing their stuff
down like my my uh my late stepfather
was stepfather [ __ ] father-in-law Jesus
Christ he was a DJ and like he was so
jealous of me interviewing fire sign the
anybody from fire sign that I was like
well wait a minute I feel like yeah
exactly right I mean he course he
interviewed chich and Chong back in the
day and I was like well are you kidding
you're jealous of me like this is kind
of mindblowing to me so it's there is
like there there are people who can at
least speak for it and I there I'm just
hoping that uh you know we can spread
the word well I think if you take fire
anything that fire sign theater did that
that addresses what you and I are
talking about Jason which is those those
everyday bits of of absurdity uh those
things need to be highlighted because
they did they did address them I think
they became known and I knew them for
their cultural satire and political
satire um but look when I was growing up
especially when I got into high school
college Years everybody was a marks
Brothers fan yeah and I was I was a
Laurel and Hardy guy and I'm not saying
I'm superior to them because I was very
much in a minority everybody oh Marx the
Marx brothers were smart and look at all
that whack [ __ ] they did and uh you know
Fredonia wow how cool is that
and I'm laughing at Oliver Hardy getting
a saw blade on his head you know I
I I still do I still do man I believe
the culture has followed me a little bit
more than it has the people that were
Marx Brothers fans although I'm sure
they would give us an argument but I
think that Laur and Hardy's every man
humor getting saw blades busted on their
head or you know tripping over you know
a dog is that's what comedy today uh
that's what you laugh at I think more
than perhaps the
the um the sophistication of a Marx
Brothers sure however you know they were
the Marx Brothers so who's this you know
I can't you know certainly they haven't
lost in any right their cache at all
yeah well although that you know they
they did luck out with the Resurgence in
the 70s I mean that's that's one of the
reasons probably why I mean it was it
was Chic to like them so that's that
would be oh yeah absolutely and I
wouldn't probably wouldn't know who they
were if it wasn't for that Resurgence
and I'm I mean I would probably be more
of a mark Brothers guy than a Laurel and
Hardy guy but that's cuz I didn't grow
up with Laurel and Hardy the other thing
is that the Marx Brothers survived
Laurel and Hardy died uh Oliver Hardy
was gone by the 50s and Stan Laurel died
in the 60s uh Groucho Marx on the other
hand was was alive through the pretty
much the 70s and had a great right uh
line in fact I'm sitting listening to
the radio I'm working at WBBM in Upstate
New York uh I don't know what it was the
mid 70s late 70s and I'm listening to
ABC Entertainment News where it came out
that Richard Nixon's enemies list
included grouo marks okay and Mark and
and Marx's quote was I deny everything
because and this is the ABC news guy
saying when reached at his home grouo
Mark said I deny everything because
everything I deny is a lie end quote you
know so we we still had Groucho hanging
around and uh and uh giving us and he
hosted a game show right my mother never
missed You Bet Your Life which was the
gro marks it was a who gave him that
show and why it was a stroke of Genius
cuz it was a fun damn show and yeah
Laurel and Hardy were strictly film
actors film comedians uh two realer
Comics who just happened to discover two
characters that were entirely relatable
very real lots of lots of pathos going
on there and uh and great comic
invention uh in terms of just Behavior
especially with Oliver Hardy and all the
weird [ __ ] that he did so I I'm the kind
of guy intellectually and I'm sitting in
a room like you Jason a bunch of people
and we're all talking comedy and I would
be afraid to say I wasn't a mark
Brothers fan cuz I didn't want I don't
want people to throw [ __ ] at me right
right but if it's just if it's just you
and me sitting down drinking beer I'm a
Laur and heart I'm a Laur and Hardy fan
so I well and that's just the thing
that's completely legit I mean I had to
turn around on on the three stoes a
couple years ago too and I had to be
like all right you know what I I get it
I get it now it's not my thing but like
I can't [ __ ] on it anymore I used to
[ __ ] on it I'm like no that's just it's
is again I I mean I'm I don't know I'm
very picky about [ __ ] I like but you
know I also I can't [ __ ] on other
people's taste anymore I us real snob
did you see the movie the the three
Studios movie no I was scared to see it
it it was oh my God it was it was
fantastic really it really was yeah
especially um Willie sasu plays Curley I
love him oh my God he was
unbelievable I have to say that it was a
lot of it was about it wasn't a movie
about the three stoes as men and oh yeah
by the way they were actors it was it
basically took them and it created a
whole new episode of their Adventure
right right was very funny very funny
all right I may have to give it a shot
now check it out just just if if for no
other reason than the acting uh the
characterization of the three guys uh is
is pretty damn good man yeah and the and
the movie ends with uh uh it's a
shame you know that song uhhuh yeah well
the it's the three of them singing
singing it you know it's a sh Mo starts
out and then curly wraps up it's it's
pretty funny I I realize we've gone far
away from fire sign theer no I was about
to pull us back don't worry but I got to
tell you I think I think what we're
talking about fire sign theater be right
up their alley you know in terms of uh
who their influences were you know for
sure I mean actually what's interesting
too is the Phil Proctor's first Al uh uh
episode of the show was talking about
Bob and Ray and I was going to ask you
if you ever listened to Bob and Ray I
wasn't sure because it's it's it's an
older influence obviously it's well Bob
and Ray were a radio show New York yeah
and so that right away uh Phil may have
been Phil's older than me he might have
heard them when he was in college I
don't know where is Phil from LA or is
he from New York do you know ah [ __ ]
somewhere in the midwest I believe I
should remember this probably heard T
Bob and Ray were a radio show I didn't
there's two things though that I will
forever remember Bob and Ray from and
they're both wildly hysterically funny
and they never failed to amuse me and
one of them Bob and Ray were hired to do
a b Brand's potato chip commercial
series it's an old potato chip ran okay
and this is this is Bob and Ray comedy
at its finest and uh hi this is Bob and
Ray and we're here with B brand potato
chips and a potato chip Brand X now
we're going to put this potato chip
Brand X in the tailpipe of this car okay
Bob started up and the exhaust pours
over the potato chip we have Mr Joan all
I taste that potato
chip yeah well what's it taste like guys
Sayes it taste lousy what do you think
now try a bell brand potato chip well of
course it's good but aren't you going to
put it in a tailpipe too thank you very
much Bell br so that's the commercial I
love it then the second thing they did
was on fire or was on Saturday Night
Live where they did do you think I'm
sexy by Rod Stewart they did their
version dressed in business suits
sitting with their legs folded as if
they were at a shareholders meeting and
the Three Chicks behind them lorine
Newman Jane curtain and Gilder rner are
doing all kinds of sexy bump and grind
disco [ __ ] but when it goes to do you
think I'm sexy and you want my body
they're just sitting there with their
arms folded in business suits mhm uh uh
if you had to see it to really
appreciate it but uh the fact that it
was taking Rod Stewart's uh you know I
hope my penis is evident in these tight
pants kind of music and here they are
looking like a couple of guys that are
going to give you a bank loan love uh it
was pretty fcking funny man so that's
all I know of those cats I always hate
cops yeah Nick I hate cops too me too I
I tell you guys what I'm going to do
I'll tell you what I'm I'm going to get
even with every rotten cop in the city
yeah me too how you going to do it Nick
how you going to do it you know what I'm
going to do no no what you going to do
I'm going to I'm going to turn in my
badge yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I'm going to burn my uniform
hi friends Ro small sport owner and
operator of the world's biggest
dealership West BC as you know we're
overdosed again with all tastes and
kilos let's just take a look at some of
these fabulous Lids the look War a
report says this key should be CED for
$10,500 in Easy Money senses of a year
to life and nobody down a complete price
to you including sticks and stems and
seeds wine soaked and sugar cured
completely clean for your smoking
pleasure the complete price only what
the traffic will allow and unmarked
bills delivered to me Ral icebag in a
plain Brown rapper by a brown shwed
Square in the dead of night that's funny
and great but it's as Square as you can
get and that it influenced uh you know
Phil doctor at the very least and yeah
obviously the culture is going to inform
what fire sign becomes but then I'm I'm
curious what I want to know and this is
something that that it's it's real hard
to track is I want to know what the
undercurrent that they were writing and
helping create the fire sign that is
like how that influenced comedians
specifically is there something like in
your own work that you can Peg as being
something oh this is very fire sign
something that I've done or something
that's clearly been influenced by them
yeah oh every day
uh the my show is a fire sign theater
style show there's a lot of characters
going on there's a lot of bumping into
each other uh there's a lot of of uh
confused talk there's a lot of of of the
the the ziness I think of the show that
I do and it's just myself I mean I'm
doing five characters so I'm working my
ass off you know and right yeah you know
I'm I think I'm going to give myself a
raise one of these days but idea that
that right there when I heard the m
of a fire sign theater I knew right away
I wanted to do that you know um the rest
of it is is strictly born of you know
that's style you know that's that's
style and that is something is is going
to kind of exist but the rest of it is
born of my own experience as a person
you know um what I grew up with who I
grew you know all these characters that
I have reflect people that I knew in my
life and uh you know but I fire sign
theater is there first and foremost and
then I would say Laurel and Hardy is in
there and then I would say Lenny Bruce
is in there and then I would say that
um uh I can't say the money Python's an
influence Because by the time I got into
my professional world I think I was
pretty
well uh I
formulated you know what I thought was
funny or at least at least what was
going to you know make me react and it
just so happened when I discovered Monty
Python I would say oh wow look at these
guys are laughing at the same stuff I'm
laughing at you know um I think the
funniest guys in the world are
three um well I would I would have to
say yeah three of
them right now for me are are John C
Bill Murray and Fred Willard and they
may be three wildly Divergent people you
know but um they all deal with the same
thing which is just the uh absolute
hysterically um
funny uh M and mundane world that we
live in you know and and all the Char
the characters those guys play are not
highly charged political sure they're
not playing they're not playing the
dictator like Charlie Chaplain you know
they're not prancing across the stage
and bouncing the world on a ball they're
they're on a golf course someplace yeah
and they're they're they're they're
they're a college professor throwing a
guy through a window there are you know
and Fred Willard with that marvelous uh
I mean just you all you have to do is
turn a switch on and Fred encapsulates
everything phony about Television right
uh personalities you know what he
does so anyway you know that um
um those three guys as well um sort of
influence you know how I do things I'm
not sure I answered your question but no
no no you did you did we always Meander
a little that's fine I think I think the
other thing is that I'm absolutely
sickened and fascinated and bored by and
challenged by the flood
of of the the the the the culture as it
pounds its way into my living room every
way every day by way of of Television um
it's just just it's giving me um you
know look uh we finally come to a point
where some things can't be sazed you
know that never happened in my life yeah
what Westboro Baptist Church you cannot
saiz that you know right uh Fred all of
that [ __ ] it's just too weird so where
do you go with with people like that
right what do you go what do you do with
that yeah and also do you how do you do
it in that like what's the tone of doing
it so that it's right because listening
again if you listen to this you you the
tone of fire sign doesn't the tone
doesn't speak satire the content does
the tone is like goofy acting like
overacting in a lot of cases goofy like
just
ridiculous like not not intentionally
off point sometimes where they're they
sound like one guy might sound like he's
reading where the other guy sounds like
he's just it's it's a intentional mixed
bag in the satire comes from that kind
of disharmony like which is something I
see what you're saying man you know what
I mean like cuz a lot of times like oh
really well isn't that but it's it's
kind of like this old timey radio feel
to it it's it's I could that's one thing
about fire sign that like I can't Peg
them I can't figure out what here's what
I think is here's what I think is going
on there I think it's it what I think is
going on with fires sign theater is
something that I I don't think can be
done again and the reason is this what
they had was suddenly
an appetite a a there was a a market for
or an audience for sending up the
culture and and and commenting on the
culture and the first thing that they
thought to do was take this racist and
warmongering and and uh you know
classist society that we're living in
and sexist society we're living in and
comment on it using this other thing
that we've got which was the TV and the
radio of the time it was very much I
married you I Love Lucy and it was all
so let's go ahead and jam that into that
because it was Radical and it seemed
like you know the most effective way of
of putting this mirror up to the world
and say look at this we're going to put
it through I Love Lucy it's kind of like
you know uh Oliver Stone's Oliver
Stone's hamfisted attempt there in
Natural Born Killers where he has that
sitcom of daddy you know molesting the
little girl you know uh okay Oliver good
for you man I I I got that one man a
long time ago Dude you didn't really
have to show that uh but at that time in
in the 60s that's exactly what what was
needed that's exactly how you should do
it take that goofy asinine Hollywood
Palace TV and thrust into it the uh
Insanity of the world
today we come from now we're 40 years
after that and that's been done over and
over and over and over again and now
today you have a lot of thoughtful
people like Louis CK mhm and there kind
of thoughtful tight standup sets there
wasn't a whole lot of theater going on
out there and in terms of other than you
know uh improv
theater um because the zaniness man and
the cookiness and the
goofiness um is almost like not real
enough I think we need to I think people
want their comedy where you sit down and
stare across the table and and say
something really funny that's
life-changing too yeah I was thinking
kind of the same thing it's it's not
it's not dissimilar to the way you know
just straight up acting what we accept
as acting has uh developed and also the
fact that most movies now are based on
something either that already exists or
had to have happened in real life or we
won't buy it which is so strange to me
because that's that's like we we can't
separate ourselves long enough to enjoy
something unless it's super real which
is not really the point well you know
fiction um has taken a backseat to the
documentary hasn't it and uh and and you
know I I I had an acting teacher once
who said to us uh it was after the
challeng exploded mhm and it had been on
television and they showed the mother
and father of Christina Christine mlli
who was the teacher it showed the mother
and father and the reaction to that
shuttle blowing up and the reaction they
were smiling mhm they they didn't they
didn't know what they were seeing they
thought oh wow that that was interesting
and I guess it's the second state and
they continued to smile and only
gradually did they look around them and
see the other people reacting did they
begin to the smile didn't disappear but
now the worried edges around the eyes
began to appear and the sort the the
mouth became tighter as they looked and
they and and you could see them and and
I remember my teacher a guy named darl
Hickman saying that's the kind of acting
you're going to have to do because
that's what people are seeing people are
more and more and more exposed to the
real world so you can't you can't help
it man you know I know what you're
saying uh Jason I really do but the
people out there have been exposed to
God Almighty man look at the I mean
you've we've seen it on TV a guy blowing
his brains out on the freeway out here
in the marina freeway see every kind of
horrific violence you can dial up on
YouTube um you so how can you do it any
other way sure sure where if you're
going to give people fantasy you have to
connect it somehow it has to be a
fantasy that's
attainable that's that can happen you
know if you're going to if you're going
to write fiction it has to be fiction
that resonates absolutely with the real
best one of the best movies and I
haven't heard anybody say this so this
will be a new new one for you one of the
best movies I've seen in the last five
or six or seven years it's Michael
Clayton George Clooney's movie about an
attorney who's a fixer a guy that goes I
loved it um is completely made up but
somehow that man the struggles of his
life the Loyalty he has to his friends M
the the beauty of the writing and the
acting was so relatable to me I I it
could very well have happened sure you
know uh because those performers carried
it through for me so I let's let's put
it this way whatever anybody is doing
out there in art they got to be damn
good for it to rise to the top oh yeah
yeah absolutely and that that that gets
to another one of my favorite speeches
as long as I'm just hogging all this
time here and Jason you're being so
polite this poor guys listening to be we
have lots and lots of paintbrushes and
lots and lots of canvas and lots and
lots of sketchbooks and lots and lots of
of of uh pallets with paint but we still
only have one Rembrandt one Picasso and
one Da Vinci and uh now we have lots and
lots and lots of podcasts lots and lots
of little video cameras lots and lots of
YouTubes but there still is going to be
a very limited number of real artists
with those things you know like like
Charles Bowski said you know God made
many poets but not enough
poetry you um I we need to you know kind
of get get with that one man you know um
there's a lot of noise out there right
now sure lots of noise and uh somebody
somewhere needs to shut up probably me
all right what an
outline well you're a good man for
listening but no this is the kind of
stuff that we like to do and Norm
honestly if it wasn't you it would be me
rambling about what I think art is about
so I think people are sick of me saying
it so it's good to have somebody else do
it who you know it justifies all my
[ __ ] thoughts it's good well I'm
glad when you said a comedy album the
first one that came to my mind was all
hell lennin marks and Fire theater in
general nothing else I I thought briefly
about David fry and some of the other
cats that influenced uh you know sort of
made me laugh but these guys were it for
me yeah if you're going to recommend
this album I mean like I said I know you
said the Nick danger thing was probably
the thing that stuck out about this one
if you're going to recommend this album
to somebody or just recommend fire sign
to somebody who hasn't heard of them or
heard them how do you make them listen
to
it what would you say she
this is the birth of modern satire I I
that's you know that word satire what
you got you you really got me in that
one Jason because I I realize now the
word satire means nothing to most people
they don't know what it yeah people
think that're just being funny as is
satire um you know the best definition
of satire I ever heard was Gary Trudeau
said it was uh you know comedy with a
point of view um I would
say this is the birth of of Stoner humor
list very true I yeah everybody who's
ever turned me on to them I'm certain
had to have heard them one time or
another Stone yeah oh yeah absolutely
there's no doubt now I was like well
this is why you like that then cuz this
I didn't get it you know just totally
that that makes zero sense but it does
it might take I don't I don't like to
say that things are an acquired taste I
think it's something where you just have
to you have to just you just got to
listen to it you just got to give it a
shot yeah I think I think if people are
interested in uh how things come about I
think the birth of Stoner humor uh this
is it man you can go and say well you
know fire sign probably were influenced
as as all of us were at one way or
another by Lenny Bruce or or Lord
Buckley or people like that but this
here was the first
mass-produced Stoner humor that your
parents let you have not knowing really
what it was absolutely oh that's nice
there's car look at that that scratch
your marks huh you know that's what they
thought so I was actually going to ask
about Buckley just given his you know
both of your pensions for voice
switching um I that might be a good
conversation for another time but uh
thank you for doing this for for one
andas sorry I ran so late apologies for
that no problem no problem at all man
where do people find you online I know
it's obvious but why don't you tell them
anyway well we we are at podcast one now
that's the platform you know uh but
we're also the best way to find us is at
www.il Hendry show.com there's a big fat
button in the middle of the page that
gives you our daily podcast there's a
huge marvelously wonderful index of our
uh all of the shows we've done down
through the last 20 years just about
20,000 hours and uh wow we have a chat
feature that we do on on Friday nights I
talk to everybody and a comment section
it's a lot of fun and uh and I'm very
grateful for the time you gave us here
Jason I appreciate it and uh look
forward to more of your show and uh love
talking love talking about comedy man
cuz it's God Almighty if laughter is not
a religion I don't know what it is you
know to me it's you know what I'm saying
brother I do I absolutely do um again
thank you for doing this um this is this
is a lot of fun I should also let you
know that Phil Proctor did tell me to
tell you that he's a fan of yours as
well and I wanted to ask you to say
hello to him and I yes thank you very
very much uh let him know from another
Phil I I I'm tell him that I'm in awe
and I'm you know forever grateful for
that I really am where are you located
man I'm in Burbank oh cool you're okay
fine I thought you were out in the last
one I last podcast I did the cat was in
Fort Wayne Indiana you know I was like
really well what we should do is have
some coffee well I'm in Fort Wayne
phille oh sorry know very cool very cool
um thank you guys for listening check
out fire sign theater go listen to Phil
Henry and as always have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress enter tainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
f-star rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook.com/ Comedy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedyon vinyl.com
[Music]
hello
Ary what the why are there DVDs stacked
everywhere
Hello Kiki is that you girl I can't see
you Ary where are
you damn it
Dan Ary thank God what what happened to
you oh the S pile fell on me I'll be
okay but but your arm is gone oh yeah I
just I had to cut it off to free myself
all these DVDs are a hazard to the
health of all of us I mean why did you
even buy all of
these well I'll tell you
the arm thing doesn't work without an
arm I know I blame the blood loss listen
to the why did I buy this podcast every
other Thursday on iTunes on
wbt.com or find us on stolen dress.com
[Music]