[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast the year is 1998 the album is
funh housee the artist Dana G and my
guest is Woody battalia thank you so
much for being here thank you so much
for having me Jason you host a
delightful podcast called my minute with
Andre oh you're so kind and uh it's it's
it's fun uh and it was fun for me to be
on especially since you let me ramble
for like three hours for some reason we
definitely ended up talking quite a
while on a on a wide range of topics
most most of which were cut out just
just in the interest of time not because
not because you're not delightful but
because my listeners are like you know
get make with the make with the wall of
Sean okay sure sure that makes that
makes sense what uh tell the audience a
little bit about yourself other than
your podcast about my Dinner with Andre
all right aside from my podcast that is
only about my Dinner with Andre I also
have other interests so I am a standup
comedian uh I live and work in uh in
Western New York I live in Rochester and
uh uh I play around the region currently
I'm also uh host a radio show called
Almost Tuesday that's a comedy variety
show that airs Monday nights around here
uh on a station called W yo and uh and
just you know I have a I have a huge
interest in comedy and I I've listen to
your show for a while as well so I was
excited to to hear from you about about
being on my
show what uh what kind of uh stuff is on
your radio show the only reason I ask is
because I never grew up with comedy as
an option on radio so I'm I'm always
curious so it's a variety show meaning
that we also have live music performance
every episode so it's uh awesome it is
like a miniature no budget version of a
maybe a Saturday Night Live or also has
a lot in common with like the best show
with Tom sharpling so it's we do a
variety of different comedy segments uh
we'll do sketch stuff that we've written
we'll also do uh sort of improvised
comedy segments we'll also do segments
where we're just talking uh about
whatever and then we also have guests so
you know like recently we had uh we had
on La comedian Barbara Gray we've had on
Nathan Raben we've had uh national
public radios Jesse Thorne we've had you
know a bunch of uh we we tend to pull in
some notable people to call in and talk
to us or be live in studio we're also
kind of on the pulse of the the the
comedy scene out here in Upstate New
York and extending into New York City
and we uh we have a lot of uh you know
we're just we're just kind of
documenting a lot of comedy and also you
know making up a bunch
ourselves that's uh that's delightful
can people stream it anywhere or is it
only on terrestrial R oh no of course
you can stream it uh so our uh you can
stream it at
wm.org that is uh Monday nights Eastern
Time 9 to 11 p.m. and then also we put
it out through a service because we also
play copyrighted music and stuff we use
the service called Mixcloud for archives
uh so that's mixcloud.com
Tuesday because they take care of the of
the licensing for the music stuff so
that way I don't have to chop up the
show into tiny pieces and put it and put
it out uh iTunes style because obviously
you throw that stuff in there and it
will it will eventually be
rejected right right yeah it's a pain in
the ass okay so let's do this uh Dana
Gould's stuff was released eventually on
vinyl not originally so like we said
this is a 1998 album when did you first
hear it uh so I first heard it pretty
close to when it came out I think I was
actually living in my first
apartment uh in I probably heard it in
1999 or 2000 but I had heard a bunch of
this material on TV prior to this
because Dana gold was in the ' 80s and
90s one of these perennial comedians who
you'd see on all of the television
showcase shows like evening at The
Improv etc etc etc uh so I had seen i'
had seen a bunch of these bits he was a
person who I never knew his name but I
knew stuff from his act and then I
learned who he was uh later on when I
was searching for comedy to listen to
and watch when I was living in my first
apartment with my roommates and we were
all big fans of like Mr Show and Dana
Gold's kind of Mr show adjacent like
sort of in the alternative comedy you
know boom of the mid late 990s
sure I used to think he was Paul F
Tomkins when I was a little bit younger
I confused him and Paul F Tomkins now
their voices aren't even that similar
they don't look they look a little
similar when Paul does not have a
mustache I call him Paul because of
course we're best friends first name
basis bu me uhhuh yeah we've been in a
room together once uh so uh yeah I used
to confuse the two of them and
eventually it sort of became clear that
they're very very different men
including in terms of style although I
don't know what kind of ComEd
Paul Tomkins was doing at this time uh
now I I I'll just tell people so you
know I enjoyed a lot of what I heard
it's a little dated oh it is it is and I
and that's part of the reason that I
picked it because I thought we'd have a
lot to talk about because I know that
you yeah there is I know on your show
you cover a lot you know what what you
could say and what you can't say or well
whatever you can say anything you want
but but what probably isn't going to get
a good reaction from an audience these
days and what people would find to be
uh questionable or offensive or hurtful
to some people or whatever uhuh yeah
yeah I mean and much as like I might
listen to it be like well you know he
means well it's also like well okay
that's fine if he means well but he
still said it but there's some really
funny [ __ ] on it too like there's
genuinely some very very funny stuff um
you can tell that his voice you can tell
what of his voice has flavored The
Simpsons since he started writing on it
too
absolutely it's so weird to me that this
this guy's particular obsession with
particular parts of Pop Culture have
made their way I don't know I I'm not
articulating it properly maybe you can
say it better because I I feel like
you're probably more familiar with his
work I know I know exactly what you're
trying to say like so Dana Gould has a
few different Fascinations which sort of
translate themselves into pop culture he
is obsessed with old science fiction and
uh uh movie and monster movies from like
the late 60s and backward so anything up
to anything from the universal monsters
up to Planet of the Apes is is all in
his wheelhouse and uh and Planet of the
Apes is like his favorite movie he's
been on a lot of podcasts talking about
it he has his own podcast where he's
talked about it at length um and then
also just old Hollywood culture is the
thing that he talks about a lot like old
polls of actors even if they weren't
actors in like monster movies or
anything he's he's sort of the guy for
those
references also things like uh also you
know
UFOs and uh and anything that you'd find
on the X Files that's also like kind of
in his uh right yeah and uh and then and
then also like uh 90 or 80s alternative
music like The Smiths and things like
that
for example on this record it's a very
particular world he lives in you know he
also he's fortunate because I've talked
about this before there are a bunch of
people who I've met who I just they'll
tell me the stories so I'm getting them
like third or fourth hand like their
associations with old Hollywood because
I love old Hollywood but I'll speak to
people they're like yeah I I speak
speaking to somebody who's been on the
show before yeah and he's like oh did I
tell you we were just having a
conversation on the phone he like did I
tell you I was friends with Milton Burl
and I'm like [ __ ] no you didn't tell me
you were friends with Milton burl guy is
too young to be friends with Milt he
knew him and right it's insane and like
he literally he got to walk into his
special humidor in his in this cigar
shop and he said hey give Dan a box of
my cigars you know the good ones from
direct from Cuba and oh wow like I'm
just like you [ __ ] and I mean
that in the politest way cuz I love this
particular Dan but uh it was just like
God damn it like that's a world that
I've missed and Dana Gould is there on
the cusp too of like they they weren't
all dead yet it's true and he made
friends with he like made friends with
Vampira oh my God like he he literally
he made he was actually supporting
Vampira in the last few years of her
life he was like paying her rent and
like taking her to the doctor and stuff
like that because he had befriended her
and it was kind of the she had she had
SE the same situation with Dana Gould as
like uh Edwood and Bella legosi in the
movie Edwood yes it's basically the same
relationship where he finds her and then
he becomes her like benefactor because
he's a super fan from his childhood is
it weird to that I partially and I I
feel like Dana G probably had this too
and that's why it happened you kind of
if you're me you're like I kind of want
to be that guy I kind of want to be the
guy who takes care of this this this
Legend who is unappreciated absolutely I
know is that weird thing when I hope to
do this with Steve
Gutenberg oh my God what I mean I'll
I'll settle for
I'm trying to it was my first pull of
like somebody that from my childhood who
I don't who isn't doing a ton of work
right now right is probably but I think
Good's probably doing fine he's he's
probably doing fine yeah absolutely prob
doesn't have to work that's the thing
that's that's a solid one no that's
pretty good I and like I Ran So I
interviewed this episode will yeah this
episode will have run before yours does
cuz these are now way way way way way
behind I'm I behind is what's happened
it I I get it no we both are uh I
interviewed Paul douly the other day and
he's a delight and I didn't realize he
had just turned 90 so he's not only been
in St yeah forever but he also we're
talking after the interview shuts down
of course he's like yeah oh yeah and
then I met Buster Keaton uh he was my
hero and I got to meet Buster I'm like
oh [ __ ] there are some people around who
legit got to meet some people that I
would have killed to meet like you know
he he met Buster Katon he also talks
about how
on his second or third Robert Alman
movie Robert Alman had never read
anything he'd written or knew if he'
read anything hey you want to write a
movie for me like he's been had these
very weird Hollywood experiences that he
is just like he gets to Rattle off and
I'm like damn that's the kind of
Hollywood that I want to of a connection
with you know so much fun yeah that's
yeah I I yeah the idea that there's that
there's still people alive who have like
these these stories from a time when
things are like simpler or like it was
smaller there were fewer there were
maybe fewer celebrities there were fewer
for sure there was less money somehow I
mean even though these people were Rich
it was like right you know movies
weren't making billions and billions of
dollars yeah yeah I I I actually kind of
wanted to ask Paul duly about this
because uh where I interviewed him was
in TCA Lake California which at one
point was basically owned by uh Bob Hope
Bob Hope basically owned this entire
part of la oh really and uh yeah and uh
you know I and I don't know enough of
the details I forgotten to add that's
that's that's a guy that I'd like to
interview somebody about again I'm sure
the the the previously mentioned Dan I'm
sure oh yes he did he wrote for Bob
newart on one of his last specials
that's what of the or not Bob newart Bob
Hope sorry wrote for Bob Hope on one of
his last specials and I'm like God damn
it you were like 20 how'd you get to
write for Bob Hope and why would he
that's whatever that's fine I'm very
jealous I'm very jealous of these guys
uh so when you first heard this like I
can definitely tell if I had listened to
this cuz this came out when I was 18 if
I had heard it when I was 18 uh I
wouldn't have noticed any of the stuff
that I now might be a little irked by
and I probably would have loved the [ __ ]
out of this album yeah it it that's the
thing is that at the time this was I
think this is representative of like The
Cutting Edge of comedy at the time
because I mean this is the alternative
era where it was okay to talk about
weird pop culture stuff which was a
thing that really wasn't in comedy
before I think nearly as much because
everybody was trying to play to the
biggest audience possible this is where
this is where comedians like dug in and
found their particular audience and it
was the same audience of people who
might go
see you know uh who might go see uh
Dinosaur Jr would also be interested in
going to see Dana Gould or or uh or
Sarah Silverman or Mark Marin or uh you
know whoever uh David Cross in the in
the 90s so I think that uh at the time I
was like oh here's somebody who talks
about things that I also kind of know
about and I mean I'm not I'm not into
monster movies as much as Danny G but I
definitely identifi like he mentions uh
he mentions 9inch Nails in here which is
a band I listen to when I was in high
school and I was like and and for me
that's like oh my God there's a new
generation of comedians who can do uh
who are and it was actually one of the
things that inspired me to do comedy
myself because like oh okay it's okay to
talk about the things that are in my
real life and also it was Progressive
for its time now I know that there's
plenty of stuff in this record that's
that are that's crazy you wouldn't I
mean and he wouldn't do it now but uh
but back then I mean like he's talking
about how he has a gay friend who he's
trying to uh introduce to his parents
and this whole thing where he's trying
to I mean the fact that like he's like
I'm cool with my gay friend but I think
my gay friend should jump back into the
closet for when my parents visit is very
much a totally fine thing and good for
you buddy back
in and now it's completely crazy to any
of us you know right yeah and but and
it's at the very least a bit like that
plays a little more like you can sort of
you can sort of get it uh and honestly
to me my favorite stuff on here is his
most absurd when he gets to the less
honestly the the stuff that's maybe a
little bit less about his actual life
like specifically when he's talking
about uh when he's talking about uh old
ad slogans like the very simple ones
that are very stupid and he about if you
don't like milk try sucking my ass if I
remember it's something that milk enjoy
and if you what do he say milk enjoy it
and if you don't why or oh [ __ ] I can't
remember now but it's like yeah but why
try sucking my ass is the punch line or
why not try sucking my ass
and yeah I I think uh
it was like cheese you [ __ ] or something
like that yeah uh I really I really
enjoy that bit I
enjoy uh I enjoy the let's see where
they're doing the the pitches for what
uh what Neil Armstrong is going to say
uh when he steps out to the
Moon uh I think that's great I think
that oh the uh the Vincent Price dating
bit is very
good cuz his impression is so
good right yeah I mean that's that's
another thing that I guess I didn't
expect with him I didn't honestly didn't
expect him to be a voice guy because I'm
realizing now I've seen him on stuff I
know he writes for The Simpsons I don't
know that I've ever heard his comedy
before today people would be like what
are you doing was like obviously I
listen to a bunch of old [ __ ] so uh I'm
still catching up so I guess I didn't
expect the voice stuff yeah it's funny
that and I don't think I thought too
much of it at the time either but doing
impressions I think it used to be more
common to do a ton of Impressions and
now I feel like you're either I feel
like you're either an impression guy or
not I feel like you're either James
Adomian or your or you're somebody who
completely doesn't ever do Impressions
uh and and Dana G is kind of this hybrid
where he's he's doing regular you know
classic standup stuff about like
relationships and his parents and his
his regular life or whatever and then
he's also going into a fantasy place
where he's doing impressions of actual
celebrities or a lot of his bits have
like a real act out uh uh sense to them
where he's like acting out a scene and
he's really going for it I like how
Earnest he is and that he's and that he
uh he performs these bits for
real yeah I feel like that's the kind of
being the ham that I am like if I were
to do standup which will probably never
happen uh that would be where I would
fall because in conversation I find
myself doing voices
whether people want to hear them or not
so I I wonder if he's that kind of guy
in conversation too strikes me as it
though he might be I'll bet that he is
and I'll bet that he's a real talker I
mean he has a he has his own podcast
called The Dana Gould hour and it's
three hours long uh first of all woof
holy [ __ ] and it's him he only puts it
out once a month so uh but it's but he
talks to it's kind of like he weaves
together different interviews that he's
recorded at different time so they kind
of jump back and forth with like some
intertial music and then he does some
monologuing and he has like a little
comedy bit that he does with John Enis
for Mr show where they're like two guys
from Boston uh chatting about whatever
um so he does a lot of yeah he's doing
like a Boston voice in that too I mean
he's from Massachusetts but he really
hams up the Boston accent for some bits
that he does um but yeah it was going
back to what you said earlier though it
is interesting that like his sensibility
of these of old timey movie culture and
uh and monster movies and stuff like
Planet of the Apes and stuff like seeps
into uh The Simpsons which he wrote on
for you know something like 10 or a
dozen years or something up until just a
few years ago and then he went out and
now he makes his own show on uh on uh
what do you call uh I don't it's not a
it's
uh IFC on IFC he makes a show on IFC
called stand against evil which is oh
I'm an idiot I've seen that show and
it's delightful yeah he's the the series
Creator in the writer for that show
basically and he and he plays
interestingly because he talks about I
actually Haven seen the show so you got
one up on me there it's it's not bad I I
like a I mean I watched it for Janet
Varney who I adore she's so much fun to
watch and John McGinley sure and it's
it's fun and Dana G plays a character on
there who's who's I mean he's just the
uh what do you call it he's the grounds
Keeper at the at the cemetery oh okay
and so he gets to play the old creepy
guy which kind of he talks about on this
album too except he talks about him at
the dump the eyed guy at the dumpy the
dump that's always the you know there's
this there's this weird thing of
specificity in comedy that is clearly
specific only to you but you you're good
enough to suck the audience in so
they're like yeah of course there yeah
there's always that guy one eye at the
dump like everybody laughs at that
specificity as though they know it and
they're like no I'm I'm I'm along for
the ride because it clearly is important
to you I I never went to the dump as a
kid I didn't have we had we had I lived
in the suburbs but we had garbage pickup
at our house
so never had to go to the dump I do
notice that he qualifies it before he
says he he says here's a thing that uh
that only men who grew up in the suburbs
will understand ahuh and he says that
and obviously he gets the whole room
anyway but uh but it's interesting that
he qualifies that and that I mean it
maybe things were different when he was
growing up versus maybe garbage pickup
to your suburban home was not a thing
until 15 years later when I was a kid I
don't
know yeah it's very funny I again and I
you wonder how much of that specificity
is like let's see what I can get people
to agree with like just as an
experiment uh how about your standup I
mean like how what's what's your ratio I
don't expect an actual math bit bit of
math what's your ratio actual personal
sh to not uh yeah you mean like uh
personal like stories about myself
versus just bits about the world uh in
general I would say it's about half and
half okay u i I find that the doing the
personal bits where you talk about your
real life or or things that are
introductory to hey this is these are
things about me that you should know
which is going to help the rest of my
standup set like I frontload a lot of
stuff about my life right at the
beginning and then that way uh it's like
people are used to who I am and then I
can take them on trip anywhere else I
guess uh and talk about just things from
my point of view that are just stuff
that I talk about like I do you know uh
you know things about things about like
jobs I've had and uh I don't know um and
then yeah I would say I would say
something like half and half it might go
back and forth between things and it uh
and also it depends like sometimes you
don't want to do uh a ton of personal
stuff and and sometimes with an audience
that is not necessarily there for comedy
like if you get on a yeah you know I've
done shows where it's like somebody asks
you hey can you come and do five minutes
on this show and it's some kind of a
dinner and there's a local politician
speaking and then uh they're going to
eat and then then a band's going to play
later and for some reason I've figured
out how to squeeze comedy into this
thing and and by the way I'm paying you
a dinner and uh these people don't know
you for the these people didn't even
know they were there was going to be
comedy on the bill they just knew about
a free meal or they're friends with this
politician or whatever or supporters and
then and then you have to go in there
and it's like surprise it's comedy and
you're trying to get like a bunch of
people with like chicken in their mouths
to pay attention to you and right uh and
in those cases it's it's less fruitful
to be like let's talk about me you
sometimes you just have to go for the
broad stuff or the or maybe even like
more pop cultur stuff where you can try
and find common ground with people in a
really short period of time there's not
a lot of other art forms I don't think
where you have to necessarily for time
or for audience uh cut down go from like
lengthy art piece to pop art piece like
you can do it in other art forms like
music but it's not that often stand Up's
one of those that's so adaptable uh that
you just have to be like oh no this this
entire piece of this thing that I might
consider my art I have to excise for the
sake of these weirdos in this audience
yeah it's true you really do it's and
when
I uh you know considering your the
audience you're in and especially in the
place where I am like I've been doing
comedy for six years now uh doing stand
up for six years I've been hosting
comedy shows for five years you know
I've been on the radio for three years
whatever uh but you know at a we're
still at a point and I'm still in sort
of a region where uh where you're going
where where it's not like you have these
big sets of fans or a huge audience
who's coming out to see just you so you
have to reintroduce yourself to people
almost every time you go on and yeah so
you're never a known quantity like I
assume that Danny G is doing this show
uh this his first comedy record he's
doing it like friends of his are in the
audience or people know him around town
he's in La he at this point he's
probably already been he has been on TV
doing stuff uh you know he's written for
TV he's been in sketch comedy stuff
whatever and so he's you know he's a
he's sort of a known person and people
kind of know what to expect when they're
going to see him and that's not the case
when people come to see me on a show for
the most part for the most part I mean
it's stuff that I do every week people
understand that people listen to the
radio show understand that but when I go
out there and do some standup gig that
somebody booked me on then you have to
you have to decide you know oh this
thing that I love this sort of you know
artier piece like you're saying uh that
has like some sort of a message that I'm
trying to put out there like about me or
about the world or about something that
I think that about a deeply held
personal belief or whatever sometimes
that stuff falls to the Wayside just for
the sake of survival in a semih hostile
environment you know right do you think
most people okay so I don't know the
sales numbers on an album like this but
let's assume they were good enough for
him to keep going as a person and as a
as a comedian and make another album uh
do you think the people who are familiar
with him
feel familiar with him or feel familiar
with this is a guy who has made me laugh
before do you think there is actually as
much as we give uh credit to this idea
that hey they they should know something
about me they should be comfortable with
me familiar with me as you say you've
got to do Exposition and which I imagine
is also funny Exposition which is a
challenge right but then you've got
somebody like him who's like I've seen
you a bunch you've never made me cringe
or you have made me laugh every time
therefore I'm familiar with that rather
than I'm familiar with you even
subconsciously from your material like I
wonder what the majority of people knew
him from uh by the time you know maybe
his next album comes out like do you
have any perspective on that because I'm
I'm just curious because do you really
need to make people know who you are and
give a [ __ ] who you are or is it a
matter of I've seen you be funny before
that's enough for me uh I think I think
it's probably more the latter uh I I I
don't I I I think that if I don't think
people have to be like oh I haven't seen
Dana Gold's standup in particular
therefore I'm not sure I want to go see
him do standup you know what you do you
find and I and this is what happens like
uh the The Comedy Club Circuit even the
the best rooms or whatever they're uh
they're bringing around people who
mostly people who are known from TV in
some way now now some of those people
started out as professional standups and
then got on TV like uh Danny Gould uh or
some and then some of those people were
TV people in in comedy on television in
some way but were never stand-ups and
had to learn it because they had the
opportunity to go on the road because
you can sell tickets for somebody that
people are familiar with on TV or or who
have been in the movies or something
like that like you know like steo from
Jackass he was never a up but he
literally does Comedy Club stand
upes
tours and you know much to the sugarin
of of many Comics who wish that you know
that that it was you know for the art of
it or whatever but yeah people go see
steo they don't care they don't care if
they've seen him tell jokes
before yeah that's a good point that's
the weirdest [ __ ] that I've ever heard
now like I've seen people say hey look
Jake the Snake Roberts is at a club and
but like it's clear that oh he's telling
stories from his wrestling days he's
necessarily doing standup I guess but he
is getting booked in standup clubs which
is [ __ ] weird right yeah it's the
same kind of it's it's a it's similar
although I'd rather see uh Jake The
Snake or uh whatever mankind or whatever
I'd rather see I'd rather see them than
I than than steo who yes who wasn't I
mean the thing about wrestlers is
wrestlers are professional talkers as
much as they are athletes so you know
like and he's a guy who's like I've been
hitting the balls a bunch hi that's like
what else like else they've done
presentational things into microphones
whereas steo was a just a maniac you
know lighting fireworks out of his butt
uh you know snorting Wasabi or whatever
but he wasn't they weren't they they
never had to learn to talk and get
laughs or anything the laughs are the
it's completely physical comedy so like
and then steo I guess when he I haven't
seen this but he's been to my town many
times I have not attended I apologize
if you're out there listening but but uh
but I understand that he does a couple
of like stunts that you can do inside of
a the because he's also like a Prof he's
also a clown he went to the cloud
college that I did not know he's yeah
he's a real de clown that steo uh he
went to the ringland brothers clown
college and so I guess he's got he's got
physical stuff that he can do on stage
but then but then I guess the rest of it
is one time we were on the set of
Jackass and we did blah blah blah
or whatever I you
know yeah see that's weird to me it's
like uh it's like it's oh hey it's the
30s and we got this circus geek who's
out of work he he used to eat the heads
off of chickens uh he wants to perform
now uh you got any you know bits you can
write for this guy right and really I
mean you'd have to all his bits Would S
surround uh eating the heads off of
chickens that would be everything you'd
have most of the bits
yeah you ever seen one of these chickens
chickens am I right you see him they're
out in the
yard too much uh they say they can run
around with their heads cut off uh I had
to test that theory once uh but I didn't
have an axe around so I bit its head off
I bit it head off you know yep that's
and then that's that's all it is I
almost delivered that Norm McDonald
style and I apologize I'm stealing that
from my buddy Allen who does a very good
fake nor McDonald joke his I love nor
McDonald so much oh it's it's hard not
to like nor McDonald he's still good and
I don't get it yeah uh there are a lot
of guys in his generation who have aged
out already because he's because he's
also kind of a dinosaur in his beliefs
or whatever well Dana Gould has remained
a p a questioning a seeking person who
sure uh who does still like to push it
but has figured out but but also wants
to do well in the room and has retired I
mean I'm sure he retired these bits
anyway because he wrote new material and
started he actually took a huge break
from standup working on The Simpsons and
having a family and stuff and then came
back to it like the last five six seven
years and uh and put out like two or
three more albums which are also very
good um which are very good and very and
much more modern you you can see you can
see the difference it's not a situation
where it's like you know like Tim Allen
is out here you know uh The Last Man
Standing or
whatever uh Danny gold has has remained
a person who whose thoughts have evolved
on a lot of these issues I've heard him
talk about how he would not like for
example there is a there's the huge use
of the RW in this uh in this album uh
and you can tell that like that's the
culture that he comes from yeah uh where
you just say that nobody cares and who
cares it and he realized at some point
that that was hurtful I listened to him
he was on an episode of the of the
Jordan Jesse go podcast in like maybe
2009 2010 something like that like way
back when they were new and that's like
a long time ago now and he talked to
that
about how about how he realized that
that word was hurting people and people
enough people talked to him and then he
and then he stopped doing it like he
won't do like people would request that
bit and he would he wouldn't do it
anymore well and I that's I mean that's
I would say the minimum you could ask
most people don't meet that minimum but
I'm glad that he does like I I he's one
of and I kind of assumed when you and I
got to talking about this that I would
that that would he just strikes me as
that kind of guy where he would be like
uh well maybe because especially listen
to the number of things in this album
that are trying to portray him he's
trying to portray himself as an
open-minded dude sure he is yes so and I
mean you either do that because you're
actually a monster or because you're
trying to point out hey I'm on the side
of probably several people in this room
I don't want you to think I I I have any
hate in my heart uh you know and so and
I don't think the bits are hateful as
much as they are ignorant ignorant of
the idea that there is somebody like
because I think I think the old Theory
with the RW in particular which I'm not
even going to say we know the one the
the ableist
slur uh you know I I think that it used
to be like well where's the victim of
this crime because that person's there's
none of those people in this room or
something like that and and maybe and
maybe because of their uh because of uh
of their disability they might not
understand that you're making fun of
them anyway blah blah blah that kind of
stuff which is horrible like like that's
not like that's the old way of thinking
about things which is a bad way to think
about things which I completely reject I
just want to go on the record and say
that I do think that Dana G is probably
one of those people who just didn't
realize and because of the culture that
he comes from like and nobody told him
or who knows what he had thought it all
the way through that that guess what
there's also people who are who have
friends and who have family members who
are uh who have are disabled and then
also that uh just general people out in
the world think that it's not
nice to to to punch down and and uh and
I think at some point he probably
figured it out and now he doesn't he
doesn't do any stuff like that so what's
what's interesting is he leans into the
word he starts out doing a bit where
that the word is almost used clinically
uh because he's talking about somebody
do I can't remember what the bit is oh
that D he's saying that his his dad
would point out he's like every town has
a town uh person who is disabled let's
say and which is which sounds which also
is a weird old he comes from a small
town so maybe yes yeah so and then his
dad when they were driving would point
out to his mom oh there's your boyfriend
pointing to that person which is a
horrible thing and he was pointing out
as his dad being shitty yes yeah so so
he's on the side of not making fun of
that guy in that way but then he goes on
to and then he uses a and then he uses a
uh a a voice yes he does oh boy and
that's and that's really the bit that's
that's the bit that he refuses to do
ever
now for sure is that like because he and
he said people used to ask for it and he
where it was the the bit where he's
where he's saying that um that wouldn't
it be terrible or like it's like a if an
intolerant person
suddenly uh became mentally disabled
or uh you know then uh and then they
were upset about it and then he acts it
out yeah and it's isn't it what if you
woke up and it was like your Just
Desserts order but then but the the pr
the the the the supposition of that bit
is that the the the premise is oh
wouldn't it be horrible to be a disabled
person yes like a fate worse than death
basically right and uh that's not cool
no no and it's weird because the the
perfect irony there is like hey I'm
trying to be open-minded here right and
at the same time the only way I can
display it is through this other set of
ignorant suppositions that I've just got
built into my brain yeah and I you know
I do respect people working past it um
you know and I cuz I try so hard like
not to be well I don't try not to be a
out of hand or whatever uh I am a bough
in a lot of yeah it really is it really
is uh espe you know I mean I've given a
little more uh you know leeway to people
who are not Bill Cosby and Woody Allen
you know what I'm saying like they
unfortunately have set this standard of
low as people where it's like okay well
your material is not great but you
you're not that guy so I'll give you a
chance to evolve and again it sounds
like Dana g g has evolved like pretty
pretty properly and that's the thing
like and and it's and the and the reason
I picked this album is because it was
part of my sort of my formative time
thinking about standup comedy and I I
knew this guy from the 80s and 90s like
like like doing doing clean material on
TV I mean none of this stuff would have
ever made it on TV that we're talking uh
even at the time I I don't think I don't
think anybody was was running around
with with the with the RW on TV even
right and uh and I think that uh and
then there's just so much of it that is
very inventive and and creative and
has uh and just the kind of the fantasy
world that he's building or the sort of
uh the the attention to detail like the
uh like the answering machine bit uhuh
which is where where he's where where
he's analyzing a a message on an an
answering for those of you who are too
young an answering
machine was like a box that had
voicemail in it that was attached to
your phone in your own home and it was
recorded on a small cassette tape
uh you know there's a sorry go ahead no
uh but but yeah but he does this bit
where he's where he's uh trying to where
he gets a a voicemail from an
ex-girlfriend and it's very quick and
vague and then he starts analyzing it
and he does sound effects he's like
Winslow he's doing he's doing sound
effects with his mouth only that are of
him playing the tape back and rewinding
the tape the sound of the tape rewinding
the sound of the button being pushed
again uh and he's he's got a
masterful uh faculty with with that kind
of stuff I kind of respect that in terms
of like I again here's where I become a
grandpa I wish a lot of uh artists and
things that that became famous had maybe
a little bit more of a background in
things other than whatever they become
famous for you know like there used to
be this cool thing where you could be a
triple threat or at the very least Jim
Neighbors who play this fraking idiot
hick could also sing like an angel uh
where it's just like it's always fun to
be surprised by people and you know I
kind of respect like any I'm okay with a
com comedian who can also play guitar
doesn't bother me I'm also like super
cool if you can do a good sound effect
like if you could do it well why not do
it cuz it does lend something to it I
think so and I and I think that that's
imp I I feel like people would be
impressed today I think that there's
things have swung and and maybe they're
maybe they're starting to swing again
and we're starting to get more silly
which I hope uh is true and I and I have
felt and honestly I feel like it's held
me back in a certain way because I would
like to be more like Dana Gould I would
like to be doing more crazy act outs or
weird sound effects or sing or or any of
the any of the things that that he's
doing um that are more performative and
less just talking and I think that there
there was a turn maybe in the last
starting maybe 10 years ago or something
where the the turn was away from uh away
from uh Dan
Cook and the like and it was a turn
toward uh you know uh that that other
monster Louis CK um and and people in
the premium was put on a person
speaking uh sort of seamlessly
conversationally sounding only about
their actual life and sort of uh this
sort of verit thing uh where where where
the premium was on 100% authenticity and
honesty and I am exactly the person that
you see on stage offstage and that's
what we've all been talking about for
the last 10 years and I think that there
is and that and that back in the late
80s early 90s things had gotten a little
crazy with
everybody uh with everybody doing this
sort of canned hacky stuff and the
whatever oversaturation and airplane
food and everything that everybody
complains about that time and then there
was a swing for the alternative stuff in
the 90s and the alternative stuff was a
swing towards absurdism
right uh and I and I feel like what I
feel like we could really at this point
I think I'm I'm sick of everybody to a
certain extent uh only doing this stuff
that that
is uh that is this is my life and it's
gritty and it's dark and there's a place
for all of that stuff but I'm kind of
over it at this point and I've heard
I've been listening to it and I've been
hearing it in rooms and everybody wants
to do it still and I'm kind of uh I'm
kind of looking for some for some silly
stuff or some uh short jokes I mean like
whatever happened to like Steven right
uh things of that nature and what
happened to uh what happened or like uh
I mean another big influence on me at
the same time that this Dana G album
came out was that uh maybe in
2000ish was that Eddie isard Dressed to
Kill special oh God damn it that's such
a good [ __ ] special it's one of the
best like if that was an album on vinyl
I might have picked that one just
because it' be so much fun to talk about
like I could it's it it's so quotable
like you can my sister and I still talk
back and forth uh in that language of it
it's you know I think it's fun I think
it's funny he's a mass murdering
[ __ ] yeah yeah uh in a ditch coved
petrol on
fire uh yeah that's that's also one that
I shared with my sister as well uh it's
a that's a God damn it if there's any
way we can ever swing talking about
Eddie as on the podcast uh I'll have you
on because I could do that forever oh
yeah oh please I would love to and yeah
and that I mean that special and we were
watching Mr show which was which was
super weird and absurd and the sketches
didn't make much logical sense a lot of
the time or like here's a weird exercise
and we're just going to have this guy
knock over these Thimbles again and
again and again for no reason you know
yeah right yeah what's what's your
position on and you be as honest as you
like on Carrot Top ah Carrot Top
I I think that Carrot Top has been doing
his Carrot Top thing and that he you
know and they used to make fun of Carrot
Top on Mr
Show they did they called they had a
character on Carrot Top on Mr show
called blueberry head it was a it was an
extremely not disguised um stupid God
reference yeah blueberry head my
God holy [ __ ] uh so I think I was
trained to hate Carrot Top and I was
trained to hate prop comedy in that age
and that there was like it wasn't cool
and there was something about the 90s
and the alternative boom there was
something about jinnie Garo and uh and
David Cross and and Danny gold and these
people that uh where it wasn't it wasn't
cool to have props it it wasn't it
wasn't cool to be overly it was like it
was like they could do their little
absurdism and their and their
you know they they're whatever and they
I don't care stuff but I think that like
the the appearance of somebody trying
that hard and putting on an old timey
show basically because K toop is putting
on like an old timey Vaudeville act or
something basically it's like that's
that's the tradition of it um I haven't
seen so much katop material recently
that I couldn't I mean like I haven't
been to vas and seen his the show that
he's installed doing but I'll I'll I'll
bet you you go see that show and laugh
that's all I've heard and everybody says
he's a very nice dude uh so yeah it's
really weird to me cuz I I when I was a
kid I love the [ __ ] out of them and then
I also fell for the cynicism of the 90s
where I'm like you I shouldn't like you
and then I hear people like no I went
and saw katop and he was fine he was
funny he made me laugh he's also a very
nice guy and it's like well I have to
reconsider now because you know I just
dismissed him out of hand and then
forgot how much I loved him as a kid now
it might be super cheesy it's not going
to be deep we're not we're not getting
any levels here I don't think but no
it's it's it's it's visual puns mhm
right I mean and and it like he I
remember hearing him uh interviewed on
like WTF and he talked about how his
like you know he just went to an open
mic and he he had brought like a like a
road sign that he had found and then he
altered it in some way to make a joke
out of it and that all of his other
jokes bound but people like the road
sign and then like the the club manager
the booker whoever said you should come
back but you should do more of that
stuff and then he built his act that way
wow [ __ ] it's crazy like how how you
hear these stories from a certain period
where like the you know the the club
manager or some kind of an agent or
something you know what no no no you
know what you are you're you're the guy
with the flared pants that's that's your
thing you're flared pants guy that's you
do that for the rest of your career yeah
hello Sinbad
um really if if you could if you could
look kind of like a genie so that people
will remember you so people will make up
a genie movie in their head you don't
actually start in that would be perfect
um oh my God it never occurred to me it
was the pants that that made people
think that oh it's the P it's the P it's
it's his clothes he all you do you put
the you put the racist turban on his
head and he's a gen he's a he's he's
he's basically Robin Williams and
Aladdin um so but what I was gonna Oh
shoot what was I gonna say I'm sorry it
doesn't
matter it's just
words can I tell you speak of words my
favorite line on this it's so dumb it's
so dumb but him talking about and again
it it also comes from I would say
something that maybe he has a little
more perspective on but he's talking
about uh not doing well financially uh
but he does talk about living above a
sex shop and basically subsisting off of
day old chocolate [ __ ] and that was
really funny yeah D old chocolate [ __ ]
is a is a great phrase and then he's
like then he talks about having to eat
them and he's
like you can just you can just see you
know the act out of it and uh
in your head from the from the noises
he's kind of making in protest you know
because it's like this should be food
you know um I enjoyed that yeah he was a
he was one of those he he
moved to uh San Francisco and and built
up his act there before eventually
moving to La for I think TV
jobs that's crazy and what's interesting
to me is uh I don't know if I'll ever
get him on the show uh but if I do I I
realize the first thing I ever saw him
in or noticed who he was uh he plays a
sandwich delivery guy in uh my fellow
Americans starring Jack Lemon and James
Garner I've seen that movie but I don't
remember that at all yeah he's just
delivering a sandwich it's like and then
he gets arrested uh that's it he's got
like two lines in the whole thing
they're are they both former presidents
in that movie both former presidents and
they're both on the run I still love it
I it's just to this day it's great but
can I tell you something weird guy who
directed that also directed The Get
Smart movie with Steve Carell and he
literally steals one of his own jokes
from from my fellow Americans and puts
it in the Get Smart movie I'm talking
beat for beat steals his own physical
well if you're I mean if you're G to
here's the thing nobody saw my fellow
American so it's so it's kind of like
well you know like like I didn't get I
didn't I I didn't squeeze this one for
all it was worth yet but it's it's it's
got prew
westwing in the White House Bradley
Whitford uh Bradley looks like a guy who
works in the white it's true he's in I'm
going to guess his only scene ever with
Wilford Brimley uh they both have
reversed initials I just realized that
uh Wilford Brimley tortures Bradley
Whitford in a movie I like how that's
super notable in my brain it is I can't
I was like why am I connecting them in
my oh wbw there we go that makes sense
uh of course that's why they that's why
they cast them of course it is that's
how all casting in movies bradfield's in
the in the casting office with other
bws we just need a we need the right W
to be opposite
WB I oh man honestly it's a movie I
don't I won't recommend people revisit
it because it's probably just my
Nostalgia flavoring it but I love it and
I still it still makes me laugh I saw it
when it came out that's a mid 90s movie
mid to late 90s yep so there you go
there's there's Dan G trying to make it
he's one of those guys who who did pilot
season like X number of years in a row
and none of the shows it shot a bunch of
pilots and none of them ever went to
series he thought he was going to be a
he thought it was going to be a
household name and it never quite
happened uh kind of like what happened
with Dave Chappelle except Dave
Chappelle went on to have a Smash It SE
sketch show yeah I can't imagine Dave
Chappelle on a on a sitcom I mean I
guess I can a little bit but I he broke
such ground with sketch comedy that it's
like it's okay at least in my head it's
fine yeah yeah he did like he did I
think he did Delle literally did six
years of Pilots that didn't go holy [ __ ]
and he made a ton of money because uh
because they pay you to make those
Pilots mhm yeah you know you go the
right one Mak six figures for one
episode you know yeah exactly and then
and then they they don't pick it up he
was uh at a and I and I guess he quit
eventually he was like I can't do this
anymore and then he went out went off
and did his own thing I guess eventually
uh you know or I think Neil Neil Brennon
was was a big factor in that oh okay
was his co-producer on uh on Chapelle
show oh yes that's right I see I keep
forgetting that and the guy and I think
the guy who like got Chappelle to like
show up for work and
like all the Stu you know because
Chappelle's like sort of famously always
late and and you know only and I've
heard Neil Brenan say Dave only cared
when there was an audience in the seats
like in like the live audience for the
sketch show so they were he said if
there were people and if there were more
people he was more on and if there were
less people or if they were further away
he didn't care as much and he didn't try
as hard that's so funny to me he could
he couldn't act for the cameras he had
act for the audience that's really
[ __ ] funny um so here's the thing I
want to make sure that you recommend
well you don't have to recommend this
album but if you are going to recommend
fun house 1998 Dana Gould uh I will say
our friends at standup records are the
people who released the vinyl version
and that's what I have right here um
what's uh what's a good reason to listen
to this album if you haven't heard it
before a good reason to listen to this
album is that it is a document of a
extremely specific time in standup where
uh much like the alternative music boom
of the early 90s like when suddenly
Nirvana's the most popular man in the
world uh the most popular kind of Comedy
for a brief moment became the comedy of
the weirdos with the very specific and
uh and nerdy references but also it had
an edge to it now uh so they were like
cool uh they were they were cool and
interesting and specific now you're
there's going to be tracks on here that
you're going to absolutely hate and as
soon as you hear one of those you can
just skip right ahead don't feel like
you missed anything just skip right
ahead just take the uh uh just pull the
needle up and move it to the next uh
move it to the next Groove you'll be
fine um and uh but but besides those I
think that there are tracks on here that
are just as good as anything else ever
and to hear the and to hear the guy
performing his heart out and uh and uh
and doing these uh voices and stuff but
he's doing it in a context where it
doesn't feel like you're trained to to
think it should be like that it's hacky
or that it's Michael Winslow or that
it's uh or that it's like U you know how
Kevin poock will do Impressions or
something like that it's not like that
at
all uh I think that there's a there's a
cool to it and I think that is it is uh
it is of its time in a way that's that's
very interesting and I would be really
interested to see if comedy's going to
sort of swing back around in this
direction again you know and I uh I I
hadn't thought of it in in the uh terms
you've been speaking of it you know just
the idea just simply doing voices or
doing a sound or like you say being just
being more performative I can't disagree
with that I think I think I like the
idea of that happen happening a bit more
I would love to see that is it something
that you would be comfortable like
actually like what would it take for you
to break out of any shell that might be
there to actually do that thing I think
actually you know listening to this over
this past week like over and over again
uh in preparation for this show has
really made me think a lot about what
I'm doing and how I have bits where
there's I mean I have a specific bit
where I'm uh which is from my real life
where I'm laugh by the cops uh and they
think I robbed a bank but I didn't rob
the bank and then something really
embarrassing happens um God like I
didn't I didn't commit the crime but it
would have been more embarrassing if
they just arrested me for a crime than I
committed or less embarrassing rather um
like if I if I had just robbed a bank
and they arrested me for it they would
be less embarrassing for what they
discovered uh when they searched me but
um but the uh but I but I have a whole
thing where I'm a bit where I'm talking
to the police officer and he's like sort
of interrogating me and uh and I would
like for that bit to be more and it
works fine you know I get my laughs but
but I would like it to feel more like
I'm really having a conversation with
another person and I think I would
actually like to make that cop a
character that I'm doing and to make
myself more of a character I think I
would like to to do more actess and I've
done I've done improv too where you're
encouraged to do all that stuff stuff
and that definitely helped me uh be more
loose on the stage and more
improvisational which I very much am I
have my bits and then I go in and out of
them and talk to the crowd uh I mean I'm
not Jimmy parto or anything but I but
that's what I aspire to uh but I but I
definitely would like to I would like to
act stuff out I would like to try and do
more stuff I mean I would like if
there's if something calls for an
impression I would like to I would like
to at least give it a shot you know what
I mean yeah you know what's interesting
too is I feel like there's this there's
this self-awareness and
self-consciousness that comes with doing
impressions where it changes the timing
of a bit where if you're just talking
and saying for instance well then the
cop said well the cop walks up to me and
if you're just doing your voice you
don't have to do any sort of uh physical
separation necessarily but there is this
temptation when you're doing a character
to give it some breadth so that there's
just distance between your voice and the
other voice which you know so it's
interesting because it would Pro I would
guess it would it's going to change the
timing of a bit if you do a voice also
really want to know what it does to the
bit and if it gives you extra confidence
if it changes your perception of your
own stuff that's
interesting I think uh I think it's
going to be an experiment now I also I
mean I've been teaching standup classes
for the past uh for the past few months
as well there's an improv theater that
asked me to do it uh so I'm acquainted
with them awesome and it's been uh it's
been really interesting I mean like a
lot of comics say uh you had you
actually actually uh I was very inspired
by your podcast because I was asked to
do this and I was a little reticent
because so many comedians are patently
against the idea of standup classes
course yeah uh and because of well
there's a lot of bitterness and jealousy
having to do with anything where anybody
makes any money ever um but the idea
that you're ripping people off because
you can't teach people to be funny yeah
as if that's what having a class is
designed to do MH uh the class the idea
of a standup class is like hey why don't
you get used to all of the apparatus of
standup and maybe get in a room where
you're forced to write some jokes and
talk to other people and sort of
Workshop things and you know throw a
little bit of theory in there whatever
and then maybe that'll make you better
prepared to have to go uh into a bar
with zero people paying attention where
you have to get up on stage in front of
strangers for the first time like that's
the and you had Jimmy Paro on here and
he talked about that very same thing
which is also mentioned never not funny
a couple of times and every time I hear
it it reminds me that I don't have to I
don't have to listen to other you
shouldn't listen to other Comics anyway
because they're [ __ ]
um you know I'm also even the ones I
even the ones I love and my friends you
know I I and I won't go off on this
today because I feel like it's an essay
worth of stuff but I'm not a big fan of
uh people believing in in and a lot of
people that I admire do uh believing in
being naturally funny I don't believe
that I also don't believe in talent I
just don't believe it I'm I'm actually
in your exact same camp I think that
that's [ __ ] and I think that that
well honestly if you start telling
people you're either funny or you're not
then you're just telling a whole bunch
of people that they should never even
try exactly and you're and and we're
missing out on people who could be some
of the uh great and amazing performers
and it's like just like anything it's
like uh if you said to somebody uh
you're either a banker or you're
not and if you don't know how to be a
banker right now then you never
will good God that's the perfect way to
put it yeah exactly and it's like well
gez I don't know anything I mean oh I
don't even know
I I don't even know what FDIC stands for
I guess I can't be a banker [ __ ] yeah
I guess well and there's certainly no
way to learn yeah that's like well the
things we use the word talent to to uh
just brush off any skill we've had and
that's like wait hold on I've tried for
years to do this I think I'm okay at
this I've I've gotten here because of my
own effort not cuz I was born with this
like what the hell like it's just anyway
like I say I could go on for people well
people talk people say things that are
the Polar Opposites of each other
practically in the same breath they say
they say oh you're either you're funny
or you're not and then they also say it
takes 10 years to get good at right
right so I mean which is it honestly and
it's like so the yeah the idea that that
you can't be taught or that you or that
you can't be funny like you know people
learn to do things people learn to sing
people learn to dance why can't people
learn to tell jokes it's not it's and
also the idea that jokes are honestly
it's not as mystical as people think it
is it's like a joke has a setup and a
punchline and if you can remember that
um and think about it in those terms
that hey here's some context and then
here's a thing that you expect and then
the thing that you expect doesn't happen
and instead I've put a little twist in
here and done something different uh
that's literally what comedy is yeah
yeah people people need to calm the [ __ ]
down and like you say I love the idea
you know that there are people out there
who might be uh you know have this
undiscovered talent and it's okay
[ __ ] try it's okay to try it's
[ __ ] okay to try I was it's
definitely okay to try and and guess
what that's why there's open mics no one
can stop you no if you're out there and
you're thinking about and I just to say
if you're out there and you're listening
to this show because you love comedy and
you've thought oh I could never do
standup I can never be funny like those
people are funny and it's like yeah
neither could they 10 years ago or 20
years ago uh they had to get up there
and be in front of people and fail and
fail and fail and fail and fail uh and
you know and and and it took they just
had to overcome it and it's the same
thing with uh you know I heard Chris
Hardwick say once that you should do
stand up a hundred times before you even
decided if you're if you should continue
to do standup if you're any good or not
yeah um and so then I did I did stand up
100 times in my first year holy [ __ ] and
uh well and after you do that you're
like well I'm in it now of course of
course yeah uh so it was a good goal and
you only have to do it twice a week uh
and luckily uh where I am in Rochester
we have a really good comedy scene we
have a lot of open mics we have a lot of
opportunities to get up and a lot of
people putting on small shows that you
can get on and then we have a club and
and then there's the whole region we
have a lot of cities nearby that you can
do stuff around into so it's it's worked
out really well for me but there's no
reason why if if you think you can do it
don't let anybody tell you that you're
not funny go up there and you know prove
it absolutely absolutely that's perfect
this this is a good way to end it but
let's also make sure uh tell people
where they can find you and your podcast
and your show etc etc etc absolutely so
uh let's see here so I'm what you been
telling you I'm on Twitter at Woody
battalia that is w o d y b a TT a g l i
a you got the silent G there like in
lasagna uh let's see here I am uh my
radio show is called Almost Tuesday that
is a comedy variety show you'll be
surprised at how many notable guests we
get to call into to us here in Rochester
New York and also we have an amazing
music scene here we have bands play
every week in the studio uh which is a a
whole different kind of undertaking and
that's uh every Monday night from 9:00
to 11: uh eastern time that's
wm.org
and my podcast is my dinner with or my
minute with Andre which is about uh My
Dinner with Andre uh in unnecessary
detail uh we we go through it a a minute
at a time and then there's uh some bonus
episodes with uh stuff like me meeting
Wallace sha in real life and uh stuff
like that even if you don't know what
this movie is I mean you'll know by
listening to the you wouldn't even have
to watch the movie honestly for the
amount that we talk about it and you'll
be able to you'll be able to hear uh
you'll be able to hear Jason in a in a
couple of weeks or whatever depending on
when this comes out when by the time
this comes out out for a while I will
just say that I'll just warn you I'm so
behind I'm I I think I'm two months
behind on episodes now because of okay
how crazy went so go back uh you can go
back right now and listen to Jason on my
minute with Andre and you can get that
anywhere you get Podcast iTunes Google
Play wherever wherever the hell Spotify
listen for all the times he had to edit
out me shoehorning in my wall of Sean
impression um oh no no no that's all in
no oh no I've kept all that in Jason oh
no the magic I just kept out I just kept
out all the uh all the the the [ __ ]
talking about other famous
podcasts thank God I didn't even
remember we did that I'm glad you did
that um don't worry I got I got I got
both of our backs as as if anybody's
going to listen but still but still to
be polite hey not everything's for
everybody I think that's the important
thing to remember exactly uh I never
tell anybody this but I'm on Twitter at
jcom jkm I've been more active on
Instagram at Jason clom which is really
what I should have been on Twitter but
if you go to Twitter Instagram too
you'll mostly see pictures of uh of
people playing music on my radio show
which will remind you to listen to the
radio show which looked pretty cool uh
and also you know performance stuff
around town here so if you want to look
at Comedians and look at
uh look at to bands playing in a radio
Studio then uh then I'm Woody battalia
also on Instagram awesome uh and I think
the only other thing to say is go to
bit.ly comedy albums that'll take you to
celery sound records my sketch comedy
record label uh we by this I I'm not
going to say it in here because I don't
know if we'll have announced it but by
the time this comes out we may have
released re-released this 1961 standup
comedy album that is really fun is out
of print and now uh we are the ones
redistributing it and we might actually
be about to redistribute actually
distribute some stuff that nobody has
ever heard from another uh kind of
legendary or at least obscure and
influential comic uh that's all I can
say just go to bit. l/ comedy albums and
there there should be some stuff there
and later this year my third comedy
album with my sketch group will be out
as well um and that should be done with
with some fun guest appearances by
people you've heard on this podcast
before uh that's about now I'm excited
so Woody thank you so much for doing the
show Jason it has been my h i mean I
I've heard this show for uh for a couple
of years now and I'm uh I'm really so
glad to have uh been able to talk to you
about uh about a record that uh that was
really influential on my life in a weird
way and not because of all the horrible
stuff in it I just want to reiterate
well you're welcome back anytime and I
uh I'm glad that it's in any way
affected your life uh even if it's just
I heard it in my ears a bunch and that's
cool that that makes me happy uh well
thank you guys for listening and as
always have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen address.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
f-star rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook.com/ comdy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedyon vinyl.com a
major portion of comedy on vinyl has
been underwritten by standup records
please visit standup records.com for all
your comedy needs and tune in to the new
standup channel available on the Roku
where you can also find select episodes
of this podcast
[Music]