hey everybody Jason clom here uh this is
a very special episode of comedy on
vinyl uh this week we find out that
Jeremy uh is pregnant um also it is our
live tribute to Phil Hartman uh we
recorded it live at The Zephyr theater
in Hollywood and I want to very quickly
thank Margie Mintz for setting that up
for us um and uh this week's uh panel is
me Jeremy gusin Mike prer and our very
special guest guest Vicky Lewis um we
sat down we talked about Phil Hartman
and uh you know what we all got to just
speak about how much we loved him uh we
had a really wonderful audience and uh
Vicky was kind enough to join us for
that hour and a half and be very candid
with us we also spoke to Paul Hartman
Phil's brother on the phone who was
wonderful and Angel Rosenthal who runs
the Phil Hartman for the Walk of Fame
campaign on Facebook please join that uh
we're putting a link up on our page as
we speak uh as I speak after I speak
shortly so please enjoy this week's
episode of comedy on vinyl episode 10
the live tribute to Phil Hartman are you
too cold I don't feel well I feel like
a you know is it the Chill from the
audience I'm going to start a
garbage this was a really bad idea this
is a coat it's good it'll look good for
the podcast that's very
true hi everybody thank you for coming
to comedy on vinyl live how is everybody
y
you're not going to be able to hear us
any louder than we're speaking cuz it's
not necessary but they can hear us there
as everybody knows we're here to talk
about Poco and um their this is their
best album Legend uh Jeremy do you want
to tell me why this inspired you so much
just to be a comedian uh well and an
actor and a comedic actor I looked at it
and
thought tonight I'm going to break away
just you wait and see see I can't follow
okay you can't that's fine but Phil
Hartman designed the cover of this album
that's the only uh only vinyl I could
really relate to Phil Hartman so
uh and's the
segue so this is a tribute to Phil
Hartman
y thank
you and with me as usual Mike prer hi
Jeremy gusin hell guy and the lovely
Vicky Lewis y
was that um I guess I'm J and I work
together on a sh so we know each other
also ah we work and I work together so
I've never met you
before or today I like your work you're
very very pretty and nice you do some
things that are a little edgy and it
makes me uncomfortable but that's why I
like
you ah drink water um so water okay
thank you I thought you'd spiked it um
so I don't know let's we can just go
around the table and just talk about
Phil Hartman but let's start with Vicky
even though it's not really going around
the table because um because it's like a
bad game of musical chair yeah I love it
I mean obviously you worked with him for
a long time but what was your awareness
of him before news radio and what did
you think of him and then how did
meeting him totally change that okay
that's a lot and you know I as I was
coming here I was trying to remember you
know all the sort of pertinent things
that that happened in my life you know
parallel with Phil and you know I have
to say um it was my first series I came
I was a New Yorker so I always was on
the stage and I I always was doing
theater and I theater's like television
but you know in front of people right
away you know I didn't real we had to
explain oh I'm just that's for everybody
out there who might not
understand on the Broadway I was and
that's and that's theater re e sing like
when you run out of talking you sing
that's why they make a music
right exactly but so I actually I'm
talking about myself already way too
much not about Phil um I sang for a
musical that Jim Brooks was uh producing
called I'll do anything and um it took
me out to LA and I got news radio while
I was out here and I had never done a
sitcom and I remember um we were
shooting the end of the pilot and Phil
and I were standing across from one
another and at the elevator of the set
and we were waiting for them to set the
lights and waiting for the brilliant
writers that we had to rewrite some
stuff and I looked over and I realized I
I'll never forget it it's so corny but I
thought I actually made it like I I'm
standing here with Phil Hartman and
something kind of Genius is happening
and you could feel it on that set you
could just feel it that's amazing you
know I mean so and I mean I could tell
you more and you can ask me things but I
mean that moment is always you know
illuminated in my head like a like a
Christmas tree ornament because it meant
so much to me and my life changed in
that very moment that night I speaking
as a fan you can feel that because there
are some projects that you watch um
where you can just feel how much people
are having fun sometimes they're not
necessarily professionals luckily they
had a group of people together that knew
how to make comedy well the thing about
the thing about news radio which is I
find as the years have progressed am I
you can shut me off or like
please keep talking okay so I mean the
thing the thing for me with news radio
that I realized um with time it's been
what 15 years yeah um or so is that we
were the writers and the actors all very
somewhat broken
people um and I say broken in a good way
um we were eccentric we were uh you know
uh left of center we were not you know
we didn't really fit in with mainstream
television and we really didn't fit in
with the world and it's interesting that
Paul Sims the Creator handpicked each
one of us um and we became this very
dysfunctional kind of I mean I consider
them all family but when you asked me
about Phil of all the people Phil to me
was the most grounded and was the most
professional and when I came in he took
me under his wing said this doesn't last
yeah you know it doesn't last and save
your money don't buy Six sports cars and
you know I got to write this down right
cuz your head I know Jeremy we talk
about your new pirate in a minute but I
don't want you to spend all your money
next week but um but it was an
interesting Dynamic I'm did he literally
give like that kind of advice and stuff
he gave it to me that's amazing it was
amazing it was so amazing and he would
sit with me and show me how to trust to
learn stocks and to invest my money and
it was interesting Dynamic to watch
because some people in the cast had
three cars and big houses and it got a
very big you know life and I I know I
thank him to this day for my Nest Egg
yeah you know um but he was the kind of
the the the stable one you know like the
NBA and the NFL they have like these
rookie symposiums to tell these guys
Hollywood doesn't have
that that's pretty cool no you're right
it would be a neat thing for the to do
too so let's get on them exactly i a m a
mentoring program I like it no but it's
a you know it's a cruel fate and if you
don't see it coming and and even with
that knowledge in my head and Phil going
it doesn't last you got to just do the
work you know when people are stopping
you and looking at you and your paycheck
is huge and it's just feels like crazy
dirty money and you know it it's hard
not to it's hard when it ends and it was
devastating when it did end I ad bet it
was devastating his relationship with
you I mean uh that just reminds me
because I've seen too much news radio
but like it reminds me of the character
Jimmy's relationship with Beth like a
same kind of Mentor teaching you stocks
exact same kind of thing very much well
and Stephen was very much a daddy too I
mean you know Phil and Stephen were kind
of the guide posts for me in that group
and you know that was
and having friends who work on the
show uh having friends worked on the
show I I probably was at 15 or 20
tapings you know in the first four years
and then you know writing the the last
season oh that sounds nice we have to
evacuate but I really have enjoyed it's
my pacemaker let me just let me turn it
off give me a
minute oh there oh there we go my
husband's a sound designer if you're
listening call in and give us for the
next
feedback give us feedback on our
feedback the live podcast um uh but what
I was going to say is like the thing
that I remember was like even like as
just having friends on the set Steven
root and and um Phil you know they
treated everybody the same you know from
like the guy visiting to the crew to
whoever and and I had this image like
one of my images of news radio was Phil
and I don't know if he did this every
show but he would go up at the audience
during the show and stuff was that was
kind of his thing he'd go in and like
talk to the people in the studio
audience too and stuff you know and it's
like people have lines and you know bits
to do you don't have you know that's not
for everybody to do but he was that kind
of a person who would go out and he
after sure he loved meeting the people
too that was just kind of that that Phil
Hartman that you get you know out in the
crowd I forgot that about him I mean he
used to because they have these comics
on sitcoms not So Much Anymore um warm
because it's cruel really who hold the
audience hostage and try to keep them
laughing and Phil would see it dying and
would you know wake them back up for the
good of the right cu the audience would
love that you know one impression and
stuff would walk out in that audience
right now and talk to them boom right
picked up so much right now if I see
all' all Fading that's what I'll do nice
to see yall what do you do for a
living everybody all at once I
mean oh my
God yeah no I
mean do you have a you have questions on
the edge of your lips I can see can see
see it because it's like it's like it's
just you know I mean and and again I
just wanted to jump back to one thing
again being a fan of the show and being
a fan of everybody was on it you know uh
news R was just it for me as somebody
who now like works out here and has a
pilot all right all right what's the
name of that pil what's the name of that
J called Aspen
on telmundo is it on tundo no it's not
on T I don't know I don't know what
network I just got it yesterday have no
information crazy mismatched with on the
show playing a talking cat that has
magical powers love that that's great
and it's you know it's what you think
I'm not going to ruin
it it's like a modern-day sort of cereal
Citizen Cane Meats water shipped down
well I don't I have no I don't know I
got descri it as a simple comedy I was
going to say something nice and now
we've gotone all this horrible tangent
um no but no as a fan of news radio
because I can see it it's coming through
him and I see it as well but you know
when I see now that they give away you
know SAG Awards and em like to for best
Ensemble sometimes that's the first show
I always think of yeah because I've
never seen a group of people who I mean
like literally at the beginning it just
like I don't know how this is going to
work and then after the third episode
you wondered how it ever wouldn't work
well and what's interesting is you know
I was in the pilot only to be in the
pilot I was written and I had two lines
I believe and so I that's why I picked
up the chewing gum right because I sat
out there in that freaking break room
for so long where they were doing all
the scenes I was like I got to come up
with something and my line in the pilot
literally was coffee day so I took the
chewing gum and I can make this annoying
popping sound with it so I it started to
become a thing and you know what was
great is that Jimmy Burrows sort of
latched onto those things that we found
and kept it going but um wow I lost my
train of thought I'm very old so sad
really wow just the
no it was it was a you know we would we
got close very T very quickly um at the
rap of the first six I believe we all
didn't want to leave one another's side
and I believe it toyed with all of our
personal lives um to be honest I know it
did um and we went we were drinking and
and partying on the set and in the
dressing rooms and the sun started to
come up and I remember the writers you
know Josh Lee who I adore and all these
guys Al Hig and and they put foil on the
Windows they covered the window they did
because the light was our enemy and we
would when we had nowhere else to sort
of hang out and the light was coming in
they were like we went to Paul SIMS
house and somebody said where can we go
to keep on drinking and hanging out and
I said Vegas right and so they're like
yes and so at like 1100 a.m. you know in
the morning we're sweating like
rapists you know what I mean like
waiting like I'm not high anymore this
isn't Fun you know but we and we Up in
Vegas and I remember coming
home little thankfully we wouldn't get
in the car but you know I remember
coming home like 2 Days Later I'd never
been that person who just you know and
it became very just clicky and strange
and I think part of the reason we were
never nominated for
Stu is because we would go to Awards
like we were banned from the SAG Awards
now when I say we I recall the evening
of Steven Rood and myself sitting
perfectly you know normally at the table
but Andy decided to ask for Helen Hunt's
autograph on his dick so it was stuff
like that you know it got a little there
was certain elements that would get and
so we were banned you know and we didn't
act as a group right ever anywhere it
wasn't possible you know so I I think
that's we scared people even even Phil
because I mean I don't know you talk
about him as an anchor but that just
that blows me away that he would still
be that kind of a crazy person Phil was
not part of that no he wasn't he was his
own thing he was he was absolutely not
in that and Stephen rot was not really
uh so much of it was mainly myself Paul
Sims Dave Andy of Mora and uh and Brad
Isaac's and Josh Lee and Joe say Vegas
Joe no but Joe the writer Joe I love
name foret Joe red hair Joe one man news
radio Jesus Christ we're old Joe Fury no
Joe Fury yes Joe Fury right Joe Fury we
became a nucleus yeah and within that
we're you know and then I saned out a
little bit you know it was hard to keep
it up yeah um and I think it took a toll
on all all of our relationships and
marriages at the time um as you will
have probably read in the Press yes
right yes and what one one other thing
that I do say in in in kind of
heartbreaking way
is that at the time of news radio I
lived with Nick
Noti and Phil lived with with Bren MH
and they were both people in the darkest
part of their disease yeah and it was
heartbreaking and I think that Phil and
I had a bond around it because we
thought that we could save the people
that we loved so Des would make things
better yes and we were not able to do so
and you know I will never forget we went
to the Golden Globe Awards and I brought
Nick and he brought Bren and they were
both sober uh Nick was sober when I met
him um on I'll do anything and she was I
guess sober I don't didn't really follow
you know it wasn't my business and they
both began to drink they got together
and Phil and I looked at each other and
I thought my life is over like I we were
so worried and um towards the end you
never knew with Phil but towards the end
of that that
season he came in a couple of
times without having shaved which for
him was was unheard of and not late but
worn and had slept on the boat and was
you know calling hospitals when his kids
weren't brought home and it had gotten
to that place that we all know it got to
and I remember he said to me how do you
do this yeah and I made up some
ridiculous thing I had convinced myself
that my relationship was going to be
okay or I just wasn't you know handling
it and when he was killed you
know I my relationship went all the way
down and I left the business for two
years and I left Nick you know at that
time and I'd been there 10 years you
know and I I feel like I got out before
the boat sank and
how I dealt with Phil's death was all I
could do was write so I locked myself
away on that Hiatus after he was killed
and I had all these literary Martyrs who
I loved my entire life Dorothy Parker
and Salinger and you know all these
great writers and Tennesse Williams and
and I just sat down and wrote about 24
songs and produced a record called East
of midnight which is out but I don't say
it for that reason but that's a that was
a journal for me of of how to walk
through that and I actually that album
was a premonition of what what came
which was my relationship just it nearly
killed me you know and so um I always
felt Kindred with with Phil for that
reason sure you know because you you
can't save the people that you love
sometimes right of of all the things you
know that resulted from his death you
know I feel like if the show had already
ended and it you know and like what had
happened happened years later I I feel
like that it was like almost like a a
God sent to his fans that you know you
guys got to do a farewell show you know
because it was to Phil Hartman you know
even though you know it it was his
character and then you know that had
happened at least on the Hiatus so you
guys had some time to process cuz could
you imagine that was like a weekend off
and you know obviously there's no way to
come back the next week and shoot a show
or anything they so there was a if I
remember it was like August I'm not sure
you know so there was like weeks or
months or whatever to get ready and all
too cuz well and I and I you know none
of us wanted to come back yeah we really
didn't want to keep going sure and um
and I also never forget this this is
going to sound all made up like it's on
ghost hunters or something but you know
I was asleep and the day the morning the
news came out Nick woke me and he had a
look on his face and I remember I sat up
and I said it's Phil like I I just
somehow oh wow I just somehow it was so
strange to me but um we didn't want to
come back and you know John love it's is
the reason I believe that Phil got on
Saturday Night Live Phil's a graphic
designer as we all know John sort of
dragged him in and got him seen and he
was on there and so you know we thought
that that choice made sense but it was
never the same and it wasn't John's
fault you couldn't blame him for it no
there some some of my favorite episodes
in that season are actually or from the
show are actually from That season um
you know it's it's you know we we you
know
obviously there's there's no denying
what a huge impact that death had on
people who knew him yeah obviously I
never met him he's the reason I wanted
to get into voice over and in into
acting the first he's the first
celebrity that ever mattered to me was
lost you know and um and that's just
mostly because everything he did was so
full of joy at least on camera you know
what I mean and I just wanted to talk
about what made him so funny that's just
so important to me I mean and Jeremy you
and I have talked about that episode of
Saturday Night Live that I mean it's I
mean you know for me I mean it's it's
like with any great performer any great
comedian and because I you again I don't
think you can call him a comedian he's
just a brilliant actor and he just was
really good at comedy and it comes down
to what Edmond Keane always said you
know like dying is easy comedy is hard
and Phil for whatever reason made it
look effortless everything he did was so
clean and specific you know I I mean and
and you can talk about bits he did from
Saturday Night Live I mean I can talk
about you know even just one line as a
reporter and peewee's big adventure
walking by he's got that perfect Cadence
and he just there's nothing sloppy about
anything he did he was he was just a
quintessential professional as as an
actor let alone is a comic and you know
we talk about that you know that one
that one Stand Out live bit where you
know he's doing the the panel with the
um was it Nord dun show and it's Tanto
uh Tarzan and Frankenstein giving all
their answers and of course you know and
you know it's supposed to be a regular
talk show she like well you know I'd
like to you know welcome these three
people for coming and like hello like
hello hello you know and Phil Phil doing
is terrible you know they don't even
have the green but he's got the bolts on
he's got his jaw jutting out and he's
just and he just maintains the face so
perfectly through the whole thing and
they ask the innocuous questions like oh
the first topic is um bread what do we
think of bread bread good and then Tanto
bread good and Frankie time bread good
you know I mean it just and then when it
comes to the end and you know it's
coming again fire bad the second time
after talking about like trade unions in
the West Indies you know after fire good
fire bad a little bit of condescension
and it comes to the end and you know
it's coming and he freaks out and
punches a hole through the wall up stage
and leaves and I mean it's the only time
I ever saw him crack in anything and it
was like the most effective thing I have
because again how are you going to end
it it was like the ending it was like
ending um uh um sorry Billy Wilder um uh
movies the the Something Like It Hot you
know like like nobody's perfect it's
like they didn't think that was going to
be the end line but it had to be you
know what I mean and like it just yeah I
I just I love watching everything he did
even the small like Sergeant Bilo he's
great in oh yeah I am probably the only
person to put those English words
together in that sense it's true it is
but yeah I just everything he did was
just you know and again as somebody
watching him as a young person watching
him on TV it was he was somebody to
steal everything from abely you know I
mean and it was just inflections or
takes or whatever it was and yeah and I
would just would have loved to have seen
him do zap ranig again on future
God just would have loved to have seen
that but I mean there's no doubt that I
love Billy West don't get me wrong and I
think everybody on the show is great for
I mean everybody's great but to see to
have him do that would have been oh just
pretty damn good impression Billy West
does though
oh oh yeah he's amazing he's amazing but
Mike was the first thing or at least the
most the thing that first hit you I
think so much of America just remembers
him from satday Night Live and just you
know they you read all the things they
called them the glue there story that in
a room and they start
going and some of the things that I
thought was I I watched some interviews
with him he did like a later with GRE
caner that's on YouTube it's fairly
because you just want to kind of hear
his side of things because you never
know these stories you hear you know
which they are and that you know the he
says in the mid 70s you know went to see
the Groundlings and he talks about
himself coming into acting later in life
and then like about to quit too because
sure he had the little falling out with
Paul Rubin over you know things that
happened on PeeWee Herman and all he was
about to quit and ended up on satday
Night Live and it's just when I think of
things you know so many people peg him
as Bill Clinton was as big and he was
hilarious but I wonder how much he got
sick of that because you know you want
to walk in the room every time and go
come on do Bill Clinton because I love
caveman lawyer that's the thing cavan
lawyer is I mean is fantastic I mean
like his Frank Sinatra is fantastic you
know but I mean yeah it's I mean just a
la and I just I would love my favorite
is the is the Cutaway from the next
episode it's like get me another Scot
show you in this whole crummy Airline it
just freeze on them all drunk and
drooling with the whole Big
Ridge oh I I'm a I'm a freak for that I
just for some reason I I don't forget it
your girlfriend does she like that
everybody she actually she half right
that and and she loves it when I do
entire Monty Python
sketches that's what it is it is a turn
on for all the men out there that's how
you turn a woman on Star Wars references
and Monte
python thank you oh
there are no women
here just so you right uh but no and
then there's one other thing that I just
um yeah no I just yeah and Phil is
amazing but the first thing because I
just want to jump back to that the first
thing that I ever remember seeing him in
or like remembering it was him yeah was
watching peewee's Playhouse the original
on HBO when they showed it the live
action the the the one for adults you
know shoir you know like that one uh and
they had the s in the Family Stone
medley and it was amazing but the the
one thing and I'll never forget it was
when he came on as Captain Carl and the
best thing is is you don't even get a
look at him because he runs immediately
enters and then runs off stage cuz he
said he has to use the bathroom so you
don't even get a look at him he's like
excuse me and he's gone right so you're
waiting for this guy to come back and he
finally does and it's it's the line that
I'll never forget and it's got this
brilliant physical bit his he comes up
to him and says wait a minute Captain
Carl did you wash your hands and he goes
no
oh and just take and covers his eyes
nose and mouth and then they sing a song
about you know Sailors washing their
hands and it's and and I just sat there
with my mouth open going like that is
the funniest thing anyone could ever do
and yeah and again it was just it was
just perfectly done you know and when I
found out that he had written so much of
it you know was responsible for that
good when peewee's big adventure came
out I went and saw that instantly and
then again when I found out he was
responsible it was you know everything I
find out about him it's just it adds to
it how about for you Jason your first
Phil Hartman and it's hard because I
know I saw him on on SNL a bunch but I
have hated most of SNL since the mid 80s
and so I wasn't really paying attention
to it um but I did I thought you were G
to say but I hated him I I don't know
why we're doing this actually I have no
IDE me no I did not like a lot of SNL at
the time so he stood out he always stood
out there's no doubt so I knew exactly
who he was but when I started hearing
him on The Simpsons I think Troy McClure
just again that was like the epitome of
smarm and again that's what's attracted
me so long for to him so much and yeah
there are people laughing in the
audience who know why um just because of
my personality but he I uh once I saw
him on on news radio sort of embodying
that like that was the thing that just
killed me because he's one of those
classic I was almost like executive
smart you know like Eddie isard is an
executive trans you know what I mean had
this kind of you know absolutely yeah
yeah it was dignified and it was it was
filtered through something else you know
because he was a good actor and you know
the the good actor acting made him a
great comedic actor he um I'm just
trying to think I totally forgot what
the hell say first thing first thing
first thing what first sketch Satur live
or that you like that that you remember
I can't I can't remember you like I me
yeah yeah The Simpsons was really the
thing that hit me you might remember me
maybe I should leave for a minute go
behind the the the curtain
um yeah but anyway no but it was on on
new yeah thank you very much um but uh
on news radio what I was just going to
say is like he's one of the classic at
least bill mcneel is one of the classic
bastards with the Heart of Gold like
going back to bco going back to uh the
boss on the dick man Dy show whose name
is escaping me right now Alan Brady
thank you and I I just think he's one of
the top five you know like oh God it's
really is Ah that's what we're actually
here for we're raising money for
Alzheimer's research old people old
people talking about things and now you
remember that man in the
car when he stopped what did he say I
forget did he have the mustache or
didn't have the mustache this happens
with me every episode doesn't matter
when I do this you're supposed to keep
talking Jeremy remember that I you
didn't hear me just
rambling um we were going to very
quickly maybe uh
yes yes let's I can read Melanie Hud's
thing yeah well we're also going to have
a quick call with Phil Hartman's brother
if I can absolutely reach him on the
phone the whole point is that this is
turned into cash in there do you know uh
we were going to very quickly let's see
if he's there cuz I'm going to surprise
him I told him I was going to text him
first um but I haven't had an
opportunity D you want me to read this
while you do that you know what see
that's buzzing and there go why is that
buzzing it wasn't buzzing s through it
what what no no not there a man
on fire there's man in box talking um
all right so what we'll do is yeah uh
read the thing and explain it are not
wor why don't you set up the
bit set up your bit okay well basically
um uh I was I was able to talk to to
Melanie hudel who of course played Jan
Brady and um Tor spelling on Saturday
Night Live While Phil was there and uh
she wanted to be here today but
unfortunately had things to do with uh
the family but she did write this so
that I could read it for her um and it's
it's just it's great I don't need to set
it up any more than that um this is so
Melanie hudle on Phil Harman I don't
think I've ever been quite as nervous as
I was when I auditioned for Saturday
Night Live it was the first of many
outof body experiences I would have over
the course of the three years I was on
the show I didn't realize that not only
Lauren and other producers would be
watching the audition but lots of cast
members as well when it was time for me
to perform my Jan Brady impression I
needed somebody to play Mike Brady and I
asked Phil if would do it he said I
would love to be Mike Brady but I think
it would be better if I read it from
offstage so that all eyes will be on you
well at that point on the one hand you
know he had a point but on the other
hand I really really went against the
plan I'd had in mind for weeks but the
overriding feeling was oh my god I've
been watching this guy since college and
I can't believe I'm standing in his
presence oh my God he eventually
convinced me and it turned out to be the
right move it was a very thoughtful and
generous gesture coming from a fellow
actor and I've never forgotten it that
first interaction that we had during the
audition pretty much set the course for
our relationship over the next 3 years
he was always stopping by my office just
to talk and he gave me a lot of really
great advice it has been said that he
was the glue during those years not only
in his ability to play the Everyman
roles but also bringing our group
together behind the scenes as well I
remember that every time he would walk
into a room everybody would start
chanting in the lowest register of their
voices
GL he cared about everybody and was a
true team player I do remember one time
he expressed to me that he really missed
working with Jan Hooks and and she
understands why they had such a great
chemistry together but he certainly
didn't let this slow him down she felt
very lucky to be in the presence of
somebody working at the top of their
game especially knowing how kind and
giving he was behind the scenes uh
Melanie has been part of a Facebook
campaign to help get Phil a
much-deserved star on either the
Hollywood or Canadian Walk of Fame why
not both yeah and I really do hope that
it happens and this is what she wrote uh
just to end up I miss Phil the world
misses Phil but thankfully he was able
to use his talents in such a way that he
left behind quite a body of work that
will continue to make people laugh for
years and years and years that's nice
was
good Melanie if you're listening thank
you yes you're not
listening you give me just a few minutes
pretend I wrote one but it's it's my
intervention letter to you he's got
Jeremy's got like 17 pag I have I've got
Jeremy did research do you want to just
take over the show now that J I already
thought I
had you are drunk with power hate you um
have we called anyone yet no we're going
toing I thought maybe you're doing that
while the reading I know was that out of
boredom or out of out of just your
curiosity insecurity on my okay that's
fine that's all right I asked that cuz I
was insecure too so that's that's good
all right let's call Paul um I just
texted him and a jump off what you said
he actually got to do Clinton for
Clinton like multiple times much to the
Delight of
Bill oh phone call phone calls just like
George
Bush that well he can't hear us right
now so recording it's even
better that's his picture Phil is one of
eight children so I
imagine yeah don't think we have that
kind of time yeah oh good voice this
would be fun
we can leave a
hello oh
Paul this is our oh hold on one second
this this does not sound good and it's
not your fault can you hear
me I can hear
you
huh oh dear oh my can you hear
me you need to apologize it does sound
like a does it not um you know what
we're having some uh wonderful technical
difficulties right now well Dan I could
hold it up to the microphone but this is
not going out there so we wouldn't be
able to hear it uh can do speaker do the
speaker yeah you know what I could do
that let's uh it's a small enough
theater here Paul uh real quick um we've
all been talking about Phil and uh just
you know we thought we'd give you a call
obviously and uh just uh you know just
uh give give me a second let's see if we
can do you on speaker here can you still
hear me I can still hear you hey yay and
the
audience the all right oh my God I got
the clap oh dear get a shot so um we we
were just talking about the first thing
obviously uh the first thing you ever
saw that Phil Hartman did was was uh be
there um but we you know uh we just you
know we all love Phil Hartman what are
you doing J I wish you had a tiny chair
for the phone put
next um but we just really quickly I
don't know we uh we've got you know we
got a few people here gathered here and
obviously I'm sure you were proud of him
because you're part of the campaign to
get him uh the star in the Walk of Fame
as well um just just tell us what it was
like to have him as a
brother well my experience with Phil
was a lifetime of first Phil you know
like just about everything I did in life
I did with Phil you know because we were
so close and Age and and he had to
babysit me a lot so
um you know he gave me my first
surfboard he uh we played catch together
you know we things like that you know
and uh he was also one of the first acts
I ever booked when I was a baby agent
you know I I got him some of his first
gigs you know and uh things like that so
it it it was just a long line of first
you know and that's kind kind of how I
look at Phil is uh he uh was set a
Renaissance going in me you know and and
uh and it has again you know even with
with him being gone so it's uh it's one
of those things you know it's like two
projects I'm working on that are
animation projects are based on original
artwork Phil did that's awesome and
we're now five years into that process
and about to do the pilots so it's it's
uh it's kind of like uh you know the
last time I saw Phil was the night our
father died and uh and Phil and I talked
and and he said you know someday we'll
do something together and uh and I look
at these things and and like getting him
at stars as um the a dream and a promise
right sure and so that that's how I I'm
seeing it you know these kind of things
that you're doing this is great you know
I just love it to see that people still
carry him so much in in their hearts
well we we appreciate you doing this I I
wanted to ask you a real quick question
about as far as if you you know you guys
spent so much time together I just want
to know what his first comedic
influences were if you had something to
do with that if you guys were both being
influenced comedically at the same time
I know he was an actor but I mean he was
hilarious so well cartoons at first I
mean we watched Rocky and
Bullwinkle and you know the Flint stones
and uh all those kind I mean Sherman and
body for some of our favorite stuff and
and uh and then uh it it became other
things you know it became films and
music and and Phil and I you know we we
not only lived together when we were
kids but later on I rented a room from
him when just as he started at the
ground Ling and uh so you know we would
commute to the office at the crossroads
of the world and and uh you know we
drive by Hannah barbar you go God
someday you know I want to do voices and
cartoons and sure enough you know he was
that's
amazing well I Paul I don't want to take
any more of your time and uh I really
really appreciate you you you doing this
for us and uh thank you for booking him
some of his first gigs otherwise we
might not have seen him anywhere is
there anything that people can do is
there anything people can do for the
push to get yeah as far as a push to get
him the the the star on the Walk of Fame
I am going to talk to Angel and a little
bit about that as well um but what can
we do besides going on the Facebook page
you know there's a Facebook page for his
his star what else can we do well the
the Canadian Walk of Fame is uh anybody
can vote on that okay so uh that's great
you go to H Canada's Walk of Fame back
slash nominations and last year Phil had
his own button and I'm sure he will this
year too um and it's just body count we
need body count and um and then uh we
just got news that Phil is also now on
the ballot for Canada's comedy Hall of
Fame oh great um but only Canadians can
vote on that one so we can't pretend
I'll get my mom to do it
yeah
yeah I swear I'll do that Paul thank you
so much um like I said this is going to
be up shortly so you know uh thank you I
just really I really appreciate I will
insist that everybody everybody have fun
Cate thank you
hey thank you Paul all bye that wasn't
too uncomfortable at all no not at all
what's freaking me out is how much he
sound
like also and when his picture popped up
too yeah yeah he does he he he doesn't
look dissimilar very much uh you want to
just read all your notes for the rest of
the show that's what you can do really
since you took so many damn notes
actually we went we went over everything
for making me look like yeah that's it
um actually the only other thing that I
had on here that I even wanted to
mention cuz I thought it was interesting
but apparently he auditioned to be the
announcer on the prices right did he
really yeah and and Rod Rody or whoever
it is got it instead of him I know isn't
that crazy show business makes no it's
insane I mean like could you imagine
Phil Hartman showing up and being the MC
for something and going no no you know
what that's wrong I can't even imagine
that you get to the point where you
don't just offer him that like I go to
appointment sometimes as you do I'm sure
and you're just sitting there and it's
like There's Tom Arnold and pet there'sa
man and why are they bringing people
know aware what part are all those
people auditioning for that's what I
want that's like I wonder who will get
it it's for the Morgan Fair child story
exactly I know how did she get a story I
don't I don't know she was auditioning
for it actually Morgan Fair brought her
in I was like this is so unfair I'm sure
we've all had that at one time but like
I had a we want a Vicky Lewis type for a
voice over but I didn't get it yes uh in
fact actually didn't get it that's the
uh my uh my father told me actually but
before I started to do this horrible
thing my father told me the four stages
of the actor's career and actually
Martin mole until death gave me the
fifth which I didn't know there was one
but the four stages of the actor's
career if I remember correctly is who's
Jeremy gusin two get me Jeremy guskin
three we need a young Jeremy guskin four
who's Jeremy gusin and then of course
five that uh Martin mole told me was
you'll never hear what happened to
Jeremy
G so uh so yeah so I mean like that I
think is that's the full cycle so I try
to remember that no matter what you know
no I like it when I go in and they're
like we're so I can't believe you came
in for us we're so honored don't get it
no yeah it's nice not their person yeah
the only other time I had something like
that was I audition for a Carrot Top
character and Carrot Top also audition
and I got it see now that's just that's
cruel that top that's that's me that is
funny
universally the thing about about La
that versus New York is that in all of
my years out here in La I have never
ever gotten any bad feedback it's always
oh yeah we loved her we going a
different way in New York when you [__]
up right don't do well they go she
sucked she blew it you know tried again
but you never so you never really know
where you you actually I did get that
note on Tuesday uh in the car early
morning when I fell no Wednesday
Wednesday no no uh when you got actually
yeah he was like what happened you
tanked the [__] AUD you you tanked
the call back and I start and I spent
like 2 minutes apologizing he like you
got it anyway don't worry my
God I was like I was like one of those
moments where you want to kill and kiss
somebody at the same time it was one of
those and of course the name of that
show is perfect strangers 2 correct
right um
actually that that's what it's perfect
strangers yes it's it's perfect
strangers too colon correct that's
actually what it is that's the name of
your pilot no it's not what's the name
of your oh it's just Aspen ASP I don't
believe there's a pilot
any I feel it's all a desperate I made
it up I actually what it is I got my I
got my it's actually s with a dollar
sign um I got my pilot's license oh good
one you need to explain these things no
I didn't no one's ever I only got it
yesterday
stupid um speaking of Pilot's licensees
Phil Hartman had a pilot's license back
to Phil to be honest with you I think I
could literally just talk about things
I've seen him in for a good four to
seven hours sure to I'm serious because
I mean like again you know like there's
so many things he did that I remember
almost verbatim you know because and
they were just you know like when on Sat
Night Live when he used to play that
crazy waiter with the was like hello you
know you take a nothing part and make it
into something uh
the anal retentive
Chef it's always hilarious well first we
fold this up then you like then you take
the refere you put that in a bag then
you took the refu baggie and put it in
another bag they run out of time for the
show cuz the very first time he like
would cut off a piece of something he'd
have to wrap put in a trash bag and
stuff and like there was and that was
the character he didn't need to put on
any physicality or a voice or anything
it was all in just the setup it and also
I remember in news radio I mean the he
never rehearsed I mean I guess at a
certain point none of us needed to we
knew who our characters were but there
was a Cadence and the stakes were so
high and so
real I to this day I don't know why it
was as funny as it was it was something
innately it's just a gift at a certain
point I me I don't know I can't I mean I
I think it comes from and almost it
might be easier from an outside
perspective especially on this but you
know I've always heard that good
directing is 90% casting and you cannot
ask for a better cast than all of you
and regardless of whether or not you
know it was the right amount of right
people for the right whatever it was it
all worked because you guys were all so
good together when you get good actors
you don't need to have great material
even as long as you're talking and
listening to One Another when you have
funny people or intelligent people you
just can't help but watch it to me to me
that show is like the The Mary Tyler
Moore Tyler Moore Show of that era the
emys well to that a lot of people have
said that bill mcneel was just back made
it bill mcneel you know and there was
just everybody bringing something other
than sitcom to it well it was I mean it
was a group of seasoned actors I mean I
was 35 when I was on that you know I
don't even look like you're 35 years
they were very sweet but no I mean you
know that was we were all we had all
been around and seen a lot you know
what's interesting I don't know if
everybody knows this a little tipit I
just
remember is that um the original
handyman SL Joe Rogan did you know this
already oh everyone knows it I listen to
the commentaries three or four times so
so sorry again all the women please pay
attention DVD commentary yes no it was
um wow really the Alzheimer's Romano
committee no it was Ray it was Ray
Romano and you know he he was didn't it
didn't work out then we had a which I
never understood and Ray would make me
die laughing because he and I had
nothing to do right so it's like they
gave I had a piece of gum in the pilot
and he had like a tool right and we're
like who the [__] are we right and we're
trying to figure it out and he would say
to me he said it to me I think once or
twice like I they going to fire me like
I really don't know what I'm doing and I
remember saying stop saying that you
know but that didn't they couldn't find
that was the only character they sort of
C right and so then we had a second guy
and then Joe but um I was going to tell
a funny thing which I it's not very nice
really but it's funny I don't think it's
mean really it's kind of mean but we
were doing a scene Andy Dick and I were
doing a scene in the break
room it was just me and Andy that's it
right and we did the scene and cut and
we go over to video village where all
the writers are and they wanted to tweak
the joke he comes running over to me and
he goes did you see that last scene was
I Funny in it Andy did yeah I said Andy
I was in it with
you I was in it still nothing but was I
funny I'm in it I mean it was I just
never have forgotten that it made me
laugh very hard wow
I mean that with all the love in my
heart listen you know Andy's one of the
got one of the biggest hearts of anybody
he uh and I saw an interview with him
that he did with Tom Green back when
there was the big controversy with him
and John and stuff and he said he felt
this love for Phil Hartman because when
he went into rehab he said Phil was the
one who called and checked in on him and
he found out later Phil was trying to
find out about getting brenon you know
is what he wanted to know but you know
Andy Andy did Love Phil you
yeah absolutely and I mean but yeah
again you know I just go to that we were
you know de collected group you know
there were a lot there were
personalities and you know and that's
what made the show great and it also you
know not a dysfunction but you know
there there was creativity there that's
what you get with creative people you
know wild no work to do the show and the
writer started writing like really uh at
the middle of year 1 they we began at
like 2 a.m. and we'd get like this many
pages at noon they'd be warm you'd be
like okay but it was always genius I
mean you know and I go on certain shows
today that I just I'm kind of like where
where have you put the writers where you
know where are those guys where is Brad
isic where is Josh Lee and and they're
all working and they're around but you
know that was a time when writers got an
18 million deal you know and writers
were I think the driver right I mean
they were the driving force and
something happened that's
unexplainable where you know it's
Network you know like like the network
did very little with that show you to
touch to touch news radio they were
there and the production company was
there but but but you know it was it was
so it was Paul you know calling the
writers in at you know 1 in the morning
and stuff you know there was no network
there and I don't all all the shows I
know of now are all like kind of N9 to5
you know kind of and I mean there's
wonderful writers out there I mean I
have a recurring part on How I Met Your
Mother and those writers are kind of
Genius you know I was I was so thrilled
to see that writing they're out there
but it's like reality television came in
or something and the bar got changed and
I don't know what happened you know
although it feels very you know hopeful
that we have modern family and that we
have you know Aspen yeah and as exactly
exactly yeah say the
coming this fall now I'd like to read a
little
poetry as far as your acting Jeremy what
do you ever feel anything coming out
you're like holy [__] I just did a
little Phil Hartman yeah every time I do
any voiceover anything yeah anytime
anything anything what specifically do
you do voiceover wise what kind of
things do you get cast for I mean I mean
it's I mean it can be anything you know
it's I mean one of the things that I
love doing is is cartoon voices and one
of the reasons I love doing it is
because Phil Hartman was one of those
people who you know let me know and I
mean I grew up with you know like those
ones in the 80s you know like gi. Joe
and Transformers and like all that stuff
and you know and a cartoon voice was ah
Megatron you know I mean and like that
was a big cartoony voice and you know
like to see Phil go on The Simpsons and
you know you know make that almost sort
of like stylized 1930s thing acceptable
to do for something you know and again
you know like cartoon voices are always
about stealing from something you know
it's you know you look at all the
Simpson voices and they're stolen from
some else it's like you know like it's
so nice to see American Dad that Paul
Lind is working again you know what I
mean like in things like that you know I
mean and and you see that and it's great
because you got a whole new generation
of people who you get too exposed to it
and Phil was he was just so good at
locking in on something in a voice that
was exactly it but made it his own it's
like J Moore doing Christopher Walkin
it's like when people do Christopher
Walkin they don't do Chris Walkin they
do him doing it you know and it was like
people doing Clinton or doing Frank
Sinatra in the 80s they weren't doing
that they were doing Phil doing it and I
think when you've taken something that
everybody knows and have basically bent
it to your own will that's a type of
skill and a type of just Artistry and
genius that you don't find very often I
think you said that really beautifully I
think that Phil you know didn't
necessarily have the soul of an actor
and it made him a great actor because he
was almost too smart and levelheaded to
be an actor and that's and that's
literally it and one of the last quotes
you know that I saw of his that that
really struck home for me is that I mean
he was in his 50s and for all intents
and purposes by my book he had made it
you know like he was getting film work
and I mean like you know definitely not
top but second or third and that's the
best position to be in because if it
tanks it's not your fault you know I
mean he was in a great position he
always did a and he always did good work
the crime to me I mean
that's you
know was that he was so pure in his
motive in life you know and he was
always working he yes and you know what
kind of broke my heart about that scene
that night was what I knew was that he
had made an emotional decision to stop
that if it if it wasn't going to you
know he was he was tired right and you
know I believe she called him three
times and he hung up right you know and
I like to you know I I think he probably
was saying no right he BR right finally
but you know he just was sleep he went
to sleep you know I just he had cold
medicine in his toxicology report if I'm
not mistaken you know and I just I just
think what an awful permanent solution
to a temporary problem which is leads me
to guns and I won't even go there you
know had there not been a gun in that
house he might be sitting here today you
know and you know F your kids yeah yeah
you know that's it you know yeah and
that was it you know and then it's just
he was he was that quintessential
professional it was you know even though
you be the top of his game he never
thought that he was there he was always
humble enough and smart enough to know
that he had to keep working yeah and he
knew it was temporary know he knew that
well of course he did I mean because he
said to me it doesn't I me and he used
to sit at his bill mcneel desk and draw
awesome all of his you know and I it's
so funny cuz I was he was not that much
on my radar when I got the show but you
know as the show went along I used to
look over at his desk and he would just
draw the most magnificent things and you
know hindsight I would have I would
stolen them you know when he passed
right no but you know um when he passed
our costume or maid
we it was kind of morbid it we all went
in and sort of took a piece right and I
took his tux jacket from the number that
we did at the piano where I sang and he
played yeah you know and I kept that tux
jacket and then the costumer made us all
pillows of the different squares of all
of his suits that's awesome um and why
am I I'm just saying that because I you
know it
at a certain point I gave that jacket
away because I wanted to let him go in a
sense do you know what I mean I just but
um he will forever be you know a
blueprint a part of my blueprint of my
soul you know I mean he he was in my
life in a chapter that changed my life
remarkably sure um and he taught me and
he led me and he made me laugh you know
I'll never forget um I think it was the
first table read and I was nervous and
somebody made a joke joke and you know
table reads are always awkward anyway
and there's always like somebody going
you know that's F horrible laugh and I
get you've heard my laugh throughout the
show but I have this like cackle laugh
but I was nervous and so I was like and
he was sitting next to me and he goes
you know you know relax you've already
got the job you know I mean it was just
like oh my God you're so freaking funny
but um I I love him and I'm glad that we
can talk about him today and um and I'll
tell another thing that'll sound like
Ghost Hunters but I was on my way to
um news radio had ended and then I was
testing for a show called three sisters
that I did following it and some comedy
check off thing know exactly only you
would make that from Aspen
but um I was driving back from the test
and you know those things are absolutely
unnatural like you're in a room this
small they're staring at you like they
smell bad cheese you know you know who
it's up against and you've already
signed the page and the money's on the
line right so I stand to make amount of
dollars that have one two three four
five six seven numbers in them a week if
I'm good in that one minute right but
and I got out of there and I was
sweating profusely and I thought I did
well and I had I sunroof and I it was
night time it it was like s or 8 and I I
put the sunroof down I was driving back
to
Malibu and I just I just would talk to
Phil sometimes and I I looked up as I
was driving I didn't crash and um I said
you know Phil I I miss you you and I
don't want to move on to another show
but I think I did well and I miss you
and I was just talking and a shooting
star went and I just I H I've always had
these moments with him in my life where
you know like I say it's like a
blueprint on my soul still yeah so yeah
I just wonder what it is about a person
like that obviously not knowing him
personally why the hell it would affect
me at all you know what I mean because
you can sense goodness in people and you
can sense uprightness and you can sense
that he wanted to do the next right
thing yeah you know I mean he was
lovable ABS oh yeah absolutely he wasn't
just I think it's that's I mean it was a
visceral reaction to him it was kind of
impossible to hate him sure sure I mean
you never saw anything mean behind
anything he did even when he was acting
like I mean he would go on interviews
and was clearly having fun Have You Ever
Seen the interview on Conan for jingle
all the way no I he just comes on Conan
says so you're here for a movie called
Jingle All The Way and he's like jingle
all the way to the
bank and then the rest of the interview
was
I it didn't matter matter he just killed
it in the first second that's him and he
like but you know he wasn't being a jerk
he he didn't care but he wasn't being an
[__] about it like it was just you
had to keep watching the whole time yeah
and again it's just one of those things
I could literally watch him do nothing
and news radio was so good about letting
you guys like do stuff and then cut away
and then cut back to it and see you know
the the repercussion of it like let him
smoke in the booth you know and you cut
away when you cut back you're like where
did that big white square come from oh
the Booth's full of smoke you know and
all you see come out from it
is all I mean it was all office
inappropriate oh yeah right I mean even
the way I mean what we came out with my
outfits was what's the most
inappropriate thing this idiotic
secretary can wear and it's and it's so
and it and like and there's one thing in
it that's really gratifying about being
a fan of of the show and you know
watching stuff now and seeing like
something so that something so obvious
that you did perfectly that they lifted
verbatim and stuck in 30 Rock you know
what I mean I mean honestly they took it
and went oh that worked there let's do
it here and it works again they I don't
want to go too far down this road but
you know they did it with suddenly Susan
yeah of course they took it exactly and
named that character Vicki no really I
didn't I mean and I you know I remember
Paul Sims going to the network you know
to war
really you know to mix this up maybe you
know but but you know do a good
impression of
you I know thank
you um that was her going through a wind
tunnel ladies and gentlemen I um was I
GNA say I thought it was good too you
know I think it was Phil maybe who said
to me you know imitation is the
sincerest form of
Television you know so I you know I felt
like that was flattering to us you know
and and they did just shoot me and all
that kind of stuff and then but you
can't you know there's you can't create
it's impossible it never works
especially with you guys had you know
again every moment you know you it's
just you didn't know who could come in
and it didn't matter because and I don't
think it'll ever happen again which
makes me sad you know but I feel blessed
that I got that because it happens so
rarely in television yeah you mean
happened in general or happened to you
just happened to an actor you know who
get get on a show that can run that is
also not creatively embarrassing that
you know can make you some good money
and you can find a job for six years
five and a half years whatever it is you
know where you respect everybody and you
you feel like the bar is raised every
day yeah you know every kind of
opportunity since then is I I have only
that to compare it to because it was my
first experience and it's always
somewhat daunting to me to try to find
my way in another setting and you know
thankfully I love to sing and I'm a sort
of a theater monkey so you know that's
what I spend my time that's kind of my
joy and I'm grateful that I have that
because I don't think television could
compare for me yeah film some film does
you know I did a film with Dave we were
trapped in Omaha for four months you
don't want to know the story that's
another podcast wow really okay we had
stay and stay's grandparents are from
Omaha as well all I remember about Josh
Le was that his pen was always exploded
in his pan pocket you remember that
on one of the writers on news radio and
ran the show the last season hilarious
great writer who always has something in
the works too I think he just moved back
to LA in the last six months as well
yeah yeah yeah do you have a favorite
scene that you did with Phil
Harman we had the make out scene in the
um Daydream episode oh yeah that was fun
um and uh cuz he's a good gu there and
but I you know I had the most fun with
Phil on a Christmas episode where he and
I were doing voiceovers together and
also when he and I sang and at the piano
so those are my two sort of no make it
pretty when she so so good she if you
haven't seen the episode she's singing
beautifully and he just keeps trying to
correct her and tells her no make it
pretty like this and he just does the
worst eel merman just type of thing
she's like but what am I doing wrong yes
it was very funny yeah that that those
moments I mean every day was kind of I
you know that show I mean the cast of
characters it just it's impossible to
not have that viscerally sort of alive
at all times in my world sure usually
for fans it seems but for the actors
it's probably personal times that you
spent it you know it's V it's dressing
rooms it's you know dramas that occurred
oh my gosh yeah I think Phil actually
kissed most of everybody on that show he
kissed he kissed Andy Dick he yes that's
right uh all the all the ladies in the
the Fantasy episode I don't know if he
ever kissed Dave he may have I think he
did I've seen him kiss Dave well
that's that's good enough for me you
know Dave would get in Drag and I love
Dave is hot in drag love Dave fully to
death I would just imagine you just had
all his kids in the hall stuff already
fitted and just put it on and you know
around did like a look like Isabella
Roselin went
to like he did that TR thing and I was
so attracted to him in a weird way and
Dave and I never made out all made out
with each other at some point but um he
and I were just close you know no we but
it got sestu as that group you know I'm
just saying
yeah um you know I uh I did promise I'm
glad we're running out of time when I
got to the part where we made out right
you can keep going I mean it's up to you
that's just going to spiral down to
nothing that's good you okay that's fine
no Andy Dick stories that's that's all I
ask that's just too
easy um uh there's uh a very nice lady
named Angel Rosenthal who is set up the
Hollywood uh the Walk of Fame thing on
Facebook I did promise her I'd call her
so let's do that real quick too and say
hello she'll say have the exact same
things to say as far as how we how we
help how we do it let's all pretend like
we hav heard she know about the Canadian
yeah will she know about the Canadian we
can also we can also Pretend We're a
much larger group Dave hello angel yeah
hi this is
Jason it's the whole podcast actually I
apologize VI is here my good friend
Jeremy my good friend Mike and our
audience
hello
everyone that was nice um so real quick
we just wanted to uh a thank you for
setting up the Walk of Fame and just
real quick I don't know just uh let us
know what film meant to you as a
performer well you know I came to Phil
kind of late I didn't really become a
fan of his till 2000 um Vicki I never
watched news radio in it land because I
couldn't keep up with the time changes
it seemed um so you know I came to him
kind of late and as I look back on it
now and especially with what I'm doing
now with Paul and and the rest of the
family you know it really seemed almost
a preparation of sorts that um I became
the the eminent expert on Phil and I am
now and um it's a nice path to be on
it's I'm certainly blessed by working
with the fan base and working with the
family and um even helping out now in
the proposed biography of Phil uh that's
being written by Mike Thomas here in
Chicago so is is that does that have a
projected publication date do we know
when that's going to happen you know I
should have work on that tomorrow um
that is bad
timing and uh he's hoping to actually uh
have a deal announced fairly soon that's
great um we we did want to we did want
to thank you we are running out of time
here but we wanted to thank you very
much for setting up the Walk of Fame uh
is is the Facebook thing the best is the
best way to do it that is the best way
to do it um if you go to Phil Hartman
Walk of Fame on Facebook you'll see all
the announcements come out next Saturday
which is Phil's birthday he would have
been 63 so um we'll be kicking off
everything in Earnest on that date and
we'll be updating probably daily um
going through next May angel thank you
so much we really appreciate iton no
problem all right wa to hear the rest of
the C you'll enjoy
it thank you so much byebye everybody go
out there and go to Facebook uh that's a
social networking site that's what I I
believe that's call Facebook go to the
Facebook and um yes Phil Hartman
Hollywood Walk of Fame right well we do
have to wrap up in about 10 or 15
minutes 20 minutes uh you know we can
keep stretching out cuz I could just
listen to you talk all day so that's
like Jeremy you're fine but um I get it
Aspen Jeremy by the way is wearing a
picture of himself Jeremy is wearing a
picture of himself
that's the problem maybe you could post
a picture because I didn't know if that
was maybe if you and Jean Wilder had a
child no that's me it's a picture of me
on my chest so I remember how humble of
you I knew I was coming down to Melrose
and I figured if somebody cut my head
off they can still identify my body so
that's what I did my God you know Mike
from the writers room in news radio did
you ever hear any stories about Phil or
were at that point where they just
didn't want to talk about it really was
the last season and I just think it was
too hard you know I mean I think it
almost you know everybody had to move on
in the sense of the show itself you know
I had been around before you know when
Phil was there just as you know a friend
of the show and by the time I was there
you know it it's interesting to me how
you know Vicki talked about the cast
because the writers were pretty tight
too and and you know in the the couple
of episodes that I was around were
really gang written you know somebody's
name my name was on one but you know it
was written by the entire staff you know
and you know I had scenes that I wrote
and all but you know it's it's
interesting how that show the cast was
Ensemble and a lot of the writers were
Ensemble a few moved on to other project
at the time but there was kind of a core
group that kind of stuck around for the
years and all too and you had to be well
you couldn't be careful but you know it
what happened was we were all such a
nucleus that if things were going on in
your life they would take them yes oh
okay you mentioned something right it
became part of the show that fact now
just go on to news radio tangent had you
met Melissa Samuels because I'd always
heard that your character was somewhat
based on Melissa Samuels do you know who
she is was she Paul's assistant at a
time or something he looked I guess
somewhat I don't know maybe maybe yeah
you know it's funny because I got this
the scene the audition scene and it said
something like the description was which
I've come to ignore every one of them
now but you know I was young to it and
and it said uh something like you know
Spacey you know which isn't me like
everything that's not me bubbly faced
out you know and I thought I'm not going
to get this so let me go the other way
and I made it really serious and I think
something flipped and you know and um
and the writers were smart enough to see
it because I certainly only knew it to
do it that way but it's when I
auditioned I remember I was sitting next
to Dave who I didn't know because I I
was like locked away in the world of
theater and I was like a kid from Ohio
where we would fight over who was going
to get the mail me and my sister I mean
there was no access to like St I'm not
even lying and so
um you know we got to go to the mall and
Heen forbid your parents knew you were
watching Kids in the Hall men dressed as
women that's right it was so was just so
edgy but so Dave was there and like
Bernie brillstein and Paul and you know
all these people were there and I had no
idea who any of them were Jimmy Burrows
and I remember I when I got the job you
know and I got to the table read and I
started realizing like oh that's pH hard
man Jesus that's day fully I would have
been nervous and probably wouldn't have
gotten it but I don't remember how I got
on that tangent of just the writers
would take you know what was going on
with us they would it was a little scary
sometimes and you know oh and Joe Rogan
used to do this thing I just have to
tell because it was used to terrorize us
I don't know if you remember this he
used to do this thing where he would
draw ahead and then he would do like
what day like today I'll do you Vicki
and he would like do in front of
everybody and it was supposed to be
funny but it was too honest so it would
be like this much of your brain is taken
up with I hate my life with Nick this
part of your brain is taken up with just
let me get through the day this part of
the but remember he used to draw those
brains he used to terrorize us like we
all would have a brain it would be like
what is he who's he going to draw today
he was always honest that's kind of
ironic that the guy who's most into
other men punching him in the head would
be writing about somebody else remember
story of Joe Rogan one day on the set
like kind of being amused that the gas
guy got trapped in his backyard with the
two pitbulls
that's kind of how I would sum him up he
funny again you have a different
experience than I do because I love Joe
Rog and I'm not saying
you by way the image that people that
the average person has of him is man
show and punching guy I know he's
[__] amazing you know like he was
always like so friendly to me like the
episode I
did so hard he's one of the main reasons
I actually watch UFC or MMA at all
because I hate announcers for anything I
mean literally and one of my favorite
ones and I know why I'm going on Joe
Rogan tagant but um it was one of those
moments and it's like it's where it's
where the reality of something butts up
against what the perception should be
and everybody turns into a [__] idiot
you know what I mean and so it's this
it's this UFC fight and it's these two
guys fighting and basically all of them
look the same now you know they all have
shaved heads and Tattoos over 40% of
their body and they got these shorty
shorts and everything else all right so
there's two guys fighting and there's
the color guy and Joe calling it and the
one guy the color gu is trying to
describe the two people and they both
have whatever their names are they look
exactly the same shaved head tattoos
weing black trunks one's black one's
white all right the guy doing color goes
and maae is the one in the in the black
trunks that have the writing that says
and the and he's trying to describe them
even though they look exactly the same
and Joe goes politically correct you
mean the black guy you know not the
white guy through just could not tell a
lie you know it was like how do I look
in this dress like the Bartlet
pear like what if you couldn't lie right
but um yeah he's that guy but he's know
he's very uh generous and fun he's a
different person like the projected than
the uh uh uh what was the eating bug
show whatever that was oh yeah fear you
know I mean he's fun he likes doing
crazy stuff he's good on it but as a
personal level just so you know that guy
uh I have nothing but great things to
say about it's funny yeah and he was you
know as we all were heartbroken but I
was most surprised to see his reaction
to Phil hard right hard yeah very hard
yeah very sensitive guy you know again
he wouldn't think you know and but you
know everybody there took it so hard it
was just there was no way to take
something like that easy no matter how
hard you you know what you knew about
his Phil and brinn's relationship you
know nobody projects that you know what
ended up happened you know and it was
great talking to brother there's a part
of me just wanted to kind of yell are
the kids okay you know just figure
they're okay I've heard that they're
thriving and that they are okay they're
with her
sister you know I I think probably Brinn
like anybody that is in the middle of a
disease was a lovely person that got
lost you know absolutely um and so that
her sister has them is probably perfect
I think one thing to make sure we
concentrate on before we end is
obviously uh you know he left a huge
Legacy for people and I don't the point
of this podcast is for people not to
forget those legacies not that I think
it's in he's in any danger with that but
I think there are people who just didn't
they're already they wouldn't have grown
up with him and they might have seen him
they're just gonna see him on reruns or
they're gonna hear his voice and not
know who that guy is um I I don't know I
I just like to leave it leave people
with uh listen to everything you can see
everything that you can and realize that
it's just go to IMDb and then be blown
away and see all the different things
he's done and understand how important
he is to why you find things funny
because there's I mean you know there's
there's no there's no PeeWee Herman
without you know Phil Hartman there's no
Simpsons as we know it without Phil
Hartman there's no there's there would
have been no uh Adam Sandler and Chris
Rock and all of those guys to come after
s Night Live that that if it wasn't for
Phil Hartman I mean uh you know news
radio wouldn't have been what it was
without Phil Hartman I mean there's I
mean he was he was on he did voices for
Ren and Stimpy for Darkwing Duck you
know like he did Nickelodeon stuff
Disney things he was affecting everybody
on so many levels even if he didn't
understand it so yeah it's you know I I
still love watching his stuff and I
laugh just as hard yeah great talented
funny men yeah Vicki is there anything
else you would like to leave us with as
far as you know I just feel absolutely
blessed that I was lucky enough to get
to spend five and a half you know five
and a half years with him yeah you know
I'm I'm a better person for it I learned
a lot I'm a better actor you know and I
miss him terribly to this day you could
see his SK skill and everybody else's
skill rubbing off on one another but you
could see there was something in him
that clearly rubbed off on everybody you
know what I mean and I mean whether it
was the way that the man could go quote
unquote over the top but still you
didn't care you believed it the whole
time I mean you know you're you're stage
trained and you knew how to go over if
you had to go over but I mean still like
slowly but surely you could see
everybody kind of catching up he taught
me to make the stakes high but to use
the forehead as a prum you know because
when I first came to TV I was doing this
still because I was on stage all the
time I hadn't figured out you know not
because I see a lot of people in
television the Trap is I don't want to
really see like I'm not going to do
anything I did an episode never mind I
did an episode of something an hour long
it's like my grandmother always said if
you don't have anything nice to say come
sit next to me
but literally I I couldn't hear some of
the I was in right here and I was like
what the [__] are you I can hear you you
know yep that's one of my I did I did it
one of those dramas and like literally I
had to wait for the person's lips to
stop moving because otherwise I wouldn't
have known where to speak like oh God
you know and you don't want to be a dick
to the lead and go what why do you
say I'm right here I can't even hear you
I know speak up and I remember like I
was doing pushing ton and Billy Bob
Thorton was in the movie and John qak
and they used to you know we would play
around play around and then they'd say
film you know and all that sound speed
and Billy Bob would say now no acting
but Billy Bob makes choices with his
non-acting you know but but Phil did
teach me how to make the stakes High I
watched him and learned from him you
know how to keep it high but keep the
prenium in the forehead area and and he
could do it better than anyone and he
was the glue of that show he without him
the rest of us were too crazy you know
what I mean his was the same crazy he
was the executive transvest of news
radio
I like that um I want to thank everybody
for being here Mike thank you very much
you're welcome Jeremy good luck with
Aspen thank for being here and Vicky
thank you so much we really appreciate
it everybody thank you for coming show y
Phil let's let's everybody today go and
join the the thing to get him as star on
the dam walk of fames both of them go
sing the monreal song Yes do that I can
do that all yeah it's not it's not a
test all right let's not listen it's not
that's not what I'm getting at I listen
you guys scare me I'm sorry thank you
guys and uh yeah have a fantastic day
and thanks for coming to com on Final
yay two applauses amazing wait a minute
forgot to hit record
and and also everybody go out and buy a
Coffey poco's Legend because if you
don't there are biggest he didn't take
the lens cap
off yay you know a town with money is a
little like the mule with a Spinning
Wheel no one knows how he got it and
danged if he knows how to use
it Mule the name's Lanley ly Lanley and
I come before you good people tonight
with an idea probably the greatest oh
it's not for you it's more of a
Shelbyville idea now wait just a minute
we're twice as smart as the people of
Shelbyville just tell us your idea and
we'll vote for it all right i' tell you
what I'll do I'll show you my idea I
give you the Springfield
monal I've sold monals to Brockway
ogdenville and north haverbrook and by G
it put them on the map well sir there's
nothing on earth like a genuine Bonafide
electrified sixc car monal what I say
monal what's it called monal that's
right
monal
mon I hear those things are awfully loud
it Glides as Softly As a cloud this week
comedy on vinyl was recorded at the
Zephyr theater in Hollywood uh producer
is Mike wardon uh edited by me Jason
clom it is a stolen dress production for
uh more information on our company go to
stolen dress.com just as it sounds the
word stolen theword dress.com uh check
out comedy on vinyl please uh be our
friends on Facebook go to facebook.com/
Comedy onvinyl easy enough twitter.com
comedyon final yeah so please subscribe
on iTunes rate US highly and uh then
we'll be able to bring you more live
episodes cuz this one was quite exciting
thank you so much and uh please join us
next
week mon don't