hey everybody it's Jason we are back
after a several week Hiatus a uh charity
uh necessitated Hiatus uh thank you to
anybody who listens to the show and who
came out to the million McFly March
because of it I mean thank you for
coming out anyway uh but we raised uh a
few thousand dos for Parkinson's
research we had a huge celebration
people came dressed up we expected about
150 we got about a thousand people to
come out and it was a ton of fun so
thank you guys we may do another one
don't know but thank you guys very much
for supporting um before we get into
this episode with Billy West which is
easily one of my favorite of all time uh
I just wanted to quickly let everybody
know that I have a book coming out it is
my second book it's called postmodem the
interwebs explained it's a satirical
history of the internet uh written in
character as though I don't know
anything about the internet and that I'm
taking a lot of urban legend as Truth uh
it was a lot of fun to write uh it's
taken four or five years uh to work on U
but you will recognize several of the
people I interviewed throughout the book
including uh James urbanc and Jordan
Morris both who have been on this show
go to postmodem book.com you can
actually pre-order it right now um and
uh yeah let me know what you think and
again it comes out on the 17th and I'm
posting you know throughout the next
couple weeks from the book's blog just
to give you some samples of what's going
on and the people who have enjoyed it
I've gotten some very nice um blurbs
from three people who have been on the
show before Jackie C Rob cutner and
Patrick ver
and with that um speaking of Patrick
verone and Futurama Our Guest is Billy
West this is one of the greatest times I
have had on this show period um he's a
hero of mine he's one of my greatest
heroes definitely my biggest voice over
hero and he was just cool this the only
way you can describe it he was cool and
as you can probably notice from the time
on this we took our sweet time it was a
lot of fun so it's myself Billy West and
Jeremy gusin uh you know frequent front
of the show so enjoy this episode let us
know what you think give us festar
rating on iTunes uh we could use a few
more of those and enjoy this episode
[Music]
thanks I'm Jason clom and this is the
comedy on vinyl
podcast hi everybody is another day
another world the year is 1961 the
artist is Jonathan Winters and my guest
is Billy West thank you for being here
oh it's my pleasure um so why did you
pick this album let's get into it well
there was really nothing to listen to uh
except Peter Pan records
Disney um uh those little yellow vinyl
kids records yeah yeah yeah like the
kind of come with a book sometimes yes
okay and um you know you know that that
that wasn't a whole lot like it wasn't
interesting to me the only things that
were at the very time was when the three
St just made a kid's record that's
awesome you know and I would like I
don't care about Captain Hook you know
but I quit going a church when I
discovered the three stoes and I found
my Saints
so uh I really did
yeah how quickly did you did you pick it
up from listening to was that the first
thing you remember then like the three
St we can start there cuz well it was
was stuck in my head they used to show
it every day before I went to school
okay um I was um I was already I think I
had just started school in the maybe
mhm yeah and uh you know so there was
only 2 and a half channels on television
they only went till about 11:00 at night
right and then they would play this
little
film um at the end of the broadcast
night and it was showing all the
combined powers of the Armed Forces and
everything and there was a poem that a
guy was narrating about how you know I I
have done this and I have done that you
know in other words I am man yeah yeah
yeah you know we've uh done this and
we've done that and he was a I guess he
was a fighter pilot or something like
that or maybe an airplane pilot even but
he talked about how he had reached the
skies and broken barriers and finally
touch the face of God and that line used
to just like send shock waves through me
I bet yeah no I mean just to hear that
turn of a phrase I I I guess I always
had some sort of Love of language MH in
me and um yeah you know and then they
would be off they'd be gone so Not only
was there no television like in the
middle of the night or anything like
that or would just go off at 11:
um there was no way you could
capture those things there was no way
you could preserve anything that you
just saw sure in other words there was
no video recording there was no nothing
you know it was like you lived with this
anxiety day and night if you were a
little freak like me that you just saw
the coolest thing you were you were ever
going to see in your life and you'll
never get it back and I may never ever
ever see it again because there was no
way to know yeah so and so the
desperation that a lot of artists had
was to just cling to it psychically
while during its uh airing and try and
suck every element out of it that you
could including the music yeah you know
and I was a little musician um you I
played trumpet when I was like nine mhm
something like that but even before that
I would just see all these cool things
and and in 5 minutes it's going to be
gone it was like yeah it was like when
you're done your last bite of uh you
know sea salt and caramel sure sure sure
you know and it's like GE you know I
don't know do I really polish it off and
then it's like I got to call it a day
it's gone it's over absolutely so um
unless you're a glutton and you decide
to of course you know go grab five more
pints right which an ex addict would go
do sure sure sure but that's a whole
another story um but uh what would
happen was clinging to those things the
only available stuff was like that was
recorded comedy mhm and that was it I
mean I don't mean I mean recorded
anything music uh we had uh I had heard
esel mhm I had heard what they now call
Space Age bachelor pad music uh but back
then it was just this exotic stuff that
like if a guy wanted to get into the uh
you know with his wife get in the mood
with a couple of cocktails and you know
before the tie came off they would
listen to Exotica right right you know
and then they go bump
uglies in the dark in the ' 50s cuz you
couldn't call it what it really was of
course but it set the mood in other
words on that note I'm going to just
real quick invite my buddy Jeremy in hi
Jeremy jemy very nice to meet you see
this is what I like to do come in late
enough so that I don't know what's going
on we're going to share
my exactly see what's happening is that
uh Billy West is giving me the birds in
the Beast speech see I didn't know there
are a lot of things I did not know wow
yeah and you're married and everything
know your wife must be so disappointed
she really is yeah but you can't sit
here and tell me that you don't have
volumes and reams of Martin Denny and
you can see the collection I guess we do
kind of who the other guy the uh he
never left Glendale California but he
wrote about exotic Polynesian Islands oh
yeah uh did all those travel logs and
things like that what's his name Les
Baer that's it yeah he lived in Glendale
and never left never left ever in his
life but Les Baxter was part of the Mel
toret okay um
meltones you know and he was a singer
but you know these guys just were
thinking out of the box at the time and
they were wondering what doesn't exist I
mean people people go see a movie and
they get treated to this beautiful
soundtrack if it's an exotic movie of
some type and all the pallets that
underscore Bliss and escape and U sex
you know sure sure yeah but uh but one
of the
records that I somehow had access to in
62 was Jonathan Winters uh another day
another planet M now I was enthralled
captivated with Jonathan winter but
before him I was exposed to Sid Caesar
yes when I lived in Detroit it was the
50s and my mom let me stay up till like
8 or nine mhm yeah and um I remember
sitting on the couch in the projects in
Detroit old giant mons TV black and
white and watching this this crazy man
you know it's the first televised image
I think I ever saw yeah and there was
here there's this crazy man that's like
pulling Hells and Heavens out of his
rear end and he's like vocalizing and
making noises and and also doing silent
stuff too and doing silent movie mimicry
sure um which was brilliant I mean
everything he could speak languages that
you would swear were real langu exactly
right yeah and I was I just was an
instant student of this guy yeah Sid
Caesar he would do m movie parodies
television show parodies and it was like
everything that I wound up to do MH just
about all of it it wrapped up in this
guy who molecularly just shook me when I
first saw him and I think that's one of
the reasons why like Sid Caesar was so
important especially at that time and
the world of Comedy I mean one it was
Live Comedy tevision from New York I
mean like this was the real deal and I
think the original show was an hour and
a half long they originally gave him an
hour and a half that's what he asked for
right you know when it was Caesar's hour
before it came your show of shows and I
mean like the the writing team that he
had also would speak of Sid Caesar as if
he was I mean he was this this thing you
know like was a God he was he was this
troubled God as most of our mirth makers
are unfortunately yeah and Jonathan
wners was also a very troubled God but
if you want to boil it down these two
guys were my heroes since Caesar didn't
make albums sure but but I was exposed
to him first yeah and I used to think to
myself what a crazy man what what kind
of man does these things and why does he
appear so iconic and heroic like right
out of the gate I suppose my suspension
of disbelief was a little different when
I was probably two or three or four you
know but I did see it and I remember
bits and and one of the things that
struck me about him like like people
wacky was invented by people who ain't
funny yeah you know what I mean like
remember those NBC promos where all the
cast of the different shows were doing
the wacky dance thing you know whatever
it
isv CAU me right you caught me unawares
even though I'm completely in makeup and
on a set oh me and they're doing this
impromptu wacky dance and uh and it used
to turn my stomach because you know that
that was co-opted by some bloodless
Godless artless suit absolutely you know
what I mean dance in is funny right
dancing more dancing because dancing is
funny okay all right that's the truth
all right you know he's like uh the
gatekeeper and the Arbiter of what's
cool and what ain't yeah um so when I
saw that stuff I said this is just
nothing but wacky and then I began to
Muse on it and I said wacky was invented
by people who ain't funny yeah well
people that were truly funny now you now
most kids and most young people can't
tell the difference who's really funny
and who ain't who's cool musically and
who ain't who's a faker M you know but
they just um there's no I guess there's
no real um scrutiny going on yeah and
also it I think there is some scrutiny
unfortunately it's like the opinions
that matter are just as loud as those
idiots who said do the wacky dance no
with more arms cuz arms is wacky that's
how my cousin did it at the party you
know that they do listen to people that
have you know a head on their shoulder
that go to the internet and say stuff
sometimes it can influence somebody to
back down sure yeah which I love oh it's
the best it doesn't happen enough I love
uh meanwhile there's all this other
crowd of people that you know it's like
anyone can play the home game mhm and
there are people that that are so
malevolent that they post with a
vehement you know and I'm sitting there
thinking about this this guy's always on
my website or he's always on somebody's
website and you look at the content and
it's usually you know it could be like
the Ladies sodality Home and Garden
website you know and some woman will be
there and it's like I just planted my
aelas you know Yahoo you know and then
there'll be another one it's like this
is also a good time to plant geraniums
but be conscious of putting out as many
Bee friendly plants as you can and then
the next post will be [ __ ]
you right it just escalates from 1 to
100 yeah and you know and you know the
stupid kid is like 13 or something yeah
just going to reach in
and I'm here right I'm here to wipe your
face in the carpet you know yeah you
don't know me and there's nothing you
can do about it it's this cheesy cheap
little form of power it's not even it's
just yeah it's it's um I don't know it's
like the arguing equivalent of ringing
somebody's doorbell and running away
absolutely I know but you know what that
is that's like uh having the ambition to
be a rock in some shoe your whole life
what an ambition it's a false sense of
Anarchy it's like they really think they
might affect some change I know they
post with a vehement like there was an
award yeah to be given yeah you know
like they're really trying uh you know
and there's no there's no Hall of Fame
for a-hole posters you know I mean if
there is it's the Hall of nothing
because because what you say affects
nothing and nobody yeah yeah that would
have that place would have the worst
gift shop ever
oh I mean it would it would be awful if
they did exist yeah remember this one
fail that was good yeah that's five
bucks totally worth it yeah yeah epic
fail oh that's 12 bucks these guys
bought you by poster number seven you
know Bismark hat you and right and these
memes memes yeah I like them better when
they were called things that just sort
of stuck in your head Yeah just
something I thought of once and then go
away yeah yeah but I was going to say
that
um you know the the idea of what's funny
and what isn't it's it's it's like that
question should just be put out to
Pastor it's no longer uh it's no longer
debatable or you know because people
it's like
um comedy's really more subjective now
than it ever was before yeah um there's
you know so many it's like Basin Robbins
you know like how many flavors of Comedy
for sure you know and then some yeah but
that's okay by me but like when a past
fail system gets created it bugs me of
course yeah because it becomes the norm
like all these new cartoons that I
audition for they look like children's
refrigerator
art you know honestly and that's the
objective sure and it's supposed to be
about nothing right and it's not funny
but guess what if you create that as a
thing that everybody wonders about why
what is this why did they do um I I I
someone thinks they understand it and
then it becomes culty of course yeah so
um but the thing about that is um these
20s somethings have created a
substandard that is now the norm and the
reason they did it whether they knew it
or not I happen to know because I'm
about 80 years old but they did it so
that no one can fail sure nobody can
fail yeah it's like uh you know if no
one understands what it's about big deal
yeah if the drawing just looks like you
know I don't know yeah looks disturbing
Deeter Max threw up or
something or you know like or like a you
know like there was somebody you know
like my six-year-old trying to do a
Linda Barry cartoon you know right uh
yeah but she's really trying she she
doesn't want subst aing as high as she
can absolutely I'm talking about
somebody trying to like come up with a
quality and not even understand what
went into the original no they all want
to be Seth McFarland so you get like two
producer masterminds that that um decide
that they insist that they're going to
do their own anemic voices for the
characters right and they think they're
Seth you know but the thing is is Seth
is a is a master a Craftsman in every
sense of the word an artisan a guy who's
willing to work like 20 hours a day if
he could I know him MH yeah I know him
I've been on his show a couple times on
uh Family Guy M yeah and uh
you know that's the stuff that counts is
everybody wants to have the finished
product with the accolades and and the
money and all this other stuff without
having to do any real work or search
your soul or bang your head against the
wall that part gets glossed over it's
almost like it's almost like somebody
saying they're sorry for something that
part's too hard to deal with for most
people now so they want to skip that
step and go I'm sorry you feel that way
right right yeah you know what I mean
it's like it's almost sociopathic mhm oh
boy am I going to
get com there's probably a wrecking ball
heading right for my bedroom right now
please you said this about us and now
you must
pay there goes my house is
disintegrated oh you little Devils oh
how I'll laugh when you die oh how I
laughed we can never die we are the
substandards
[Laughter]
we take the low road doesn't
everybody old man Relic from the past
cling to your standards and Aiming
High that's another thing we talk about
on the show a lot is uh and I don't like
to sound like a grandpa whenever I talk
about it I don't just like old comedy
because I'm nostalgic I like old comedy
because I do appreciate that these are
people who had a fallback which was like
a whole like I can [ __ ] dance like a
[ __ ] I'm doing comedy but I can
also dance I can also sing because he
trained well you were what was called
originally in a Hollywood a triple
threat yeah right now you don't even
have you you could be like an idol
threat you know well I mean like well
that's what I love like Singing in the
Rain when they're Des describing Lena
when they come up the great idea it's
like wait a minute we can't do that plan
like Lena why she can't sing she can't
dance she can't act triple threat right
I mean but that's what I can't stand him
I can't stand him oh that was Hans conre
oh God so good the great Hans conre I
love that movie but but but that's
literally what it is you know it's it's
I don't think you know you know you talk
about all these kids and everything not
understanding where it comes from but I
mean but look at how they were raised
they were raised in like a generation
that where the media basically was
bombarding them with the message you're
a superstar or you're nothing mhm you
know what I mean lifestyles are rich and
famous all the sudden Don't You Wish You
Were Me
yeah don't you wish you were my leg that
gets to walk on this property you know I
mean just it was almost like you never
you're not going to be anything and so
they just had this Superstar [ __ ] in
their head and it's like everybody was
proud of the job they had mhm if you had
a good job and you were supporting your
family it's like you didn't always have
one eye you know go down the marina and
you've got a nice kind of little speed
boat you know right wooden oldfashioned
with the glass wind you know and then
and then you start looking to the marina
left and right and there's these like
castles on wheels on on waves and uh and
you start feeling like nothing so
imagine growing up like that feeling
like you're nothing if you didn't have
everything right but but there is a way
to have everything it doesn't happen to
everybody but you got to work like crazy
otherwise you've got a a country full of
um Lottery dreamers mhm you know all I
got to do is this and I'll I'll be also
I'll be famous and I'll be original yeah
and it goes to entertainment too it's
like I don't even have to have any
tangible skills like look at all the
people in reality television who make a
career out of being I mean less
interesting than people I know who
aren't in entertainment well number one
my heroes weren't effing celebrities
yeah they you know they just weren't My
Heroes were artists I no celebrity
worship if there was a particular man
that portrayed a part I believed in the
character sure I don't want to hear what
he has to say politically and all this
other crap He's Just Not That
interesting what he became as a
character was a concerted effort of guys
who wrote they were they had literary
backgrounds they didn't watch TV to
learn to write for TV mhm you know what
I mean yeah they they had literature
that they were students of and um you
know it just
uh I think well what I want to say is
there's people that if there are people
taking me seriously the other stuff you
don't have to take seriously but but I
wound up doing everything I dreamed
about out but I was willing to work for
it I have immigrant mentality you know
if I had the chance to work for 20 hours
a day I would do it to this day you know
it's just like that's all I know Ma Jour
as far as New
Frontiers I can't tell you too
much I tell you Jackie's fine and we're
all fine right here you know I was
thinking fny I don't know why Kennedy
came mind but but it's almost a Walder
Brenan if you think about it Walder
Brennan talks like this Dan down in the
belly and if you sort of change it a
little to KY and Frontiers going ahead
as far as the campaign goes I you know
it's pretty
close a lot of people don't want to put
that time and effort in but with me I
had no choice it was passion it was
Obsession I had OCD add no ADHD I was
just diagnosed with that yeah like at
the beginning of this year [ __ ] and I
was like I got
ADHD I've read Lots about it but the
thing is is you're the last one so my
friends were saying you paid somebody to
tell you that we could have told you we
could have told you and I'm going yeah I
know if I had like a buck for every
conversation I interrupted I'd be I'd
have a house in Bermuda you know that's
what I I teach and I actually made that
rule our last meeting I was like can we
all just please just speak without
anyone interrupting and then before the
next person could agree with me I
interrupted them and I was like well you
know like well at least I know where
we're starting so I'm not going to
follow my own rules see what I just did
there you know it's like they look
there's kids are born learning machines
you know they're sitting there going we
saw what you just did there is the worst
I mean and actually and that's how I
learned it's like that was it like I was
lucky enough to have somebody who who
exposed me to your show of shows Monty
Python's Flying Circus you know Warner
Brothers cartoons you know Faulty Towers
like all that stuff when I was little
and when you see that when you're in
that impressionable age there's no
substituting it with crap right there's
no going back to crap you have there is
you have to maintain that level and then
you start finding these bizarre things
the fire sign theater when I was 12 you
know things like that um that wasn't
exactly my cup of tea because that came
when I graduated after I graduated high
school but but I mean the stuff that we
were talking about like Sid Caesar and
Jonathan wyers Danny K yeah right these
phenomenal The Comedians like Jack
Carter so underrated he was a Dynamo he
was like a Robin Williams right I mean
seriously and of course Jonathan wyers
was the Prototype yeah you know Robin
Williams MH um he was inspired by the
same pretty much the same stuff as I was
sure everything was Jonathan winners if
you if you can see a man on like prime
time television on like the Jack py show
having a conversation with his
shoe you know I was like that's for me
yeah that's this is like sent right to
me as a gift yeah that's the way I used
to look at it how did you get a hold of
this album first was it in the family or
you know what it is you had to find
things just like hey you know in
someone's Corner in their house you know
and I'd go oh my God and so uh the whole
idea of another day day another planet I
mean I loved futuristic stuff I liked uh
this thing that made me laugh comedy
when it was called comedy sure I mean I
think something really really really
funny is going to come along someday and
replace comedy soon but I don't know
what it is you know what I mean it can't
be called that anymore yeah it'll have
to step can't call anything rock and
roll rock and cool and rock and roll was
invented in the ' 50s I'm sorry
everybody it's gone yeah Gone Gone out
yeah um but I got a hold of it and I
remember listening to it and it was like
I I found myself doting on particular
bits and then someone got me or passed
something along to me that was Jonathan
winers live somewhere uhhuh and he was
he was taking requests from people yes
yeah and so if you have any requests you
know I'd be happy to do them for you you
know and uh somebody said um an elephant
wrapping a present for his girl
girlfriend and he goes an elephant
wrapping a present for his girlfriend um
got to be the male
right son of a [ __ ] and and but it was
clean and beautiful it was pure it was
like a thing of pure beauty poetry and
motion they all those guys they they
knew how to tell a dirty joke that left
it up to the audience of course they did
was the best you know like I don't want
to hear you use the words I want you to
leave it as innuendo so my brain will
fill in the
thing on the planet and make me so
embarrassed that I have to laugh I mean
but but also you have to be you am what
you is I mean if that's the stuff that
you're good at and it makes people
laugh you got me you got my vote but but
the old buzzards used to say you know um
I don't I don't like these new guys you
know they work blue and everything
meanwhile there's tapes of these guys
behind closed doors at roast and stuff
and they're filthy
yeah I mean they were working dark blue
oh yeah and um so I thought about it
it's like they they're bitching about
like Dice Clay and stuff and uh and you
know I wondered it' be like if you had
like um George dice Burns you know
something so I'm standing in a bank line
with my tongue up this chick's
ass what else is that to
do when they laugh I smoke when they
don't I tell a joke oh
oh
[Music]
oh that's a great bit yeah it is
fantastic George dice
Burns I so I see I know the cleanest
dirty joke in the world and I told it
over the weekend at a convention I was
just sitting there and these people are
sitting there and I said I know the
cleanest dirty joke in the world like
little Johnny Jones that's kind of how I
come off you know like the boy next door
with no
ster you know hi and uh and so I go I
know the cleanest dirty joke in the
world and I go did you hear about the
guy that couldn't come Dead Silence we
had to go get
[Music]
him [ __ ] love but see I used to do
stuff like that when I was like you know
before I was 10 years old I used to
think of stuff to evoke a reaction but
it was not well received you know what
and especially by my own friends really
yeah that's something I try to explain
to people and I didn't get much readout
on it but we me and Tom Kenny and uh
Anthony kumia who was a radio
personality and uh George low who was
the voice of space ghost we're sitting
there and you know and I said something
about how if anybody here feels like
they've got talent and they don't know
what the hell to do with it or you're
bursting to contribute and you don't
know where to start well here's where I
started it's like you go home you're
constantly sitting there how to dream up
something cool to show to your friends
that came from you not sh and tell like
hey look you know look at these
sunglasses man yeah no something that
originated organically from you that was
you're hoping to an elicit a reaction
usually laughs or just whoa you know
something something cool yeah and you go
in front of them and there's no readout
you do something and it's just like they
just look at you and I used to say I
mean inadequate I'm I'm like
malfunctioning you know because I'm
nothing not even a boo or a yay just
nothing and I'd go home and I'd work on
it and I'd keep trying and trying I wish
some adult could have stuck his head
into my world at that time some really
cool adult not just your average you
know full of [ __ ] when I was 10 years
old I was convinced that that most
adults I knew in my Heart of Heart were
full of [ __ ] sure I did I was a very
like a little cop a little Detective
watching listening watching because it
would serve me later on in life of
course but um you know I wish somebody
could have come in and just said listen
it ain't you it's them yeah it's not you
yeah you know how would you feel if
every day you had to go out and somebody
there's this uh you know you would be a
constant and painful reminder of what
none of them will ever ever be able to
do mhm you know how would you
right and I
said not too good really you know the
same way I feel when I go watch like
movies and there's somebody that's
funnier than hell and it's like I just
want to be that I wish I could be that
but you never get the chance to say
anything to the guy sure you wishing but
that was like nebulous that was a dream
to you didn't even dare think like that
like how on Earth am I ever going to
meet that guy and you know what it comes
to pass that I met almost all my herir
up yeah that's great yeah you know I
mean not many people can say that no and
they said don't do not like whatever you
do don't meet your Idol because because
you'll be disappoint because your your
undying agulation and love for them
could turn into abject hatred so far
that theory turns out to be [ __ ] on
my show at the very least that's that's
the purpose of the show well you have
good taste I do have good taste that is
true but I understand that like there is
that that absolute fear and you know
growing up as a kid myself with just
tons of fear and OCD
anxiety yeah 100% yeah I just didn't
know I had it I thought I was judging
what they say my insides to everyone
else is outsides yeah and I just thought
in my 20s and 30s and even 40s I said
maybe I'm just a [ __ ] and I can't like
deal with life on life terms yeah yeah
but it's not even like that I finally
got help and the woman women have always
been my best teachers in life by the way
100% and um and she saw me she was very
compassionate she said tell me about
what you do in the morning and I said
well I get up you know what about your
career I said everything is going like
so great it's it's incredible and yet I
have no reason to silently celebrate mhm
it's like I don't even think of of like
being happy or content because I'm
fighting this other thing that appears
out of nowhere like what and I said I
wake up in the morning I'm doing okay
and all of a sudden my breath gets
staggered MH like like think of
something just something from 28 years
ago pop in my
and I go like I'm reliving it again
that's
OCD yeah and then I felt like there was
a sort of damle over my head because I
felt I was in nothing but trouble mhm
and my mind would run wild with this
stuff and she's looking at me and I and
she said then what and I said I go in
the shower and turn in the water all of
a sudden this black cloud just crushes
me down to the floor I have I just don't
know what to do and I go I fetal
position I look up at the drops going
down the glass and said I can't go out I
can't go out there yeah I just can't I
can't nobody would understand but but
then I said well you know don't worry
about it everybody has this happened to
them somehow they pull it together and
so she she had a tear in her eye and
looked at me and she was shaking her
head slowly and she said Billy nobody
has to live like that in this day and
age I said what do you mean so she sent
me to a pharmacologist and I I actually
was treated MH for all all these things
that were just a way of life sure and
you know and and I wanted who's asked to
you kick when you find out at 50 that
you had chronic lowlevel depression you
basically your whole life could have
been a write off right but no cuz I knew
I could a b
instantly what's good and what sucks
yeah you know people forget people that
have normal feelings and don't have in
lacks of chemicals and stuff I mean what
is it like what are you born without
like
a183 worth of chemicals MH you know and
that's all it is sometimes but you have
to have talk therapy because of how you
conducted your life as a result yeah uh
of having to deal with those things um
but I mean that's that's basically what
it is no levels of endorphin mhm oh
nothing just the thing that makes you
give you a sense of well-being who needs
it oh
nothing yeah I have Doritos who needs
that that's right well some people I
love talking about this stuff because
every time I go to ComiCon you know it's
like why is he buming everybody out with
his stuff and I said because they know
everything else
about I offered up I offered myself I
put my bangas on the line you know in
public and honestly what's going to help
more repeating some piece of information
that take six seconds to look up on the
Internet or something that might
actually connect with somebody who's
going through the same thing well but
there's a certain kind of person usually
that winds up with this stuff and a lot
of them are sitting right there in front
of me and and I have people like looking
like they're going to cry yeah when they
look at thems and you know it's like
someone had to say that otherwise
there's despondency mhm you know and I
said you know just there's help you know
seek be a Seeker just keep going till
you find what it is you need talk to
people don't be afraid to ask for help
yeah and I said because it's murder and
I said I know a lot of you are sitting
there saying the same thing yeah you
know what Billy it is murder
and uh so people thank me thank you for
talking about that I go through it day
in and day out um like a lot of people
not a majority but but like a good
amount of people yeah have those kind of
problems well and I mean that's that's
another thing too like we at the Robin
Williams tribute that we did over the
the weekend we're talking a bit about
Jonathan Winters because obviously it's
going to happen yeah so and we didn't
dwell too much on mental illness because
we didn't want to talk about it in a
[ __ ] live show but like love getting
into it but just cuz we were talking
more about his career and we had this
little [ __ ] right next to me and
I don't mean to that's not to insult him
this guy does the most intensely
upsettingly good Robin Williams and he
looks exactly like him really who is it
his name is Jamie Costa I'll show you
the video after YouTube video
upsettingly good upset like he was born
with it but also can imitate like you
know you can look like him but if you so
he's sort of like the Von meter of uh
absolutely right but at the very how do
you even know that reference is what I
want to know where are my seven now he's
going to pull something out to embarrass
us all being would you like one of my
seven copies of the first family do you
have yucka Puck uh I yuck's on here
absolutely is Yuba Yuba the tuba on here
that one is not on there but yucka Puck
is the first song on that thing right
there that I love here's The Comedy Spot
Rob That's The Comedy Spot
Baldi I was out with tickles last night
oh you should have been there
Rob yeah we just did this one a couple
weeks ago that [ __ ] album is weird as
[ __ ] oh for Corn's sake
buddy oh for crying out loud buddy but
do dick F Dyke Impressions like 80 years
too late he's still around maybe you
know it's fine that's I met him once
yeah did you oh that was probably my
favorite thing on the on the Jonathan
winer's album is his impression of uh
what is it uh not bosi but um carof
carof it's just it's it's just he just
goes into it so seamlessly it's just so
fantastic well you know that makes me
think about the um the albums where they
had impressionist doing you know the
first family like the Von meter records
yeah um the story of Von meter in case
nobody knows is that you know he was an
impressionist and he had a damn good jnf
Kennedy impression so that was his
golden ticket as they say in Wonka land
you know he found his horse and carriage
and he was just being so popular and
making great records as the president
and the first family with other
Impressionists and then Kennedy was
assassinated and it's like the rug of
Life pulled out from underneath him yeah
I think Lenny Bruce's line was well Von
meter
screwed sounds like him yeah but um I
mean this guy that does Robin Williams
you know what if he's doing it means
he's got the spirit of crazy in him
which I applaud yeah he'll find his own
voice yeah he will he's got to reinvent
himself and stay true to what he feels
we were actually talking about that
exact same thing on the stage I mean I
wasn't trying to give this guy advice
but Rick Overton's on stage and he's not
one to shy away from giving people
advice so Rick Overton was just pumping
advice into this kid on stage and like
Rick is is one of the best I've ever
seen and one of the smartest that I've
ever seen I just I just sit there I I
hold all these people in real high
esteem I'm not like a snob that you know
uh I don't want to get into that or you
know or secretly angry because
somebody's funny than me I mean stand up
is a really hard thing I couldn't do it
I thought I could but you know what uh I
would go down go out on stage with no
material because I felt like there was
nothing nothing at stake if I was just
spewing out 12 minutes that it took me
three years to get together and write
and and hone it right I just I I wasn't
afraid to die that was my problem yeah
if I was screwing around and I found
something I was divining for Brilliance
or whatever you want to call it if I
found one thing it was worth it to me to
find something that nobody had covered
or or just a certain way of uh
presenting something that was just
really different yeah but you don't have
time for mistakes sure is it was it easy
to recognize how different Jonathan
Winters was even as a kid though like
that absolutely what was it that like
immediately set it apart for you um if
you can identify that might be well
let's put it this way he wasn't London
Lee or Stanley myON h handleman mhm you
know these guys the comedians that would
come on MV Griffin sure but when
Jonathan wyers came out there it was an
event okay I mean it was
like it it it resonated the emotional
resonance that came from a television a
caod ray yeah and uh that was not wasted
on people like me and most people
because they were pretty much smart
about stuff like that sure there was
some guys that just were sort of boozy
you know hey everybody comedians
people that just didn't even come from
that street they just came from you know
like a Skyhook brought them down and
left them off and then came back to get
themely yeah those the one thing too is
that Rick Overton was talking a bit
about that Jonathan Winters to the very
end was pretty Lucid in there so it's
not like you can't call this crazy even
though he's you know he's been he was
pretty open about any mental illness he
had but like it's not like that's what
this was oh Red Skeleton same thing sure
yeah you know they'd have to get him out
of a tree oh man and Jonathan witer is
pretty much the same thing like he would
float away like helium he'd get into a
Persona zip it up and disappear yeah and
uh very hard to retrieve yeah but I mean
it was because there was a part of him
that was reticent that that was sort of
afraid to be who and what he was and I
certainly understand that it's a safe
you know the shoreline is always right
within distance if you're if you're
mimicking or or you got a thing that
makes people laugh yeah um but to get
help helps you reinvent yourself into
more of what you needed to be yeah yeah
is there something specific about
mimicking is it a comfort thing it is
but it just came natural to me I didn't
think much about it oh hi I had a great
idea all right never
mind yes I know I'm going to Dublin next
week yes I know that thanks for that
update thank you for
so I slept him some ridiculous thing boy
it must have been $10 you know and uh so
I got all the way back to hotel gee they
just like they were burning on me and um
my wife said uh what's the matter with
you and I said well I got some pictures
I want to get rid of them give them to a
buddy
and so I said um here here they are and
what they were were
statues of the museum there clown had
given me the
shaft uh
and of course I got the shaft in a
number of towns but I just want to warn
you if you ever do get over there while
you know just be careful that's all they
are is just those statues don't means
nothing you know unless you dig statues
I
don't I find them awfully
cold
um but I crawled up in the arms of a big
one one day and the guy took a picture
of me that's the first time I went away
but um
faite on this album there's a lot of
really I'm trying to remember you got to
refresh me because I haven't heard it in
a million years okay all right all right
uh well there's a side one is just
entitled opening California and he talks
about San Jose and pronouncing at St
Joe's being a little confused that I
remember that you know why because when
I first came out here I saw La Siena and
I said to my friends you know what that
means don't you the Siena
see that's brilliant I I got so much
mileage for about 8 seconds after LeBron
James came on the scene in the NBA CU I
turned all my friends and I was like Wow
LeBron you know actually that's a very
famous name it's French and they go
really what's it French for the
braon yes well played see and everybody
looked at me like what the [ __ ] is your
problem you know what though you know
what it is it's I hate to say this
because your friends certainly aren't
swine
there was a saying called Pearls Before
Swine you know it's almost like if you C
A if you gave a caveman a dollar bill he
would wipe his ass with it he might have
a revelation later yeah but what you
were doing was time release humor you
know maybe the dran or the contact cold
capsule will work for them later in the
24hour cycle or it won't help them at
all yeah exactly yeah that's what that
is yeah know D there's a lot of stuff on
here there's eigor and the monster yes
the Lost Island
oh when he does yeah the be movie
picture guys that's great do you know
that me and Tom Kenny did a a cartoon
called be movie it was part of um oh
yeah transv uh no tun Sylvania mhm
Steven Spielberg and Tommy played the
flying leatherneck hero you know with
the scarf and the leather jacket and he
you know I don't know if we can take on
these people you know he was doing his
best um you know phony baloney hero
pretty boy mhm fighter pilot and I'm the
tail Gunner and my name is
Jersey and after after anything I said I
would say the word hey you know like uh
yeah well all the ammunition gone
hey but that's a New Jersey thing
mhm mind on my money myy my
mind there we go go nice only man who
can make a phone call interrupting show
work thank you so much and and the
record scratch no l oh yeah oh are you
kidding that was best part of it that
was the best part of it all I know he's
about to drop some [ __ ]
now pretty hip huh that was I'm wher
than
white you know I'm like I'm not even
white I'm clear as Bill Murray once said
to Larry
Bird I what was George Carlin people so
white that they're blue yeah Adam and
Anatomy is pretty
prevalent see everything oh that's
funny uh let's I made a few notes about
just some good bits on here where he's
just oh we's talking about going there's
just one really funny bit where he's
talking about going to a movie and how
you bring your snacks your blah a box of
clothes there was just this line a box
of clothes was the funniest line to me
and I don't know why but that's but that
was
him that was him taking Divine dictation
that's the only way I can put it like
whatever broadcast
Center that that was aiming towards him
and he had the only receiver in the
world or one of the few yeah that's what
would happen yeah you know just
something would pop out
but but he
also he walked on a net he lived on the
net mhm you know uh without one
underneath I meant the line he walked on
the Trap the what do you call it the the
Highwire high wire act that no that was
him and I think like people like Eddie
is are kind of tuned into that same
frequency because you can tell like like
especially in that like the going to the
movies bit he he was like okay this is
when I go into the list and then he just
you see his brain literally leap three
feet out of his head and he's just like
I'm going to come up with things on a
list you know it's like yeah you got
your popcorn your milk dge bag of
clothes you know your lobster thermador
your you know butterfly net you you know
and like and he just and he's going and
he and he comes right back to the movie
things so you don't even notice and and
that's like EDD Eddie isard sometimes
he'll go off on something and he's
coming up with the list and all of a
sudden there's toast and jam and
whatever the hell else before it comes
back to yeah but but he'll always but I
think Jonathan winer's probably had a
loose sketch of what he might do sure I
don't think he ever did it the same way
twice and that's what's so amazing is
like listening to these bits is you'll
hear people do stuff on albums and
they'll trip over themselves or have
little catches or whatever he you know
this is all coming stream of
Consciousness and there is not a lag
there's no filter it's going right from
his brain out of his mouth and it's
incredible
um I don't know he he would scan
everything and everything for its uh
potential for being personified
personification like you know oh little
bluebird you know and he would just
start messing with it and there is a
little bird here and it's like you know
tweet stole all its ideas from me
Twitter you know you can't see it but
and it is blue it's Robin's egg blue
it's ceramic that's real cute too bad if
something were to happen to
it thanks guys
yeah thank you for breaking I just broke
your bird you know I mean that's pure
John of the winers yeah yeah and what
what I was noticing too is just like if
you look if you were to try and break
this down if you felt like it the
premises are so so incredibly simple oh
yeah just to give himself so much room
to play well he would say you know he
demonstrate in like one minute 100
things you can do with a pen and pencil
like what they can become
mhm uh yeah those bits on there I
remember a lot of them and it it made me
think like that pretty much early on
before I uh before I put together things
M the way most people are supposed to
yeah you know like uh I can remember
like I have a hard time remembering
movies I remember certain parts of them
because that's what I fixated on right I
went to see
um I went to see the deep blue mhm that
beautiful film about the divers that
were going down so deep no one had ever
gone that without
equipment and they would just go you
know and uh this one guy fell in love
with a dolphin mhm and everything and I
didn't like pay a whole lot of attention
to the dialogue yeah you know what I was
doing was watching the sea and its
different forms and I got lost in it
yeah and so I'm watching this peripheral
corner of the movie and somebody how'd
you like it I said it was beautiful you
mean like the plot and the characters no
beautiful I was lost yeah the
ocean no and that makes perfect sense is
that that's where if you have that
certain type of brain that's just how
shit's going to work for you um did so
when you first starting doing comedy and
stuff were you at any point inspired
directly by Jonathan Winters or were you
just your own thing when you kind it had
a tendency to try to be that way cuz
when I prepared um written material mhm
it just wasn't funny okay and it wasn't
coming from me totally it was coming
from what I thought I should be doing
okay yeah yeah yeah you know and it it's
like there's a disconnect there sure you
want this unbroken pure connection your
mind your heart your body and your soul
mhm it should be like sort of joined up
and then it rings true to people yeah um
Louis CK you know I mean he couldn't
spend the rest of his life life
imitating George
Carlin no and he said it himself yeah
yeah and he did he did a great Carlin he
was doing his best Louis CK doing George
Carlin but he was never going to be as
good as Lis CK was going to be and it
was never going to be as good as
Carlin's going to be right and you'll
become a footnote to either one yourself
or him yeah the other
guy there I mean he even play he somehow
makes hey out of the lights go out twice
in this album and he just somehow he
gets a laugh both times the lights go
out of course yeah because he's dealing
with it and that's one of those things
that I saw and and you notice when
you're like a young comedian you're
stealing from people it's like the [ __ ]
that blows your mind is when you're like
wow this is just something that I know
is not planned or anything else and he's
got the audience still right or she's
gotten the audience right in their
pocket yeah and I mean and holding on to
it you know I watch Gregory Hines do it
once you know like and you see it in
bizarre places I went to go see um 12th
night Shakespeare in the park in New
York and Gregory Hines was playing feste
and all of a sudden the sound crapped up
and the sound went out and there was a
technical problem and all the lights
went and he had to riff as feste I mean
like he couldn't do it all on I am pamer
but he stayed in character for like
three and a half minutes very fertile
ground you got it but he went for it he
he went and he Dove right into the
audience first row I got rich New
Yorkers in the front row let's make fun
of these people awesome that's part
Panic mhm and that's how you
overcompensate for being mortified you
know and so I think I'll dive into the
front row and but he started with the
material what and give up Show Business
yeah you got it wrists and then he had
them and by the time it came back on he
just seamlessly went right back into the
lines and everybody gave him this giant
almost Standing Ovation you know and
because he never never let it drop well
see the thing about Jonathan witer is
something like that happened to him
happens to him and he doesn't have the
standard what to do if this happens or
that happens he wasn't his brain was not
concerned with those things right cuz
you know once you've set boundaries like
one night something or other is bound to
happen so I better be prepared with like
some
witty dialogue or something yeah uh Hey
I just made that up you know um it's
it's almost like most comedians had
something ready yeah like a
standard in Show Business was like the
Henny young man thing you know he's like
uh I solved the parking problem I bought
a parked car and if you heard a door
slam he'd go and stay out right of
course you know I mean but those were
like MH they knew exactly what to do
when little junk happened in a club yeah
you know broken glasses or whatever yeah
I feel like Jonathan Winters any of this
was an opportunity to play yeah anything
that happened yeah why do why do some
old hack need bit when there's a chance
to do something new in the moment why
because most people couldn't handle that
though that kind of [ __ ] pressure you
would think on somebody and I don't know
the specifics of his mental illness uh I
just know that that would kill me I
don't you talk about Robin Williams no
no just just Jonathan Winters like just
being able to I don't know you know
there's a common theme Here of all these
brilliant bastards uhhuh that's you know
I mean I could raise my hand mhm I
didn't have screwed up Rain waves where
I needed to kill people right luckily
you know or animals but but I mean I was
in my own way through no fall of my own
and it makes you behave certain ways and
a lot of it is destruction destructive
cuz somehow you don't think you're good
enough no matter what you can't hear
laughter when they're roaring and even
if it is laughter it's it's not even
given that thing where it's not not the
right kind of laugh yep but you know do
you know what I realized early early on
that even Robin
Williams uh would fall into these places
when you when you listen to and perform
where
he was he was um not confident in his
own stuff so he was Notorious because he
was sort of a fast forward Thief sure
sure he he claimed that he was so quick
that if he heard something that he
didn't know whether it was his or
someone else's he even stole the title
to his first album reality with a
concept that was some schlubs bit you
know that was all he had that was it and
he used to say you know Robin why and uh
Robin paid him of course of course yeah
I mean he paid him a lot of money sure
but but I mean uh that's that speaks
volumes about how even he was like
unsure if what he was doing was working
yeah yeah you know and that's a great uh
Temptation MH when you panic you know
you just grab some line see if you can
get a laugh but I was not like I said I
was never afraid to die sure yeah some
nights it would be like brilliant and
some nights it' be like going to hell on
a twisted metal Fireball
grease Pole to
Hell the best kind of comy do you know
are there just off the top of your head
are there any because he actually does
he actually even breaks down and talks
about Impressions on this which I think
is [ __ ] fantastic going from Walter
brenon to JFK is a really good bit like
just like you just have to do this and
it's [ __ ] fantastic well those were
the guys who were observant observant
enough to pick up and invent the
impression of someone in their time like
we always Carrie Grant never said Judy
Judy Judy but you know who did Larry
storage oh right right right yeah you
know Judy Judy Judy you know and that
was because the the rhythm of it would
commit you to the laugh just the pure
rhythm of
it and um and that it hit and it was the
way Carrie Grant would speak anyway
because it was almost like a getting gun
you know when I saw those two big
beautiful boobs I knew that I was in
trouble you know like declarative I was
just watching some like get hot and I'm
like I'm watching Tony Curtis I'm like
that is the worst impression I've ever
heard but he makes it work God damn it I
know well that's you could apply that to
cartoons too even a lousy impression of
somebody's a voice no one's ever heard
before exactly yeah you know so I'm not
afraid to do that like Nixon in Futurama
so great well that bastard drafted me in
1970 and um and they were stenciling my
name on the Foot Locker I in the draft
lottery I had number 30
I was going to go to
Vietnam so um so I went nutty and tried
to drink tons of sea water you know and
uh what else take a tablespoon of
linseed oil and give yourself a
temporary heart murmur none of that
worked but what did work was I had
hypertension already and I had the
flattest feet they would suck the floor
if I was there for you know they were
just flat and uh so I got out but
I mean that was that was harrowing
because I just got out of high school I
was playing in bands had a guitar
shaking my tush around you know in
Hispanic Hispanic pants and you know I
didn't even have any lines I didn't have
to pick up girls they would just be
right there in your face and I was a bad
boy I drank and did a little drugs you
know so I was cross addicted but for
some reason these girls wanted a
project they needed a project you know I
know I can you know it's like they think
they're
pigan you know and I was like this
smashed Elija D little
E I got a get S you
say um you know but
um but Nixon you know that whole thing
is I didn't have to go there and so
let's see cut to a million years in the
future you know to this very day in the
Nixon
Library on a complete um Loop MH is all
the [ __ ] that I did as Nixon on
Futurama really his
Library well they're redoing the the
whole Library that's F Oh They'll
probably take it out because I made
reference to it a million times told
what a bastard he was oh no I mean I'm
sure they'll love it cuz they're trying
to update it can I tell you why I did
that though most people just are like
why or just it's beautiful I don't know
maybe he did that or something but no he
never did that I saw the debate between
him and John F Kennedy in 19 what was it
60 is it 60 Jesus Christ yeah what about
on TV it was the first televised
presidential debate ever so it was kind
of significant and they had these
close-ups of Nixon like as close as they
could you can see his car is opening and
closing letting little fluid out and the
hair
that are inside of
them yeah it's like Rena sty gross
closeup oil panc of like his tooth or
you know so anyway here he is and he's
like I don't see why
I'm and while it was going on he was
sweating and his 5:00 shadow was coming
in like
2:15 and he was like I started to look
at him when I said to my mom mom he
looks like he's going to turn into a
werewolf
and so I I I sat there you know it's
like Larry tall but you know whatever
you do no matter what you hear keep the
door why do he sound like a southwest
Indian Mexican I think it was a thing
back then it's like it was good to sound
like you had crackers or cotton in your
mouth somehow I don't know why Church
Alfred Hitchcock I didn't know he was a
role model ass I have some sort of
impendence you now get to the annoyance
that interrupts all this art with what
they call the
commercial yeah I guess that made you
more important than you were you talk
like a
hamster but but um but I mean there it
was playing in the museum and um that's
great that's amazing but I mean I did
that because he really truly looked like
he was going to break out into like like
canob whatever you call you got it yeah
you know liuan he was very liuan towards
the end of the debate and I just thought
he was going my fellow
[Laughter]
American he would have got more votes
then the writers on the show wondered
why they said why do you do that that
aroo thing and he says don't don't I
mean don't ever stop because we love it
and we're looking for ways to just put
it in everywhere but they also followed
suit with version of agnu who had no
head but could still
go one of my favorite futureama bits the
headless body of agnu which is just I
think it's bril it is it is there was so
much that you could comment on in that
show it was everything and anything I
ever dreamed of being part of on every
level mhm as a matter of
fact somebody said what's it like you
know to just like hear your voice coming
out of everywhere on TV and radios and I
said it's surreal and the problem with
it is
um I have to pretend it wasn't me that
did it otherwise I'll rip myself to
shreds yeah with self-critique yeah you
know if I hear it it's like a lot of
times I don't go back and listen to
stuff that I did if it's like radio
interviews or even this you know it's
like I don't revisit it that willingly
because because I'll you know what it is
I got a heart and a soul see and and if
I say stuff that is just like makes
makes me get the do chills you know it's
like why did you say that um I I can't
stand it yeah and I I would have I would
have done it like this or I would have
said that you know you never it never
clicks off you have to just live with it
you compartmentalize you pretend you had
nothing to do with it yeah yeah and the
worst part is is you know when you don't
even have say over which edit or which
take they're going to use like even if
you did a great job or think you did
you're like why they use that take damn
it well that's that's you know the
people that you know just have something
in them that that you drive yourself to
become what you think is a superlative
and nothing less you won't settle for
anything less in yourself yeah and a lot
of people just can't let that go a lot
of history all through this territory uh
my family made it as far as the high
river and just
quit and uh chickened out a bear
attacked uh one of my ancestors and you
know and that sto that would stop you
let's face it you know made us turn back
for some more grits and uh some more
mini balls and things like
C and uh that's what I my my grandfather
told me they just quit there you know
didn't get as far as St Louis as just
bear attacked the wagon and everybody
went let's quit let's quit
and so they went back
in every time I see a bear I quit you
know I saw Smokey the Bear one time
light at forest fire that was the wild
sing I Smokey B whole thing went up you
didn't have a scout hat on either but he
was he was in the
nude you always you know they clean it
up for the kids on television put them
in
suits Bo I'm telling you if you see one
of them in suits in the Yellowstone look
out it's like I met Al Lewis Grandpa
monster yeah met him a long long time
ago and I have I've had dinner with him
I hung out with them and everything I
think I have a menu from his original
restaurant Grandpa's restante you got it
in in New York yeah yeah say it right if
you're going to say it restante yeah
yeah
yeah yeah it's not pasta
Miss but I was in his restaurant one
time and he was there and I was eating
and it was delicious there was only a
few people in there there was like a
young couple with their little daughter
and there a couple of Bitties from like
the Midwest and they're just wrapping up
and and they go we just wanted to say
thank you this meal was so great and
we're going to and he's like yeah yeah
yeah and they're on their way out and
then they keep ramping up you know it's
like yeah he's okay yeah yeah goodbye
now thank you and it's like oh and we're
g to you know and blah blah blah she
kept like augmenting like ramping up
again like someone does to you on the
phone they can't hear you squirming
trying to say goodbye I'm trying to wrap
it up yeah trying to wrap it up somebody
ramps up again so so these women were
sort of very you know they didn't mean
to they had hearts of gold I'm sure the
both of them but he's going yeah yeah
thank you okay thank you and it's like
bye bye door closes and he goes drop
dead he was very
sardonic but he had a heart of gold
himself that whole exterior was just
what you think it was for sure probably
protect his own sensitivity oh yeah but
he told me he never watched the monsters
really he said he never looked back and
watched the monsters mhm you know
besides it wasn't out of vanity or or he
was just uh too afraid to to see it and
hear it he went on to become an NBA
talent
scout right around that time that's
interesting and he discovered little Lou
elinder oh my God you know Kareem Abdul
Jabar yeah he is an NBA talent scout I
know that that's crazy I know and you
know he was of height to play basketball
he always looked like this little well
no that was just him next to um Fred
Quinn yeah Al was a six-footer yeah wow
you know and I said Grandpa what's the
secret of life you know he was about 94
what's the secret of life if anybody
knows you do and he goes here here well
and he says you got to do what you love
and love what you do yeah
yeah he's laughing
and uh I just learned so much from guys
like that I me to me they're like these
missing one of the world they're the
missing link to like our past in Show
Business and comedy yeah yeah I hate
that I don't have a link to Vaudeville
that I don't have any direct link to
Vaudeville in what way to interview like
somebody I could plop down there're a
couple hundred-year old guys who might
have an idea what the [ __ ] I'm talking
about you know well I know but anybody
who participated got to be long gone of
course I know but I I want something
with somebody's son Somebody's Daughter
oh yeah what's that gu name Freddy
Jessel yeah right yeah or Harpo's
son oh yeah well adopted he doesn't
count that's a joke I'm kidding no they
weren't all adopted locco Mark they
weren't all local marks yeah there was
so many marks Brothers you don't even
know about G Gamo zeppo those were the
zeppo
yeah just on the stage right gumo was
just on the stage correct yeah I don't
even think gumo did much on the stage no
I think he left way before they ever had
a career movie Zeo was in the first
movies that's when there were the for
Mar yeah but you know it's like couple
of the apples fell real far from the
original tree you know not all of them
land right in that Orchard some of them
do a cartoon turn in midair you know
fall into another Orchard yeah fall on
the back of a turtle and go off
somewhere but those three drove
everybody nuts oh they made it and was
like their little private playground
batting people around like toy mice when
they were boys yeah yeah and their mom
encouraged it oh yeah part Margaret
Duman had a restraining order against
them CU they used to go to her house and
just like do donuts on or lawn or move
things around so she was like I you
might have to explain Donuts yeah yeah
exactly well donut is um when you get a
car and you just decide to keep your
foot on the brake and all the way down
on the gas and let it go and turn the
wheel all the way to the right or the
left circles I'm going to the air and
ruin my tires yeah you got it hilarious
so yeah they used to do it on her lawn
apparently why though because you just
said it cuz they were sons of [ __ ]
apparently they used to show up to like
they would show up on set two hours late
you know like grou would show up first
it' be two hours or he would show up two
hours late then they would wait another
45 minutes then Harpo would show up then
45 minutes later they get tired of
waiting for Cho and the first two would
leave then Cho would show up so be half
a day before anybody was actually all
together to shoot anything smelling like
sex and God knows and gambling yeah
three different kinds of perfumes oh
100% well that's what Al Lewis told me
about Joe E Ross did you ever read about
him no I only know a little bit about
him there's a there's a website and you
got to find it it's called um uh it's
like he was the biggest slob really in
the world and uh and it's something to
do with that but I I wish I had the name
so you could just look read about this
guy and I asked Al Lewis I said hey Al
you know innocently because I just
didn't know what was Joe E Ross like he
was um you know Gunther
toty uh on car 54 yeah which is like a
brilliant brilliant show was on Bilco
and he was on Bilco um both Nat hike and
scripts yeah yeah yeah and Al Lewis told
me there was nothing like a Nat hike and
script let me tell you oh yeah yeah and
uh and I said what was Joey Ross like
and he said just as dumb as he
looked I'm dying I'm dying because I
know
exactly cuz he couldn't remember his
lines Nat he drove Nat heik into a heart
attack what it says in the article that
that he tried so hard and he and he
wrote all these beautiful lines and Joey
Ross couldn't get through it so he had
this like like someone stuck him in the
ass with a pin look on his face all the
time
[Music]
like [ __ ] and of course it worked better
than hiken could have ever dreamed of
course but the guy was so handson this
was his baby so was bco and and Joey
Ross was like a slob and he'd have
hookers in the dressing room he Mar
married the eighth
hooker and I said what was he like Al
and he goes he married
hookers oh my God yeah he didn't even
tell me the half of it I only got like
so far with him and I read this article
and I was like going oh my God
incredible oh my God
like I know I'm I'm supposed to make
this about probably me or something but
no this is what this is the good stuff
this we've talked about Jonathan
Winter's what's your name fry I guess
yes um no I don't know who I am but but
I but I just read this article so I'm so
like in the moment something that
happened last night and it said that
that one thing that almost killed
everybody was that there were on the set
the sponsors wanted to visit the set you
know they were all excited they got the
show and everything God and um they went
stopped by to see D Joey
Ross and the door was a little bit open
and someone came in and they said all
you could hear was screaming in the
hallway and people like getting out of
there as fast as they could he was
masturbating [ __ ] sponsor I mean that's
what you live and die by people jump off
buildings over stuff like
that
God I
was was it good for
me oh wow I love those stories Jesus
Christ but you know that's the junk that
that's the Grist for the mill it is and
like unfortunately and here's like the
sad part it's like like that's great
Hollywood lore but like where are all
the great stories about Sid Caesar and
your show shows and there are there are
great but thank
God um oh my Calypso players wait wait
wait wait so that was dud that bit just
lied in the ditch and died I didn't even
get you saying I paused it before you
did the funny the funny voice
unfortunately so what's the matter with
you you know supposed to keep everything
it's none of my business what if it was
what if somebody died I don't know you
are you an alcoholic X none or something
I am I no issues I as OCD as we were
talking about earlier I am uh yeah 100%
that's no no I know it's just it you
don't want you didn't want to screw up
your product and yeah yeah well no I
don't indulging me it's like hey man he
might uh throw a gutter ball you know I
got to watch out for him I don't even
know him worried about ruining this heed
me
you know there's a real quick bit on
here and I don't mean to derail us
actually no actually it's not because I
know I'm I'm rerailing rerailing exactly
there is one bit his voice where he's
doing the it would be an offensive bit
but it's not cuz he's making fun of
movies where he does this native Chief
and it sounds exactly like every Frank
Welker old man voice that I've ever
heard and it's really makes me wonder if
I just wonder if that that could just be
frank Welker's natural thing that he
does but just coming from that bit you
know that coming from the back of the
throat everything comes from somewhere
everything including Jonathan
wyers he was exposed to that somewhere
mm yeah and he says it I mean almost
everything he bites off of he's like oh
it's like so and so or this guy or this
person and he does this weird hybrid
cultural references and but but he put
it in his own blender and like there's
nothing more unfunny than like an
impressionist doing dead on Impressions
right with no invention yeah you know or
uh you know Jack Nicholson uh you know
buying corn in a grocery store it might
sound something like this you know and
it's like oh prepare for all the oxygen
to be sucked out of the
room you know and Impressions I mean
give me one beatus Arthur for every
Christopher walking you know give me oh
God right yeah
right um Walter I'm going to wrap my
legs around your head like a cheap
turban ma blanch
we had her on Futurama did you she was
theu holy [ __ ] right duh she was with us
oh God [ __ ] did she did a piece of
acting that brought tears to my eyes
with one word that's how good Miss beus
Arthur was yeah she uh was the fter and
they exposed her for what she was and
why did she do all these things to
everybody for what end and she looked
like she was the machine looked L like
it was going to cry it probably had two
like dodes or things that look sort of
like eyes and and she just she looked up
and went why like she was going to cry
and then she snapped and turned on them
but but it was like it was so heartfelt
yeah it was just so it rang true with me
she's amazing yeah and I'm real
sensitive to that stuff great acting and
I mean be Arthur Jesus that's [ __ ]
fantastic I mean like even like the
little St you know you can talk about
Golden Girls you can go back earlier
even her stupid bit in the history of
the World Part One right you know like
it's great you know it's just so
perfectly her and you know like in M
she's better than Lu ball she the best
thing in it she's just amazing she could
do anything I mean like her her sense of
humor was so specific and so evolved and
dead on all the time yeah is amazing
dude Futurama I have to imagine it
facilitated you meeting some of your
heroes or am I wrong am I un crack for
imagining
um well Pam
Anderson you know what and we're
done no no you know what no I I I had to
turn that into something because
everybody even the geek guys were like
Los especially the geek guys yeah like
hi my God hi and when she came to do the
show we're in the recording studio and
I'm like looking around there's all this
like Ruckus going on it's like Miss
Anderson just came in the front door you
know uh swordfish to land shark this is
you know Miss Anderson is about to enter
the recording studio and okay okay
popping circumstance and she didn't walk
in imperious or anything like like
you're supposed to kiss or ring or
genuflect or avert your eyes she sits
down right next to me and nobody was
saying anything and I just looked at her
and I said Miss Anderson um I don't know
if you know this or not but there's this
tape going
around and everybody's looking at me
like what is he doing you what do you
got Tourette you can't you have to say
something always but the thing was is
she cracked up laughing how she did of
course she did cracked up laugh she was
married to rocker Tommy Lee otherwise
see that separates him from every other
Tommy Lee in the phone book rocker Tommy
it's the obligatory POS instant
identification of who or what the hell
he is yeah it's like yeah well you had
to say like rocker Tommy Lee otherwise
you're like that nice Asian boy who
lives down the street Tom Lee right
they're so nice no no the other guy that
looks like the Tabasco devil oh oh
rocker Tommy Lee yeah all rockers have
that picture in they bring it to yeah
they bring it to the uh the barber here
and they show them a picture of the
Tobasco devil I want this and nothing
less or I will beat you senseless
I many patches of skin in in the beard
as cheesy pirate look you know nothing
says party like that cheeso pirate look
Captain
Morgan yeah bring a picture of Captain
Morgan to the buan or your makeup artist
you know what a great thing to say to
her man I would have loved to have done
that just to just for her to start
laughing and go it's like so you know
this this Kim Kardashian then huh you
heard of her yeah I don't know I think
she probably be really big I don't know
who knows nowadays Drew Barrymore mhm
came in to do Olive the Other Reindeer
that was a uh MC raining production MH
yeah and Joe pants of course of course
yeah that's cool good you know I was
talking to him about getting divorced
and he says instantly he's in sense and
he goes Billy stay
married stay married you can do whatever
you want you know but in other words
from personal experience he probably got
wiped out of pocket maybe a few times
well that's why uh I was doing a U I did
a pilot reading uh number of months ago
that something that John C had uh uh
helped write and all the people who are
working on it [ __ ] right so John is well
I wish I could have you know met him too
that would have been neat but they were
just like oh John C is working on a
pilot and and of course like the three
other guys in the group are like yeah
well he's getting divorced again so he
needs to make some money just like like
there I was like oh so every time I see
him doing something like yeah he's
getting well look at Shatner you know
doing game shows and promise margerine
commercials I promise do e promise
marger you know everybody's got to
everybody's got to wear the dog suit you
know at some point I did yeah when I
worked in radio they said we got to have
our mascot go down to the record store
and promote the station and it's like
they got this Fleet bit and dog suit and
I said all right you know and I go in
and you got to wear the dog suit you got
I'm sorry it's very hard to avoid that
hey as I look
down um I noticed that I'm having nipple
erections little cold well would you
like me to turn it off no Throw Another
Log in the air conditioner I'm an all
the way guy you know I don't go halfway
I want it to the
extreme we're going to cut glass with
nipples later on you can stare at those
two things all you want and you're not
going to see any milk or any semblance
of
it only a dream until now
milk it's easier to get to than some
other
Pantages did I say that
no just I deserve to be just
khaul by Tommy Lee the pirate I just
found out what that was I didn't realize
what ke Hall was you know it's one of
those things like as you know an
American I live in a city like I grew up
in New York it's like you can make a na
or a farm term and I'm like that's cute
what is that something with ducks I
don't know no you know what it is and I
now know what it is they R you by the
foot you're you're attached you're
tethered and they push you off the front
of the boat front of the boat you get
one guy on each side and they run you
along the bottom along all the Barnacles
and everything until you come up the
back and if you live they would haul you
back they do and then try it again
because maybe your number was going to
be up this time couldn't believe like
that is see that's the thing we're doing
the right thing now by explaining what
all this [ __ ] means it's education yeah
because I mean the older I got I if I
was with like a younger girl or
something I always felt like a curator
in a museum you know like I'd always has
to preface everything I said was uh you
know a long time ago like before you
were born there used to be this group
you know and they were real cool and I
dug them
man you know and I'm not supposed to
know well at the time it was limp Biz
kid you ever listen to limp Biz kid oh I
regret that I have
not you know no it's fine I mean those
guys [ __ ] I was I mean I was already in
and out of bands when those guys were
sitting in their own [ __ ] so it's like
it's hard for me to have any holy
reverence for anybody uhhuh yeah yeah
except I do no good when I see it like
in in young people yeah you know the
ones that aren't the fakers we go back
to that theme of like you know a lot of
people don't know the difference sure
but gez I mean every now and then you'll
see an old soul pop up like Amy win
housee right you you get to see yeah
younger people I said how does she have
this wisdom and in her voice and all
these years in her
voice um because it's the real deal mhm
um it's like Adele same thing first time
I heard her I was like is this some
africanamerican woman from Chicago where
she from yeah but when you saw her you
didn't say anything about her weight or
anything to be honest with you I was
amazed one she wasn't from the United
States and two that she wasn't black
those those two I didn't those are the
real reasons why you should like
somebody well I mean like hon no not cuz
they're not black but I mean but a lot
of guys no one should like anyone if
they're not black well okay well I'm
part black wait there it is I'm a
millionth black is you can see this
little mole here on my stomach my
distended
stomach uh no I mean she um is
incredible yeah the thing is there's a
lot of guys that'll be like you know you
know fat pig who cares no I know but
there are many many guys that do that
especially like look on the internet you
want to talk about those horrible trolls
and all those people making those
dumbass comments oh yeah that you got
that is the worst oh yeah the worst
they're garbage humans well they were
they were born bored yeah you know and
that's their hell to live in that's your
last laugh over you know about all these
imbeciles is that they're born bored
they just spend their whole life with
their mouth hanging open waiting for the
next big thing that they can denigrate
keep in mind that I haven't planted
anybody out there any magician you know
that kind of
stuff there might there might not be any
message at all or certainly any payoff
but it'll be
live this is uh you
know back East we have what we call the
ivy leager I'm sure you see him I wear
Ivy leak suits I also have some Robert
Hall
pants I have a saxs overcoat abrami and
Fitch tie and so I try to you know split
it up a little bit for
everybody but this Ivy leager I've never
I don't know uh exactly where he comes
from he's a strange breed whether he is
uh was born oh like
failed it's all over friends
the sun went out
um not too far from Grace Cathedral am I
well I'll cut across and say a few
before I
go well those episcopalians need help
and I'm one of
them you know what that is an
Episcopalian that's a Catholic that
flunked his
laddin but it's a minority group don't
knock it too hard you know crazy that I
would ever have and I do it a lot and I
probably annoy my friends online but
like I speak out a lot about people who
are [ __ ] to people because they've
got as much privilege as you can
possibly have and then the internet
compounds that privilege you know and
it's it's just [ __ ] upsetting when
it's just like there's Talent there's
Talent there's people yeah but the thing
that bothers me is I grew up and I was a
young
man and I was you know I experienced the
feminist movement at its beginnings
and I actually before I graduated from
high school and this is the truth I'm
not you know wearing my heart on my
sleeve or be a feminist feminist Hustler
or anything like that but I read the
female unic by J Germaine Greer I read
the women's room by um Marilyn French
these were all feminists that were
writing and they were angry they were
pissed off the only one who wasn't was
Germaine Greer she loved men but she had
a lot of she felt that they were in sore
need of Rehabilitation yeah which is you
know hey you know what that means that
you think there's hope sure you know and
uh so I read all these things because I
wanted to understand why when I when I
was raised I was raised old school I'm a
gentleman I was raised by a woman um I
I'm evolved I get it I leave the seat
down you know the works yep you know I
would stand if a woman entered the room
at a table in a dining room or if I I
would stand if she had to leave for a
minute sure you know and and I would
hold the doors and you know it's good
for me it's a good thing for me that I
don't look like
Meatloaf I mean at my I'm 63 years old
are you talking about the food or the
singer well he was one on the same I
know was close one had slightly more
hair well meatloaf is a product of
itself I think but um but you know I
would hold the doors and I would be
going out with a young girl what I'm
saying is that I you know not when I was
63 I'm 63 now but like 10 15 years ago I
could still go out with young girls but
they were Hollow victories you know what
I mean and they didn't it wasn't because
I told him who I was or what I did you
know that was just like does that even
really matter so uh so I hold the door
and the girl would be there in shock
like looking at me suspiciously like
what are you doing I'm holding the door
for
you why you know and then it it it
occurred to me that most young guys are
into this whole m misogyny thing just to
just to rub it in yeah you know and I
was appalled don't that that [ __ ]
doesn't play with me it never did yeah
you know and so now it's really funny to
do rape jokes and everything and it's
like you know I I
just I don't want to live on this planet
anymore [ __ ] uh there's a that's one of
my favorite memes actually that it's
Farnsworth and that one and all you have
to do is will put up any horrible
atrocity so one picture of it and then
put that one at the bottom and I go yep
it you got it yeah but you know I mean
uh but I do know the good stuff when I
see it let's see we can talk about new
stuff Taylor
Swift yeah Katie
Perry I was a Veronica guy you know like
what when I read RG comments I was a
Veronica guy number one I love trouble y
sure tlor Swift is like secret covert
trouble like the evil little girl
that'll pee in your plants you know
after you go to
sleep but Katie Perry is feral yeah
she's feral you know got balls and uh
and she's really great I think she's
brilliant that's the stuff that I you
know I think Taylor Swift is very super
clever and great too yeah she's got a
lot going on yeah but I mean to me
they're Throwbacks yeah you know the old
soul thing mm is where did you get this
from coming up in the day and age you
did with all the cultural references
that you were swimming in yeah of now
yeah yeah in terms of Comedy or shows is
there something that sticks out to you
in the same way nowadays
yeah you know this may may not break
your heart but I stopped watching TV in
the
80s no it's probably a smart thing it's
no seriously I did number one I was a
Coke addict and I didn't have a TV there
you go but if you look way high up here
it's still up there in the corner of the
sinus somewhere dad's iron long Ed he
live oh dad you know but but um but you
are a music guy I'm trying to think
what's funny um Key and Peele oh [ __ ]
yeah I love them man I mean it's like
it's it's Little Britain one more it's
11 I mean not to be like judgmental or
or like snoody about it no ke and Peele
I mean it's just like thank God where do
these people come from usually Britain
yeah right right you know why because
it's not about crassness mhm over there
they they do have I mean like they do
have their fair amount of you know like
their toilet humor but I don't think
they need to rely on it or for you they
need to rely as much as American a seems
victimless for the most part sure sure
sure I always love that stuff yeah even
though I'm a mean bad Moulder MH you
know but I try to keep a lid on
it like Courtney Love everywhere
Courtney Love in my face and everything
and it said I want that in my face as
much as I want a dirty soil
diaper which is what she looks like and
I think she she like had people
deliberately make her look like that mhm
mhm yeah sorry about that that's all
right I really do enjoy the fact that
your first album was written entirely by
what's his name with the hole in his
head
oh that's where they got the name for
Kur
Kaboom apparently the new documentary
about him is supposed to be quite good
which one really there's two of them out
so which one oh one's called Soaked in
Bleach which is actually not the lyric
by the way no no the other one okay the
not that one the other one really good
and it's it's uh culminating a lot of
stuff and it's not nice to anybody
writing doll Parts you know yeah
apparently got how do I how would I know
that how do I know that why do I even
know that I don't know can you imagine
to know you guys you guys will
appreciate this cuz you think I believe
you think like this is um you know
there's always like you always grow old
no matter what you try to do and in
Futurama it's fsw said you know gravity
makes Chumps of us
all and uh it's true but you're going to
be in a nursing home or Assisted Living
someday it's just a fact of life as long
as it's got a a high I'll be good yeah
you know well and every Thursday night
you know it's like piano night you know
and they have someone come in and play
that generation's favorite song like P
got your troubles in your own KAG and
smile darn you
smile that's what they would play and
everybody would like relive it and come
to life sure I mean I said this
generation of like self-pitying white
people the emot you know types or you
know it's like uh these guys that sing
about like I want to be dead and all
this you know it's like you know then
why don't you just like invent crack
addicted mother you know jokes or or
songs that have about babies being born
in a
dumpster you know and you're
crying about what you even had to do
black lipstick on your lower lip I mean
how effective how affected is that you
know it's like the guy the white guy
that comes from money with his head in
his hand like looking downward like
should I kill myself today this evening
and uh and
so I was like thinking about all this
stuff and and like there's so many
followers they're going to be old too
all the kids that listen to that stuff
and they're going to be in the nursing
home on piano night and some old guy's
going to come in and pull out the song
book he be like um I am in pain thing
somebody kill me come on
sing you know and they're all sitting
there I am doll
Parts I think Eddie Murphy did it did
the said that once in his bit it just
like what's GNA happen like when our
generation gets old and we're all
sitting around in the nursing home like
reminiscing go like oh man your mother
could sure do the butt you know it's
like dou yeah exactly um you know what I
never I never heard that bit but that's
what I kept thinking thinking about is
like that's what happens to new music it
becomes ancient music and yet there are
still people that that was their frame
of reference that was their Touchstone
or like wouldn't that be one of the
things to put Kiran over the edge like
you know like you think you're writing
something that's you know personal and
and emotive and you to misconnect with
somebody and all of a sudden you get in
you know the elevator at the record
company and there's a musac version of
the thing that you wrote you know and
you got to listen to it going all the
way up you know going really this is
what we went with here okay I'm worried
I'm going to get played out by chumba
WBA I'm I'm really worried that on my
last breath that shit's going to be
playing in the background it'll be
totally worth it yeah I get what do you
want what do you want played that your
just seriously just thinking about that
that's exactly I think about it all the
time rivers to cross I know it's really
stereotypical but I love Jamaican music
and I think it's gorgeous I'm half
tempted to make it music comedy that's
insane it's not insane no no no I'm
trying to think of something like
something fun like for me I think it
would be comedy though me the emperor's
theme you know from Star Wars just
looped over and over again until all the
Flames have died down I want that a
little uh imperious and po probably I
want a comedy song yeah but a good
comedy I want to have you know what I
want you can just you know if you if you
can find this I suggest you just put it
on this podcast it's um the Portsmouth
Symphonia okay version of
also uhhuh where they all switch
instruments yeah they're perfectly
capable musicians but they they're
playing sheet music with other people's
instruments everybody in the orchestra
went to another scene on something that
they were at least knew how to play and
they play it and that's so funny cuz I
did I I directed um uh the Inspector
General did and my opening bit was they
were all in Tableau Frozen everybody in
the end Tableau at the beginning of the
thing and then we had the curtain slowly
rise to that piece so it went
[Music]
[Applause]
and and the Cur is roing so slowly you
can kind of see what's happening the
clarinetes it's all off it's like The
Little Rascals this frantic little
clarinet that was catching up with them
as they were going downhill
like holy [ __ ] it is brilliant brilliant
piece of music and it took a about it
took the whole piece to raise the
curtain and I did that thing would like
raise it a little bit then a little bit
more then bring it down bit that's great
that you did that it was and the
audience loved it they love the piece of
music and just the the visual that went
that's the stuff I live for it was so
much I love that piece that's awesome
wow yeah I need to hear that so that so
my frame of references is pretty much
like the time that the Wonder Years for
me was kind of like when that album came
out I saw Atlantis the Lost Continent by
George pal I went and saw The Time
Machine like four times Rod Taylor it
was made in 60 I think it was released
in 61 okay and uh so good yeah I mean
but that's the stuff that my head was
filled with and before I went to school
we talked about before I went to school
every morning they showed the three
stoes so I had no use or room for
Academia I had a head full of this stuff
but you know what it was it served me
better in life than anything I learned
in school because anything I was forced
to learn in grammar school kindergarten
grade school high school school would
have no practical application in the
year 2015 yeah it just wouldn't so I
might as well have never gone to school
I was right I you know I just wanted to
to listen to the Stooges to the point
where I couldn't enjoy them anymore so I
began to look for stuff in the corners
of the picture to obsess on and it was
Larry chewing up scenery so the little
that he said was just like Sublime to me
be careful Mo you know and just add and
everybody could do Mo and curly but no
gave a damn about lar hey Mo there's too
much Tinsel in the
tree which is where Stimson J cat came
from and I was actually I remember
seeing the first episode of Ren and
Stimpy uh when they released it I was I
was in high school and I was obsessed
with any new cartoons especially if they
came out on Nick because Nick was doing
stuff that no one else Saturday morning
got it I mean not Saturday morning
Sunday morning they wanted to do
everything network television was not
doing exactly and I and me and my
brother were 100% on board we watched
everything they ever did and I remember
when Ren snippy came on the first time
we sat there me and my brother with our
mouths a gate like somebody how old were
you oh I must have been I mean it could
have been like 15be you little Dickens
you you look okay to me thank you you
turned out like some noral what year did
Premiere it was close to that 89 90ish
my
91 perfect timing that I did I started
doing them in ' 91 okay dog and uh R
stpy yeah I'll remember seeing it and I
remember going to school the next day
like like this with my head looking and
every like who saw it do you see
it that's that desperation that I had
when I was a kid I'd go to school the
next day and did you see did you see
that thing on TV last night and they go
no I didn't let me let me do it for you
let me show so you had to recreate it so
that you could hang on to the the uh the
dynamic the thing that made you crazy
you wanted to with everybody and I was
thrilled because there was one girl who
had seen it Kathy U I'll never forget
she had seen it and the two of us for
about a half an hour before school even
started GE geeked out and I had her yeah
we were amazed and I remember I we were
talking and she was like I just love the
voices and I was like yeah it was so
nice to hear Larry again and and she
went what are you talking about I'm like
Three Stooges Larry and she went she
picked right up on that awesome well I
mean again I was I was my my dad was
showing me Mark Brothers Three Stooges
Abid and Costello WC Fields Harry langon
Harold Lloyd Buster Keaton you know
Charlie Chaplain since I was three so by
the time I got to 16 my lexicon of like
things that I could grab on to was
bigger than most didn't that serve you
like a zillion times better than
learning what the pedmont was and what
is silt still have no idea what any of
that crap is yeah my test question what
is silt yeah thank you no no idea I can
tell you 100% it served him cuz he's one
of the funniest [ __ ] I've ever
met only person I can talk to about most
of this [ __ ] about old comedy this this
[ __ ] you I I I got to appreciate
thank Christ oh now we
friends I was waiting I was waiting just
to find out if I actually like friends
now but know it's the truth like that
was the stuff you know so good stuff
like that used to make me just sit there
and and just con your stuff that album
cover yeah cuz I had my my imagin we're
looking at um from another world world
with this almost like a scream Queen
except she she uh I don't know it's
hypnotic and there's the spiral on
everything stuff like that used to make
I us to go I used to go my dream
girl you know I was like we were at a
session once me and cre Summer Frank
she's a voiceover you know who she is
and Jess harnell the great Jess and
we're sitting there and um C got a
fashion magazine European fashion
magazine until it's time to do something
I just kind of stay there because I'm
paranoid that that if if I get caught
with my pants down I'll die not ready
sure you know but these guys are Pros
you know so she's reading this thing and
I look over and it's a it's a pull out
like a fold out page and all I see is
these Arabic madeup eyes with like a
facial The Veil The Veil mhm and I'm
looking at had it and I I'm fascinated
I'm I'm instantly attracted to those
things and she pulls it down and she's
got these meny tattoos and I was going
oh wow I I don't even know if I know
what that is those are those Hannah
tattoos yeah indan yeah and then she's
got a gun in her hand pointing it at you
Fu and I said my dream
girl I love trouble I guess I just do I
don't know it's it's like that great
line from uh Annie Hall where is you
know like you know when I was a kid all
the kids fell in love with Snow White I
instantly fell in love with the wicked
Queen you know yeah yes oh when I saw
black Sunday uh in 1961 see these are
the references I keep throwing out 62 60
61 late
50s um I saw the movie Black Sunday
great book too which was a um it was a
dubbed film it was I think it was
Spanish okay was it Mario Bava oh that
black Sunday or was it Italian oh my God
I don't know the one with Barbara steel
yeah oh my God you know I'm sitting in
the theater and I have I'm having
arousals for Barbara
steel not when she was like alive before
she was put to death but they had a mask
that had all internal spikes that face
towards the face when they put it on
your face and then they would take a
hammer and you know and that would put
the death of vampire well she comes back
and she is is stunningly beautiful with
call rimmed eyes you know and everything
and there's something so unearthly about
her and I'm getting
aroused you know I don't I'm not sure
why because maybe it was cuz it was
dangerous you know I was an abused kid
and so you know I want repetition
compulsion especially from a beautiful
woman and uh I I I have to say it that
way I'll cry no really it's tragic but
um but anyway here she is and then this
doctor comes in and he's just looking
around he runs into her and she's got
him in her tractor beam suddenly there's
nothing he can do and I'm getting like
really aroused you know and uh and all
of a sudden he pulls off he pushes her
and holds on to her and she's all like
dead bodied you know like rib cage and
leather guts and justay everything and I
was basically going you know why can't I
meet
that you know because I was so into
monsters as you know I was turned off by
people just cuz of what was going on
sure and uh monsters were like the thing
that made me feel like I was alive
inside feeling scared was better than
feeling nothing yeah yeah you know so I
so I uh you know I I uh I hung my
identity on all the things that made me
crazy when I was a kid but I did I F
mathematics all the way through school
and that scene where you're a dummy and
that I was surrounded by brilliant kids
who wanted to skip seven grades you know
and said now we have to sit here for
this you
know and then they say John wers go to
the board problem number six my God I
didn't know the first one 11 know six
you know and you go up there eraser and
the chalk breaks and now they
go there's the dummy
again
boy and one guy bugged me one day he
said boy how dumb can you be and I said
well I'm going to cold coock you when I
get out
there recess time I wrapped Awin around
him
[Applause]
twice Robert B was my idol I had no
blueprint for design I had no male role
models so to see this guy in a tuxedo
and a gunun and a go car and these
beautiful European InterContinental
women you know I said that that's kind
of I wish I could be that that's that's
my guy you know it was he was my dad
yeah but uh yeah same reference points
yeah from that time and now they're
making a new man from Uncle movie saw
that I don't know what to think about I
mean there's certain times where I was
like I know what the Man from Uncle was
even though I wasn't a big fan because
it was before my time really but I like
I know what it is and I've seen show of
its time on television I'm just worrying
like when you try to reboot something
like that I mean is is a younger
audience who they're obviously skewing
it for even going to give a damn I mean
they'll give a damn if it's flashy
enough cuz to them it's brand new it's
flashy enough yeah I mean is it
basically going to be like the American
Kingsmen is that what they're trying to
do because if they do that it might make
a ton of money sure that's what it looks
like too well it's like the reboot of
The Untouchables I mean same characters
but it was in no way like the 50s TV
show which I also used to love yeah one
of my favorite songs in the world was
written by Nelson riddle and it's the
themed to The Untouchables M that that
big you know you can look at the album
cover and they show all these shadowy
figure in the dark big city looming and
these guys had hats on and they were all
like looking around and you hear this
big theme that portrays that like you
know there's a lot of dangerous dudes
out there meanwhile they had no idea
that in the
future all the little angry dudes that
are on the internet and and just roaming
around out there angry angry or or make
those guys look like gentlemen the truth
you know what I mean they wouldn't kill
anybody if it didn't have anything to do
with your business right yeah yeah you
know and now it's like you know
demonstrating once again that man is the
only animal that kills for the sheer
enjoyment of it except the age group is
lowered yeah right I sound so gloom and
doom no no I think I do I do have faith
in a lot of things sure but it still
sounds like it's coming out of when I
see you guys I go look at these guys you
know it's like they're not sitting there
with their thumb and their nose waiting
for me to do everything you know you
guys are live wires you're Cur you have
intellectual curiosity well yeah I mean
you know in this world what else is
there you know no but I appreciate it
you know yeah I really do you know I
want I want to make sure I bring up
because I'm curious do you know remember
what the spec the the [ __ ] my brain is
just off the Three Stooges cuz I'm just
I'm sorry I'm just my brain's not
working uh this three stes record do you
remember what it was like was it a song
was it a bit like had to have been songs
right it was um they were songs they
were mixed with little bits yeah it was
very like a 45 or an LP I'm sorry you
said it was one of those little like
yellow they made those little records
and they came in a sleeve like a 45
except that it had a 33 and a third hole
on it oh okay yeah yeah so um it was
like molan Curly probably in' 61 is
everything else I'm talking about and uh
they would go going into a studio and it
was this crappy little band you know a
Glock and Spiel a snare drum and and an
Oregon or something yeah that was it and
me I did a send up of all those records
once really it's a it's a record called
Christmas party with Eddie G I saw that
listed somewhere the other day cuz I was
looking to see if you'd done any comedy
out you should throw some of my version
of 12 Days okay me and Eddie gordetsky
Eddie G was we were friends 30 years ago
we were two bums in radio you know
dreaming about what it's like to be the
man what must it be like you know we
were high as rats sitting in back at the
radio station on our break and I said
what what must it be like to be the guy
you know we're sitting there meanwhile
one of us knows because he's the guy he
produces almost every major comedy show
on television Jesus Christ with Chuck
Lori yeah okay oh yeah he created Mom
that's his show uh I don't know if he
solely created it but Chuck was involved
but I mean that's that's Eddie show
really yeah one of my students who I I
teach at the High School for the Arts
she's the youngest daughter on it really
y you know it's the three generations
she knows Eddie yeah and Eddie always
had a flare for the time relase joke
uhhuh he really did it was like you know
he would uh he would leave an answering
machine message and it would be like hi
there please leave a message and
whenever you got his phone you heard
that message but what I didn't know is
he changed it every day and said the
same thing and I didn't notice the
little various differences because he
had me but but only a certain type of
person can think that way of course yeah
you know he was it was always he offered
up a laugh mhm he was one of those guys
you know he was just insanely funny born
with a funny bone in his head but I mean
we were just like two guys in radio
trying to rip it up and we did some
really really cool things which was in
opposition to the wishes of the program
do and the myopic uh you know uh
administratives and uh you know and I
grew up to do what I did but it it was
all because of the stuff that inspired
us you know we used to listen to Eddie
Lawrence records you know the old
philosopher mhm do you have any of that
I don't it's that guy that would go hi
you
bunky you say you've been walking around
you know and and he tells this story
about the sad and woe he says you know
well you're waiting you don't have no
money for tinsil so you're waiting
around for Grandpa to sneeze on the tree
is that what's troubling
you bunky and then there would
be well lift your head up high keep that
chin up keep it up keep it up and go out
there and take a flop on the ice and
never give up boom boom that
ship it was a it was a whole routine and
it was great he's this crazy nut Eddie
lawen used to do um he'd be doing the
news or you know radio news and then
he'd say and now it's time for the dog
and cat report and and he would like say
and you dogs out there you know who you
are you know and it was like The Surreal
held the ultimate Fascination yeah for
the both of us we loved Supercar the
puppet show seen yeah yeah you ever
watch heard of it yeah you got to go
watch it it's it's like that's surreal
superar it was an English puppet show
okay it was um Jerry Anderson mhm who
did Fireball X5 who did Thunderbirds who
did Stingray all right yeah all those
creepy English puppet shows I mean that
stuff was more important to me than like
passing any test or or you know having a
social life yeah because how what kind
of so I had back then comic books I
loved comic books needless to say and uh
I had about one and a half friends and I
had no common interest with any just
about any other guy anywhere but I heard
there was a kid on the other side of
town that had comic books and I didn't
even know where he lived and I found him
I was like a like a like a homing pigeon
or a truffle pig you know there's
truffles on the other side of the town
all I need to do is go within the area
cheap color
[Music]
ink comic books
I knew it and I remember his name his
name was I shouldn't say his name I
don't know what happened to him I'm sure
he's still into Comics probably I know I
am yeah yeah yeah of course well I am
and I've and I've lived to see the day
where I was in comic books right yeah
you know I I even was drawn as myself in
Mad Magazine when I was doing the Stern
Show they did a parody really on the
Stern Show and I see me with this puppet
with the New York Yankees cap that I
used to wear one of their artists drew
me I was so flattered yeah of course I
was so flattered I mean that stuff was
like Canon to me mhm it's amazing that
is incredible be drawing in Mad Magazine
but I mean my sense of humor was pretty
much shaped on junk that I read in there
yeah yeah yeah you know like there was a
beautiful panel cartoon by a guy named
Dave Berg yep and uh the Lighter Side
Lighter Side and so you know it talks
about like um you know a woman will
spend hours in the mirror before she
goes on a DAT desperately trying to look
sexy and when some imbecile responds to
the stimulus it's like you pig you know
but basic truths of life and guys you
know it say uh you know there's always a
good name for a drunk you know like
Jolly Old Ed but it would always be fat
old
Fanny yeah and that was the basic truth
yeah yeah but it took mad to to like set
you straight yeah it was so great I was
an alder boy I knew the mass in Latin go
figure you know and all of a sudden I
said you know what I I spent all this
time following these stories when I
could have become a scholar of the
brothers Grim right you know what I mean
and the thing is it kills me uh I
probably know more about religion than
most people and the stuff that I hear
come out of people representing God oh
it's the worst and and again it goes
back like I was a religion major in
college you were oh sure in what what
what a comparative religion I was just I
was into everything it's like oh what's
this about what's this about how what's
the difference between this and this
right what the the branch devidians were
big at that
time Waco um yeah so faric so good um
but yeah with with religion it's uh it's
just the most fun ever and Carlin was
one of the best people to talk about it
as far as comedy was concerned you know
it's just like you know like religion is
nuts because you'll have this guy who's
describing God you know he does that all
right first you got your all powerful
God there all powerful he can throw a
boat right over a hedge That's How
Strong he is all right first all
powerful you God and he knows everything
you know and like you want this guy to
be describing you really no you know
what I a real life situation I was
always questioning everything nothing
made sense to me that's why I was more
attracted to Fantasy and Whimsy and um
you know picturesque picker esque
whatever you know meaning silly and
playful
um because nothing made sense to me I
was in parochial school and I I got out
and I was like going to the bathroom in
one of the rooms and and took a drink
you know and there was real old oil
paintings on the walls of these places I
mean they were real old M and they were
oils some of them might be probably
worth a fortune if you could go dig them
up today sure but there was one of the
garden of
Eden and they showed the apple and they
showed the serpent and Adam and Eve and
I'm looking at it and I'm studying it
and studying
it and a nun happened to come by she was
older before I before I say this uh
story I better take a
drink Billy West is taking a drink of
water yeah the one at my feet fell over
but no matter cap was on it I filled the
air properly
there so anyway she comes by and she's
watching me stand I'm just standing
there looking at this thing and she goes
what's so interesting and I turn around
oh um I this painting yeah what do you
like about it if you do like it you know
real like come out with her Dukes up you
know oh God and uh and I said well I'm
just fascinated by it yeah why and I
said well because there's some things
that you know I mean I know the story
and um
you know God created Adam in His image
and
likeness um and he took 100 pounds of
clay from the earth and I'm I felt
stupid saying these things because I
never said them back to anyone it's like
you're supposed to take that and pound
that into your little skull and you
better remember that buddy cuz there's
going to be a
quiz you know and so I said 100 pounds
of clay that's right you know and I like
and then um he fashioned it into man in
his own image and likeness that's right
and then he formed Eve from he God took
a piece of Adam's Rib which became
personified somehow I didn't say that
somehow you know from the clay to you
know Prime and uh she said yes that's
right informed Eve she said what so
what's your point and I said why do they
have belly
buttons woo woo woo the anger train
coming at
me this angry teac Kettle skewing and
screaming [ __ ] you know and it just it
didn't make sense to me yeah cuz every
painting I ever saw them they got nice
little yeah not even the lousy ones that
get pulled out by a by an impatient
doctor that's like yeah no no no just
nothing yeah just beautiful little innie
M isn't that nice NOP makes perfect
sense it's a great one this might have
been painted 3 400 years ago yeah you
just and they didn't even figure it
out but some stupid kid in Detroit going
to parochial school you know oh that kid
nothing ever changes yeah it's the same
thing you know I got to watch what I do
like in front of housekeepers and stuff
because if you piss them off they'll
write a book about you now it is now you
don't even need to do that no but I mean
your camera in the corner I think of my
housekeeper you know if I ever did
anything wrong next thing you know
there'd be a book there always is MHM
and it would be called oh
B I like how do you spell that you
know there probably uh how it sounds
it's it's got that um well it's not
castillan because there's no in it
exactly okay it's like through closed
teeth that's
disapproval yeah because um I knew some
uh a Puerto Rican family and one of the
daughters was drinking a little too much
coito at Christmas time and uh coito is
like heavy duty M and U the mother's
sitting there and she's watching
somebody get like stewed and she's just
going
okay okay and it's just like I I love
that stuff it's the stuff of life oh
yeah it's the rich Buffet you know
that's the best of Life lingo people's
attitudes and everything he served me
well you know like I said why did they
even bother going to school you know I
did go one year at Berkeley College of
Music but it wasn't even a college then
it was a school of music oh before it
was even part of college right oh
interesting yeah it was a school MH and
uh I couldn't wait to get out of there I
wanted to be playing music I wanted to
be on the road you know I didn't want to
talk about it sure but then look at that
I was smart there too because all the
people who make hit records all the
rappers you know they start out taking
their award and they go I like to thank
God and God is a going don't pin that
[ __ ] on me don't thank me for that I
took that day off I went fishing I don't
know who you're talking about I don't
have anything to do with this yeah right
I could see it every year you know oh
gez it means I got to go to you know
another galaxy or something and hang out
with people that are
intelligent um and uh you know it's like
they don't even know what a gcff is or a
treble cleff and it's it's like that's
the highest award you can win in music
mhm and so I'm glad I didn't spend any
waste any [ __ ] time at the Berkeley
right yeah and I went out and I made a
living as a musician you I wanted to be
like the best guitar player in the world
sure sang mhm but we didn't have uh we
didn't have Ries that they just didn't
exist you got to do it all yourself no
this was like the mid to late
60s early 70s and you broke a string you
to sit there either sit there like a
fried egg till till you figure out how
to change it or I would launch into
voices and noises and all that stuff and
it became apparent to me that sometimes
the people liked that better than they
like the music I mean when they were
plotting for us they were plotting for
the Rolling Stones or or whoever was out
there at the time cuz we were doing
covers but you added character by just
but I I just thought it was illegitimate
compared to music you know that's how
clueless I was yeah yeah yeah I mean it
makes sense I I had no idea that that
was something that was viable right and
that I would actually go on in life to
make a living at it yeah I didn't go to
be famous I didn't go to be rich I I
never thought for a million years that
you could ever achieve that yeah I was
just bursting to bring something to
table mhm and and all of it is a result
of the albums we're talking about the TV
shows and
um is there if you I consider myself
extremely fortunate you talk to anybody
Tom canny we talk about this all the
time how
how grateful how much gratitude we have
because the odds of this are a billion
to one and I know it yeah and uh that
we're able to continue working and then
I haven't had a break from working for
30 years yeah you know and there's not a
lot of people that can say that that's
why all these schlub celebrities want to
do what I do for a living of course of
course you know because they want to
keep being relevant right and so they
have no problem with their anemic voices
you know being used for cartoon they're
just who and exactly what they are I
wish I had that Liberty right life would
be so much easier if I could just go
down and be Billy West for anything you
know talking toilet or a bottle of
bleach what's wrong with my nasy flawed
plain
vanilla that's that's like Bel LA or
drags like a you know a cart with three
wheels that's the funny thing like
you're sailable because you're
recognizable as a star whereas you got
to be a chameleon and that's the [ __ ]
Talent of it and also it's I would I
would much rather as a fan of all the
stuff I would much rather pick people
out well it's not even pick people out I
would rather have somebody whose voice
is suited to the character as opposed to
somebody who wants name recognition
which has nothing to do with the product
that they're trying to sell you know
like let Batman be Batman or or
Daredevil or whichever car Invader Zim
or whoever it is I did the pilot for
Invader Zim I know I love somebody was
talking about it I didn't think anyone
could possibly even remember or know
that oh yeah well I mean the the guy who
drew it used to do this comic book
called Johnny the homicidal maniac which
I was a big fan of so when he went over
the animation I was like oh gotta go
check that out wait who did the rest of
the series my brain is just totally shut
off though uh you mean who actually well
there was that kid um Jon and Vasquez MH
mhm he didn't want me to be Invader Zim
after I did the pilot because uh he said
that uh I was
Overexposed how dare this little son of
a [ __ ] who hasn't proven a thing say
I'm overex and I realized you know what
he's right
so my friend intensely incredibly genius
talented Richie Horwitz did it and his
interpretation was gold to me I was
thrilled to death you know great yeah I
mean I would much rather hear people who
know what they're doing and embody the
character but I love people
automatically assume that there's a feud
attached to everything so so what
happened when how did you feel right
right right did this it's like what that
one of my best friends got a job yeah
it's fine believe me yeah I don't give a
dismal damn who gets what you know I
don't covet something yeah when someone
else is doing it go I could have got
that do you know how prevalent that is
in 100% I could have that could have
been mine I could have done it of course
anyone could have done it you like
Spencer Tracy said acting is the easiest
thing in the world know your lines don't
bump into the furniture yeah yeah boom
and be able to uh fake sincerity yeah
that help 100% because when you can fake
that you can just fake
anything if uh that ain't the quote and
and I wish I hadn't tried to steal
it we towards the end we like to always
have people if you're going to recommend
this album to somebody let's say because
some of our audience I'm hoping are
younger people who don't know [ __ ] about
comedy that's fine that's what I like so
let's say they haven't heard of Jonathan
Winters or don't know him from anything
well saying they don't know [ __ ] about
comedy is lit
antagonistic you got to them a littleit
I'm trying to do when I was like five
I'm hoping there were a lot of
5-year-olds listening to this I didn't
know me too especially after some of the
subject matter that was
by my brain my evil side uh so what we
like to tell them like if you're going
to recommend this album to them having
never heard Jonathan Winters what's
what's a good way to condense why this
album's good to listen
to
um not that it would matter to a lot of
people but this is a man that could come
out in front of a bunch of people he had
no instrument he had no Loops he had no
beats he had nothing and Magic emanated
from him because of his brain firing
synapses in a magical way and that's
what he has magic it's very intimidating
when you're up close and personal to
someone who has true magic yeah it makes
you like you don't know whether to [ __ ]
or go blind it was like my friends you
know yeah growing up they they don't
have magic and you did yeah and it's
your fault you know and suddenly that's
you're not to be spoken to or you know
but if you do want to see that there's
lots of places you can see that watch a
guy like hitz you know go on YouTube and
watch a man with a piece of wood cat gut
a bow you know some strings on it and
and create Magic with an instrument no
special effects no nothing no
pre-programming no touch of a button
anything this is a human being yeah
that's if you want to see that and you
can deal with that you know that's where
you'll that's where that's something
that'll you know just uh set your hair
on fire I mean you can't you can't go
back to the other stuff you know it's
like it's like you've looked over the
fence and I'm like this guy is a
comedian like how do I go back to you
know Dane Cook when I've seen this you
know it's like I mean and Dane Cook is a
lovely man I'm sure I don't know him
anyway but I mean like and and I love
would that be like a Danish epicurian
Chef or something yes that's what he
meant yes a a Danish Chef exactly yes
um not as funny as the Swedish Chef but
funny more laughing on the inside Chef
no but but that's just it and like one
of the things I love about uh Jonathan
Winters is like you can see it's a mad
mad mad mad mad world and see a a little
bit of that but it's a scripted film and
he had to stay very much on the rails
you know they let him you know of course
I mean especially when you see him doing
physical bits like when he's on the bike
and you know you're just literally like
how is managing to stay up but when you
see him on The Tonight Show or you see
any of those clips where you know when
it is totally different when he steps
out from that couch or even when he's
still sitting on the couch the look on
Johnny's face or whoever it is is
totally different when Winters is going
than any other comedian there is there
is almost it's like watching somebody
getting ready to jump out of a plane
it's like something wholly unexpected is
going to happen and we all got to be
it's like looking at a burn victim you I
I can't I shouldn't but I must but I
have to I I cannot look away but look at
how interesting this is so we've just
compared Jonathan Winters with a burn
victim jumping out of a plane
that's okay I just wanted to make sure
Define burn victim yes Define airplane I
I leave I leave it up to both of you
that is not my responsibility oh [ __ ] um
boy to be continued yeah right do you
have anything to promote thank you for
being here number one yes my pleasure
all right I mean you're you're a hero of
mine so it's this is a [ __ ] honor but
we've we've talked about you as far as
Animaniacs is
concerned drama gillion times but you're
finding out who my heroes were that that
put a tilt in my Kilt exactly that's
what this is about those guys are the
knees knockers you know yeah when I meet
them Jeff Beck I met Les Paul Stan
freeberg freberg [ __ ] yeah but Stan was
one of my heroes that's amazing and I
worked with him did you and he told me
you know you know more about me than I
do H yeah of course I said but how did
you do all of these things you know at
that time he says well I was a young guy
I had a lot of energy and you know those
are my heroes yeah who went just for the
pure love first and foremost and had to
figure out how to Market later and be
slick and clever that way do you have
anything coming up that I let people
know about I I have a podcast that I
just put up awesome yeah it's the Billy
West podcast name yeah Billy West
podcast.com all right it's also on
iTunes and it's clean as a whistle no
right I want to sell a show you know of
course of course yeah I want to cling to
my vulgarity no it's art
man no I mean I can it's it's a
challenge to just try to be silly and
surreal or or impressionistic or
whatever label you want to throw on it
but it was just like there was just
stuff I felt like doing and saying and
yeah that didn't necessarily not like I
was soliciting for Laughs or anything
like that it was just it's a lot of it's
just silly yeah and then I wasn't afraid
to do it and uh so you know I hope
people listen they like one of them's
like 40 minutes long yeah yeah I know
some of these little buzzards like go on
for 17 minutes I know what that's the
show what that's it done does that make
me a bad man because I went for 17
minutes cuz there's no parameters on uh
the internet and cyberspace there's no
okay 20 minutes you got to be out by 30
yeah [ __ ] that no that's not good no see
the beauty of all of this stuff Twitter
yes um are you just at Billy West the
Billy West at the Billy West who's the
[ __ ] who stole at Billy West
from you at Billy West yeah did somebody
take at Billy West somebody must have
Billy West instead of the Billy West I
don't know I'm just saying somebody that
were going to steal they stole awful
stupid you know what about at Alec
Baldwin right you know it's a bottom
feeder I know Billy West seems to be
popular this is the age of the internet
Claim Jumpers and the wild CS if anybody
wants to get in touch with me I am
Humphrey Bogart on Twitter uh you should
be now I am what's your real one why
don't you promote that Jeremy guskin I'm
the only one I have no Google gangers no
and nobody on the planet as far as I
know has my name so Jeremy guskin I'm
that on Twitter on Facebook on Instagram
everything I don't have to do any weird
like the real or1 or nothing there are
Jason clowns who are my exact same age
really exact same age that's cuz that's
not a last name you hear a lot no it's
not and oh and please don't ask me John
K
questions I mean think of it this way do
you really want to bring that mountain
down on
yourself you know there's this one kid
he doesn't get the message and I keep
telling you he's
like why do you hate John K or or like
when you were doing did you hate John K
then or everything has to do with John K
and I said to this kid you know I would
I would really appreciate it if you
didn't extric inextricably link me to
John K you know I said I I kind of have
a little more happening than he does I
think maybe maybe you want to ask me
questions with my name in
it that's okay you know what it is it's
like this I got to straighten everybody
out just as bad as those cartoons where
it's like you know some kid is up all
night because someone was wrong on the
right done many the Serenity Prayer
being not available to them you
know yeah handling the hard no but I
can't I can't straighten everybody out
but and I'm not their Republican dad
that wants to teach them a lesson and
all that [ __ ] that's what your podcast
is for you start straighten people out
no it's like it it doesn't have any
victims it doesn't it's not like trying
to teach people a lesson it's just it's
Whimsy yeah it doesn't call yeah it's
Whimsy you don't call your listeners uh
idiots or whatever I called them earlier
right which is not what I me no but I
almost called the show hey
stupid I seriously thought I even had a
theme song Alice Cooper had a song
called hey stupid hey hey hey hey hey
[Laughter]
stupid nice you can have it if you want
it I'll take that I might make that my
ring tone once I pull it off of this
stupid I'd like to hear that every time
my phone goes that would be a great
ringtone I know all right well everybody
everybody needs to follow both these
guys on Twitter you can follow me if you
want to you can find me I'm not going to
tell what my name is I'll find you you
you'll find me uh listen to Billy West's
podcast for f say it say it because I
don't want to hear any whining about it
I mean I feel like anal first initial
last name j clam JK l a m m I was going
to say as it's spelled but you know as
it sounds but no J clom I'm J clam
everywhere which is stupid I should have
gone by something interest that nobody
can figure that out right like Dracula
bulldozer exactly right at Dracula
bulldozer is where you will find me soon
enough I love you because you put
yourself last you just remind me of me
no no no everybody else comes first do
your yeah women it's like guys are
idiots they don't learn till the till
like they're really old and have to find
out what a girl really wants so it's all
about saying yes no I'm second your
pleasure comes first yeah I get that
yeah you're multiple O's and all that
other stuff you know come first anything
as long as I get to
multiples I think I will quickly promote
even though this is a a ways down the
way uh we have a Parkinson's benefit uh
coming up here in Burbank October 21st
2015 called the million McFly March come
dressed up as Marty McFly I will be
there uh and it's to raise money for
Parkinson's will you be there Jeremy be
dressed as Doc Brown of course because
you've played or as 3D it's very Noble
Jeremy has played my doc and I have
played Marty on stage a number of times
um and uh that's one of the reasons I do
time to do plays and all that cool stuff
oh you can come on over we won't pay
anything but you can come to our show
every month if you like that's not why
you would do anything oh I know believe
me it's so much fun it's you would have
got a bill for today yeah I know 100%
couple hours yeah yeah teamer team are
we in Golden time for podcast right now
son of a [ __ ] it's not safe harbor
exactly J Hawk one of the cars please um
you know that the teamster telling a
bedtime story to his kid once upon a
time and a
half brilliant on that note uh thank you
for being here again my pleasure thank
you so much there's no camera here but
I'm shaking the hand
man particular I knew I knew you would
be you would you couldn't resist coming
over I said Billy I'm glad you did yeah
and I met I met two nice kitty cats that
were floating around that's right and I
spoke cat yes you did that was amazing I
wish got that I wish I recorded that
[ __ ] it was fantastic um but I mean they
I I think they just got tired of hearing
me talk but they were just moving in you
know what they can smell C on me oh sure
well also when you were making those
insane loud screeching noises they ran
away several times really no and then
they came back do that it was funny you
kidding I'm like aie Osborne you know
somebody somebody asked him a question
like you know hey you know that was like
what what were you thinking you when you
bit that bird's head off and everything
and at that that news conference or
whatever and he
said what what you put the bird he like
I did that all remember who who made me
do that [ __ ] yes I know oh poor Aussie
well we always end the podcast by saying
have a good thing but I thought about if
what if I said have a good brain thing
and maybe you could follow up the line
you know I'm not going to make you
perform wait wait okay I'm not going to
make you perform you tell me to shut the
[ __ ] up no I would never do that okay
but it's but it's my option and my
decision whether I decide if I let you
Co-op uh exactly right my spontaneity
and my alacrity 100% so if I said have a
good brain
thing and you said I already did then I
would just make me well you mean is that
like a fry thing it is a say it again
all right all right all right all right
I didn't even pick up on that queue and
I'm usually pretty good fr's got that
brain thing oh that's oh that's right
yeah okay have a good brain thing toine
thing even
[Music]
better comedy on vinyl is a production
of stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
Levens
please visit stolen dress.com to listen
to our other podcasts read our blogs
read our tweets watch our videos and
read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
fstar rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook.com/ Comedy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedy on vinyl.com
[Music]
[Applause]
and e
[Music]
[Applause]
h and