[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast hi everybody it's Jason clom
host of The Comedy on vinyl podcast I'm
honored today to have uh Tommy Chong on
the phone with me thank you so much for
doing this hey my pleasure nice to be in
uh somewhere where am I you're in
Burbank right now let's say you're in
Burbank okay Burbank okay because I just
got back from Berlin oh did you I was in
Germany yeah I like Germany is wonderbar
it's really nice it's it's beautiful I I
lived there as as a kid because my
parents were in the military so uh I
missed Germany a lot oh so you you did
where where what uh Berlin or no the the
biggest not biggest but the city we were
in the longest was Vis Boden it's I
don't know how large it is honestly I
should know but I
don't uh but it's very pretty as on on
an Air Force Base but it's honestly just
so beautiful I miss it a lot oh yeah I
love I love it you know what I love most
of all is when you fly on Lanza Airlines
uhhuh the the the announcer they talk
quiet oh okay you know and you know what
I mean it's so annoying you get on a
plane and you you get all this the
fashion the seat belt to take the you
know all that
crap you don't want to hear that you
know tons yeah well all of Berlin is
very uh very uh civilized
uhuh um okay so I wantan to I you know
what let's let's start here I don't know
I I know the only part I really know
about your history is you know that you
started out as a musician obviously
there's a lot more to your life than
that you started out as a musician and
eventually you meet cheich Marin and it
seems like that's history but what were
your comedy influences early on if you
were a musician
first well my earliest comedy influence
was red fox when I was really young we
used to go to this dump uh it was an AR
like an army base was a like a dump they
never had back in the 40s and 50s they
never really had uh kind of garbage
collection they just had a dump that you
would take and dump all your stuff there
and and we found you know did scavenge
around there and I found a red fox uh
party record they called the 78 yeah and
that was a that was my first taste of
recorded comedy and and we couldn't play
it in front of our parents but sure when
we played it it was it was very x-rated
and and and and so much fun and so red
pox was really was my earliest uh and
and plus uh like I grew up uh in the 40s
50s so we had radio uh you know the Amos
and Andy and Jack Benny and Bob Hope and
so I'd listen to the radio shows yeah
and I'd hear the comedians uh you know
all the Comedians and then R and then Ed
Sullivan so so and my Dad loved to you
know he loved to be funny he loved to
laugh it was a we I grew up in a very
comic uh driven uh childhood yeah now at
at that time so I mean I know you're
born in Canada you're you're in Canada
at the time though when you find that
record yeah yeah I'm in Calgary Calgary
Alberta Calgary Alberta okay and so was
there I mean it's funny because every
influence you listed that I heard was
was was American were there any was
there any Canadian comedy to speak of
that you knew about there was a a pair
of guys called Wayne and Schuster oh
yeah sure they Wayne and Schuster they
were the hot funniest comedians that
Canada had you know had that like Martin
and Lewis who was Wayne and Schuster and
and I think the daughter I think Rose
went on to become a big uh uh well-known
producer okay you know I think she was
on the the
um uh what's that show at night uh
Saturday Night Live I think she was one
of the original writers I'm not sure wow
okay all right so that's all right that
see that's this is one of those things
it's where I think if if you if you grew
up in Canada at a certain time it seems
like it it depends on when you grew up
there your influences could be heavily
American regardless um oh yeah yeah or
european sure European you know anybody
like like bville was still happening you
know when I grew up sure and so so so
there was uh you know anybody that was
on Ed Sullivan was from Vaudeville and
the thing is about Vaudeville like I
went to the Crazy Horse Saloon in in
France when we shot a movie here in 1980
and the Horse Saloon would have these
Comics they were like MIM artist because
no one spoke you know a Common Language
and so they'd have to be funny with
movement you know like Charlie Chapman
and uh and so I I I picked up a lot of
influence uh from from uh the VOD
villian Comics yeah that's see that's
that's amazing and and was that okay uh
was that influence laying dormant as
you're a musician or were you doing
anything comedically before chich and
Chong well when you're a musician in a
black band which I was you're in a
constant state of humor uhhuh you know
you're you're just laughing all the time
because we would you
know play the dozens you know without
out each other you know and whether you
want it to be or not like when I joined
when I was with Motown my nickname was
hey
[ __ ] oh my God hey
chinan in fact that's what Bob Marley
said to me one time time when we we
opened for Bob Marley and the Whalers
and uh we went to the rehearsal and and
we walked into the dressing room and it
was just smoke fi looked like a a chich
and Chong movie and out of the darkness
I heard that hey chinan say something
funny man oh my god wow yeah well I mean
I did read and I you never know how true
this stuff is uh so I guess I can ask
you I did read that that you supposedly
came up with an alternate name for one
of your BS oh yeah yeah well we never
had a band name you know that's the way
we were you know we had a a nightclub we
had a place to work but no uh no uh
uh uh official name okay with Motown so
so we're joking around and that's where
we come up with four [ __ ] in a CH is
my wallet over
there parents oh I got I'm looking for
my wallet it is in my ear
it's in my phone it's attached to my
phone oh my God so I guess little daddy
in the bachelor's was an easier uh name
to sell is is well little daddy in The
Bachelor I never named that that was
Tommy Milton the singer that named it
you know and the funny thing was he he
was little daddy all right although he
was a big ass football player and uh but
the Bachelors none of us were Bachelors
we were all married and that's where
that's when I met my uh my uh now wife
you know she was a young girl and and
that was the first thing she pointed out
to me was the band she goes why do you
call yourselves the backers you're all
married well we're not going to call
ourselves little daddy and the married
guys right right so okay so if you don't
mind tell me the story because again I I
feel like there's not enough information
about this out there I should know as a
big fan of your work how did you meet
chich CH well I got fired from mtown I
you know I realized every move that I
made was because I was fired or kicked
out of somewhere like we got kicked we
had we started the band in Calvary and
then the mayor and the in the chief of
police actually kicked us out of out of
the out of Calgary oh God we were asked
to leave during the Christmas rush and
we were glad to leave and then when I
was in out in Vancouver after the gigs
ran out because we were sort you know we
weren in't a professional band we were
like a bunch of guys throwing together
that could play rock and roll so we had
no idea about the the touring uh you
know what you how you tour different we
never had an agent okay right we would
just get gigs and then when the gigs
were finished like uh little daddy you
know we we broke up because we never had
any work ahead of us and so we're so
used to all us are so used to being fir
that we just got fired ourselves and and
so I ended up uh you know going back and
then I ended up so uh I got fired from
mtown that was my latest one after I
rode a hit hit song for them I got fired
because I had to get a green card and
and uh the tour manager didn't know what
that meant and so oh no when I missed a
gig when I missed a gig he fired me and
even though mtown was paying for it but
when I got fired I stayed fired I went
back to Vancouver and I started a
theater company uh in a strip joint and
and then we had a another actor like me
long here and then we had a straight guy
and then our straight guy's wife found
out what he was doing and so she fired
him and then that's when I met cheich
cheich was in Vancouver he was avoiding
the draft and he was also uh uh looking
for a job and so when I met him
uh I hired him at first as a writer and
as an actor writer actor well everybody
was writer actors you know there was
that's the way it was and so and then
when we got fired from my brother my
brother fired us because we had played
out our our string in in Vancouver we
started attracting the
non-drinkers and for a bar that's death
you know because they take up room that
the alcoholics need you know to spend
all their paycheck yeah and so I we got
fired from there and so then teach and I
came to LA to make it as Comedians and
that's how we did it and so you're at
the club and you just needed some
entertainment and you figured why not
comedy is was it that simple or was it a
little more involved than that no it was
the strip club and and the girls would
come on with these elaborate costumes
and and and I noticed that crowd really
wasn't interested in the show sure they
were just they like the at osphere and
and the girls would get on stage and get
naked and and and it wasn't really a
show it was just a like a party where
chicks got naked okay and uh and so I
decided that and we had a singer and we
had a tap dancer you know MC in the show
but no one was watching them and so I
when I came home without a band I
started working the lights and writing
shows and then I realized hey I could
write a show with the strippers because
I noticed that they were so beautiful
when they before they got into their
costumes and so I wrote a uh the first
show was about after the show and we're
having a pajama party at one of the
girls' house and and so the girls would
come in their street clothes one by one
and then they would undress and get into
their pajamas or their little um sexy uh
what are they call I forget what they
night gown sure okay and uh and then
Taps would come over with Genie the sing
and they would say hey that was a great
night we had tonight hey Taps why don't
you show us that that dance you did that
was amazing so Taps would do his dance
and then now the whole crowd is looking
at him and he was so good that he he got
a non-core and so he had to do uh two
acts wow and at the end of the show that
night he quit because he wasn't hired to
to do his act he he just wanted to be
the
MC and not do anything and so uh you
know we lost our entertainment and so I
talked to the the doorman who was you
got a Dave Graham he was very funny guy
and so I said I wanted him to take over
Taps this place and so uh David said I
will I'll do it if you do it he put it
on me and so I said oh okay so we became
a a comedy team uh uh David Graham and
myself and then we uh and and then the
rest was history we started doing
improvisational uh comedy and we just
never looked back and when chich and I
joined up all we we did the same bits
you know that we would do uh in the show
and uh only cheich and I did them you
know back to back and uh and we tried it
out in in Vancouver at a at a battle of
the bands and we actually won the
contest without playing a note it was
just teach and I doing comedy oh my God
and so we knew we knew then that I and
and I knew you know I'd been through the
Motown School of Hard KNX and so I knew
what it took you know and two guys
without instruments you know can make a
lot of money more than a a band with a
ton of uh expenses right wow so you
essentially do this weird thing where
you invent an artsy form of of burlesque
basically like that's kind of what
happened and then you just yeah it
doesn't fall into your lap but you must
have felt like you had an aptitude for
making comedy and then you meet the guy
who who just is a perfect compliment to
your work what was the material like
then is there anything like it on any of
your albums or was it totally different
what was the act like not a whole lot
nothing on the albums no what happened
when we were playing for uh you know
bikers's trip clubs we would torture the
bikers you know we would do some very
classical bits and and you know bikers
expecting hard or strippers and they
would get uh like we had a mime artist
we had a classical guitarist and the
mime artist would come out and pretend
he's picking flowers and then we had
Dave would come out pretend to sing a
very classical song and then I would
start the humor by coming out to a door
pretending that I was half asleep with a
rolled up newspaper and and stripped to
the waist and it looked like I and I'd
walk over to Dave and I'd beat him beat
him or both the head with a new
newspaper saying what kind of [ __ ]
song is that and and that would start
the humor and then we would go into uh
all sorts of humor so but our our
material was more tits and ass you know
sex a lot of sex jokes in fact we got a
lot of material from the Playboy joke
column okay we would act out act out
their jokes you know and and so when CH
and I ended up in La uh the only common
denominator was getting hot smoking dope
that was the one thing everybody related
to and then plus the fact chich was uh
Latino you know Mexican and Cho and so
we added the Cho uh character and the
stoner character and that really
resonated with the world and then when
we did Up in Smoke that really cemented
it yeah you know I mean that was that
was the really the birth of chiching
Chong that's so that's so crazy what was
your experience I know you might not be
able to speak to ch's experience but
what was your experience with improv was
it just like a necessity you're just
like I'll figure it out as I go along or
did you have any experience with it no
other than watching it but you know
being a musician you know and a lot of
the Improv actors that I met over the
years most of them were had Music
Experience okay because what you learn
in music is is you learn how to uh how
to uh uh improvise you know you get a
theme and and then you improvise off
that theme sure or or then you create a
new uh a new uh uh song you know and so
jokes are Just Like Music you know
there's a beginning a middle and an end
and you know you have a punchline and
then you can uh uh you know then you go
on to the next set you know so I wrote I
would write a set like I would do a
music set you know different different
songs but we it would be comedy yeah
different comedy bits and so I just use
my musical uh training and and the
comedy it's all about timing and and uh
I had a natural thing for it and so did
cheich you know because cheich would
entertain his family I would I I was a a
watcher I when I was playing on the chin
circuit they always had a black comic
open opening sure yeah you know the
black uh the you know the black clubs I
always had comics and MC's you know
people that would talk to the crowd you
know not like uh you know anab was very
hip yeah and like red fox and that it's
like it is today you know like Chris
it'll be like Chris Rock going on before
the before the strippers you know and
and doing his bit and so I I was uh
lucky enough to to be part of that world
earlier you know in the early early 60s
the late 50s and early 60s and so I had
that ability uh you know to entertain
and uh and and that's that's really what
uh got us the kind of success that we
ended up doing that's crazy that's H
that I I love hearing stories when
people don't intend to get into comedy
and yet all they turns out all they got
to do is try a little hard at comedy and
they're just great at it I mean that's
one of the it's great I love stories
like that well my you know my early
training I played guitar when I was
eight years old and I used to play with
a a f fiddle player I was I played with
them for about 8 9 10 11
12 years old and I was background guitar
or or uh what do you call second guitar
you know Rhythm rhythm
guitar and he told me right from the
beginning keep it simple you would say
keep it simple and give the people what
they want you know and so I just used
that Creed through my life and it always
worked yeah you know because the simpler
that chich and Chong became the more
basic we were the more popular we became
sure because everybody understand simple
you know uh the intellectuals and the
and and the people that aren't so smart
you know yeah and the trouble that I saw
with some some of these more
intellectual intelligent comedians is
that they they're they're cracking you
know themselves up but they're leaving a
lot of audience in the dark you know not
knowing
you what they're talking about
sure whereas When U te and Chong you
know there was never a doubt as to what
we were trying to say you know yeah well
I mean I I would argue that at the very
least though that doesn't that doesn't
exclude the any of your your comedy that
also kind of got deep whether or not the
the material was I mean you guys were
saying some I don't know you maybe I
mean do you think you were saying
anything daring cuz I mean you're pretty
anti
you
know well it's not so much
anti-authority as it is pro hipness yeah
okay it's it's something that uh um you
know to me you know
anti-authority I I look at this people
you know and and it's been my experience
that it's better to be friends with
those guys than it is to piss them off
sure
you know so I I had a lot of police uh
uh we we do chich ch's dad was a cop
uhuh he was like a a he taught uh law
enforcement he was right up there and so
chich was raised by a a serious uh uh
policeman and so cops became our big
fans you know because we never we never
were anti- anything we were just proot
okay all right I I get that again so
even even if you're doing like stadanko
I guess he's not even the bad guy in
that sketch he's just kind of
boring well he he just had to learn yeah
you know what he did in the movie the
great thing about Chichi Chong movies is
that nobody got hurt and and and nobody
uh got killed and nobody uh um uh you
know we we never tried to turn anybody
into drug addicts you know right we we
were just trying to get do our life it
was like a day in the life of a couple
of Stoners you know sure well I and
which is I mean I I think maybe I don't
know I'm trying to think of what my
favorite part of your albums is because
that's the stuff I grew up on for the
most part and I oh yeah I grew up with
it late you know this is stuff my
parents owned and passed on to me um and
and I and you're curious and sure you're
a writer I guess yeah so you had to you
had to uh experience or you have to
learn about everything exactly and so
when you're yeah when your friends would
talk about chichin Chong you had to go
check it out you know and then when you
were ready for that kind of information
uh you would understand it as they grew
as you Grew Older I think that's true
well you know what's funny is I will
I'll say at the very least we were super
proud my best friend and I became best
friends over uh weird owl's music and
over your comedy and uh we were the
first kids in the neighborhood to
discover chichin Chong so we but what's
funny is we're probably the last kids in
that town to ever smoke pot I'm almost
certain of that which is funny because
you know but that never mattered to us I
think it was just like how good your
comedy was you know the the characters
you
know yeah yeah I mean it was uh we had
so much fun doing it because we were
always stoned but not you know not just
bloto Stone we'd get high enough to
appreciate what we were doing yeah and
and so we would have more fun listening
to their albums I think than the
audience
did because we would just I mean we
would create it and then sit back and
listen over and over and over again and
and then we would say oh well we got to
fix this and make this a little better
and that a little better and it was
always done for love Yeah chich Chong
everything we did was for the love of
humor it wasn't for them you know
thinking well CBS will buy this or or uh
you know oh this will be you know we can
do this you know we're clean we never
thought about being clean or dirty we
just thought about being funny yeah well
and that's what's funny is that then
people like myself can come along and
say man you took all these Chances with
language when it's like no this is what
we thought worked right yeah exactly
sometimes it's hard guys like myself
tend to get up our own ass when we're
when we're thinking about stuff we love
you know so I so I well yeah well well
you guys are analytical you know and and
you know the rules and and and and
that's why you enjoy it more because
then you understand exactly what rules
were breaking you know right and then
you yeah then you understand what rules
are really full of [ __ ] you know what
are real that's exactly true I you know
I I think one of the things that's
inspired me the most is you know I when
I made my first comedy album I was 19
and my favorite thing was cutting
together all the sound effects and doing
all that [ __ ] myself and I know you had
Lou but I was curious like what was the
production process like of those albums
because they are some of the best mixed
albums I've ever
heard well exactly what you what you
said what we did uh Lou would only get
the product after we had it how nailed
down basically okay and then we'd send
it to Lou then we'd send it to Lou and
he'd give me his notes he'd F me in the
middle of the night and give me his
notes and then we always gave him the
bits to do the music chich and I never
did the music louther that was his
expertise sure okay and so and so uh
that was that was our uh uh method but
te and I always you know we we were the
ones that did the sound effects and we
had fun doing them you know we knew
where to put them and how to put them
and then and then we played played with
him you know the sound and everything we
had the best time man I didn't know you
did the sound effects yourself that
changes things so much for me to be
alone
huh I sorry I just didn't know you did
the sound effects yourself that that
kind of just blew my mind that blew the
[ __ ] out of my mind sorry for the
language but holy [ __ ] that's amaz so
what were you uh I guess let's get a
little technical what were you carrying
around were you going around to places
or were you doing all the effects in a
studio sometimes we would uh you know
like when we did the drive-in bit we
went to a a drive-in movie theater last
one in LA and we recorded us driving
over the bumps MH uh we recorded that
sound and then uh uh like gunshots for
instance we would get the the the
security guard at A&M records and we'd
get him to fire his gun off in a in a
bucket of sand or something oh my
God just to get the sound and if we
needed streets that was easy if we
needed uh uh kids I had all my my kids
and they would get their friends and we
would all end up in a studio
you know uh making sound effects and
singing and that and my like one time
the tortured old man bit uh we needed a
a woman screaming and so that was my
wife Shelby we had her in the studio we
want her to scream she screamed and yeah
we had so much fun you know it was just
uh if we could go back to those times I
I'd go back in a minute but yeah
unfortunately unfortunately we got bit
by the movie bug and when you get
when you start doing movies it's it's
the ultimate you can't you physically
can't go back you know sure well I mean
at the very least we've got this example
of a bunch of albums that have I think a
lot of heart and obviously obviously a
lot of work went into them that uh are
going to stand the test of time at least
even in terms of just the technical
stuff like I it's you know I think you
could just listen to those for the
technical stuff and be really heavily
involved in it yeah you're into that
that thing and and now you know I think
one of the
the biggest accomplishments is that
we've influence so many artists you know
like Quinton Tarantino he's a big
chichin Chong fan yeah and you can see
our our mark on his all his movies you
know they always had this CH Chong sort
of attitude yeah uh in them and then
we've influenced like Howard Stern you
know Howard Stern was like you he'd grew
up on our albums and so he he he went
right right to the you know right to the
hardcore uh hardcore uh you know radio
stuff yeah and
um do you and what else was I gonna say
I'm sorry go ahead no no no uh well I
was actually gonna ask you of your
albums do you have a favorite
one uh not really not really they all
they all they all sort of let's see
favorite albums probably the first one
yeah you know yeah because that that was
such a milestone you know that first
album represented uh all our struggles
you know trying to make it I mean CH and
I you know we struggled for about two
years and it was a struggle you know
when you try to support your family or
two families in my case you know uh
luckily both of my women
worked you know they had jobs and and so
chich and I we just did the couch you
know sleeping on Friends couches and uh
putting up with you know three dog night
really helped too because they were uh
the drummer Floyd is a brother-in-law of
mine married to I was married to his
sister she was my first wife and so they
have they opened a few doors for us you
know but uh all in all it was it was
just a labor of of love the whole the
whole trip yeah and and that whole time
that you were waiting for that to happen
uh was it just doing Club gigs or
opening for ACT everything we could go
everything you could get okay everything
we can get they never had comedy clubs
in and so we would go to the black clubs
and then they would hire us you know for
25 bucks or 50 bucks you know some real
cheap price and uh and we could rely on
them you know and that's what kept us
alive for for a year two two years you
know we and we do any freebies that we
could do and then we you know we
couldn't go on the road because we were
uh you know saddled with the family but
uh we could stay in town and then and
then but it was a recording soon as we
did Dave's not here then we got jumped
into that upper you know upper echelon
of of Comedy yeah know because when you
have an usually you're in comedy for
years before you do an album and but
chich and I were we were only in it for
maybe a year before we started doing uh
recordings wow and the way we did it you
know most ComEd comedians you know they
record their act right their live act
right but we were we were opposite we
recorded an album you know and it was
all about uh it was all about uh uh you
know being being hippies in this you
know in the 70s that's what it was all
about and drugs anything to do with
drugs you we we cornered the market on
that and then we did kind of material
that you know that only kids could
understand you know they couldn't play
it for their parents right although some
did sure you know a lot did and uh and
then if you do anything forbidden that's
another key to success you know yeah I I
I mean I love that you're able to break
it down so succinctly about what worked
about your comedy that's kind of great
to me I mean it's it's it seems it seems
simple but at the same time obviously it
wouldn't have worked if you guys didn't
have this huge love for writing sketch
comedy which is a thing I don't get to
see as much
anymore yeah yeah it sort of faded it
faded away you know like the committee
had a movie out and I don't think it
even got got distribution uh yeah people
people forget you know and then the
comedians they copy like the Sam
Kennison model that's all that's out you
know sure now you know and uh oh
although uh Richard Lewis his style is
there's one Carmichael is that his name
black black guy he's he's doing that
sort of like train of thought oh sure
Gerard
carmichel yeah yeah okay yeah like he's
he's carrying on that tradition yeah you
know Steve Martin you know his style is
gone we haven't seen that you know wild
and crazy guy uh model
anymore uh you know like I said
kennethon Andrew Dice he has to change
his act kind of sure you know you can't
rely on you see you can't get you can
what what you do you you raise a crop of
of admirers and it's an age thing and
when they grow out of you then it's time
to move on because you got to make way
for the new com Comics coming up that
have their audience yeah but you still
so yeah it's always a system yeah you
still got a pretty DieHard fan base
though and very least you get to perform
for them you know on occasion right I
mean is what's that
like Yeah well yeah I mean over the
years you know I've developed uh just
myself you know teach too but I
developed like there was a uh what's it
called uh that 70 show
uh uh time you know period of my life
yeah yeah five years five years in my
life was the sub show six years you know
and and so I got a lot of fans from that
sure then I got I got I got fans from
Dancing With the Stars you know all
right yeah
yeah millions of fans that just know me
as a dancer that's amazing and then you
know the old chich Chin chong fans you
know they see me go through all my
changes and so yeah we've managed to
stay uh pretty much relevant even to
today now I'm into the weed uh business
and which is so natural for me sure but
it's not something where I just put my
name on it and you know forget about it
but I go around and I I promote and then
and now I'm getting more into a uh heavy
uh spiritual side of it all and and like
I I just came back from uh uh Berlin and
and they had me do a little talk and and
the talk really was about how a
marijuana cures and and and the Cure
starts in the brain you know the brain
is the Central Command poost for for us
you know and it's the brain is also
where the soul is stored you know the
Consciousness is stored yeah and so I I
did a whole talk about how we are pure
Consciousness and therefore everybody is
relevant you know because everybody on
Earth is necessary to be here you know
yeah and uh and that's why you have to
respect everybody's uh Journey
regardless of what it is regardless of
it's Robin Banks or if it's uh uh you
know preaching to the to the
you know to the followers whatever it is
is uh is relevant yeah and you can't uh
you can't really make uh uh any kind of
uh distinction as to what is good what
is bad because every like I said
everything is relevant and the basis to
that is because we are Immortal beings
you know we've always been here we will
always be here and so all we're doing is
learning uh uh uh you know learning how
to live and we it takes a few lifetimes
to to learn say on Earth you know but
we're learning and uh some aren't you
know some are still in kindergarten and
some are uh you know in advanced uh
University you know but everybody has a
right to be here and everybody and no
one has the right to
criticize I like that I I like that and
I I like that we've actually kind of I
feel like that's that's been a theme
through what we've talked about this
whole time I mean like you gave me a
pretty good idea of of your own Journey
which has been I don't know insane like
filled with luck filled with Misfortune
but it's all led to stuff that you
learned how to appreciate exactly you
know like I said I got I got fired to to
every position in fact I rode a movie
one time called the Peter principal and
it was about two two two rocks fans who
sneak into an uh concert by pretending
the Ries and end up getting a job as
Ries but they're so inept that they keep
getting promoted instead of
fired like they drop equipment so they
oh take them off that put them in charge
of driving and then they show up late
you know and so they end up being uh
guitar texts and then they mess that up
and they end up performing yeah and they
end up becoming the star because they're
so inept to be doing anything else yeah
and that really is life you know that's
what we usually do we sort of like uh
and and and the only law of the universe
is karma which is a cause and effect
that's the only law you know if you uh
if you uh plant Bad Seeds you will
suffer if you plant good seeds you will
uh Prosper so that that really is the
simplest way to look at everything and
and but and the thing is that I have to
learn and that's why I said you know to
you uh you know just uh uh you know what
do you want to know because you can't
really tell people you can't give people
directions unless they ask for it yeah
you know what I'm saying sure I do and
that's really that's really what
preaching is all about you know if
someone comes to me and asks me like you
did I I I'll gladly give anything I know
but you know to to walk up to a stranger
or to someone that's on another path and
to start uh spoting my my uh
philosophies it's unw wanted and and it
wouldn't be learned it wouldn't be
accepted so that's what I learned you
know stay on your own tow that's what
the yoga say you know I I I like that a
lot and I like that I like knowing that
that guy that you that you're the guy
that's in your head that you are the guy
who created uh you know just some of my
favorite comedy of all time because you
you people can call it Stoner comedy if
they want I look at it again I might be
up my own ass about this but I look at
it a little more deeply than that I
think it's great character comedy uh
that happens to have pot in it and the
pot's fine if that's what brings you in
great but the character comedy is my
favorite part and it's obviously got the
heart of the two of you in it I really
do love that I yeah and and and it's
done with love yeah if you notice you
know we don't there's no hate there's no
there's no uh meanness involved you know
even even the the the killing the girl
tonight old man you know the Nazis I
mean that that that is some of the most
favorite what's his name Quint Tarantino
watch listen to that over and over again
when he watching when he wrote in
glorious Pastor that's amazing that's
amazing but you know what I mean I mean
yes it was it was showing Nazis killing
Jews but there was comedy with it and
there was comedy in in in the camps
there was a ton of comedy in the camps
because like I said before you know
we're Immortal beings and this is just a
stage of life that everyone's going
through and and and being caught up in
the Holocaust is just one of them you
know right and and and realizing that
you know and
so if you uh if you have that knowledge
a lot of us aren't aren't supposed to
have that knowledge you know or else you
wouldn't do what you do you know you
have to come to this this uh epiphanies
all by yourself yeah and and that's
about all I can say well and that's and
that's perfect um I will say you
mentioned something about planting good
seeds I'm going to thank you very very
much from the bottom of my heart for
planting uh a million good seeds in my
brain and for making me want to keep
making comedy I mean if it wasn't for
your comedy I I wouldn't keep I wouldn't
be doing this I wouldn't have this show
I my life wouldn't be the same so it
really does mean a lot to
me I appreciate that you take care thank
you so much thank you guys for listening
and as always have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
five-star rating and a nice review you
can find us on facebook.com/ Comedy
onvinyl Twitter at comedy onvinyl and
find everything else at comedyon
vinyl.com a major portion of comedy on
vinyl has been underwritten by standup
records please visit standup records.com
for all your comedy needs and tune in to
the new standup channel available on the
Roku where you can also find select
episodes of this podcast
[Music]