hey everybody Welcome to Comedy on vinyl
this week we have a very special guest
Matt besser talking about his favorite
Lenny Bruce Album please make sure to
follow Matt on Twitter at Matt besser
and to listen to And subscribe to his
podcast improv for humans it's on the
Earwolf Network that's improv the number
four humans a very special thank you to
Matt pess for welcoming both Mike and I
into his house and and uh an extra
special thanks for welcoming me into his
house 20 minutes later than Mike I got a
little lost that is unlike me but it
happened and we all have to deal with it
all of us including you I'm done uh so
yeah please listen to this episode and
enjoy and again please make sure to
subscribe rate US highly and do the same
for again Matt's podcast improv for
humans good evening ladies and gentlemen
and nice to be here at the most famous
theater in the world the
wonderful Palladium Theater
haha well folks I just got back from L
wages Nevada funny thing about working
lost wages folks the way to make a lot
of money there when you get off the
plane walk right into the propella I
tell you a funny thing happened folks
this little pansy walked into the bar
and and then into the motel jokes the
Army jokes The Impressions 10 12 15
minutes and he's bombing nothing but not
left one now he goes into the dying
jokes oh well folks I wasn't born here
but I'm short dying here h a lot of
different ways to die and blah blah blah
now he starts with putting the audience
down well Freddy Freddy boy I see it's
squaresville squaresville for the first
show The Greatest in them all
oh
RAC let's go to show business Heaven how
about it
myestro how about it
myestro Alec
electrician let's hit it boys a rock by
my baby walks off gets a little courtesy
Applause two people sounds like Citizen
Kane terrible all right everybody hi
thanks for coming to uh comedy on vinyl
this week we are speaking about uh the
Lenny Bruce album I'm not a nut elect me
and this week we have Mike Warden hello
and Matt besser thank you thank you for
having me thank you for helping me get
here um so we just generally like to
start you know why what's so important
about this album to
you um I think when you sent me the
invitation to be on your show you said
influential or did I just make that up
no that's exactly what I said which
might be a different Choice than
favorite um
sure the order of my influence and
standup vinyl would be my parents had
all the Bill Cosby stuff so that was my
first stuff I listen to I listen to
every single Bill Cosby
record um and that that dominated my
youth uhuh
um and they had a Woody Allen record too
that was great that was pretty much it
in my memory of what my parents had and
and I didn't really as a kid buy comedy
records I don't know if it occurred to
me or not um but then but then it was
Steve Martin like so many standups in my
generation would probably
say people my age would probably either
say Richard prior or Steve Martin as
their
number one influence and Steve Martin
was probably more the direction I went
and then Andy kman who didn't
really have a record I don't think but I
I his things that I saw on video
probably influenced me mhm um more than
anything I was kind of Blown Away by
that but that that wasn't until really
when I was in
college
and but I'd have to say what I when I
learned about Lenny Bruce which was
College too that that was when I was
starting to
consider that standup comedy could
actually be a career like that never
even occurred to me when I was in high
school I I thought I was going to be an
investment banker like my dad that's why
I went to college and I in my I don't
know even how I thought of it I guess I
thought that if you wanted to be a
comedian or even in a band or something
like that you had to be from New York
City or Los Angeles like a city and I
was from Little Rock Arkansas so it
didn't even occur to me that I could as
much as I love those things it never
even occurred to me that I had the right
to be one of those things which is kind
of
odd um is that what you studied in
school in col economics for about a half
a semester until I realized how stupid I
was compared to everybody else who was
in the class I was like well this
obviously is not what I'm good at um I
went to school at ammer College up in
Massachusetts so that was also a whole
different scene than the Arkansas Little
Rock Arkansas I'd grown up in
so my mind was being opened up in all
sorts of ways but um I was an American
Studies
major and I chose for my thesis Lenny
Bruce awesome um so it gave me a great
excuse to do nothing but listen to uh
Lenny Bruce
recordings and uh I got just about every
one of them on vinyl um except for this
one oddly enough which may be my
favorite I have it on cassette but
um all of his stuff
is pretty amazing in the story of Lenny
Bruce what he did is pretty
amazing um I I picked uh I'm not a nut
which it's not like I'm not even sure if
any of the ones the bits here were any
of the bits that he got arrested for my
guess is
no and and the and this one doesn't
necessarily have my the most of my
favorite Lenny Bruce bits sure but it
has the
ones where he starts to talk about just
The Business of Being a
standup and comedy and censorship itself
and he talks about the process of Comedy
I think at when I was listening to that
in college that was fascinating to me I
never heard that even if this guy was
you know four decades before me and so
much of the humor is referential and you
can't understand it but I I could
understand that or be fascinated by that
and there's one bit in particular the
padium mhm which is probably half of the
recording it's it's like a a it's
probably a 30 minute bit if not a 20
minute bit um but that is one of his
Classic Bits and that is one of my
favorites
uh we can we can just talk about that
bit I guess that but that bit is
[Applause]
about a standup who's doing all
the you know sleazy standup joints which
in those days squirt strip clubs or the
backs of a of a
bar Vegas yeah stuff he was doing or at
least definitely where he started MH and
um that standup gets a little tired of
that scene he's like I'm ready to take
it to the next level and he wants to do
the padium in London which is like the
biggest
Showcase Live showcase there is and as
the as manager says that's not your
scene man that's that's Beville he's
like no that's the next level so I'm not
going to just repeat his whole his whole
bit basically he goes he goes to London
and he
bombs three times and uh then in the the
third time there's two funny things
about it one he has to follow this woman
who does this dedication to all the all
the dead soldiers all uh all the English
soldiers who have died in wars and then
brings him out which is like the worst
thing that an Entertainer can go through
and he has to follow that and he bombs
again but this time to get himself out
of bombing he starts going [ __ ] the
Irish you know Screw the Irish and that
gets the London crowd loving them going
yeah screw the Irish so where they were
just giving him nothing all of a sudden
they start going
crazy
and that's before I was a performer that
was interesting story mhm once you
become a performer it's even a more
interesting story I think cuz you you
I've gone through that exact exact exact
thing I uh when I was doing standup in
Chicago I once had to follow this
guy um who ended his act he he was a a
black comedian he ended and he was
really funny but um he ended his act by
saying before I go I'd just like to tell
you a story I volunteer with Mally
handicapped kids on the weekend and this
weekend I was over speaking to one of
those kids and he said
edmmond um why is your skin Brown and my
Skin's white and I I told him you know
some people are brown and some people
are white and that's how it is um and
then the little boy said well why can't
I be brown and I said well you know you
were born white and I'm born brown and
that's just the way it is and the little
boy said to me I wish everybody could be
all the colors of the rainbow so we
would all get along good night good
night
everybody and then introduced
me
and and he did that to me a couple of
times and he already he was a funny guy
but that's just like leaving the next
guy in a hole like getting all
sentimental purpose like to make himself
laugh was it no no no I I'm not going to
give him that much credit he he was
doing it to get people to go oh what a
good guy kind of clap clapping as he
went off you know like oh not only did
we laugh tonight but we all learned a
lesson um which is that that you know
that same false sentimentality and that
that Lenny Bruce brings up and he has to
follow and uh another interesting thing
about that is that bit is kind of a
metaphor for
him in that what people really love
about him was at the end if they could
boil him down to something he was he was
the the word back then was sick sick
comedian and what we we call like a
shock I guess is what the word we use
now but he's he's a sick he's a sick
crazy comedian and and at the end like
really what they just wanted him to do
is say [ __ ] or tits or [ __ ] M
um and that's kind of like yelling screw
the Irish so in a way that was a
metaphor for his own career that just at
the end it was just let's go see him
curse and get arrested right right um
instead of
really talk about stuff so how long was
it then for you after standup that
sketch became a thing for you I mean for
those who don't know who are listening
uh Matt obviously you started the UCB
with with three other people right
correct okay so how long after stand up
then did it become
sketch in my own career yeah well I
started doing standup right after I did
it in college a little bit enough to get
the bug and then I went to Denver or the
Boulder area right after college cuz a
friend of mine was there and then I went
to Chicago cuz of the boom there was a
ton of clubs in Chicago and I didn't
even know what improv was I went and saw
this this place at The Improv Olympic I
saw Tim and Chris Farley and Kev dorf a
lot of funny guys go up and do this
thing called a uh an improvised heral
and who and that that flew me
away um and uh so that that that's the
transition I'm not sure if
I'm answering your question but yeah I
wasn't the plan wasn't to get in sketch
and bringing it back to Lenny Bruce what
people
that only casually know Lenny Bruce's
material or what they've read might
might think that he was always just kind
of talking about society and semantics
but really that's only the latter part
of his career once he started getting
busted before that like this
album um he's just talking about
everything and doing a lot of characters
really like just every one of his bits
he does multiple character voices yeah
and he's not I don't think he's really
people talk about that enough I'm a
hustler as long as they give I'll
grib but I know that someday there's
gonna have a
tribunal we'll all have to answer I'm
sure of that I'm just waiting for the
day I'm saving some money to give back I
know I was stealing I didn't mean to
take it they gave it to me we'll all
have to answer they'll line us up the
guy be in the black shrouds all the
performers all right line them up all
the offenders there State their names
and their salar the sentences will be
then Meed out the first offender what is
your name there Frankie Lane how much do
you make a week Mr Lane 10 $12,000 a
week it's remarkable what do you do to
earn from10 to $12,000 a week to spend
one burn his
wig break his legs 30 years in
jail get them up here the next one what
is your name Sophie Tucker
and how much do you make a week Miss
Tucker 20 to $30,000 a week what do you
do to earn 20 to $30,000 a week I'm the
last of the red hot burn her Jewish
Wreckers and jellies and the crepe gowns
with the sweat under the arm get rid of
her back him up here the next one before
he became the comedian that he
became um who just spoke honestly he was
like so many comedians he was an
impressionist like he calls the guy
Frank Dell Frank Dell
impressionist you know he's saying that
kind of disparagingly cuz those guys
would just
go here's Bella Losi ordering Chinese
food or whatever they would just do an
impression and not much comment and
that's what he did too so he was
adapting really good at voices and going
back and forth Just is a whole standup
skill in itself so in a way he is a
sketch performer and it was only
retrospect I was like you know what I
think that's one of the things I really
liked about him he was kind of pretty
much doing sketches by himself there's a
a bit on this album called the defant
ones um which is really a sketch I mean
that's what it is he does it with the
guy Eric Miller this guy in his uh jazz
band and he he did throughout his career
a couple of bits with Eric Miller
there's actually a better bit even
called um is it the one how to make
colored people comfortable how to make
uh uh black color people relax that's
what it is um at your party yeah that
one's that one's one of the classics and
really funny this one's pretty funny too
it's a parody of the the movie The
defiant ones but uh it's just a straight
straight up sketch on a standup album
and I
think especially for this time how many
people did that I I can't I can't think
of another standup album that has a just
a sketch all of a sudden like that from
this time period right I mean the other
people who were doing characters like
somebody like Cosby like you mentioned
early it still wasn't a sketch it was a
long long long story they weren't
defined voices they were sort of right
and you didn't have another person join
ex
um or yeah I mean Jonathan wyers and all
those guys did it by themselves but I
can't remember anyone going and now
someone's going to join me and do a bit
so that it seems like if he
had been around 10 years later he would
have just been in a sketch group maybe
right maybe
I I hadn't heard a lot of his character
stuff um until last few years because
when I was in college I was introduced
through women's Studies
classes that we were we were yeah so I
heard the most like the most of scene
that they could get which wasn't really
character-based stuff it was just like
straightforward and that's all I would
listen to was like three or four
Snippets and it wasn't until recently
that I actually started listening to
more of his stuff and I didn't realize
how character-based it is is
wonderful and uh yeah I mean PE it's
interesting cuz some other people we've
talked to on the show like even the
regulars that we spoken to they're
usually they're hesitant to bring up
Lenny Bruce because to them they're like
yeah he's not really a standup and I I I
I would disagree with that I think again
I think people know he's not really a
standup yeah how did they say that I
think they consider him or what how they
really put it maybe not so much not a
stand up but they just generally genu
generally didn't find find them all that
funny which is
it's I think again they're judging him
based on the later stuff where he was
just sitting there and reading Court
transcripts well there's a couple of
Proms and you have to listen to it with
a historical ear a little bit but
um one there are just a ton of
references that would would go by over
anybody's head that isn't like into that
era big time um but to me you get the
gist of what he's talking about even
when he's saying references you you
don't really have to know the reference
to understand the overall bit even like
on this album that the Esther Costello
story that's like a specific movie that
was out that year that he's making fun
of but you still get that the movies he
sets it up he's like it's about a blind
and deaf girl who's blind and deaf this
whole movie is this real sad movie at
the end of the movie she gets uh
brutally raped and all a sudden she's
not for blind anymore and he's like what
kind of moral is
that and he takes and that's funny he
takes like five minutes to say what I
said in in a minute but uh and you might
get lost but uh or he has this other bit
about um calling up to get calling up uh
411 to get a a phone number and it's
just a simple observation that Jerry
Seinfeld probably made you know it's
just like if you call more than once you
feel like changing your voice cuz you
feel like an idiot that's just a simple
comedic pres uh premise but people have
to realize that people didn't really
talk like that and do standup like that
before Lenny so as a standup people
should appreciate that like there's so
many things where where people are like
Ah that's you could even listen to l
Bruce thing and go oh that's hack and
it's like yeah it is hack but he did it
first right right um and people just
don't get it he set up so so much of the
basic structure for how standups do
standup so to say he's not standup is
absurd it's a lot more to say I don't I
don't relate to it I can get sure yeah
you got to concentrate it's a little
intimidating sometimes you really have
to be like focused on it mhm I he's got
a lot more casual approach to the
audience and I don't know again I don't
know what your standup was like but did
did any of that influence you I mean oh
no if you're you're saying that I do
stand up like Lenny Bruce not at all um
but yeah that's what it wasn't an
influence of
like I want to get up there man and
really dig it you know I wasn't uh if
anything the first time I went up
everybody thought I was Bob doing Bobcat
go weight cuz I was so nervous I was
stuttering and my hand arms were shaking
and I had this crazy loud nervous
energy um and people thought was funny
and I was and I pretended that it was on
purpose you know all that nervous energy
and that kind of became
my character for a while which is
nothing like lny Bruce at
all but uh to me it was more the
influence
was especially being in college before I
was doing it at that point was holy [ __ ]
like a standup was a historical figure
like he
the way we think about censorship and
art today he was the the Forefront of
that he he was the middle of that and
that was a standup comedian I think
that's so [ __ ] cool yeah um the only
guy we have to compare that to now would
be Howard Stern right is another hero of
mine and I think he's really
cool
um and like to take just a snippet of
Howard Stern you wouldn't listen to it
go that's genius the way you would a a
Woody Allen bit or a Steve Martin bit or
whatever but you have to kind of take
the
overall you know the the overall
uh body of work and what it means and
what Howard has done for censorship and
freedom of speech and being able to
speak comedically with
freedom and not be repressed and I think
it went from Lenny Bruce pretty much to
him
you know and there were some guys in the
middle
like Richard Pryor Sam Kennison but
uh I think you can almost point to or
Eddie Murphy I can think you can almost
point to some of the stuff they did is
setting
back
uh doing stuff that was offensive and
not intelligent right like when Eddie
Murphy does Ralph you
know you know one of [ __ ] the other
one the ass just we just did that that
record a couple weeks ago yeah it's it's
like as a kid I laughed but like as an
adult look back I'm like that's just
homophobic simple hack [ __ ] yeah um
but that doesn't take away from the
genius of the rest of the album sure um
especially for being however old he
what's that especially for being however
old he was at the time the rest is
pretty damn good right but so people
could say that's offensive and maybe be
right and then but then you point to
Lenny Bruce and he was able to defend
every bit he did he could talk about you
know gay people in this um make fun of
gay people but do it in a more
intelligent empathetic way sure um it
wasn't judgmental there was nothing
judgmental about what he did unless it
was judgmental against being a bigot it
seemed to be you know just just more
smart like he had this bit
about and he says [ __ ] over and over
in a way no one could do that today
because
you would think there was hatred behind
the words but when he did it you didn't
feel you didn't feel that cuz he was
saying ker [ __ ] the next Senate so you
didn't feel like oh he hates mhh you
knew that wasn't going on but his his
bit was something about
uh uh [ __ ] man there's no one braver
in a [ __ ] like uh uh you know these
guys scop to each each other in the
movie theater and just lean over and
start jacking each other out now that's
that's bravery that's courage let's put
those guys
in the Army that's real courage you
don't see any straight guys doing that
they'd get their ass kicked you know and
I don't think that's a hateful
no but you know it just it depends where
and that was such a big point of his you
know that's became his thing was saying
it's context it's how you present
it what's behind the word not the word
itself and you know the whole Michael
Richard's thing he would have been
saying hold on Laugh Factory don't say
you can't say the word [ __ ] that's
crazy yeah you you just can't have a
racist on your stage there's a
difference
between don't say the word and don't
allow racist on your stage and he would
have been smart enough to explain that
and do a funny bit but so many
intelligent comedians were just like
don't say the word and we're going to
stop doing it and we're heroes for doing
that it's the words the problem it's
like come on but unfortunately most
Comics say well that's the drunk to do
and they all do that drunk and they
don't see that kind of drunk the drunks
that they don't report are Cafe drunks
that they see time and time again I call
them white collar
drunks now the best part of these
guys it's not when they're in the club
watching a show is when they first come
in because they're really Juiced out of
their nut but they drug that they don't
want to be associated with drunks and
they just walk extra cool when they were
so no one knows they loaded they think
they're impeccably dressed always clean
shaven buff Nails whacked out of their
skull you think I'm drunk don't you no M
you look perfectly sober godamn right I
am listen right
here hey why don't you stop wiping those
glasses for a minute will you and listen
to me
what do you want some trouble
H want a little trouble glass wiper
huh have they it seems like they've
missed a whole lot I mean were you a fan
of George Carlin I mean after this I
mean I was I was um I mean he he went
out of his way to not be compared to lny
Bruce understandably cuz they're not the
same kind of comics um but I I don't
know I guess I guess my question is is
it is it okay
if is should there be any conflict
between being a funny person and being
important because a lot of people find a
conflict you know or you know just let
him be a comic he doesn't need to be
saying important things
or I know how I feel say again do do you
have to say important things to be a
comedy no I'm saying do you people try
and make it uh exclusive mutually you
have to either be funny or be saying
something important or something
intelligent um and it seems to me and
again people just I think that's what
puts some people off of somebody like
Lenny Bruce where he is he's being
offensive he's also being brilliantly
funny but he's also saying something
important and some people get turned off
by that and I guess my question is why
why do you think that might be that's a
deep question right there it's a little
convoluted actually better way to put it
well first off a lot of people might
know Lenny
Bruce my first intro to him was Lynn
the uh the Dustin Hoffman movie M which
was brilliant and if you watch that you
get the impression that all like I was
saying earlier in this interview all he
did was talk about semantics yeah um and
he did a lot of that and some of his
most brilliant bits are that like that
bit to come come come two preposition
come as a verb
um I think those are the bits that
people know and those that's just a
[ __ ]
satirical bit about language and
censorship and freedom of speech it's
just a real headyy bit but that I think
that's what most people know him for and
that's not all his work and then in the
end all he
did was uh read his court transcripts
and and just kind of do commentary on
him but um he became really obsessed
with that it seemed toward the end yeah
yeah I mean CU that was his whole life
but and I'm pretty sure that's there's
not much if any concert footage of him
besides that so I think
unfortunately that's what he becomes
known for but really that's a small part
of of what his body of work was about it
wasn't all about that um so and how I
try to think who are other comedians
that are
considered what word are we using here
important or I guess
influential and yeah what other ones
would you say like that
like like I don't think him is
necessarily being like if someone would
go he's a political Comm like no he
wasn't I mean he he did talk about
political stuff and racism but he wasn't
Mort Saul who was was his contemporary
that was the he was the political
comedian he makes it crack about him on
this Al some and he makes crack about
Shelley Burman and I've heard I think he
had a a thing with Shelly Burman which I
wish I knew more about cuz he's always
kind of throwing out his name I'm never
really
quite understand what he didn't like
about
him um it seems almost every comedian
lists Lenny Bruce as an influence and
then trying to look up stuff I can't
find people who Lenny Bruce ever said
influenced him like his direct
influences I was having a tough time but
I didn't read his book did you read his
autobiography I've never read his
autobiography so
um was autobiography is half [ __ ]
for one how to influence people on yeah
um I've talked already influence people
like half of it's made up but um the
Albert Goldman biography is is brilliant
it's a great book if you're really
interested but
um yeah I mean who would his since he
pretty much changed stand up that there
there was no one like him mhm like a lot
of people say one of his friends who
wasn't a comedian was his biggest
influence I forget the guy's name but
and there's a lot of comedians who could
say that like I think there's a lot of
comedians who have that funny friend
they grew up with who was funny and
never became a comedian but was very
influential in their sense of humor and
uh Lenny Bruce definitely had that guy
in his life it's a shame I can't
remember his name um but other than that
he it was all cheesy kind of jokey
you know hny
Youngman type humor it was uh it was
either jokes or Impressions it wasn't
people just speaking honestly about
stuff it must have been freeing to be
able to find something else to talk
about but then at the same time to be
sort of slapped around for talking about
something different besides the old [ __ ]
I I I just can't imagine what that feels
like and I feel like no there aren't any
stand-ups who nowadays who have anything
comparable to deal with there's not much
to deal with is there what do you mean
no outside influence other other than
just your life spouting your life out on
stage maybe finding a character and
doing something but I mean he had you
know politics to deal with he had people
he had the uh you know he had the FBI he
had everybody else you know trying to
clap down on him I I don't feel like we
have that well what we do have
interestingly enough is
uh what has happened to Michael Richards
what happened to Tracy
Morgan um
um is
technology is technology going to start
censoring Comedians and then what
happened to Patton Oswalt recently too a
standup ComEd
uh he was doing a set basically
uh not an open mic show but a small show
at a restaurant or something and a
member of the audience started taping
him and he was like stop taping me and
then they got into it
um you know and
uh you know he went after her like you'd
go after a Heckler sure and then a
fellow standup the next day wrote A Blog
you know calling him an [ __ ]
so and I don't want to lump Tracy Morgan
and Michael Richards Paton all together
but it's basically it's like now we have
people in the audience with their cell
phones who can now take take a piece of
material out of cont text mhm or even
not the material just have their opinion
online on Twitter immediately mhm uh
like it just happen to D Cooks I'm I'm
listening like four or five examples of
cell phones or Twitter or social
networking commenting on a standup
immediately and the standup in the worst
case ruining his life with Michael
Richards yeah a little less than that
Tracy Morgan affecting his career career
not ruining it but definitely him being
slapped around having to make apologies
and
[ __ ] Patton in his case not
affecting his career but him having to
deal with [ __ ] online for a week
same with Dan cook so it definitely
affects people it affects the next way
they're going to do material the next
time they're up or maybe it doesn't that
just
depends how they're going to deal with
this new type of censorship but it is
kind of a it's not from the government
it's from our own fans yeah it's kind of
weird or our fellow
comedians for you I mean have you ever
experienced anything like that I mean I
know you don't I mean do you still do
standup or are you still exclusively I
know you do shows I do know you
do um uh yeah I do I don't know if you
call it stand up I do solo I go up solo
and do characters or do what I would
call bits mhm
um have have I I've been affected by
this what I'm calling technological
censorship I I don't think so I mean
I've done stuff before
where I I've I'm always going after the
pope and the CH molestation stuff in the
Catholic church I just think it's crazy
and I think it's crazy how people don't
talk about it I think it's crazy
how cath people call themselves
Catholics don't do more about it so I'm
always making fun of that
and I was doing a bit one I think I was
the I was being the the Nazi Pope and
doing a bit about it in in the bit
talking about how um Hispanic Catholics
in particular are crazy on the down low
and no one will admit to being gay in
that culture which is dead on fact and
this Hispanic Catholic in the crowd uh
uh threw a chair at me on stage really
what yeah
so it definitely riled him up enough to
get violent and then I didn't break
character but we we we I I taunted him a
lot about that religion is definitely
something that people kind of go off and
I think that's one of the reasons that
people singled any Bruce out so much for
the obscenity stuff was the
religious yeah they say in when he got
busted in Chicago that is what it was
about um they might have pointed to the
the obscenities the reason but they say
him going after the Catholic church in a
town like Chicago was the his biggest
mistake yeah and that's what the cops
were saying when they were busting him
he even does that bit though on there
about how it's going to offend the Jews
so you know we think it's probably going
to offend we think it'll offend the
Gentiles too yeah he does this bit about
going on the Steve Allen Show which is
another behind the scenes stand up and
talking about censorship which is
fascinating me about going on the show
and it sounds like a a
story that Bill Hicks would have told
about Letterman or Louis SE could tell
about going on Letterman or Conan today
about how they they go through your bit
you know the guys on the shows they
still do that and they examine every bit
for who it could possibly offend and
it's not just words it it can like this
particular bit was about he couldn't you
can't get buried in a Jewish cemetery if
you have a tattoo Steve Allen's got a
very hip sense of humor and he cracks up
everything I'm doing producer bill
harbach is hip but he's got a little
more to lose so he gives these kind of
laughs
like now I went into a bit they didn't
let me do on the island show I have a
tattoo it's really it's not a cocka M or
anything doesn't rub off because of this
tattoo I never couldn't be buried in a
Jewish cemetery that's the Orthodox
scene have to go out of the world the
way you came in no mark no changes which
certainly disab the rabbi philosophy I
don't know where that
swings I got back from Malala so I'm
over my aunt's house in Jamaica Long
Island I'm in a kitchen I'm washing with
a Roki
soap she pins the tattoo so she looks
and she
flips it's your real Jewish seago you
say look at you did you're ruin your arm
you can't be better than that je
Cemetery what do you cut the they B this
in a gentile Cemetery like you all right
okay
now the guy says to me you can't do that
joke why not um so his suggestion was
well I only have a tattoo on my arm so
bury uh all my body in the Jewish
cemetery except for my arm bury that in
a Christian Cemetery and they're like
well that's offensive to the Jews and
he's like no it's not and then they took
a day to think about it and they came
back they're like you know Lenny we
thought about it and uh it's definitely
offensive to the Christians too because
that implies Christians will be bury
anything in their
cemeter so there's no cursing there it's
based upon a fact that Jews have that
silly thing in their religion about
tatos MH and he certainly wasn't making
fun of Christians that's a that's just
looking to be offended kind thing so it
points
out the absurdity of censorship yeah and
uh and it's crazy how I bet you could
still you could do that joke without
problem right now on TV but I but I bet
they look over it a few times still yeah
and think about it well there's a couple
people like Tim mention currently who's
really
pushing his atheistic comedy everything
is about religion with him and it's all
about atheism and he can't get any
anything on American TV for the most
part he's been on a ton of podcasts he's
been he's got specials but he can't get
on anything
interesting I guess it scares people but
I yeah at the end of the day the bottom
line is what's what's in the way of of
of speaking your piece a little bit I
mean
does I don't know uh I had another
question they they seem so fluid Lenny
Bruce's stuff to come back to this every
bit seems so fluid was it all written or
was there a level of improv impro
another wasn't not much I I don't know
if he says it on this one or another one
I was listening to but he even speaks to
that he was actually it wasn't this one
it's another one he's talking
about um these these bits
really uh written out people think I'm
ad libing but I adli at most like 10 to
15 words per bit that's right so uh no
he he these were well thought out bits
um if you hear him do them on different
versions are like yeah that's pretty
much the same way another interesting
thing about
the padium bit which I didn't find out
until I was
improvising Dell close was a
contemporary of Lenny Bruce and he is
the mentor of the Upright Citizens
Brigade he's one of the original Second
City committee guys who invented the way
we do improv today and
he told us a story of when Lenny Bruce
was working this bit up was first
working on this bit the plaum about the
standup who goes to the Big Show in
London uh dell was in the audience with
his friend
Frank and that's how the character name
came Lenny Bruce is out there and he
sees both of them together so when it
comes time in the bit to name the
comedian he goes Frank
Dell and that became the
the bit so that that's such a kism weird
thing for me that in
college I would love this particular bit
so much and then eventually the guy who
the guy's named after becomes my mentor
it's very small world weirdness there
you're going to have to put a cover of
this a photo of this up on oh I know it
has to go this just an amazing cover
insane it is I want to buy that from you
do you think they have that cover do
they have that other album they have
another one of those they might you can
have this one you kiding me oh no no no
not at all they've got a good selection
of stuff at the um Counterpoint right
next to the theater there his first
album which I have is
uh the sick humor of Lenny Bruce I've
never heard that one and they have a
bunch of those in the store and I wanted
to buy this one it's and it's uh it
shows him in a eating a a picnic layout
on
a uh grave in a graveyard and that was
just considered crazy back then yeah I
mean it's even pretty sick now
but then that can I see that was
considered just outlandish what year is
that album I'm going to guess
1957 or 56 of course it doesn't so it's
definitely old wow um I you know I was
actually thinking about this listening
through through this and then again
realizing how how much he depended on
voices listening to your stuff in
podcasts and seeing you online and and
your sketches as far as your voices a
lot of them do you've got some similar
intonation sometimes when you do voices
I mean does that come out intentionally
or is there definitely not I think
that's the Jewish Gene if
anything cuz there's an English voice on
here that he does is very similar to one
you were doing on on I can't remember
what probably Comedy Bang Bang the other
day but yeah like almost spot on and
that's true what what's really
impressive and I I wish I've challenged
myself to do and I really Haven it is
how he goes back and forth so quickly
between the voices MH um that's just a
that's a difficult skill it and he he
utilizes the different intonation
microphone too like he would pull it
away you hear it louder he does that a
lot so you really have to I I really say
to say it I have to focus I was trying
to listen to this uh last weekend on the
treadmill and I'm running and there's
like TVs around me and stuff and I'm
like I couldn't I couldn't like no and
he does a lot of bits where he kind of
just have half sentences where he just
kind of ends and you just kind of have
to be in the
flow you know where he's going you just
have to know it's like you fill in the
blank like you know what the guy's
thinking I think that's that's that's a
lot of the charm of it I loved listening
to I cannot remember the album that I
first heard it would it had some bits to
this so it might have been a compilation
actually now that I think about it yeah
the the I almost chose the one that's
called the what's it called the bits
that got me arrested or whatever that
that
has if you're going to get one Lenny
Bruce you probably get that one cuz it
is all the the famous bits um Carnegie
Hall is also just fascinating cuz it was
such a big night for him
yeah um and and there is stuff that's a
little more EX extemporary in there I
love the writing on this one says if you
value your license and reputation do not
Air This Record obscene not fair but I
know that's from well that's from my
that's my from my radio station I stole
these records from but yeah those are
warnings from it's like we have this
record but you can't play
it and that's you know the
1990 and I try not to harp on this too
much cuz people get I think get annoyed
with it but the physicality of having a
record I mean did you did you every time
we talk to somebody usually they've got
a moment where they just sat down with
the headphones and and and a record
player and just listened and just had an
experience with them themselves in the
record I mean is that part of maybe not
this album but I mean can you relate to
that that's
interesting um when I say a moment with
yourself it sounded a little creepier
than
actually it's funny by the time that
I was fantasizing about being a comedian
myself I was in college M and that's
exactly when
CDs was starting to to take
off
um so in the way I think you're saying
like I sat down and would look at a
Woody on thing and go one day one day or
something like that like I don't know if
I had that moment like to me I like
these these uh cassettes you see here I
got these on the streets of Boston and
to me there was something more
more what's the word uh Contraband or
something cool about the like Lenny
Bruce cassette that I can't find in
vinyl that I could only find in a
cassette on the street in a
city
so or in St Mark's Place and you know in
New York City or something like that so
uh that might have had more of a punk
rock feel versus my record
collection like I said it was all it's
it's I still have every comedy record
that I've ever bought but it's it would
be all my parents Bill Cosby's and then
once I got to college I was getting
funny ones like I got this one here
called the undernourished comedian
Frankie Scott you're in my act a
hilarious comedy Party album recorded
live for adults only and it's just
[ __ ]
all these jokes about being skinny oh
God amazing and I got another one called
Sam levenson but seriously
folks and that one's just family comedy
it's about this is comedy anyone in the
family can listen
to I got Freddy Prince Dick Gregory fire
sign
theater Flip
Wilson Oh what would you you that's the
one I have one I bought we haven't done
that one yet doesn't have a name great
it's really good does it have recipes on
the back re on the yes is great it is a
lost art form again I won't harp on it
but you know you get to play with it a
little bit more there's you got you know
I gu I I guess CDs you can have more
liner notes and all that all M were now
I mean even CDs are disappearing people
are which I think it's a shame I mean
this this thing of just doing stuff
digitally I I think it just just stuff
just disappears to The Ether I I feel
like songs that I buy on iTunes like
they just disappear the next time I get
a computer or something like I'm it's
like oh stick your stick in the clouds
like it's not the same to me no I do
want to hold it in my hand on some level
yeah I feel like people are losing
something especially with comedy because
you don't feel like you own it you don't
have again you don't have a thing latch
on to if you can't go see it you need to
have it at least for me I needed to have
it in person in my hand that was why I
love to listen to George Carlin and you
know have something physical now if I
can only straighten out govern a
long doesn't want to listen to me I
would have had him over but he won't
dress you know just sits in his pajamas
won't put his teeth in or anything is
sitting cursing at his wife running
around taking species of motels like
he's really a delight though he really
cracked me he had the greatest political
campaign of any public figure I sh him
on television dig his political platform
I'm not a
nut what is that right no honesty better
schools I'm not a nut that's all I got
so I don't wet the bed elect me that's
all
forget Governor long is really a sign of
our times how did the governor get out
he fired the people who put him
in go fight that kind of
action you're a nut you're
fire I only had records growing up
because my parents were had a huge
record collection so I all the Cosby
stuff and the stuff that I wasn't
allowed to listen to was locked in a
liquor cabinet which was the the um uh
Richard prior at was of course we
because of the dirty words
just in the same way we got into the
liquor cabinet for the liquor we also
got into the liquor cabinet for the for
the records too but I bought records
when I was in college because they were
a lot cheaper at the local store I could
buy a record for a dollar and I got to
buy a CD for 20 at the time it was
before the price would even come down
cuz CDs were just yeah ridiculous that
is um uh I don't know do you do you see
any possibility for Resurgence in this
kind of thing for exactly the reason
we're talking about where people might
possibly want I mean I know some people
do Li
releases on vinyl and all that stuff I
went to a recording the other night that
they're only going to release on vinyl
Jah right yeah that was there the other
night so and he's doing it almost like
it's like that's what's partly funny
about it is it's released on vinyl
there's there's definitely part of it
I'll tell you I got you guys made me
bring this this Technics back out from
the garage I mean that's where it's been
for the last four years Danielle was
like why are you bringing that out my
wife and I'm
like um cuz I want to list my records
she's like but you never list to your
records I'm like I know because it's
it's in the garage awesome um so it got
me to listen to some stuff I hadn't
listened to in a while um and there's a
couple of bands that only released on
vinyl and they've given me records which
have just sat in my closet for the last
two years and now I finally can listen
to their music so you guys definitely
brought me back to the Vine
pretty funny the problem with in my life
and it's a silly thing to say but there
aren't a lot of flat surfaces on my in
my house to put a uh heavy Technics
record player down
on um it's definitely a commitment to of
space you have to make it is in v in the
storage of the vinyl is too I think
probably everybody has a water damage or
sunlight story if they're vinyl
collectors yeah
um but yeah it's a shame there's certain
guys in music like Steve Albini who
uh very adamant about keeping vinyl
around just because um a belief that
it's better sound quality even right um
once you get past the snaps and
Pops well I mean some of these are
beautiful sounding some of the the I I
found a few I think this one was in
pretty good shape even though I heard a
skip on it last night I was listening to
the MP3 skipping like crazy but um yeah
no I love that it's important to me just
as in comedy although Again comedy
albums are cheaper I just love the
physical whether it's CD or record I
love having the physical in my hand like
I I still Ru the day that I went and
took my CDs out of their Jewel cases and
put them in books so now I've got six
books and I hate that now when I buy a
new CD I've got to shift the entire
album over and then so I can throw
another a in there you have to
alphabetize I do that's a mental problem
beond but I I need the physical thing
and I'll throw it on my computer now I
have it but when my computer dies guess
what I still have the album I don't I
don't have to put it in the cloud or pay
money or whatever sound like old men I
just love it I love the physical copy um
I don't want to keep you much longer but
as as as far as uh you know if you were
to leave people cuz you know one of the
reasons we do this is so that people
listen to stuff they've never heard of
or they never would have thought to
listen to why would you say listen to
this
album um
I I guess if if it's about if it's if if
it's to to learn about Lenny Bruce it
might not be the Sal it might be the one
that uh is called um what I was arrested
for uhhuh um cuz that has all the famous
bits and probably even more of his
Classic Bits but so I might I'm I'm
working my way out of your question I'm
not sure I would cuz you guys asked me
what was my most influential so I would
I guess I would recommend it maybe to
someone who's fascinated by the history
of Comedy yeah and that's why I think
this
is it's something he talks a lot about
that bit the plaum I just think is a
classic bit yeah that needs to be
listened to and then I think these other
bits are just just really show off his
his character work like he does that one
the white color
drunks which is just a very
simple like he wouldn't have been
arrested for that right and uh but you
know what he could do that on TV today
yeah it's just all about it's just a
very simple observation that when people
mostly do drunks they do the
typical uh back alley fall
down red nose drunk yeah and he does the
white color
wine drunk it's just a different kind of
specific drunk and you want to relate to
that you know what what is it 50 years
later you could you could do that on TV
tonight just do it really well like he
does it or you could do it lame and not
be that good
so so as a as a as a as a sketch guy
who's not really a standup I think this
is a cool stand to look at that most
people wouldn't think you would think
you think John winners when you
think stand up and sketch you don't
think Lenny
brce that's a really good point or you
think Robin Williams or Billy Crystal or
those guys are Dana Carvey you know but
Lenny Bruce you
think straight ahead talker talking
about politics
and which really isn't entirely what he
was at all maybe most famously what he
was but not entirely what he was so he
he he did so much for standup just in
general I think art in general like
across the board he's done so much for
it without his obscenity trial and what
he did then yeah like you said earlier
where would we be with a lot of this
stuff yeah it's good to have that to to
look back on if somebody tries to shut
you down not that I've had that happen
but you know if if I were lucky enough
to have somebody try and shut me down it
would be good to have this as a backup
up I think and it's not only just when
you mean shut you down you mean like you
can't say that yeah
um it also should be uh something to
think about what you maybe shouldn't say
or like just be smarter about what you
do say when you
do like to
me our this era of comedy's [ __ ] is uh
gay people um and I don't think there's
a lot of people saying the word [ __ ]
necessarily there is there is some
but I I don't think there's I think more
of the problem is jokes the punchline is
just and he was gay yeah and he sucked a
[ __ ] and that's just the whole punchline
and that's just that's homophobic and
hateful and
people we should be offended by that
people should think of the semantics of
how you use the word gay right um and
that's the type of stuff that lyy Bruce
talked about too it wasn't just we
should be free to say anything you got
to see the other side of the coin too
it's like in a good context because I
think oh this is actually pretty
interesting the obscenity
law comes down
to
um there's like four points um one is it
cons is it trying to create lustful
intent in the audience right so that's
one thing
um the other one is it offensive by the
community
standard um which as he pointed out in
the area of San Francisco where he got
busted there were strip bars on every
side of them so that Community can he
say that his words were creating more
lust than the
actual tits and ass around him of course
not um wait what what got me into this
or we just talking about the comun of
this the four points of the observ no
right before
that shutting down yes yeah using words
respons oh the judge said he he said uh
if the words have to offensive words
have to prove that has at least
some redeemable
intent and and and the judge rulle that
his did and l Bruce is like I don't want
that to be what gets me off I think the
whole thing is redeemable so you're
basically saying it's all [ __ ] except
for a little piece and he's like [ __ ]
that that gives everybody a right just
to come out and be dumb asses and
pretend to be smart for it and then it's
okay he's like I don't want to represent
that everything I'm saying is smart yeah
so don't act like I'm just coming up
here going [ __ ] [ __ ] tit ass mhm and and
what's funny is when he was being when
they would read back why he was in the
court they would have the cops come up
there and read testimony they're like
these uh this is the words this is what
his act was but they would just read the
curse words so this there go uh tits
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] tits tits ass
[ __ ] [ __ ] and it's like Lenny's
like wait a minute this is this is how
you're going to judge my ACT can I do my
act and he he made the judge make him do
allow him to do the act in court it's
like you're completely taking these
words out of context and if this is a
just like people do to Howard Stern like
people who don't know Howard Stern think
he's just the judging
strippers part of the show they've seen
on the E network they don't know he's
speaking very satirically
about life Society politics every day
you just don't hear that that part of
the show so you just they just judge it
by the one part it's like no man he's
it's it's all good that's the hard part
there's no filter for intelligent people
intelligent people have to listen to the
whole thing all the way through and
intelligent people would want to listen
to the but that's everything becomes a
filter in order to condense it and make
it interesting to people yeah and that's
frightening and sad but exactly what
you're talking about you don't want he
doesn't want to stand for people just
saying whatever the hell they want just
because they can but it happens you know
not to make this too political but it
happens way too frequently I I think in
comedy I have a podcast called improv
for humans it's on the awolf uh.com
Improv 4 that's the number four for
humans and uh if you go to MattB uh at
Mat Fester on Twitter that's where I get
my suggestions from that we improvise
from so check that out that's awesome
awesome thank you again and uh thanks to
Mike and thanks to Matt pester and
everybody have a good thing thank you
good he all right folks do a little bit
here uh screw Ireland folks how about
that H they really bum wrapped you the
IRA I read about them they're really no
good screwy Irish what do you say about
that
one they really give you a hard time
those mix how about it folks screw the
Irish what do you say about that thing
HH okay a Heckler in the balcony that's
the funniest thing you've said all night
boy that's like screw Island screw
Island
take it easy Buster let's not get out of
line it's just a little joke now bust
school school Island the manager what's
going on out there school Island School
Island get that bum off the stage go to
the newal scool the bast get the Bobbies
back Folks School the Irish they stole
the ground back back to the dressing
[Music]
room he was
comedy unital is recorded at Fort
awesome studios in beautiful downtown
Burbank California it is produced by
Mike Warden and edited by Jason clown
comedy vinyl is a production of stolen
dress entertainment visit stolen
dress.com to listen to our other podcast
watch our films read our books look at
pictures of us go to our websites read
things about us etc etc please make sure
to subscribe to Comedy on vinyl on
iTunes and rate US highly uh you can
also follow us on Twitter at comedy
onvinyl or facebook.com/ comdy onvinyl
also please be sure to subscribe to our
latest podcast which is called looking
forward a hope moir in case you can't
spell that just look it up on Stolen
dress.com it is the audio book of my
first book that came out in 2008 and the
audio book we released uh just last year
so please yeah check it out it's free I
think it's pretty funny it's going to be
rolling out over the next couple uh
months yeah the whole thing will be
there thank you so much and have a great
thing
[Music]