[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast hi everybody it's Jason clom uh
this week we're not talking about a
particular album but I do have you know
I didn't ask you do you want me to call
you John Schwarz um John Bermuda Schwarz
today I'm you're Bermuda today all right
Bermuda Schwarz is in the in the studio
with me so uh let's talk about your
influences so I know that I emailed you
a long time ago and you're like I didn't
listen to a lot of comedy albums that's
fine you're on a lot of comedy albums I
listen to so I still want to talk to you
about your influences um so you're a
master mimic in terms of and maybe
that's by uh maybe because you had to be
but or is that something that you've
always done I think I've always done
that I always heard stuff on on records
and on the radio and I always imitated
that so I was already tuned into hearing
something and duplicating it mhm and or
trying to duplicate it so you know Al
didn't have to get me up to speed at all
I was already there I was already on on
board with him and the way he wanted to
do things M uh some of the early stuff I
I grew up in listening to music in the
early 60s and and into the 70s of course
uh you know my parents had uh I did have
you know some comedy albums in the house
had Alan Sherman sure and uh uh you know
some kind of things like that and and
some Jewish uh comedian albums and stuff
and uh but my parents also had Latin
orchestras and Jee Kuper records and
stuff like that and by the time I
started becoming aware of a lot of uh
pop music the Beatles had just had I was
sitting in front of the TV on February
9th 19 you know 64 wow like like
millions of others were MH and uh uh so
the Beatles of course were a big
influence uh you know a little later
Frank Zappa and sort of his humorous
take on a lot of stuff sure um you know
I just I I uh as it turns out Al
listened to a lot of the same stuff that
I did I mean you he was just a a couple
years behind me age-wise but he was a
big fan of The Beatles And The Kinks and
uh the monkeys and the Rolling Stones
and and Zappa and you know we listen to
a lot of the same stuff and we also both
listen to the Dr Demento show I think I
started listening probably in 71 or so
and how early is that into the run of
the show very early I think within just
a year yeah okay that makes sense wow
that must have been like the first year
yeah yeah I know they called 1991 his
20th anniversary so oh okay yeah all
right 70 or 71 would have been started
here in Los Angeles gosh and so I was
right on board with that as was Al as
were a ton of people in high school and
Junior High yeah so it's what we listen
to did you have a ton of friends who
also listen to dementa with you or was
it your thing where you were no a bunch
of people uh uh bunch of uh friends and
also bandmates and school orchestra and
stuff like that and those were the
people that worked with me on Pico and
svh and the ballot of woodsie owl and uh
um Mr ghost goes to town okay yeah so
they were you know they weren't just oh
we have to do a music project it's like
cool we're gonna send something to Dr
dento that's so great and so it was
although all of that stuff I mean I
really shouldn't have taken credit for
it I mean I sort of organized it and I
was the contact person but I I certainly
didn't write any of the songs uh I I
really didn't sing or very much on any
of the songs you know yet it became
known as the John Schwarz project yeah
yeah yeah okay and and actually I think
at the time it was just John Schwarz and
later on in deference to all of them we
we agreed that John Schwarz project was
a little more inclusive okay and uh it
uh you know that was that was the
beginning for me you know with with
catering to Dr Demento a little bit at a
time when not many people were sending
homemade tapes yeah uh I was I was
literally the the second or third person
ever to get a homemade tape plate on his
show that's insane which is what
prompted the interview in 1980 where I
met Al yeah oh my God that's that's a
very quick history of that brings us up
from the Beatles to Al mhm a strange
trip what a short strange trip it's been
you know you mentioned in your email the
Beatles and the other day I actually had
another drummer on the podcast is uh
name is Tony Thaxton he's a great
drummer uh and uh also just a very funny
dude and we we were drawing all kinds of
just comparisons between like how
comedians learn to M mimic when they're
young and same as drummers same maybe
maybe most musicians are just going to
learn of course by listening first I
would unless your Mozart when she seemed
to be able to pick it up immediately but
uh he mentioned the Beatles and I was
like you know we could have talked about
the Beatles as a comedy group he's like
well shoot we should have done that
because I I don't know did you have was
it just their music or did you like them
as funny guys too did you watch the
movies well yeah I was I was right there
with hard days night and and help and uh
eventually Magical Mystery Tour which
was I wouldn't I don't know if it was
intentionally funny but right right
right uh you know yeah I was I you know
all the the TV appearances and stuff
like that and and the teen magazines and
books that were coming out and all of
that stuff I was right there got every
album you know whenever a new album was
coming out there was always you know
that was a birthday present or a
Christmas present or a you know I was I
did good in school present or whatever
it was you know that was always my
reward was getting an album that's great
uh bought the singles I mean I I just I
was really really into that yeah you
know probably more so than than other
contemporary groups like The Beach Boys
at the time and the stones at the time
even I mean I came to appreciate those
groups later on sure uh when the monkeys
came along they were that was what the
prefab for yeah they referred to them
and and and there was a lot of that kind
of very obviously deliberately you know
the the comedy and and you know the
interaction between the guys and a lot
of good music a lot of great music you
know written by a lot of great
songwriters yeah uh so so that was the
attraction too you know for that so I I
guess really Mo most important was the
music for me and uh as it is with
anybody of course yeah what were what
bands before you got to Al what bands
were you in because I I read off of your
website just that you were seem to be in
a bunch of bands before
I I I played with a bunch of different
people I think my first well my first
real band was 1970 or 71 with some guys
from school not my school from another
school that's funny which at the time
was unheard of I mean you really didn't
have a way of connecting with people
yeah you unless you went to school with
them or or they lived in your
neighborhood and I honestly don't
remember how I got hooked up with them
but they went to uh Culver High uhhuh
and I I was in Hamilton High okay and uh
they'd come over to the house and it was
a very odd uh it was a tree well they
played together okay okay one guy played
Flute one guy played piano all right
they called themselves r&t unlimited M
and the uh the r was Jeff Rona okay Jeff
became he is uh he does a lot of
Hollywood TV scores and stuff like that
he he got seriously into the business uh
and the T was Bill turer okay and Bill
played piano he could play trumpet he
played guitar he could play drums he was
one of those guys that could could put
his hands on an instrument and make it
work jez and sound really good at it but
no bass player at the time so they'd
come over we had a piano in the house
and and I'd bring my drums downstairs
into the the living room where the piano
was and they'd ride their bikes over
sure and uh you know no amps no nothing
you know the flute player would have the
flute you know in a backpack and that
was it yeah and and we'd play Just drums
Bas and piano I'm sorry drums uh flute
and piano that's crazy now my archiving
began at that point really I'm I'm well
known as archist and a lot of stuff I
made tapes of every rehearsal that we
did real toore tapes and all of that's
been committed now to digital and and uh
I just I don't know why I just I you
know I must have been very proud of
myself and thought that'd be cool stuff
to have and as it turns out it was cool
stuff did you have you do you listen
back Have you listened back do you
listen back often two separate questions
um I have and uh not terribly often I
mean you know it's interesting you know
it's it was very early on in my drumming
uh experience i' had only been drumming
for
um about five maybe five years okay okay
and not really you know not doing
anything professionally MH and uh I I
you know I I because I wasn't
experienced I tried I did a lot of
things that that weren't the norm sure
you know that weren't maybe considered
to be right and therefore some of them
were actually pretty cool cuz I just
took chances and did some pretty cool
things I also did some really bad things
so I listen and and it's like you know
it's like oh I would never do that now
and then you know that's like God I'm so
glad I don't and then I listen to other
things it's like God I I would never do
that now I'm like too much and you know
I'm too much in a box now to do things a
certain way I would never go outside of
the box like I did back then without
even thinking about it without knowing
and it's like you you learn you learn to
to be sort of in a box yeah the cool
thing is there's a bunch of money in the
corner of that box of course of course
you a little dark corner of the box it's
great but you know I listen to stuff
it's like God I I would never play those
parts now and it's too bad yeah was you
were you self-correcting as a quote
unquote better drummer or just as a more
experienced drummer or was it like did
you take lessons were you working with
other people who are drummers or was it
just self-correcting well I I did take
lessons and a lot of it was you know I
would and at the time I would listen to
these tapes and and uh to hear back what
I had done okay and it's and uh so I was
able to hear things I knew back then
it's like that's not working and then I
knew back then also it's like wow that
was a really cool lick and listening to
that stuff 40 plus years later uh it's
like yeah that's still that's a cool
lick I have I have to remember that I
have to you know bring that back into
rotation and then other things I did
it's like boy I'm so glad I grew up and
got out of doing that kind of miserable
stuff yeah but interestingly the the two
guys and we added a base player soon
after that and we we
uh well the order is the order of it is
we first did uh Pico and Suva yeah sent
that into Dro that was April of
19873 right okay and uh we sent that in
and it got one it got it came in second
out of like over 100 entries of local
people now the show was only local at
the time it wasn't National and uh and
we uh we came in second and because it
was an instrumental mhm Dr Demento
played it as his theme song for some
time he could over it right course you
know without obscuring the lyrics that
we didn't do uh uh um shortly now one
other interesting note Al had also uh
submitted an entry to the peon Spa
contest really I as I learned more about
it first I thought you know well he did
he didn't now Dr dendo played the top 10
entries yeah that night and and uh we
didn't know until we heard it come on
the radio that we had placed at all
that's great uh Al was not in there and
I thought oh you know poor Al didn't
make it into the well it turns out I
just found out recently from Dr dento Al
submitted his tape too late oh no he
gave he gave it to Dr nendo personally
uhhuh at an Afterschool assembly at
Lynwood High uhhuh uh in in uh April or
maybe late April of 83 MH and and it was
too late to uh be submitted to me and
and Demento put it in the trunk of his
car it stayed in there he sold the car
oh no and it's
probably probably somebody saw that and
erased over it or threw it out that's
hard so there's there's apparently not a
recording of This anywhere no and in
those days you recorded something on a
cassette and you just sent it off you
didn't keep a copy so there's no well he
says there's no copy of it right right
right right anyway uh we uh so there
were a number of players on on this uh
peon SP thing all from some from my
school MH and some from other schools we
had a guy named Barry keys on trombone
Barry I think went on to play in The
Tonight Show band wow for a time we had
uh this Jeff Rona was in there Bill
Turner um had a couple of people from
the school orchestra in Hamilton High at
the time we had a guy named Richard
Elliot on Sachs Richard Elliott is a
very well-known sex player okay now he's
not if if you named the top five Sachs
players you know you first say well
Kenny G everyone knows K sure sure
Richard would be in that top five that's
amazing that's shows how much I know
about music of course that I'm hearing
this all for the first time but that's
amazing it's it's uh and and there was
there was someone else as well I just I
can't think of every I've got it all
written down some sure anyway the core
of that uh went on we decided that uh
beginning of 1974 we recorded another
song The Ballad of woodsy owl uhhuh now
that was just uh that was uh Jim Walker
on bass Bill Turner on piano Jeff Rona
on I don't know if I I guess he was
playing flute okay um my brother came in
and played uh something on it okay uh
played Maybe guitar or banjo or
something uh there were basic drums on
there and then I sort of sang talked
sang uh you know the the lyrics not very
well even though I wasn't singing you
could tell I couldn't sing and we sent
that in and that got played that's so
you well it's it's uh I was graduating
in in 74 U the other guys you know were
still at this other high school and we
we somehow wangled our way into the LA
County Battle of the Bands this was like
a real Battle of the Bands sponsored by
the city pars and Recreation I think
sponsored it and uh they had uh prelims
at some of the different schools around
and somehow I had gotten hooked up with
uh well I know how I I was seeing a girl
at at Culver High okay that I had met
through these other guys and back in the
day I used to leave my high school at
noon MH and go over to Culver High and
go have lunch there when you could go
walk on someone El campus sure go have
lunch and then go sit in on the classes
for periods five and six like in Theater
Arts and in their band classes I ended
up playing with their Stage Band for
something I don't know why that would
never happen now you could never do that
and uh but we we went through all the
prelims as a combo group The the four of
us Jim Bill Jeff and I and we made it to
the Hollywood Bowl finals and played the
Hollywood Bowl it not my 74 was not
still not my first time at the Hollywood
Bowl I did something there with with the
marching band a couple of times but wow
this was this was pretty cool you know
where when we were the four of us were
playing there were like people just
watching us that's insane and we tied
for first place wow uh on that they made
up an album which I'm sure only the
people who were in The Thing bought
copies I was see even then I was smart I
bought two albums of course one to keep
one to have yeah yeah yeah and and uh so
one is open mhm and one is still sealed
oh man and uh so that was pretty cool so
you know we essentially won the the 1974
in the combo division mhm uh I don't
know that anybody else from that uh
competition went anywhere didn't I mean
we certainly didn't as a band right
however Jeff Rona won instrumentalist of
the night really for his flute playing
that's awesome so he was already you
know he was already spotted as being a
talent and I think the judges were uh
Pete Chris Le who was one of the studio
uh I think a flute or a sax player okay
okay uh Tom Scott uh um uh Mercer
Ellington who was Duke Ellington's son
all right and some other you know like
an industry heavyweight was there and
they were the judges that's great at the
bowl so that was pretty cool anyway we
we gradually as we as they graduated
high school we did one more thing and
this is like June of 75 long time
between these things that we recorded
for Dr dendo we did Mr ghost Goes to
Town uhuh and sent that in and that got
played so good and still gets played
every couple of Halloweens mhm and after
that we didn't do much musically you
know I I want to say that was my first
group r&t unlimited or actually we
called ourselves Pursuit okay by the
time we were doing the Hollywood Bowl
thing it was Pursuit MH and within a few
years after that we sort of all went our
separate ways Somebody went to school or
I went got a job or whatever it was
anyway
um but I I wasn't in another group like
really in a group until maybe 7879 I met
some guys and uh met a gentleman named
Joan Nipper mhm and Joe and his brother
Scott Nipper and uh a guy who played
trumpet harmonica saxophone flute uh
named Kevin Anderson William K
Anderson uh were had me do some demos
with them I was doing a lot of Demos in
the in the late 70s around town and I'd
run into these guys and I can't remember
how I met them but we wound up doing
this group called Nipper uhhuh and we
did all the new wave clubs around town
that's awesome made nothing mhm you know
put put together made up a single and uh
I did up the artwork for the single now
back then I you know we didn't have
computers this is like 1980 so no
computers no Photoshop you know not not
for me MH so literally I was doing rub
on letters lret really buy a big sheet
of of letters and and you know there'd
be like you know in in a very limited
selection of type faces and you get a
whole font you know all the characters
in this particular type face Pioneer
helvetica you know stuff like that there
were maybe a dozen that you could get
yeah and I have I had this nylon
burnishing tool you know with kind of a
little bit of a soft point on it that
you could actually rub the letter on and
completely rub it on okay I knew how to
Drew draw blue lines cuz when you shot
it to be reproduced the blue would
disappear show up right yeah and and it
was all very and so I did all the
layouts for that I I did the photos
again no help from Photoshop developed
photos and cut them up and lined them up
and did this whole thing and put
together all the art for the label and
and the artwork on a sleeve for the
single that's great we did uh so even
then I was sort of involved a little bit
in the logistics of of uh doing stuff MH
and
uh September 14th 1980 now I'm still
working with Nipper at the time I'm
working at uh uh North Hollywood
speedometer MH which was one a
speedometer repair shop okay as well as
an off-road equipment shop lighting and
and different kinds of things that
they'd have for different cars and I
worked in shipping and
receiving there and I had come from a
Cadillac dealer in Glendale went to work
there and it was during that time I met
Al yeah and uh we did uh we recorded
Another One Rides the Bus M and uh I I I
don't know what the exact words I said
but folkore suggests that it was uh hey
Al you you know you should have a band
I'll be your drummer yeah yeah and and
those fateful words right so you know
when we we all and he was still in
school at Cal paully St Louis but but we
went about our business and uh about 3
weeks later he calls and says remember
that that Another One Rides the Bus it's
like it's getting played nationally it's
insane I said what what happened well
now by this time the Dr nto show was
syndicated nationally sure well what
would happen is in in all these major
markets you know the and Demento usually
ran on Sunday nights when when a radio
station had run out of stuff and they
would just you know run stuff at at 8:00
p.m. or 10 p.m. sometimes and it was
very kind of a a little niche thing and
tucked away but you know didn't
interfere with the rest of their
broadcast week sure well what had
happened is in a lot of these markets
the Monday morning you know Zoo wacky DJ
guys had come in they'd listen to the Dr
Demento show that aired that night you
know and scour it for fun stuff to play
yeah all right and so within a few weeks
of us doing it here in Los Angeles doing
it live and happily Dr dedo recorded it
sure uh now it's now it was heard like
in major markets now now these guys are
grabbing it they're it in morning drive
time that's crazy which is huge of
course and that's that's really where
things took off that's not just I don't
want to downplay Al's Capital single
from a year before my bologa came out in
December of 79 MH a One-Shot Capital
deal yeah uh very Niche thing yeah but
you know is that single one that's
available like that people or is that
more the collector's item version well
it's collector's item now yeah yeah yeah
but it's uh they're out there I mean
Capital distributed it it was out in
other countries I mean it was a
legitimate issue but it was strictly a
novel yeah a novelty thing and I don't
think they or Al thought it would go any
further it was a one shot deal that's
interesting uh in fact I I guess when it
came time to shop labels they must have
gone back and talked to capital and
capital probably said nah we've we
already put some out on him enough
already with with the
accordion and uh so Al Al telling me you
know about you know this is taken off
I've got somebody I've got a manager uh
I'm going to be home in January I want
to get back together we want to record a
few things we put out an EP and you know
let's let's do this MH so he did and we
did and
uh I didn't do the artwork on this this
time he had uh he and a buddy of his
photographer friend named Bill Burke
also known as beff Bill uhuh uh did the
photography and I think the layout uh no
l set this time well actually there was
some but but the back of it was a lot of
hand hand uh you know hand drawn text
mhm and uh that's a very rare that's
that's on the placebo label okay and
that's a very rare they did a thousand
of them and in fact I drove Al our alen
I drove all over town and went to re
Rhino records and music pluses and Tower
Records and stuff and dropped off you
know can can we drop off five of these
singles you know 10 of these singles
anyway and and up until recently I know
Al was still sitting on a hundred of
them so there's not that many out there
oh my God that's not the rarest thing
that would have on yeah but I mean
probably the rarest things are the Dr
Demento shows where there would be well
the rare ones are on real toore tape yes
yeah but but he was airing on 170 180
radio stations back in the 80s and
Westwood one who was a syndicator would
literally press up that many um they
would duplicate that many tapes or later
press up that many sets of LPS yeah a
dozen extras so they would do like 190
or
195 shows mhm and that was it yeah so
that's that's a a much lower number
obviously than a thousand sure and plus
those are spread out across the country
so those are really hard to find I have
every one of them do you wow but uh
where where Al is interviewed or the
funny 25 show as well are are archivable
I think yeah I I've noticed that around
at least at record Surplus in Santa
Monica every once in a while you can
find some dementos but nothing that I
again i' I'd be looking for weirdo like
that would specifically be what I'd be
looking for yeah it's it's uh well every
every show that uh and later on CD uh
every show that had an interview I think
qualifies as something that's worth you
know you could I mean Al was played on
probably every show since 1976 yeah yeah
you know it would be you know you can't
put them all in the archive course just
it's that's two nuts yeah yeah but an
interview is a special thing or an
appearance in the the the funny 25 or
the funny 50 or whatever it is the end
of the year show is a special thing yeah
uh so those are in the archive and I
have copies of all of those now having
worked at Westwood one that was an easy
thing for me to do okay took one off the
top of course why not what was do you
know I've never been able to talk to
anybody who listened to Demento from the
beginning I I talked to people who lived
in different parts of the country I
never got to hear it I didn't know who
Dr Demento was till high school and
somebody gave me a CD that it was a
compilation and uh so what was Demento
show before people were submitting stuff
that's what I always think of as people
submitting stuff well it was you know
he's he's very much of a of a
musicologist I mean extremely
knowledgeable uh uh old Jazz and you
know really the history of of 20th
century music yeah is is his thing
there's a lot of kind of one hit I I
don't want to call him one hit wonders
but a lot of sort of novelty things but
a lot of very cool obscure Jazz stuff so
a lot of the stuff he played he played
old Vaudeville things okay uh you know
or or things from the ' 50s 40s you know
some some big band stuff a little bit
but with a leaning towards the novel and
novel being both comedic and also rare
yeah uh so it was It was a very uh you
know it wasn't just a lot of wacky stuff
and I mean the show did eventually
become a lot of just sort of wacky it
really focused on the comedy I'm not
saying that's a bad thing sure it's just
it it evolved throughout the 80s uh
throughout the 80s throughout the 70s
rather uh in fact by the
time I got to meet Dr Demento and and
was asked if I would do an interview it
was you know was in the summer of 1980
he asked and and it was because at this
point his show you know was comprised of
a lot of stuff that people send in you
know in fact a lot of well-known uh well
Al was one of them yeah uh you know but
I was one of the I was very early on it
was like me Ogden
edel that's
it probably you know in in in 73 it was
you know I mean so and and also of
course I was playing around town at the
time with Nippers so Dr dendo thought
well I could give that a little bit of a
plug but it might be cool to get one of
the early people on there yeah that's
anyway and of course I I met Al and and
Another One Rides the Bus and the whole
you know all beer drummer thing mhm so
uh uh but his show was it it had a very
different tone early on uh but he would
play you know the Flying Saucer records
you know Buchanan and Goodman um you
know other the Stan freeberg now Stan
was a huge hero to Al yeah and uh yeah
Spike Jones you know so it was all very
kind of cool
stuff but with with a leaning towards
the novel but there'd be some old
there'd be big sperbeck stuff I mean
there'd be some very cool old Jazz stuff
you know 20s and 30s stuff yeah so it
was It was kind of all over the place
and later you know by by the mid to late
'70s it had become focused on Comedy and
Novelty yeah and with a leaning towards
you know a lot of sort of independent or
SL homemade uh music you know again of
which Al was one sure and uh and uh he
had become the most requested artist on
the show I mean perhaps even before the
the record deal you know I I I think
because because Dr dedo's fan base knew
who Al was yeah he was the resident
songwriter yeah the you know he was on
on the show you know almost every week
right you know he did PSAs he answered
phones he would uh you know just say
wacky stuff you he was just sort of one
of the cast members along with jungle
Judy and and musical Mike and and
Captain Chaos and some of you know the
other ludicrous Lori you life-size Lynn
I mean it was all and and after I met Al
I sort of became I I I would come down
every week or two or three and and
answer phones and just sort of be there
sometimes whether Al was there or not
and and for a short time you know for a
year maybe I guess I was sort of one of
the cast members that's great but not to
the extent that you know that that Mike
and and Damascus and some of them were
you know Sulu Su Luben uh who married a
guy named duboff so so she became sudu
instead of
Sulu or Sulu do I guess Sulu dashd how
did how did your work with Al Escape
being novelty when or when and was it
conscious like because it it definitely
did it's it's it's its own thing now
it's it's its own thing and and I guess
the the parent genre is novelty but that
includes satire yeah and and uh you know
and comedy comedy is not necessarily
novelty oh but but it's novel in that I
guess it has a uh sort of a narrow
appeal although you know judging by you
know the thousands of people that come
to see us every night you wouldn't think
it's that narrow yeah yeah yeah yeah uh
I mean there's some major big bands that
are out there you know that are well
respected that you know would love to
play some of the venues we do yeah yeah
but again this is after years and years
and years after Decades of building a
following and we've hung on to that
following and and I and it's not because
it's novel it's just because it's good
yeah and uh I remember the first time it
was 99 is the first time we videoed the
show to produce a a product to produce a
live concert VHS and DVD MH and I and
it's very hard to tell on stage I mean
you can put a camera out front and and
shoot the show you know just have kind
of a a one view of the show and the
audience noise and get a little bit of a
sense of what it is but you really you
never know but in watching this properly
mixed and edited camera work and proper
lighting and everyone doing a really
good show that night yeah I really got a
sense of of what it is that that people
you know why they come to the the show
multiple times you it's the same show
why would you come several times right
it's a good show well it's like if you
like a certain TV show or a certain
movie or something you may watch it
several times of course you know I mean
I still watch I Love Lucy yeah you know
when it's on and and bewitched and you
know it's stuff I've seen you know
Columbo episodes you know it's it's
stuff I've seen to death yeah and I
watch them because I like them it's like
God this and I'm watching us do our show
from an angle that I never see it sure
yeah and thinking I I get white people
this is actually very good yeah even
though I'm I'm in it I can I can
separate myself and it's like this is I
I would go see this maybe not 20 times
you know on the same show but sure sure
you know you know once or twice or three
times would be plenty but it's very very
good and the same thing again when we
did in 2011 we did the apocalypse tour
MH on uh actually at the beginning of
that tour we we made a video of the tour
that went on sale almost immed
immediately it's like well do I go to
the show or do I buy buy a DVD well I'll
go to the show and buy the DVD there of
course of course and and uh I watched
that and it's like yeah it's still I get
it I know why I know why it's grown MH
and uh and it's still you know and uh
well that was only a few years ago and
it continues to grow I mean we've you
know it's not an accident that we're
playing some of the biggest and most
important venues of our career yeah and
and the kind of classic venues that
major acts play I mean the Hollywood
Bowl is not some you know Club in a
college town in Upstate New York right
right you know we we we've done that
yeah you know at a time when we should
have been playing clubs sure yeah yeah
yeah but we've grown and it's it's
always it's yet to level off MH and and
we'll see uh what the future brings you
know the the plan is to go out in 2018
MH uh for for a while and uh the show is
going to
be I don't think Al made a secret of it
it's going to be primarily Originals oh
God are you kidding me our are Originals
yeah are you kidding me no that's what
you know that's this is this is it's for
the fans it's it's for the the fans who
have let us know it's like you guys
don't do enough Originals well we got 14
albums worth of parodies yeah you know
with with a single or two or three from
some of them that we have to there's not
a whole lot of room for Originals of
course you know and we don't want to go
up and play for five hours yep yep so we
we've uh so the balance of parodies to
uh to the the ratio to Originals is is
pretty high yeah that's changing yeah uh
in 2018 gosh that's amazing uh there'll
be some parodies but it's primarily uh
uh originals and we're also and again AL
has kind of made this known uh no
costumes no video no backing tracks you
know no percussion Loops or we are just
playing and for For Better or Worse holy
crap and we're just playing like we used
to do a long time ago uh you know and
I'll just I I wear what I'm wearing now
we a t-shirt or whatever you know if I
don't want to shave I don't have to
shave and we'll just
do a concert you know it's not the show
it's a concert yeah oh my gosh and I
think the fans are going to dig that
because that because we're going to play
stuff we're going to play stuff that
we've never played as a bandh yeah I was
wondering that like there has to been
there have to have been a few things
that have just never popped up on stage
right just Studio oh there a lot of
stuff we've never played Crazy a lot of
things we haven't played in a long time
yeah and a lot of stuff coming up I mean
I already know there's a list of 50 60
songs
and no we're not playing 50 songs a
night what that means is it's going to
be different show every night yeah yeah
and that's also that's also the lure so
people that are like you know they want
to come to see the show because they
like seeing the show they're going to
come now because they know they're going
to see something different than they did
last night of course of course uh so
when we're in a region uh we're going to
have a lot of repeat business yeah just
so they can hear the different the
different things we're going to do I
mean in
theory no no show will be like you know
every show will be unique yeah to some
extent I mean every time we talk about
your music on the show which has of
course happened plenty of times in 3D is
the first album that we've ever we ever
talked about because my best friend and
I became friends over that album like
this is that that's the reason I started
the podcast is this damn album and I
love it so much but that's the one thing
that comes up is every nerd that I talk
to we're all nerds it's just like why
does nobody talk about the originals and
it is like just a huge thing I think for
like maybe it's a badge of honor maybe
it's just like well you don't really
know weird now unless you know you know
originals and my phone's on that's super
classy that was really great turn that
off um that is almost never happened um
but yeah I mean that's the thing is
those originals are just so hugely
important and I my next question was
going to be about does it get is it
weird for you having to play somebody
else's song essentially even though and
and do you make it your own can you make
it your own I don't know what it's like
well for on the parodies yeah uh no it's
it's not weird for me no at all uh
what's weird is sometimes in one of my
other bands I'll be playing a song that
we've parody okay yeah and and now I'm
hearing some and very often we'll make a
change of arrangement stuff like that so
uh you know there's one of my bands
plays uh uh I love rock and roll now we
happen to do the exact arrangement of
that song yeah and I and I know the
exact you know of course I don't even
have to think about it yeah but we also
do uh uh American Idiot mhm mhm mhm and
and they do it much more like Green Day
okay that Arrangement and I have to
really think about that yeah and and
it's weird even though it's the same
part and it's pretty close to what I've
been doing for years I really have to
think about it because it's not that
familiar to me okay because it's now
it's like I'm not hearing the words I'm
used to hearing yeah so I I actually
have to think about that I'm on my toes
with that one or if somebody wants to do
uh god um well there's there's a number
of the songs you know a lot of the older
songs where these bands will play the
original version of it and and I like to
think I'm up to speed on it but you know
I'm not always now with Al's Originals
when we're doing those Originals those I
have somewhat made those my own because
in a lot of cases I mean well in every
case those are my parts yeah so if if I
like the parts I played on the record
and I usually do those are the parts I
play sometimes if we played a song for
years and years and years it's you know
something will occur to me oh I wish I
had done this instead you know I'm going
to start playing this just a little bit
of a change up and you know but not
something I could have done at the time
sure you know not something you know it
takes years sometimes to have a part
occur to me that it's like oh that would
have been nice you know if I'd had
several years to think about it before
recording it but sometimes we only had
several weeks Al would present a song
it's like okay hurry up and figure out
the parts you want to do and those are
going to be the parts forever yeah
that's going to be committed to you know
some media for all eternity so so make
it good it's like I don't know you know
I mean I'm pretty happy with with the
stuff I did it's couple things I would
do different but you know not to the
extent that you know I don't agonize
over it I wouldn't re-record it if given
the opportunity sure sure you know
although that would be interesting to go
in and re-record an album of of
originals and just with today's slant on
it now interestingly we
did the movie that came out last week I
think how to be a Latin lover uhuh with
uh there's he's a major Latin star named
I I called him Eugene mhm it's AO okay
uh uh verdez F God I can't even anyway
Eugenio and and this is like his first
movie geared towards the American Market
towards the English speaking market and
it actually was like the number two
movie last week and it and it's like
number four this week or something I
it's really hanging in there wonderful
well we had a little bit of a cameo in
there there's an outdoor scene there's a
birthday party MH and they wanted to use
the song happy birthday mhm which
ironically was the very first real thing
I recorded with Al you know
intentionally not not got sucked into it
like Another One Rides to the bus but
where we got together and said okay
we're doing a song named happy birthday
today um and and I think the deal was
they didn't want to license the original
recording H from Sony or or it would
have cost too much okay of course every
movie claims to be on a budget sure and
so we went in and
re-recorded uh happy birthday birthday
Allah the you know the first album
version wow as closely you know as
closely as we could yeah including Al
Al's lyric about there's an Arab on
every corner uhhuh I was going to ask
about that line today that's that's uh
oh that's in there cuz that's the lyric
yeah it's the lyric you know that's and
and it uh it sounded pretty good yeah it
sound and that's the version used in the
movie that's amazing that's to the
Casual listener especially as quickly as
it goes by you'd never know as it
happens and ALS not a secret that's
going to be on the medium Rarities disc
in the Squeezebox set that's coming out
November 24th yeah on uh Sony Legacy
records and uh CDs yeah literally
records and C LP and and uh CD mhm that
box that looks amazing it's going to be
it's going to be great uh I have again
with my archiving ways M I have curated
essentially all of the photos in this
100 page booklet really that's in there
in fact just today they said hey have
you got any photos from uh you know
we're up to the medium Rarities you know
everything is chronological and we
needed some uh photos that sort of
represent the stuff that's on that disc
yeah have you got anything from this
this this this or this I said no no no
yes happy birthday yes I've got that so
I sent them pictures not only in the
studio recording that yeah but uh and
literally just a few days later we were
on set I got a picture of a nice picture
of us and these white tuxedos which we
were playing in but a nice post picture
of the four of us and the core band and
uh it it was it it was pretty cool uh
you know it's it's neat being involved
with the label and it's not my first
time where I've supplied stuff to the
label in fact I'm apparently s such an
archivist when it came time to issue the
uh Essentials disc which is a a two- dis
uh hits package that Sony CBS BMG they
have the Johnny Cash and Elvis Presley I
mean every major artist that's got
enough material ends up on an Essentials
disc so there was first there was a two
dis version a year later there was
another version with a bonus disc
Essentials 3. so there's Essentials 2.0
essential the essential we're now yank
ofic 3.0 well the cover photo they
wanted was a photo that was shot it was
like a studio shot while we were with
Sony and they they didn't have it oh my
gosh and they said have you got this
phone and so had an 8 by10 and I scanned
the 8 by10 holy cow cleaned it up yeah
sent it to Sony and that's what's on the
cover is my scan WOW of their own photo
wow so they're they're apparently not
you know they let me be the archist
that's fine yeah yeah so uh same with
all the album covers that are being
reproduced for for the Set uh I mean
they had the most recent ones sure that
were in a computer sure everything else
they no idea of course of course that's
so I
I shot and not not CDs because those
have all sorts of little dots on them
and stuff like that at the time all the
albums came out they would make 12-in
Flats mhm like high quality printing
like like the covers were mhm even for
albums that came out only on CD they
still do this 12 x 12 promo Flats so I
had album size Flats clean yeah of
everything wow I shot those cleaned them
up yeah you know tweaked did whatever
yeah and and made them look better than
they ever looked when they were new and
sent those off to Sony I didn't even
send them the I sent them off so they
could scan them that's insane they still
have them yeah uh I guess if anyone's
entitled they are sure but it's just
interesting you know for for a Catal a
label that owns weird 's catalog Lock
Stock and Barrel that they still have to
come to me for stuff right which pleases
me and amuses me so much of course it
does well I I got to you know I've had a
lot of uh one of my good friends now is
a fire sign theaters archist I I've had
a few other archist of them are you okay
good yeah see and I used to know the GI
the tale of the giant red of somatra
like from beginning to end really I used
to I used to know that whole thing like
I used to know Billy the mountain you
know from you know all all of that stuff
and my and all of my friends did too all
the same people that listen to the Dr
dedo show were also fans of the same
things credibility gap yeah oh gosh I
love so much I mean I I I knew all of
that stuff yeah uh not So Much Anymore
SK Proctor was in here uh just this
weekend actually and we interviewed him
about don't crush that dwarf we're doing
like one album at a time with him and
that's a ton of and I I had his his
buddy who's an archive is here and every
story you're telling me now is just the
same kind of crap he has to deal with to
do fire sign stuff and get that going
and that is so overwhelming but like
that's clearly so well I guess my I was
going to ask like how involved I'm
assuming Al writes everything but then
that could be a completely ignorant
assumption he writes absolutely
everything he he does well certainly
lyrically yes lyrically and and
musically on The Originals of course uh
there are certain there are certain
things they'll specify for each of us uh
sometimes there's times he'll say just
you know it's going to sound like this
you know the drill you know what to do
right uh so I mean he's he gives
direction of course as he should he's
the artist the writer and the producer
sure uh and and the payroll clerk so he
he uh you know he's the boss he's the
man the guy the one the kid yeah uh so
yes he should be telling us what he
wants but it just depends to what extent
sometimes he really wants something very
specific I need a specific base part
here I need a specific little keyboard I
want a specific drum fill here you know
or or I want it to sound like this but I
don't want what they did on that album
you know that we're sort of alluding to
I don't want it to sound like we're just
stealing from that right so in a lot of
cases you know and with with all of us
we have to sort of on The Originals put
ourselves when we're doing what came to
be known as Style parodies whether the
doors or white stripes or whoever it is
uh we have to put ourselves in the
mindset of those players what would they
do if they were coming in you know what
would John denmore the doors drummer do
if he was coming in to play on
Craigslist and told I want you to sound
like you're playing with the doors but I
don't want you to necessarily play what
you played with the doors but I want
people to think that it sounds like
something you would have played and
that's what I had to do yeah was I had
to be John Densmore for a day yeah and
without being him I had to allude to him
and and I mean there's only so much you
can't do you know there's some things
you have to do there's production value
that lends itself to those things
there's some
signature Parts you know but you know
without trying to just copy a particular
song yeah so you know Craigslist had you
know some very obvious writers in the
storm you kind of thing going on etc etc
uh so so in doing the originals you know
sometimes we're left to her own devices
and and uh you know but Al has the final
say on everything and yes he does you
know he writes everything he may ask for
an opinion well which line do you like
better do you like this line or do you
like this line or or if I say this word
in this line uh like he said uh in
uh God it it was
uh first world problems there was an
original line and I have it on his
original demo something something thing
about butt hurt MH and he says to me
says do you know what butt hurt means
and at the time I didn't I said um no I
suppose I could Google it must be the
kids are probably saying that it turns
out they were uhhuh yeah you know and he
knew that but it's just like well with
somebody who's you know yeah you're an
old fogy but you're also involved in the
Arts and you listen to a lot of music
would you possibly know the reference
and I didn't and he pulled that line wow
he changed it to something else yeah uh
for me yeah yeah yeah I wish he left it
in now I know what it means now it would
be very funny perhaps if we do that song
live there we go uh you know he'll put
the original lyric back in I mean he's
welcome to change the lyrics on his own
songs you of course they're his songs of
course some sometimes if he uh it
doesn't happen often you know but once
every four or five or six shows on on a
parody he'll like he'll forget a lyric
but that doesn't mean he stops singing
yeah he'll say something
else and sometimes sometimes it fits and
it's funny and sometimes he just
stumbles his way through it but more
often than not he puts in like just a
different lyric that it's like well that
works hey you know what why did you he
says it's my song I'll change the lyrics
if I want okay I mean I know how excited
I am to see you guys live and I probably
wouldn't notice I'd be just too high on
how amazing the show is you know but the
but the fans know because they're
singing along sure sure and all of a
sudden Al saying something different
like Al forgot Al forgot the
lyrics he he saying something even
funnier this time right and I mean I
guess that's my question is if if you're
obviously so heavily involved regardless
of you don't have to write the song to
have left your stamp on it or to to
enjoy it to to actually to have it be a
piece of art for you you know but you're
also so invested that you're the archist
so you must love it so much maybe even
more than any of us fans can appreciate
well because that's a lot of work you
know I I I didn't start out deliberately
doing that I just always did that with
all of my groups I mean I have with this
group Nipper I have a whole box full of
I have all the original paste UPS I did
for for the single that we put out
amazing I mean I I you know I've just
got all that I've got a ticket from
every show we did MH uh I've got photos
I got tapes I got rehearsals I got gigs
I got you know posters we did I mean
I've got all of that stuff it was just
something I did when Al came along it
was just something I did yeah you know I
the the very the night I met him I
started archiving yeah I had uh uh to
enter metr media Square which was the
owner of uh Channel 11 at the time mhm
and kme uh the mighty met Metro media
was uh was housed there as well it was
sunset and the uh uh Hollywood freeway
in Hollywood uh and and you know it was
sort of a secure facility even back then
so you had an access card a little
handwritten pass for the night and Dr
dedo had a bunch of those sort of
pre-signed so he he uh would write them
out for the people that were coming that
night we would meet him he would hand us
the cards so if anyone we saw anyone in
the inside it's like okay I've got my
card I'm I'm okay to be here I I kept
that card you know even that first night
yeah even though it was just a chance
meeting I still have that card and it's
in perfect condition it's amazing I mean
it's absolutely pristine I love it and
so the night I met him I began archiving
yeah and everything we did uh you I
always had a camera with me I didn't
have one that night as turns out uh on
on subsequent visits to the show I did
but every time we were in the studio
every gig every tour rehearsals MH uh TV
shows everything I always had a camera
and uh I just took photos endlessly
sometimes I had two cameras one had you
know slrs one had the black and white
film uh the Manola SRT 101 which is an
older camera by the80s uh had black and
white and that was a real Workhorse and
I had a Canon one program uh that I shot
color mhm and I had some different
lenses but I had a big camera case that
had all my gear in it and it went
everywhere with me on the road and of
course in order to see the pictures as
as we went along I had to go to a lot of
1our Photoshop of course yeah and I
always got two sets of photos MH one to
keep and one to to hand out yeah you
know or or one to put in my box of
photos there was there were the AL
photos and there were the me photos so
depending who was in the photo you know
one set just went into the archive and
the other set got handed out and you
know maybe any extras went into my
another photo album I had yeah so it was
a very expensive Pursuit Of course
looking back of course uh you know I was
always like I never had the luxury of
doing stuff overnight because we were
always on the move and I would shoot you
know 20 30 rolls of film during the
course of a short tour M you know to two
three rolls a week maybe so uh it was an
expensive an expensive deal before I
knew how to write things off right oh
gosh
I wish I could go back it's too far to
go back and revise my taxes but uh and
I've got all of those photos every
stinking single photo yeah is in a box
in order in a box in several boxes in
order there are the Weird Al boxes there
are the Mi boxes there's a little bit of
crossover between the two but there was
a point where I realized you know
doesn't matter which box they go into I
I'll be able to find it MH you know I
don't need duplicates you know if I'm in
a photo with Al does it go in his box or
mine well after a certain point it just
went in mind yeah and and I I I know to
find it later and at this point after
going through the collection of photos
and posters and all the other stuff for
behind the music for the unauthorized Al
book uh in in uh
1985 for the box set book in 1994 MH for
uh the Weird Al book in 2012 MH uh
driven biography MH uh label the label
needs this label needs that now the
label you know has gotten tens of
thousands of my photos for this booklet
obviously they're not using them all in
in doing that most of the stuff I've got
has been digitized more than once
scanned digitized or there was a point
where they were just all digital yeah uh
I went through recently and and
reordered all of my photos I had an
interesting experience with uh with the
guy who put together the uh the uh Weird
Al book uhuh with with us and Nathan uh
Nathan Raven yes yes and he came over to
my house for a couple of weekends went
through all my stuff with me wow uh went
to Al's house went through all of his
stuff but he went through every photo in
my collection oh my that had there unto
been in order mhm and they got seriously
out of order he would group them and
stack them then like just gather them up
and stick them back in the Box more or
less within the year that of you know
the index card for that year mhm and
they had been that way ever since
they've been that way for over 5 years
now MH except when I needed to find
something for Sony just like last week
and it's like okay I need to find
something from this video shoot I'm
going to go look for it yeah and I
realized was reminded how out of order
everything was I thought okay that's it
and I spent two solid days putting
everything back in order oh my and I
realized it was then I could I could
tell a very obviously cut off when
things went digital mhm after which
maybe 2003 was the last year I had any
kind of real photos mhm okay and after
that there were some years I had no hard
copies at all yeah none uh I think the
most recent hard copy photo I've got one
photo from
2012 uh that somebody else gave me okay
that's but but 2003 to 2004 was the cuto
off where I went 100% digital and I I'd
already been using a digital camera but
uh I've been through so many digital
cameras because the quality just gets
better and better MH but at this point
hopefully I don't have to go through all
those photos again photos again
everything that's worth seeing I think
has been scanned and digitized and
cataloged and and renamed in order with
the photographer's name on it you know
usually me yeah and and hopefully now
this stuff's been digitized to the point
where I don't have to touch another
photo of course you know now that now
that I've put them all in meticulous
order it's probably the last time I have
to refer to them yeah but uh yeah that's
the extent to which I take my archiving
very seriously and it's not just photos
MH it's Al's product mhm or product that
has anal reference M there there are a
lot of albums CDs where Al has been
thanked for one reason if his name
appears on it I get a copy yeah I buy it
or I mooch one or whatever or I refer to
it at least in the discography if I
can't get one sure and I still discover
some I keep on top of it pretty well uh
these days but I still occasionally
discover something that's like God I got
to get that or or how didn't I know
about that just five years ago you know
when the internet you know would allow
me to find it of course of course 20
years ago I I I don't know how I knew
all those things you know I mean I was
online 20 years ago but it just it
wasn't the resource that it is now yeah
so I've got a collection of product from
around the world uh video audio um promo
items radio station things uh different
distributors I've got our CD catalog uh
with four different
distributors uh e EPA which is epic
portrait Associated labels which was CBS
that they were our first distributor
with Scotty Brothers then they went to I
think they went to BMG okay reissued all
the CDs on BMG by this point uh I
think I think there were no more LPS so
all the LPS up to that point were were
epic MH uh after that there might have
been a couple of BMG but then it was
strictly CD then they got distribution
with Warners WEA so everything was
reissued under weah MH um wow and I
would go out and seek different versions
they had different catalog numbers the
early CDs had full artwork the later
ones didn't yeah uh for various reasons
interesting um the uh you know they
repressed not repressed but repressed
the the CD so the CD catalog numbers of
course and the the label art was
sometimes a little bit different so
those all are in the in the archive as
well yeah uh when Sony took over
reissued all the CD had to go get them
all again oh my gosh uh you know I've
got them in uh under Scotty Brothers I
got them in their original long boxes
mhm and they're all shrink wrapped wow
so they're brand new some of them may be
promo items mhm but they're all brand
new does the internet once told me and
it could be it's the internet so it
could be mistaken that there that off
the deep end was released on vinyl
somewhere in
Europe
uh I haven't been able to find it or
enough information to find out so I use
that as an excuse to talk about it on
the podcast but I don't know okay it it
was it was released on vinyl probably as
a bootleg I think either from Korea or
the Philippines okay okay there was
there was it smells like Nirvana was
released as a 12in MH with with the off
the deep end artwork okay okay uh in uh
Britain okay interesting I I believe I
didn't know maybe German H I don't know
but that that was like a 12in single
novel you know not novelty but a a niche
sure kind of thing but yeah CDs had
certainly taken over by that point I
remember remarking to Al in ' 89 when we
were wrapping up UHF I said this is and
and everything was coming out still on
cassette mind you so cassette cdlp I
said you know this is probably going to
be our last vinyl album yeah and you
know officially issued by our label and
uh and I was right MH as it turns out uh
so for off the deep end it was just CD
and cassette I I if there was a European
album on vinyl I'll have it in my
archive I don't off the top of my head I
don't doubt it uh and I don't have the
and the archive is not available online
I can't I can't look at it right the
discography is but it's a US discography
because everything outside of the US
even Canada is is very hard to pin down
and if and if I can't be 99% complete I
don't want to do it at all understand I
don't want to be I don't want to have
anything not be accounted for if it's in
the
US well all of Al's albums and product
and reissues and all that are all
accounted for mhm there might be a promo
thing here that I'm not aware of you
know stuff like that course but Europe
and and uh Asia and Australia and South
America and are just are very hard to
pin down I would I would I would imagine
and and Canada as well and and so I
don't I kind of don't even try in terms
of the discography so I call it a US
discography makes sense and and that's
relied on as the official discography do
you you know what I should ask you um
because this has been fascinating but i'
I haven't asked you do you have a
favorite original that you guys play is
there like one that either is super fun
to play Super Fun to listen to I'm
curious because I have some weird deep
cuts that I don't know if anybody else
cares about but I'm curious like what's
well the deep cut you're going to hear
deep cuts at this next I can't wait
that's just you're going to hear stuff
that that none of us want to play but
just it's just to like bring it out and
and you know for the fans who would
never otherwise of course you know stuff
we've never played live and and
sometimes for good reason I I don't know
you know that's that's the very most
difficult question I have is you know
what what's your favorite song what's
your favorite original what's your
favorite what's your favorite album and
I just you know it's it's usually album
wise now it's usually the most current
album because one it's fresh course two
we've you know with each album we we
grow we grow as players we grow as
programmers our listening abilities grow
uh our our technal technical abilities
grow and so every album is for for
various reasons better than the last I
think Al's humor gets gets better it's
not as goofy silly you know food related
as it once was sure it's
very it's it's
uh it's I don't want to say it's more
adult right it's just it's more honed
it's it's it doesn't rely on being goofy
and W there's still a little bit of that
but it's not all about just being goofy
and outrageous he's got some very
incisive absolutely you know commentary
I mean there's some social commentary
going on that's why trigger happy always
stands out to me so much I love that and
whether whether he believes it or not
whether he's sending a message or not
and sometimes he does and sometimes he
doesn't uh it's just he knows that it's
something that will raise somebody's
awareness and get them to think yeah you
know while while you know that's not
always the goal it's he's not writing
stuff to get people to think but it's
it's while he's at it you know it's like
well I can be funny and and maybe get
someone to stop and think about
something you know this is important or
or some people think this is important
maybe you know my my listeners should be
aware of this of course you know but not
something he wouldn't ever put you know
something like that in the liner notes
you know visit save the whales you of
course right yeah that would defeat the
purpose donate to you know eat the
animals or whatever oh he doesn't eat
animals whatever or don't eat the
animals don't eatthe
animals.com tell them Mal sent you now
you know favorite song I you I I like
them all MH you know there's nothing
that I that I dread playing it's nothing
that I fall asleep while I'm playing
it's like you know it's nothing like God
why do we have to play this song
uh because in the case of The Originals
those are all my parts so I mean it
would be sort of hypocritical for me to
say I don't like the song When I'm doing
what I did on it you know I I get to to
replay the parts that that are the parts
you know that are things that I made up
or that Al told me that I should be
making up or whatever it was uh you know
that's stuff that I'm proud of so in
that respect I I like them all now
there's some things and and come up on
this tour uh we are doing some of the
longer songs mhm some of these long
songs are songs yeah some of them are
about cities in New Mexico not the
capital but the other one sure and and
uh so so there are songs that's like God
I I got to play at top speed for 13
minutes minutes after we've already
played for an
hour now also yeah with the with the new
uh concert format coming up and without
videos uh that to enable costume changes
that we won't be doing so no videos no
screen no costumes no nothing
uh we're going to be playing I mean I'm
not going to get a break I'm not going
to get three four five minutes here and
there go back and have a drink of water
sit in front of a fan I'm playing we're
playing non-stop wow well eventually we
will stop uh so it's going to you know
so you know there are songs that it's
like God I hope we don't have to do that
one every night yeah yeah uh I I'll I'll
uh Albuquerque is uh okay it's on the
list yeah yeah I don't I don't think
it's going to get played every night but
there are some other
rather lengthy songs yeah that are going
to get played and and so we get into
those it's like you know I got to play
non-stop for seven eight nine minutes
whatever it is you know 11 minutes 15
seconds whatever Albuquerque is you yeah
uh so but favorite songs they're all I
like them all yeah that's that's a
reasonable answer I I I can't I can't
ful it because I also like it's very
hard it would be impossible to pick one
or 10 or 50 sure uh and we have all you
know 14 albums worth of songs there's a
lot of songs and a lot songs that were
never recorded that we've played I know
I know gosh originals and and parodies
you know I can't wait for this I got
chills when you mentioned the whole
format I'm like oh goodness you've just
designed a concert for me that's so
amazing well that's that's was Al's
thinking it's like you know this is this
is just for the fans it's not for the
people who's like wow Al got a number
one album he must be really special
we'll buy it we wouldn't normally but
we'll buy you know he's hung in there
for 30 plus years we better see his show
before you know one of us dies right
right and uh
and that's and and that's not a bad
thing you know it's like when you're
when you're popular it's like people
gravitate yeah but the the fans have
always been there and we've got new
Young fans yeah uh and a lot of them
will be at these shows and we've got
fans that have been with us 20 25 30
yeah years longer I love seeing multigen
external fan like groups that come oh to
the shows it's amazing it's an extremely
wide demographic in the audience I mean
there's 5-year-olds there's 65y olds
well the 65y olds are on stage uh no
there's there's it's a very wide demo
and and unlike I don't remember exactly
when it changed but in the very early
days Al's appeal well because you know
so closely related with Dr dento uh was
was more towards kind of adolescent
males sure Junior High high school maybe
college men boys uh very few females at
the time so we would go do shows and and
it was rare to see girls in the audience
I mean it was the crowd that liked mty
Python and three stoes and stuff like
that fire sign theater of course and uh
and Weir out well over time you know
certainly by the by the early to mid 90s
that had changed it was very much a
50/50 kind of thing and I don't know if
it was Al's appeal or if the guys had
gotten were old enough to to start
dating bring in their girlfriends that
makes sense I mean I can understand why
why some of the nerdy guys back in the
day didn't have girls with them yeah
yeah uh you know it was it was partly
the girls didn't like it and partly they
probably couldn't get any girls right
that's that's uh changed a lot you know
with all due respect to the male nerds
out there there are plenty of female
nerds too of course yeah I married to
one she she goes to the shows with me
you know that's nice um so so it uh you
know it's it's a very and then the age
range yeah uh has has expanded
tremendously and it's not just the fans
from 20 years ago bringing their kids
now uh it's it's fans from 20 years ago
sometimes there's you know their kids
are there sometimes there's new fans
that are young 5year olds 10 year olds
what ever uh you know anyone really who
can understand lyrics and uh you know
has enough money to buy a ticket we love
them they're they're what we no that's
that's
terrible uh no if their parents buy a
ticket that's good no you know anyone
anyone who sort of gets what we do I
mean it's kind of an ageless thing
anymore it's it's the adults get stuff
you know if there's something a little
bit blue and in Al's you know lyrics and
and you know he's gotten to be kind of
the master of that uh you know over the
years uh you know the parents know that
it's kind of above the kids' heads they
don't they don't have to worry about the
kids hearing that other than in 15 or 20
years you know the kids will go darn
that's what he meant right right and and
then the parent you know Dad why didn't
you tell me that's what was the parents
have a different problem right but uh no
Al Al's he's very good at at
knowing he
doesn't he doesn't how do I put this
he's careful about his lri lyrics in
terms of not because the kids you know
don't hear these things on TV and in in
other forms of music and in school and
stuff like that it's not that they don't
hear words and lines and stuff that you
know Al wouldn't
say he's concerned that their parents
will hear them hearing it from Al yeah
and and uh that reflects poorly on him
of course so he's able to to sometimes
convey a thought and couch it humorously
you know typically and uh and get away
with it and he knows that the parents
know that the kids won't know yeah and
uh you know till much later that's the
art of it and I I love it um he's he's
got he's very good at that and there's a
little bit of that on on each album yeah
uh okay so I again normally we sort of
wrap up I say why would you talk about
this album we're not talking about one
album we're talking about you know a
career that is still going strong for
several dudes all at once who all have
the their own input um but I would like
to I don't know when this will come out
but what do you want to promote where
can people find you online well I am
online at Bermuda schwartz.com b r m u d
s c w r TZ period c m m like in
summer uh and uh and any other pertinent
links are on there of course weirdal is
weirdal.com and I had set that up many
years ago uh I was his Web Master in the
beginning I was his Web Master when it
wasn't even his site yeah it was my site
about my experience with him amazing and
it evolved into his site and I got the
weird all.com domain and I spelled w d
which is correct and then I also thought
well everyone gets this wrong let's get
w i e r of d l and so we've still got
that so you cannot you really have to go
out of your way to spell Weird Al wrong
to not get to the site right so you
could you could spell it either way and
we've got uh some fans whove become
friends of ours over the years and they
went out and sought weird al.net weird
al.org wow and they have those forward
that's great and and uh but basically
weirdal.com uh is where everything Al is
uh we we converted that to a WordPress
site uh two years ago okay and uh Al can
maintain that yeah if I go in to do some
work on it WordPress is too easy I have
to go in look at all the code y yep and
and I can manipulate the code if I'm
looking at WordPress I mean I know it's
supposed to be drag and drop and you
know and it's just
I I can't I can't do it right I have to
go in and put tags and do all which I
know you know that's how I learn I still
code sure I'm I'm the kids call me a
coder or a codger I forget it's just one
letter whatever one letter up that's
fine uh but yeah I still I still do
websites for other clients you know uh
not as feverishly as I used to Sure uh I
mean you know all all the WordPress and
and the the Wicks and places like that
that you can just have they have all
sorts of drag and drop ready to go Stu
you really don't have to know how to do
that stuff anymore and frankly I just
haven't kept up with it yeah so I'm not
taking on any new clients at this
timeart but but uh the Weird Al
I the site was so deep I had so many
pages and so much information that when
Sony agreed to host the site as they did
for almost all of their artists because
they controlled a lot of the promotion
within the those artists site they
hosted it they granted me access to
their servers wow
uh only so much access because I did try
to go up a level to get into their I
couldn't do it I I just wanted to see if
I could get in there they they knew I
would do that so I I couldn't but they
let me into their server and they hosted
and when they first got the site they
said we have never seen such a deep site
yeah I said well I started this site
before anybody had websites yeah yeah
you know I did this site in 1995 mhm and
uh so they were they were extremely
impressed and the site is still pretty
deep that's great yeah photo galleries
have made their way over to Instagram
and Twitter these days which Al controls
he feeds that Facebook to an extent so
the site is a little bit static uh it's
used just sort of as a a resource all
the tour dates are on there set lists
are on there again these came from my
archives uh the discography is hosted by
Jeff Morris who is Dr
demento's archist I guess man Friday
he's also been on the show we've had so
many archists on the show and Jeff is
great Jeff always hosted the uh
discography I don't know why it would
have been simple enough to put on
weirdal.com but he said I'll just I'll
just put a text version of it up if
that's okay and you can link to it I
said fine yeah why not so I always kept
that updated and we're uh I I'm working
on one that resembles the current
weirdal.com format the the kind of gray
the little more AER uh format of that
and I just
haven't it's it's not completely up to
date there's just so many little things
thanks to Jeff Morris yeah pointing out
well you know this thing came out didn't
come out before this and you've got it
on the list here and there was this
other thing that came out here well
you've got you know UHF you know came
out on Blu-ray in this year but you put
Blu-ray up you know in the other thing
you know up in 1989 where but that
couldn't have possibly been so he
catches me on a lot of stuff and I've
got a long list of things that I have to
decide how to do it so that it meets
with his standards which are probably
higher than mine so I'm trying to please
Jeff on on of you know he's more
meticulous than I am but you know what
that's that's good of course he keeps me
in line uh when did Squeezebox come out
again Squeezebox uh Street date on that
is November 24th November 24th at the
end of 2017 2017 and uh that's out on in
both LP and uh CD and the way that's
being accomplished is uh if if anyone
hasn't been to the site that was
promoting like the the pre-sales on
those the way that works is they're not
doing like a little tiny accordion for
the CDs yeah they're doing one size and
it's going to be a big Square Accord
because it has to obviously fit LPS yeah
they are making special jackets uh in
the size of the LPS really with a little
pocket in the back that the CD goes into
for the CD version so that it will fit
in the same large box gosh that's insane
so for those people that have to have
both versions like me uh they're going
to have two of these big p sized
accordion things that's hilarious the
accordion doesn't play sorry uh the
booklet is is uh I've already got a copy
of the first half of the booklet uh and
and the way and it's a very collag kind
of a thing uh it's very very cool it's
so cool to see these things there's a
lot of photos in there that have never
been seen even with all the different
Outlets I've had for the photos in the
archive I pulled out a lot of new stuff
for this I pulled out stuff that's never
been used I pulled out contact sheets
and show two guys from Sony came out to
the house uh in in 2014 20 2015 sorry
before the the tour began they came out
in April and spent a couple of weekends
with me going through everything wow
more so than Nathan Raben had done for
the book they really they just they went
nuts that's insane and one of the guys
guy named Mike duette uh is a major Al
fan and and he he was kind of like oh
yeah that's got to be in there he sort
of qualified what what you know was
going to be important to the fans love
it and uh and it was it was pretty cool
it was very very cool so I just recently
got to see the booklet starting to take
shape uh they're working on the very end
of it as we speak uh and and I'll see
the second half of it you know I've got
PDFs basically of of these and uh not
complete but what they're intending you
know nothing's been balanced or anything
like that but they they've got the
layout that's great and it's very very
cool oh I cannot way it's really there's
a ton of stuff it's like man the the
it's things I I mean I've got photos got
contact sheets of negative strips that I
shot in the studio that that have never
been printed yeah wow I've got so
there's like contact sheets in this
thing that people are going to go wow
that's that looks like it would be a
great photo if it was we never printed
any of these things yeah you know we did
contact sheets and that was it wow of
course I've got all the negatives sure
if I ever I could do my own book of
stuff none of which is in the Sony book
yeah yeah mind you or or Nathan's book
yeah oh or as I like to call it my book
or as Al likes to call it the weird
albook uhhuh no I I curated probably 95%
of the photos in that book and that's
great easily 99% of the photos in the in
the book that's coming with the box set
that's so good so I'm I'm I'm really I'm
very happy to be involved uh to a much
larger extent than most musicians are
involved with their label MH which it's
actually not even our label anymore
right right that's the AL very very uh
publicly uh decided to not resign sure
with Sony or anyone else yeah uh after
having a number one album number one
cool goodbye right actually that was
that you know what the departure was in
the works and and you know with the
number one album I think both Sony and
Al thought hm maybe I know Sony did Sony
certainly wanted to to uh continue the
relationship of course of course and Al
was ready to essentially go independent
yeah um and uh which is not a bad thing
sure no no I think being independent is
is great if you're at a point where you
can be independent I think if you're
independent because you're just starting
it's still a very uh tough road to Ho as
they say yeah uh it's a very tough climb
to uh what do you do do you get hooked
up with a label to not sell any albums
right uh you know it's it's not it's you
know and and if you don't sell albums
and you can't get the right promotion
can you go on tour and and get anybody
to come see you can you make money that
way right it's it's very difficult you
know YouTube is great exposure but it's
how do you draw people to come see you
there of course and it's free but it's
like well how how do you get people to
go see you and then will they come see
you live and and pay five or 10 or 20
bucks to come see you right you know can
you do a college tour can you do and and
it's tough with Allen and a lot of other
artists that have left their labels uh
they're in a position they're at a place
where they can continue doing what they
do yeah and the labels have been great
but there's not actually a need he
doesn't resent it it's just I don't have
to have a label yeah they're not going
to sell any more records than I can and
they don't book our tours you know every
everything the whole rest of my career
is separate from the label if I'm not
selling records you know why why bother
yeah well I'm I'm very excited for the
future I am I cannot wait to go see you
guys live next year uh my gosh this has
just been a blast like I obviously
you're wome if you want to come back on
and talk about fire sign theater we
could do that all day um but well I
don't know that I still remember the
tale of the giant R of
Sumatra uh but I I swear to God I knew
all the all the lines was blind I I tell
you I I was so hooked on uh on stuff
from that album and stuff from a lot of
I'm my python I was a huge fan sure uh I
and I would I I actually had I had the
phone company list my name as Jim blind
uhhuh so that in the phone book it would
read blind Jim which was the
dog which was oh my God uh Hemlock
Stone's dog in in the in the show that's
amazing in the album blind gem fantastic
and I'll tell you how many how many uh
you know the society for the blind how
many people saw that and thought that
was a reference to my being blind would
call that number but I just thought that
was so cool I hope for the S sake of
your archiving that you still have a
copy of that phone book you know I don't
well it never occurred what year was
this uh somebody's got one
789 there's a hoarder out there who has
every phone book I lived in Glendale so
if there was a Glen
or a valley phone book or a downtown
area phone book it's so funny so 78 7980
would have been the year and and it's of
course the phone number is no good so
feel free to call it uh I don't I don't
quite I don't remember the phone number
I have it written down somewhere but it
was that apartment and there's there's a
couple of iconic photos when the placebo
EP uh was pressed up Al got them in
plain white sleeves he had also printed
up what became the the front and back
cover which was just an elongated I
guess 7x14 sheet that he folded and then
he had like 7in uh they weren't myar
sleeves but they were plastic sleeves
yeah uh and so we had like a a placebo
EP assembly party at my apartment which
was me Dr Neo and Al and so there's
pictures anytime you see a picture with
Al holding up the placebo EP or Demento
holding up one of the discs or whatever
and there's this horrible orange
wallpaper in the back that's my
apartment in Glendale
uh which is which is where I was living
when I met Al yeah I have I have other
pictures of it's where we recorded the
Dr Demento jingle really that went uh it
was just
drums drums and and like Temple blocks
MH and it was uh I didn't sing on it and
you and you'll know why in a second but
it was the one you hear it on the Dr
dementa show still and it was Dr Demento
Dr Demento Dr Demento and there's like
this laughing at the end which he and
and we left it in and actually I think
we I think we brought it in from the end
of another song we had done M and we
just like taped it you know edited into
the end of that it's great that is also
on medium Rarities that's F and I Remix
that I have the original tracks on that
in digital and and everything's
separated and I I remixed a version you
know under Al's supervision and it's
cleaner than it ever could have been
that's amazing because the copy Dr dedo
got was at least a second generation
cassette sure of a cassette right so it
it was only so clean yeah this is the
original pora Studio cassette so it's as
clean as that it's it's that it's like
listening to that
cassette uh it's it's I'd never heard it
so good that's amazing and uh so of
course I won't get credit for remixing
that of course uh I think uh I think
Pac-Man came from me mhm um which is
fantastic uh and that might have been a
little bit of a remix I had the Pac-Man
music and I had the Pac-Man vocals and I
think I I comped that all from the the
Masters mhm and I think that's my mix as
well wow so that is also cleaner than
anyone would have ever heard it well
every nerd out there needs to pick that
up he go see you guys live like I'm
definitely going to do um this has been
honestly just so much so much fun I
really appreciate well for me it was a
trip down memory lane yeah well I I I
wanted to I want to get your story I
wanted to get your side of things I'm so
fascinated with all all the other stuff
you did before too it was just
mindblowing and I I wish I had known
that you were one of the first guys to
get stuff played on Dr dento but it's
fun to discover that while you talk to
somebody um again thank you so much um
oh my pleasure thank you thank you guys
very much for listening and as always
have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
five-star rating and a nice review you
can find us on facebook.com/ Comedy
onvinyl Twitter at comedy onvinyl and
find everything else at comedyon
vinyl.com a major portion of comedy on
vinyl has been underwritten by standup
records please visit standup records.com
for all your comedy needs and tune in to
the new standup channel available on the
Roku where you can also find select
episodes of this podcast
[Music]