hey everybody Welcome to Comedy on vinyl
this week we have special guest Rachel
Bloom I just wanted to give you the
heads up she does have a brand new song
out just came out uh yesterday uh
Valentine's Day it is called pictures of
your dick it is hilarious check it out
like it do all the good stuff that
you're supposed to do to nice funny
videos and uh also we I uh have a
special announcement uh my documentary
my comedy documentary Lords of soap town
is uh on we have a fundraiser going on
right now on indiegogo.com so I'll put a
link to that up on comedy on vinyl you
can also go to Lords ofo
town.com it's a comedy documentary about
freestyle walking if you don't know what
freestyle walking is doesn't matter just
check it out I think you'll find it
pretty funny we're just trying to raise
$5,000 to complete it so anything that
you or your friends or your family can
uh donate would be absolutely very very
helpful and we've got 30 days to raise
that and yeah please tell everybody um
so yeah this week we are covering Weird
Al Yankovic's even worse which is one of
his tighter albums and uh we we pretty
much gab on and on and on about uh Weird
Al in general and uh dreams in this
episode so enjoy it and thanks so much
please again don't forget to subscribe
to us subscribe to Rachel's videos on
YouTube and please check out Lords of
soap town.com
[Music]
your butt is wide well mine is too just
watch your mouth or I'll sit on you the
word is out better treat me right cuz
I'm the king of C your life h on H on H
on H all right
my zippers bust my buckles break I'm too
much man for you to take the pavement
cracks when I fall down I've got more
chins than
Chinatown but I never used the phone
booth and I never seen my toes when I'm
going to the movies I take up seven
Rolls because I'm fat fat I'm fat
usually here too but okay that is true
they just started her working Sundays I
believe her response when I said you
were going to be on the show was squeal
and die exclamation point she's very
excited she videos oh awesome I'm
excited to talk about comedy music I
have two new videos coming out like the
next couple I've been doing a lot of
Comedy I just now like comedy song in
the past like few months it's all I've
been thinking about and doing so I'm
excited to like analyze it awesome but
we're already recording so we can going
on this hey everybody Welcome to Comedy
on vinyl uh with me as semi usual is Dan
hey hey and with me as not usual is
Rachel Bloom hello hi hi um so if you
don't know who Rachel is she uh was
quite famous for the video [ __ ] me Ray
Bradberry which uh I think got
everyone's attention including right
when did you get to meet
him at this point that would have been a
year and a half ago year and a half ago
yeah that was well a year yeah year and
a half ago yeah how was that it was
awesome it was great really in honor
he's one of my favorite authors
legitimately so that was great I don't
think you could make a song like that
unless you were genuinely a fan of those
no and I think that that song came from
like you know a genuine feel like a like
a genuiness of like not feeling like
modern pop songs were representing like
my romantic interest like it wasn't just
like it wasn't just like oh all these
like what's something that nerds like it
wasn't like that it was like it was like
I really like this I really love this
author I feel about in in ways that
other people feel about Thugs and you
right well speaking of oh yes yes Dan
brought something I think uh well you
signed this for me oh my God I'd love to
I just for the people listening it's and
there goes theen oh let me get the pen
yes what is it it's the stories of Ray
Bradberry collection of short story I
think this is the first Ray Bradberry
book who's already signed oh someone
signed this in
1982 I just want to read the I want to
read the inscription uh this is dated
November 13th 1982 it says Mike it's
incursive this
gift this gift marks a wonderful year of
friendship I'm looking forward to the
years uh we'll have to read and reread
this together love Janet uhoh it sounds
like Janet wanted more than friendship
and Mike was like oh Janet gave me a
book I'm gonna give this to this used
bookstore Janet's crazy so sad maybe he
wasn't really into the whole SciFi
fantasy maybe Ray Bradberry [ __ ]
maybe you can make your inscription just
as depressing I'm going to do the exact
same inscription okay that way if people
see
this
Mike found this book at a used bookstore
you [ __ ] love
[Laughter]
Janet and Ary said that if she was able
to to make it she would have brought one
of our pets for you to sign oh man I
love signing pets
uh while while Rachel finishes that that
inscription we this week we're going to
be doing Weird Al even worse um and I
again I told Dan earlier I'm not sure
why I picked this one I think it's just
because we need to do more weird now
we've done two so far well I think I
requested I was like let's do comedy
music yeah so yeah it's one if it's more
not obscure but less listen to albums by
a at this point yeah yeah I I have to
say cuz I first started listening to we
all cuz my my mom had the giant like
compilation had this like multi-is set
but you know what really surprised me
about this album is um the songs that I
like the best were not the parodies were
his Originals I I he writes really
really good um you know original songs
like the the Melanie song is really cool
favorite it's really cool old days it's
super dark and good old days is also
really good I loved this song is just
six words long yeah that is great that's
a oh man look at this record this is
great that blew my mind it was So Meta
for me as a whatever I was 11 or 12year
old when I first heard it so it's it was
it's very that that one that song I'd
say is like the closest to like a song
of his being a sketch yeah totally true
which now you get so much in comedy
music it's like the sharpness of that um
yeah it was I was really like I really
want to go and listen to all alms and go
beyond the parody now and hear his
original stuff I I would like I've been
hoping to see them him rele or somebody
do like a tribute album where it's
people just covering all his Originals
because people people don't think of him
that way yeah which is depressing to me
because he's a wonderful songwriter yeah
yeah apparently stuck in a closet with
Vana White was his first original song
that was considered as popular by the
fans as his parodies really mhm which
one did you say was the experiment where
he wanted to see the good old days he
said was an experiment to see if he
could write a song where Charlie Manson
and James Taylor collaborated I love
that I love the unexpected of like
meanwhile I'd be torturing rats that's
such a great specific yeah I was reading
about him today and um apparently Prince
will never has never given a permission
you know weirdal doesn't need permission
right it's very specific parody laws
that say like you don't need but he gets
permission just to maintain Goodwill and
prince won't give him permission so he
won't do a Prince song but apparently
like he was doing some benefit and he
was going to sit in the same ride with
Prince and he got like a letter from
Prince's manager being like you do not
make eye contact with Prince oh my God
you do not look at Prince and he was
like holy [ __ ] yeah I know it's cuz
everyone else apparently Michael Jackson
was such a weird Al fan he like gave him
permission outright and actually the
music video for fat is shot in the same
set yeah as bat like that's amazing to
me brilliant lady you know there's yeah
there's also a thing where Lady Gaga
wouldn't give him the rights to Born way
thing I was remember reading about that
but apparently it wasn't her it was her
manager and then when she heard about it
she was like oh my God no of course I'm
a huge weird do fan which is so cool I
can't imagine her being
actual Diva actually made me happy for
Weird Al because he's talked about on
his blog how he's a big fan of Lady Gaga
he loves what she does he loves the
person that she is as an Entertainer
yeah and it really hurt him that she
quote unquote she responded that way
yeah [ __ ] managers [ __ ] managers
man
managers and I I will just as a point of
bragging just say that I was in the
video for that and [ __ ] exciting it's
the best thing in the world for perform
this way you were in Perform This Way
that's crazy in the far where he walks
out n yeah yeah he's on the far right oh
my gosh that's so awesome so you've met
we out yeah I mean he was really nice to
everybody I didn't really get to meet
him meet him but then I went on uh the
nerdice TV special like two months ago
and I got to shake his [ __ ] hand it
was like I was like ow and he looked
around and because it kind of creeped
him out and I'm like ow sorry he's like
hey I'm like um just like you know
you're you're one of the reasons my best
friend and I have been friends for over
20 years like oh thanks man and shook my
hand and like nicest guy in the [ __ ]
of course he is oh that's so great to
hear it's so just satisfying my my
boyfriend's writting for how at your
mother and they did an episode semi-
recently where the whole uh I don't know
if you guys watch that show but but Ted
the whole time has been like who wants
to go to a weird out concert and he
keeps quoting it and then the tag at the
end and then the whole episode Ted keeps
saying that he that he gave um Weird Al
the inspiration for like a sergeon and
everyone's like yeah Ted yeah Ted he's
like no seriously I wrote him a letter
proposing that song and the next year he
had out and everyone's like whatever Ted
whatever and then the tag is Weird Al
and it's like 19 I guess it would have
been like 1980 something and it's weirdo
with his old 80s hair being like oh
here's another letter from a fan dear
weirdo my name is Ted Mosby Ted what a
stupid name I think some great song a
song idea would be like a surgeon Like a
Surgeon Victor put the coffee on it's
gonna be a long night and anyway there's
all these pictures with the writers and
the crew of that show just going like
they've had like a lot of celebrities on
that show and I and my boyriend like no
one was ever as excited to just they
were so
giggly and that man does not age you
throw that wig on him he looks the same
as he did in the80s [ __ ] vegan or
whatever he is and he possibly drinks
baby's blood it's frightening yeah like
he's too nice to drink baby's blood but
he drinks baby broccoli blood
oh Str dreams
doctor listen to me tell me what this
means first I'm going shopping in my
underwear then all of a sudden I'm
floating in that air my lips fall off
and everybody's on St donuts and hot
dogs are flying everywhere I to wait a
minute you ain't heard nothing
[Music]
yet next comes a part that I will never
forget now I'm being follow B these
fresh and spies they give me some velro
and an order of fries suddenly I'm
bowling on the Starship Enterprise I
fall down a hole and that's when I
realize I'm stuck in a closet with
white I'm stuck in a clet with B white
now
I loved hearing those two stalkery songs
though cuz like that's also my
sensibility like comedically also tends
to be kind of creepy and I think creepy
is like such a funny uh thing to do in
songs and like those two songs are so
they're so [ __ ] up also like like
everything else on the album is very
clean like even stuck in the closet with
Vanna White but like those two songs
like get dark and I love that and so
committed but most people nowadays they
just know how to write what they think
funny lyrics and there's there's a
there's a lack of commitment on the part
of the singer or the musician yeah
they're also not comedy those two songs
aren't like those two songs aren't like
uh I'm [ __ ] crazy like they don't say
they don't comment on what it is which
is a lot of problem with my with comedy
a problem I have a lot with comedy songs
sometimes is they tend to be
like me I'm crazy I don't know that's
the only little too self-aware of their
situation real crazy people are not
self-aware they don't think they're
crazy what they're doing right that's
the problem I have with political comedy
songs a lot is it's very hard not to be
like like I hear a lot of political
comedy songs that'll be like I'm Sarah
Palin and I'm [ __ ] insane it's like
well Sarah Palin wouldn't wouldn't say
that she she would probably feel very
Justified and like one part like going
with the whole commitment and not
knowing that you're crazy is in Melanie
he says how she won't answer her her how
she ignores his phone calls so he has to
dig through a trash to learn about it
yeah I love that lyric and he's pissed
that she's doing this to him like you're
making me dig through your trash to find
out about you that's not right um answer
my crazy insane calls please yeah and
you know lately I've been because I've
been writing like just the past few the
past like two months or so I've been
doing like I have two new music videos
coming out like that are done and I have
another one that I'm filming on Thursday
and like I've been really I've been
really realizing that rhyming is very
hard to make funny uhhuh uh but I
laughed out loud in Melanie when he
Rhymes when he basically he reveals like
I wouldn't have gotten know you for for
that telescope and Telescope I forget
what what L doesn't rhyme but but it's a
rhyming lyric and it's funny which I
think rhyming funny
lyrics can be like very I don't know
it's hard they're hard to do cuz like
you expect what's coming and like
there's a risk in it sounding cute and
yeah that's so true you know how do you
um that's actually a really good point
uh how I mean I know why I mean I think
we all know why he's lasted but I mean a
guy who who starts out and comes across
as a novelty for the first few years
he's out like you can't deny his power
at this point but what the [ __ ] does a
man do like that to stay alive like I
don't know how he stays relevant other
than being up on what's cool you know
well I mean I mean he he has faded
though a little you know I mean I think
he has like a bit of a Resurgence when
like when he did like perform this way
and he's been doing stuff lately but
like you know his Heyday was definitely
I would say the late 80s or 90s probably
right yeah but I mean no not few people
can stick around for 30 years and still
be good and still be writing good music
I I feel as as like again somebody who
was in novelty quote unquote right well
I think part of it too is that you know
he was smart with his money and now he
has his own Studio that's true and he
produces he produced for Ben Folds right
that's true he produces real
music he produced the um uh that one y
the one song Silverman that one or no
the the the first one he just been full
Rock the suburbs Rock he produced Rock
in the suburbs if you watch the video
he's in the booth playing with the no I
knew that I didn't know that but that's
because he produced it oh my God his
Studio that's one of my favorite albums
yeah I love Ben Folds that's awesome
have you and actually his recent Ben
Folds uh Style parody is pretty good and
Ben fold plays piano on it too right I
think that might be the third time we've
said this on the podcast but that just
and um the most recent new Hansen song
yeah produced by weird album he's in the
video as well playing the tambourine
what a good guy he's so nice what a good
guy that's that's the good thing about
his parodies too is like especially in
fat it's like it's it's not just like a
it's not making fun of Michael Jackson
it's using the genre to make a new song
which is always the best Ty type of
parody yeah exactly I love Ham on ham on
H oh it's so smart that's so smart when
I heard that I was like oh of course Ham
on
there was no other thing it could have
been oh it was so great oh it's so funny
and I think one of my other I didn't
like because I you know I back in the
Heyday of N I downloaded a lot of Weird
Al songs and I didn't know what most
most of them were from cuz it was just
like did a search for Weird Al you know
you end up with some of the not Weird Al
songs as well the vagina song and such
and such got the wrong foot amputated
Weird Al would really do that but you
know now like just looking at this I
didn't realize how many of my favorite
songs are actually on this album cuz I
love I think I'm a clone now that is
it's a great creative as [ __ ] I think
I'm a clone just full of full of
terrible terrible puns that are
hilarious yeah and then and you know
Melanie good old days lasagna is so
silly yes that's that's the great thing
it's so the whole album well except I
mean you know Melanie and good old well
like most of the album is so unabashedly
just like silly balls yeah
yeah do you when did you I don't know
when did you start doing funny music
um well you know it was kind of this
like trajectory like I was I started out
as a big big musical theater kid okay
and I knew I liked writing but it wasn't
until uh I was a musical theater major
in college and then I got to college and
simultaneously I got into a sketch group
okay so I started doing sketch and then
separately I started taking classes in
like musical theater writing okay and I
would gear I started writing kind of
comedic musical theater songs but it
wasn't really until I graduated from
college and I started writing um because
I wanted to get a show up at the Upright
Citizens with theater just like a sketch
show that I would write and star in and
um and I thought of an idea actually
this is I haven't thought of this I
originally it was a sketch show that
took place within the context of the
Broadway show a course line so it's like
a confessional of a of a fake character
and every sketch would be but but then I
realized oh if I'm doing a sketch of
that takes in a CH line I should write a
musical sketch and I and I thought of a
a musical idea of a song for a song
about the movie Space
Jam uh which is actually currently in my
one person show it used to be and it's
called and it takes basically it's like
a person in a chus line and someone says
to them uh what tell us an important
story about why you became a dancer and
it and the song is like I love the movie
Space Jam and it's all and and and it
it's revealed that Space Jam actually
basically this frivolous song That Just
describes the plot of the movie Space
Jam and then finally the director's like
stop stop wh why are you singing about
why is Space Jam so important to you and
then the end of the song is like when I
was five my daddy left my mom was
addicted to Coke and it was just it's
just dark story and it was like I was
about to kill myself when suddenly I saw
the poster for Space Jam and I realized
if Looney Tunes can play basketball who
says I can't quit drugs and it like ties
back so that's really that's really
actually the first comedy song I wrote
and my friend Mikey wrote the music for
it it was brilliant and I remember
hearing it and being like oh this is
like really fun I mean and that's at
this point 2 years ago it's been very
recent that I've just combined I mean
the musical the love of like kind of
musical stuff with cuz you know
especially being like a musical theater
major and then being in a comedy group
MH I feel like I often heard from
friends like so when are you going to
decide like when are you going to choose
whether to do like the musical stuff and
that included like musical theater
writing like when you going to choose to
do the musical route or like the comedy
route and like you don't necessarily
have to no no so but then in that case
but you still did grow up listening to
this kind of stuff yes I did and I
always had appreciation of Comedy but um
and I and I Lov you know the ad Sandler
album like I I did love them however at
my heart I was very much a musical
theater kid and you know something that
I was listening to when I was listening
to this weird album it occurred to me
you know a lot of like comedy songs I
loved as a kid musical theater songs
looking back are not funny they're very
cute very clever like you listen to I
mean I never was like laughing out loud
at Cole Porter but uh you you listen to
like a Cole Porter song and actually
Steven sonheim just released a book uh
he just released a series of two books
where he analyzes like his own lyrics
and other people's lyrics it's amazing
it's called finishing the hat and look I
made a hat and he talks about how he
talks about comedy songs in it briefly
and he says Cole Porter is clever he's
not funny because it's word play and I
felt like that's a lot of Comedy songs
in musical theater it's very clever
whereas like weird out especially in
like this song's just six words long or
Melanie it's not clever it's not playing
with words it's not trying to do riddles
it's just like this is the joke here is
my joke and I feel like that's so
important when I got when I started
doing sketch comedy my sense of humor
changed cuz I thought a ton of musicals
were funny and then the second I started
doing actual real comedy I was like oh
this isn't musicals like yeah a lot of
them aren't funny this is this is how
you do you know jokes and [ __ ] think I'm
a clone now is actually closer to the
clever as opposed to funny cuz it is and
and and weird has a lot of and weirdo
has a lot of uh clever and he does have
a lot of cute and uh and but what I like
I mean you know fat is like clever but
the jokes in it are so blatant it's not
I don't know it's like not cute to me
it's great like there's something about
just like he go he commits so hard and
the jokes are so just blatant out there
the there's nothing koi about it that's
what it is you know it's like songs
where it's like koi and cute that I'm
like just tell us what you mean yeah
couldn't think of any
lyrics no I never wrote the lyrics so
I'll just sing any old
lyrics that come to my
child you really need
words whole lot of rhyming
words you got to write so many words
M to do it to do it to do it to do it to
do it to do it right
child this song is just six words long
this song is just six words long this
song is just six words long this song is
just six words
long I know that your prob is
sore cuz I didn't write
anymore I just didn't get to complete it
so that's why I got to repeat it this
song is just six
[Music]
words is there is there anybody coming
up that that that you've seen that again
I know we didn't you didn't say hey
let's do Weird Al necessarily because
he's like my hero everything um but is
there anybody that's that's got your ear
right now as far as oh comedy stuff
music comedy oh man I love Jean laois I
do not know this um Jean laois he does
these amazing comedy music videos he did
he does this he did this recently this
amazing musical video called I don't
give a [ __ ] and it's just like most
rappers claim to not give a [ __ ] but I
give the least amount of [ __ ] and it's
just this amazing song about all the
things he doesn't give a [ __ ] about he's
really really good um um uh and there's
this
guy around La called Zack named Zack
Sherwin his moniker is MC Mr napkins and
he's really funny okay I've heard of him
yeah and and
um oh man I just I just I just checked
out Bo Burnham stuff he's great yeah and
um uh who else is great oh and then I'm
I'm really good friends with this group
and this is more of a period piece but
the Apple sisters uhuh yeah um and
they're just like I love them I'm also
really good friends with all of them but
they their songs are great because they
take that the the best of their songs
take the like kind of 1940s cute genre
and then something very not cute with it
mhm which I love it's hard to do that
right too it's hard to balance that cuz
there's I mean there's guys like what's
what's his name [ __ ] who doesn't
write original music Richard Cheese
who's like okay here's my thing I'm G to
do a lounge guy and do a song you know
etc etc and after two songs he's done it
yeah I get it whereas opposed to
somebody like Toby hus does a Rudy C
which is supposed to be Frank Sinatra's
bastard love child and [ __ ] sounds
exactly like Frank Sinatra and also
things about filthy filthy filthy yeah
yeah amazing um did you one thing that
we kind of discuss a lot like Dan and I
grew up listening to Weird Al it's kind
of what we became friends over um did
you have is there any music or comedy
that you grew up like was there anything
that you have had like a personal
connection to like that or maybe you you
grew to know somebody better listening
to Comedy or watching comedy or whatever
oh um did I bond with friends I'm trying
to think cuz you know growing up the
this is what it is is MHM it wasn't
until like my senior year in high school
that I became friends with the people
who were listening to Comedy okay I was
previously more friends with like drama
geek like so we I mean I when I say like
I'm still behind on music because all I
did was listen to show tunes so I I
loved comedy and I loved SNL uh I just I
didn't have friends who were like into
comedy I had friends who were like into
show tunes a ton so like I bonded on
that like you know like when I say
artists I bonded on like Steven sonheim
was by far like the thing that I like
he's that that artist is like is the
thing I grew up with but like I wish I
wish that I had more of a childhood
connection to Comedy stuff because I
loved
comedy I just listened to show tunes so
much it kind of eclipsed you know like I
wish I'd watched I didn't start watching
Mr show until college and you know the
same with like Ben Stiller show Dan car
to a lot of those too wish I hadn't been
because I mean I remember when I have
like my interview for my college sketch
group you know they were like who do you
who are your comedic Idols you know I
said like Gilda rner as every girl does
because and I really do love her and
then I said George Carlin cuz actually
yes George Carlin I would say I don't
know if I necessarily bonded with anyone
on it because again I felt like I was
the only one listening to Comedy until a
certain point when I was like 17 or 18
but uh my parents had had uh was it
Napal and silly putty first okay anyway
my parents had one of their books one of
his books and I started reading it and I
thought it was [ __ ] amazing and now I
have all his books and then I saw him do
standup Live Twice once in high school
once in college so I would say he's the
comedian um who who I kind of fell in
love with but I was late to the game you
know I knew I liked comedy it was just
that I liked comedy in from a very big
musical theater standpoint and I just
didn't I was so busy you know memorizing
Gypsy that I like never really got into
comedy until like late High School like
I remember the first time I read the
onion which was my junior year of high
school and my mind was blown I was like
oh my gosh I didn't realize things could
be this smart this is so cool yeah like
yeah well I mean it obviously hasn't
hurt because what you're doing is I mean
you're doing so much comedy now and
people are respecting your work so
that's matter it's wonderful and the
show that I have running at UCB right
now is very it's a it's a it's an
actor's desperate musical theater
showcase so it's it's Musical Theater
comedy songs very specifically and yeah
no I don't and when I I mean when I got
into college I actually very much
disliked being musical theater major so
I really flung myself into my sketch
group sure to the point where I would
say that I really majored in sketch
comedy in college CU because it was a we
put up a show once a month it was like I
was making up for lost time that's what
college that's what college was for me
it was like it was like 18 years of like
sort of like definitely knowing I should
like comedy but like focusing on musical
theater stuff and like not having room
for the two and then like in four years
fitting in like kind of trying to play
katchup and being like Oh my God yes and
like writing you know two sketches a
week just like really trying
to catch up with everyone else now was
was the the theater thing uh just your
own thing or is it from your parents
like no it's my own thing yeah yeah
totally uh my parents are very very
great that they always supported me
being in the Arts I always knew I wanted
to be in the Arts I was very much like
the little kid who was like always going
around singing I was like the lead in I
was I was I was very committed to being
um a musical theater actress growing up
I mean I I you know I was very that
music video I steal pets I didn't steal
pets necessarily but uh when I was in
sixth seventh grade I was tortured it
was it was awful I was really made fun I
mean it was it was really really bad and
I kind of immersed myself further into
like taking singing lessons and dancing
lessons
um so you can relate yeah yeah yeah it
was I would say that I would say that
every and and the reason I like comedy
songs is very much comedy still feels
very Escapist for me sure it's very much
like like I love High
premise stuff you know like I it's also
the way I learn sketch but like like I'm
very much more likely to write a sketch
about about like time traveling dicks
than like the intricacies of than just
sitting down and talking about cheese
you know like high premise stuff makes
much more sense to me because that's
where I'm coming it's the same it's the
same like place in my mind like I'm
really into like you know Science
Fiction and Fantasy and like that love
is the same area in my mind as like
musical theater it's like all Escapist
for me sure I mean and that's probably
the healthiest way to approach it it
it's way healthier than I'm in it for
attention which I you know you're
running I think I think that's why I
went all into sci-fi fantasy 2 spending
you know 12 hours a day reading you know
ter good kind yes yes oh I'm in the
middle of the have you guys read The
Magicians no I'm right in the middle of
the sequel right now love Grossman it's
like Harry Potter for adults it's really
good looking for some it's about it's
about a it's not it's about a wizard
school and it's about a wizard College
so they like [ __ ] do drugs it's
great it's really awesome
uh yeah but you know like there's this
there's this great sketch group that I
have friends on called Harvard sailing
team I don't know if you've heard of
them and like their stuff is so it
starts with these very like simple
premise of like you know how people it's
almost like they're saying you know how
people do this this is that tiny
Behavior magnified a thousand times and
they do it so well and that's a style of
Comedy that I I I I can't can't quite
grasp because it's coming from such an
observational sure natural I I love it I
it's when are we going to hear the time
traveling dick song oh that's that's my
very soon actually last night I I did
this thing called sketch gr at the UCB
Theater which is where you write and
perform a sketch show in like 12 hours
[ __ ] and I and I wrote and acted in it
and I did write a sketch involving a
wall of dicks really it was a sketch
actually it's a sketch called um it's a
game show called am I in a dream right
now where it's like
it's like the game show where you decide
are you in a dream right now so it's
like all things that could be a dream
and could not and then it's just like
and now presenting the wall of dicks you
have 10 you have 30 seconds to jerk off
all these dicks like is the are you in a
dream is this dick wall real holy [ __ ]
yeah that it was really fun my friend
and I yeah my friend and I in school
were obsessed with writing like sci-fi
sketches like he and I wrote my friend
Jeff and I wrote this sketch when we
were like Junior it's called now that
you're president and it was about a
president it was President of the United
States like just being inaugurated I
guess maybe senior year cuz it was like
just as Obama maybe got in office okay
and uh and it was like Mr President now
that you've been president um we have to
tell you some things and then it was
basically revealing all the conspiracies
so it was like uh JFK was not killed by
someone on a grassy null he was killed
by a grassy null and then it's like you
just cut to like a patch of grass with
like evil eyes it's like the null is
being currently taken in for questioning
so that [ __ ] is really funny to me
that's pretty good you me want to fly my
head against the wall you make me do the
limbo you make me want to buy a slurpy
at the mall you make me watch The Gong
Show there's really something kind of
strange about you baby but I can't
exactly seem to put my finger on it you
make me you make me you make me that's
what you do to me you make me want to
hide a Weagle in my shorts you make me
want to fall home you make me want to
write a dozen book reports then P myself
a styrofoam sometimes you make me want
to build a model of the Eiffel Tower at
a Bel and Waffles you make me you make
me you make me that's what you do to me
you make that's what you do that's what
you do that's what what you do to
me you make me want to hang out in a
trailer park then take my hamst to the
beach you make me want to do my laundry
in the dark and use a recommended bleach
when I'm with you I don't know whether I
should study neuros surgery or go to see
the Care Bears
Movie that's I have to ask you though
kind of got to go back a little bit yeah
have you had a dream about a wall of
dicks yeah because that that seems or is
just no wondering if you're drawing from
personal experence not actually have you
seen a wall of dicks I've earnestly not
had a dream about a wall of dicks you
know it's a recur dream that I have a
lot that I mentioned in the sketch I
have a recurring dream a lot where I
have to go to the bathroom really badly
like in real life I probably have to pee
sure and in the dream the only toilet is
like in the center of a room full of
people like I had that dream I had that
dream repeatedly where I have to poop in
a toilet that's like in the middle of
like a banquet or like well you can poop
in this toilet uh you know but the
toilet's on a stage like it's it's yeah
it's an After Dream holy [ __ ] wow yeah
toilets and weird places but I think
that you know that also comes from is
did you guys go to like Progressive
preschools no I didn't go to any kind of
preschool I went to monor and I didn't
realize this was weird until years later
there are no it's just a row of toilets
in these really progress really
Progressive preschools you go into the
and this is when you're no four years
old right you go into this um there are
no it's just toilet toilet toilet
there's no stalls so you're [ __ ]
next to some next to a boy who's peeing
couldn't handle that like I definitely
be I remember like taking shits while
like my friend who was a boy had his
dick out and was like peeing in the
toilet next to me I don't remember the
bathrooms of my preschool but I'm pretty
sure it was just like a oneoff like
there's only one toilet well that's it
was a small had M Small Town they would
invested in more toilets and not walls
though I think yeah I I like thinking
about it
now thinking it you know I can't say cuz
I'm very progress and I I love that that
was Li you know I was raised like very
openly about sex and stuff and like but
like I think that's where those
nightmares most it's not even nightmares
I never wake up in a cold sweat it's
just weird dreams I I'm never scared
like the dreams aren't me like oh I
can't [ __ ] it's it's more being like
really are you sure you don't have a
toilet that's like in a stall and
they're like nope nope you just have to
[ __ ] in this toilet on the spaceship in
front of the commander of the spaceship
so I think that's where that dream must
come from is remembering having having
watching you while you're [ __ ] yeah
I also didn't go poop in the toilet
without a diaper until I was four years
old so do you feel that that maybe the
toilet is where your acting need comes
from you have to be in front of people
no okay good no I was going to say we
might need to to to dissect this I think
they're separate I think I just I I grew
up with so I think I just as a kid had
so many personal issues about pooping
and Afraid the toilet was going to eat
me and you know like anyway sorry you're
supposed to be talking about even worse
I'm pretty I'm pretty sure that talking
about you having to poop in front of a
ton of people is even worse I guess yeah
I had a actually had a dream right after
I had not has nothing to do with pooping
it's it's a preschool dream uhhuh uhuh
and I think I had it once more years
later but I only vaguely remember it and
it was right after I graduated preschool
MH we had a play school castle and a
Play-Doh monster ate everybody that's
scary you have some [ __ ] weird
stories and dreams from when you were a
kid man that's going to be and I think
it was I think it was because you know I
didn't want to leave yeah cuz it was it
is right after I graduated you think do
you think the Playdoh monster
represented like
adulthood swallowing you up into adult I
think it was Play-Doh okay all right
it's fair I don't think I was that that
advanced yet at at 5 have you guys ever
been like this is going to be really in
have you guys ever been like super
depressed like never know what that like
like but like so you know like the
dreams that you have when you're super
depressed at least the ones that I have
are so [ __ ] up and scary and like
almost like scary like Sci-Fi movies
like I don't know in college I was like
really depressed a lot and I had this
like I would have like a lot these crazy
dreams involving like torture oh my God
this so this is the weirdest dream I've
ever had I had a dream this was at the
height of me being upset I had a dream
that aliens came to Earth and they like
projected in the sky it almost looked
like a DVD menu but instead of a DVD
menu it was like ways were going to
destroy
you and you had to choose and and in the
and basically then the aliens um
projected this message that was like
here's the deal we are going to give
everyone on Earth an hour to kill
themselves whoever isn't dead in an hour
we're going to kill you and it's going
to be really painful so you have the
choice to kill yourself really pain LLY
now or like wait for us to do it but by
way you're going to die so then it was
this dream about everyone going off to
commit suicide God and um oh my God it
was really dark and I walked into like a
room where everyone and there were all
and some people were putting their heads
in ovens and then there were like a row
of sinks where everyone was like
slitting their wrists [ __ ] it was the
most [ __ ] up dream I've ever had but
it was a really good premise for a short
story or something movie right there you
rbbery about that no I didn't should
Steve K yeah have you seen the trailer
for Seeking a Friend for the End of the
World oh my God I saw it yes that looks
so good kind of a romantic comedy but
there's an asteroid that's coming to
Earth that's going to destroy everybody
and their last attempt to stop it failed
all right and they're like we're
definitely going to die in three weeks
awesome it I I want it to be really good
I I hope so I just want Steve Carell to
have a good Steve's going to Steve
Carell is looking for the one that got
away yeah yeah and Kieran nightly is
like an Australian
accent I thought she was just being Kira
nightly yeah I don't know I can't
remember where she's from is she from
Australia maybe she is from the Moon
wait she's but she she wants to go back
and see her family she doesn't think
she'll see so they travel together to do
that and I'm going to guess they end
it's a road trip movie it's a road trip
mover movie through an apocalypse I hope
that the movie ends I hope that the end
of the movie isn't somehow that there's
no asteroid or the asteroid no I want
the asteroid hit it has got has to right
I hope I feel like that would negate a
lot of the movie if it doesn't it
absolutely would but that's Hollywood so
God damn well this is the way it could
work the interesting thing about that is
like psych there was never an asteroid
and you realize like oh I just had a
really great time only when I thought I
was about to die should we all live our
lives like we're about to die what about
all those people like Pat oswal who's
been banging all these chicks without
protection he was saying he does they
don't care they're going to All Die oh
yeah that line where he's like they
don't care if you're related they just
don't care
yeah I feel like if the asteroid doesn't
exist there's the world after the
asteroid is going actually going to be a
terrible place that's a funny movie idea
the aftermath of everyone thought the
world was going to end and then it
didn't and you have to deal with the
fact they having like your brother's
baby and
[ __ ] damn it I love uh post-apocalyptic
stuff I think apocalyptic question no
I've not had a dream like that but I've
had some very depressed dreams so I can
totally relate okay I had I haven't I
haven't had one that good I would have
really have been entertained by that
dream yeah I I wasn't necessarily even
scared I during the mo during you think
even during the dream as I was terrified
in the dream I was like this is [ __ ]
cool and it's also that thing that's
also the thing in the dream you know
like sometimes when you have very
cinematic dreams you kind of know you're
in a movie so there's a little bit
that's emotionally removed yeah there
was one yeah I love dreams I have I have
a recurring dream holy [ __ ] this is or
at least recurring it's not even a Rec
recuring Dream It's a recurring set in a
dream where it's like a cabin in the
middle of a swamp like a broken down
cabin and then inside there's like a
hidden passage uhhuh and that's that's
it the dreams are always about different
things but that tends to be there and I
don't know what that means cabin in the
middle of a swamp and I can tell you
that I don't recognize the place lost I
don't L cabin from okay he's never seen
and this was when I was a teenager it
was when I first started having this so
lost was not even a from up state New
York cabins are everywhere I know it's
like solar swamps where are you from
yeah Upstate New York oh up oh we've
been friends since 1990 oh wow
depressing wait I'm trying to calculate
22 years almost oh yeah so wait be 22
october9 mhm and then you remember was
in high school you said or no no this we
were in uh fifth grade at grade fifth
grade okay mhm to answer your question
I'm means you were okay yeah you were
born in 1980 yeah yeah got to go in the
way around for this one I was like wait
I I'm not offended I weigh 165 lbs no my
uh my boyfriend's turning 30 uh next
week really well happy birthday
boyfriend yeah yeah he's trying to think
about it I think but I'm sorry um yeah
uh yeah dream
dreams so what was the first time you
listen to Weird Al let's let's go there
I was really young my again my my
parents you know I would say the people
I knew who were most into comedy are
probably my parents like even though I
hung out with drama NS my my parents
like I watched all the like classic
sitcoms with them like I watched
Seinfeld and like uh like my mom would
tape all the shows from the week on a
VHS and at the end of the week we'd
watch them all so we'd watch like
Seinfeld Mad About You Frasier it's a
DVR but it's like the old fashioned yeah
uh and then my mom
had this giant Weird Al CD compilation
and I just remember listening to it the
I remember you know I remember seeing
eat it for the first time and just
thinking like my mind was blown yeah
yeah I was like
[Music]
food isn't it
strange feels like I'm looking in the
mirror what would people
say if only they knew that I was part of
some geneticist
plan born to be a carbon copy
man there in a p tree dish late one
night they took a donor's body sell and
fertilized a human egg and so I say I
think I'm a clone now there's always to
of me just a hanging around
I think I'm a now every chromosome is a
heavy
down yeah I just remember like he does
he does videos like he doesn't just do
when did you first see a video then Dan
oh it was pretty late it was on MTV yeah
when he you know whenever he was
whatever album he was promoting at the
time you know cuz he always did LTV yeah
that's right every time he had a new
album he would do LTV on on on MTV so
and I don't I don't remember remember
what album it was yeah huh cuz I mean I
I can't remember the first time it was
probably in Germany sometime that I
heard it the first like cuz I think we
rented one of his video compilations in
Germany I I grew up my for four years I
lived in German my parents are in the
military so oh cool I got all of my
American pop culture one or two years
too late so I was way late to the game
on a lot of stuff all my Golden Girls
episodes were a year too late that's
hilarious wait you grew up in JY when
you were a kid so that would have been
when were you you were in Berlin were
you uh no I was I was in West Germany I
was in you know the on the American side
was just before I think we left two
years before the wall fell as it were I
consider myself responsible okay good
job that's just how that goes thank you
Dan that's really cool wow but yeah so I
think that's the first time but it was
on it I think I saw his videos first and
I think it was very funny that he did he
eat Harvey the one Wonder hamster in one
of those or did he throw him I think he
puts him in his mouth and think he does
okay that could be what it is but that's
the first time I ever heard and then it
wasn't until years later that Dan and I
became friends over this stuff so I'm
just always curious so your mom was
really cool if she had all the weird owl
stuff on yeah they they really my
parents really appreciate comedy um but
they didn't necessarily expose you to it
like they didn't like say you have to
listen to this no well because also it's
not like they grew up it was very recent
you know like they would have I mean
when I was exposed to it it would have
only been a few years so it wasn't like
it wasn't like the Beatles or you know
it but but no no it was very much like
also it was clean so you know I mean
this whole album is very clean album
it's it's you know it doesn't have curse
words or no and I want to say that I
just we were watching TV also one time
we saw eat it and maybe that's why my
mom got the albums but either way I
think I remember seeing the music video
for eat it first actually and then you
know I think at the time I also was like
a picky eater so I want to say that like
my parents were like eat it have some
more chicken have some more pie like
just eat it like the frustration with me
not eating anything that's funny yeah
that's kind of the same thing with me
and dad like he didn't say you have to
listen to all this stuff but he had so
much comedy and I would just raid his
you know his vinyl collection listen to
you know all the the different things
yeah yeah and and and I wasn't it wasn't
a thing where like I I sat down and like
you know like memorized every weird all
song it was very much like uh oh this is
the first time I've heard someone doing
like comedy songs that's
interesting and I mean I want to go back
and listen to all this stuff now and
kind of become an expert yeah I sat down
to memorize yeah that's that's true did
but since then I mean who since then
have there been any other ones that
you've gone back and listened to people
that people have said look you do comedy
music you should listen to this person
uh yeah uh my dad used to talk a lot
about Tom Lair growing up and and I One
recently and I listened to I have one of
his albums I've been listening to it
yeah it's really interesting cuz he's
kind of that Bri he's kind of that Gap
mhm he's Bridging the Gap between like
that kind of old school light-hearted
you know piano comedy songs with like
hard jokes like poisoning pigeons in the
park is so funny uh what is this song he
has like oh down he has this great song
where it's like down I want to go down
to
Dixie where we had a lot of slaves like
it's very right uh my dad used to quote
this one song that I forget what but
it's just like everybody hates the Jews
yes ah [ __ ] what is that that's uh it's
like everyone something day uh oh crap I
was just singing it just the other day
but it's on the album we did when we did
that album last time uh everybody's
thinking about it's supposed to be you
know appreciation like you know you're
supposed to love everybody on that day
yeah but everyone hates the Jews yeah I
actually want So I listened to that one
Tom lir album I want to get more of it
um and uh and then of course I mean
they're very recent but I I also think
the Lonely Island are legit brilliant
they're so good I know I have their you
know their two albums and turtleneck and
Shane is such a good I was just thinking
of that song Today mhm it's it's crazy
good that song is crazy good but I don't
know how they're pulling off hip-hop to
you know comedy hip-hop two years two
albums in a row when everybody else is
trying that and failing miserably who
who's trying and failing miserably
everybody on YouTube seems to be trying
to do that they try that as a thing but
I think at the end of the day Lon on are
also just good sketch writers you know
like exactly I see I think a lot of
Comedy music is out there I mean my
problem with like not my problem but I
think a lot of people when they write
comedy songs or maybe like well the it's
the fact that I'm singing it's fun so
like I can say anything as long as I'm
like singing and like it'll be funny
yeah and also I think that uh Lazy
Sunday you know was so big I I've seen a
lot of Lazy Sunday knockoffs where it's
and and that's a general Lonely Island
ripoff but it's it's rapping about
something in a badass way that isn't
badass and I think that's really tired
now and I think that's a lot of Comedy
hip-hop now where it's just like uh you
know go and do store and it's like yeah
Lonely Island did that saw that yeah
that's cute um then there's I mean but
there are there are good ones there
Dragon Boy suede is really funny and
then um but yeah it's just it's it's
seems hard to get right and I I don't
know what people do to get musical
comedy right I don't know what you did
to get it right with that video I think
having this sketch comedy background is
a big part of it because now you're not
just writing a funny song you're using
elements of sketch comedy but just
putting it to music and I think there's
a there's a different approach yeah the
way that I look at it and like you know
again like I am I'm still kind of
learning what it is but so far for me
what it is is taking the rules of sketch
and applying them to song and you know
like when you're doing a genre parody
sketch like you're doing a fil Noir
sketch it's like that I mean especially
with these
song especially when you're doing genre
specific songs which is often most times
my way in is like deciding like okay
well it's this or the genre and like it
it's almost like not easier but it gives
you rules that's what it is is like okay
I'm writing um like I have a song like
that I wrote that was like a n a jazz
song from like the 1930s and I was like
okay what do jazz songs in the 1930s do
what are they about what's a Twist on it
so it's like it's a set of rules to
follow that are that feels very just
like classic sketch comedy writing to me
that makes sense um
sorry [ __ ]
sorry [ __ ] I had a question this
happens every time this time in the
podcast like my brain just freezes up
because everybody else has been talking
and I've been listening oh [ __ ] a duck
um I was going to ask you about one of
your songs um well there are three only
three out right now so there are only
the three okay feel bad so I listen to
them all good it's called I was a
mermaid now I'm a pop star it's a little
more absurd yeah thank you it's it's
like it's it's very like
absurdist uh it's it's very it's very
absurd but so as when will this podcast
go up uh probably Wednesday Tuesday or
Wednesday I will have a new music video
released on Tuesday or Wednesday I think
yeah all right you make sure please to
plug everything at the end of this plug
everything at the end of this I mean you
can do it now I'm not saying stop no no
no although stop it's if it's not it's
called pictures of your dick I like that
music that's really funny great huh no
it's not it's not on a wall actually is
a time traveling it's a time traveling
dick dick music video yeah but I mean
that's that's the other thing actually
I'll use that one as an example um
because it does bring up what I I had
forgotten about it's got elements of
it's kind of got a Kesha parody element
to the mermaid one oh yeah 100% but it's
not you're not just doing a Kesha joke a
lot of people parody that one song of
hers like just [ __ ] over and the
first one was cute but after that I okay
get it c a skank yeah the sing Talk one
and that was more pointing out
it's actually mocking the industry not
really her as much specifically using
her to
Mo but then yeah I mean you're you're
taking that you applied it to something
about a [ __ ] mer killed yeah it and
thank you I'm really glad that you liked
it um and uh yeah that one's like a
little more like kind of absurdy
although that that one recently got me
like hired for a job I would say about
the other ones yeah oh really that's
awesome I'm going to start writing for
Robot Chicken in like a week and that is
bitching excited I'm excited and in the
and in the interview we were just
talking about music videos because I
plan on pitching some music video ideas
and they mentioned that one specifically
like stylistically and I was like oh
cool that's awesome that you like the
Absurd weird one that some people you
know yeah well I thought kind of felt
cartoon intentionally felt really so
like I can see why they would love that
so much um yeah I'm trying to think uh
[ __ ] yeah but but back to parody songs
you know I think and I think I've just
never thought parody songs that are like
um I'm Katie Perry and I'm a [ __ ] like
it's like okay cool cool that what why
what of that right right you know like
it's it's just stuff that's like the
artist being self-aware or just poking
fun at the artist is I don't know
there's no subtext to it whatsoever
people don't understand that or when
people do some people do parodies and
they change like a couple lines and then
like keep the chorus like the same and
I'm like I don't be creative like what I
think is great is in on weirdo's new
album when he has his song You Know
Party in the CIA that's [ __ ] he
actually has he you know on the chorus
Parts he actually sings different things
whereas Miley sings the same thing every
time so in essence he's more creative
than her in his parody and it's probably
one of the best s on the
[Music]
newb why won't you go out with me she
lived across the street on the 15th
floor of the galmore building I saw her
in the shower reaching for some soap
I knew she had to be the girl for me and
to think I probably never would have
found her if I hadn't bought that
telescope
oh what can the problem be sweet
man why w't you go out with me oh I'm
excited and that's that's when weird
all's best and that's what he does is
he's not just a parody artist he he's
not he's not parodying he he takes a
song and the essence of the song the
essence of the artist and then he makes
a new idea which is like parody at its
best yeah exactly yeah I mean and God
and it you have to be a good musician to
do it that's the other thing that people
seem to forget you have to be a good
musician the three guys in Lonely Island
have to be good rappers I mean whatever
you know they're really good yeah we're
also probably the only one who's
probably able to get away with actually
referenc sing the band in it like you
know smells like Nirvana mhm yeah I mean
but but I think he's more mocking the
grung like the the garage grunge thing
that's how we got it approved though I
mean he called them up when they were
backstage at Saturday Night Live and
said uh so I'd like to do this parody
like okay is it is it about food oh yeah
I was reading that and he's like no it's
kind of about how people can't
understand anything that you're saying
they're like okay they they were cool
yeah and later on they they you know
they said you know that's how they knew
they made it is that weird wanted to do
a parody of them like that's how you
know you know that you're famous you're
a pop culture icon Weird Al s does a
parody of you yeah K I think Kirk coang
called him a genius was like weird
probably right millionaire did
Chamillionaire said he's amazing rapper
well he does that [ __ ] in all one take
too doesn't he yeah that entire song
like he he if he doesn't do in one take
he twist and does it again he is a crazy
perfectionist also yeah his diction is
impeccable yeah like he really is just
has the words the most important thing
which is so important it's time
traveling diction it's time traveling
hey I thought was the worst call back in
theory you know there's a could have
said it was a wall addiction which that
would have been better that's really
funny damn it there's a campaign to try
to get Rial to be the next Super Bowl
that would be performer for next year
considering CU I don't watch the Super
Bowl I don't think he would flip off the
camera like Mia what what who did Mia
off the camera was paying attention it
happened for like a second it doesn't
even whatever kids know what the bird is
whatever showing a tit is one thing like
I guess that's bad like whatever
everyone's seen this like who cares that
needs to stop being a thing who gives a
[ __ ] I I don't she has to pays for it
does she really really oh God she has
enough money I'm sure she's yeah exactly
it's like all bull craap it's like
basically a curse on live TV fee is what
it is yeah whatever ridiculous that is
yeah Weird Al would be cuz then you'd
have like picture if he did Fat you'd
have like thousands of fat people or
like people in fat suits coming forward
it would be like this ultimate have you
been to a weird all concert that was my
next question I have not been to a weird
all concert I really want when his next
concert I don't know when me look up I
actually would love to go to a weird out
concert we went to one went to one for
his new album and did you go to the one
wait where were did you go pag he just
oh he just did one with the Largo lgo
might have been this weekend actually
atgo
really awes weekend he probably would
have had his quick changes of such a
small venue look at look at up cuz I'll
go to I want to go to I haven't been one
in 10 years it is a multimedia
Extravaganza that's so cool but he does
a quick change into the the fat suit in
what like a minute like I don't even
know it's usually like three four
minutes they show like a short or
whatever still like the suit [ __ ]
inflates it's also great that he does
that you know like some artists like
would be like man fat was from like
Fat's from like 20 years ago man I I I
do new stuff now but he's like nope I'll
do fat yeah I it I feel like he's like I
spent $2,000 on the suit I better do
that yeah yeah right
$2,000 that means a lot to weird um but
yes nicest man in Show Business I'm GNA
$2,000
is half the amount of I feel like he
missed missed a chance to call this
album alpocalypse M you're right you're
right alpocalypse oh
alpocalypse yeah we feel like Miss a big
opportunity and then it could have been
lips um and it could have been lips
doing something aloca lips could have
just been redundant to the point of
complete
nullification until the word has no
meaning
anymore um well I I uh I feel like we've
taken up an hour of your time so that's
usually when we stop there we lit like
we like barely talked about the album we
talked about dreams that's how it kind
of goes
um and if you if you'd like to do
another one let us know because we'd
love to have you on oh awesome it was
really fun being here um plug away what
what what should people look out for
what are you going to be working on well
I have two uh music videos coming out
one should be coming out around
Valentine's Day either tomorrow either
February 13th or February like 15th or
16th okay and that will be a slow Love
Song and then I have one coming out in I
think probably March that's basically
ready I just want to space him out
that'll be um like a new kind of dance
music video and then along with that I'm
probably be having a Kickstarter for an
album I have five songs already recorded
for an album but the kickstarter is more
to raise money for the couple of songs
for the album that need a live Orchestra
like I have two kind of um one is like a
Disney parody and one is a like an old
school kind of jazz like uh jazz song
and both of them need live instruments
so I'm going to probably be and then so
that's probably Kickstarter for like
five ,000 so and then there will be like
prizes you know well once you have the
kick cider up let us pleas let us
know oh that would be great yeah I I
really want to do the album thing and
then I I really want to like I don't
know just keep a lookout you know I'd
love to start performing live sure and
uh keep out I guess keep look out that I
don't I don't even know how to go about
doing that yet what's your uh I mean I
have a show at you I have a show at the
UPR C theater in La that is uh it it's
not going up in the next month or two
cuz cuz La is a crazy timer now with
pilot season but it's called Rachel
Bloom as a triple threat and it's a a
half hour show that I do I would say
probably for that just another maybe
Kickstarter just get enough money to pay
for how much it cost to go with like a
place like Largo that's a good idea cuz
Largo is a small venue so it's probably
not crazy expensive but it is very
popular for like large like larger
celebrities and a lot of people know you
know whatever happens there is awesome
yeah there are a lot of venues to do
that that stuff and and I have a
collaborator on the pop songs too where
like we could get together I think it's
just a matter of I think you know what
it is is that I'd wanted do I'd want to
put on an album so that at if I had a
few like concert mini concerts I could
then sell the album there so I think the
album comes before live sh it would and
it would be good to do that like right
after the album because exactly you've
got the you've got the momentum behind
you that'll be this year what is your
YouTube url again oh uh it's Rachel does
stuff cool and uh is there a Rachel
bloom.com or do you just Rachel do
stuff.com Rachel do stuff.com yeah I
need to update that website uh there
should be a mailing list thing on like a
mailing list link that I need to put
up I'm not techsavvy that's fine that's
fine you're only a internet star that's
fine you
don't that's that's um all right well
thank you so much Rachel oh thank you
this has been awesome um and uh yeah
everybody again thank you to Dan for
being on the show thank you to Rachel
Bloom for being on the show and uh have
a good
[Music]
thing life was so much simpler then Dad
would be up at dawn he'd be water in the
lawn oh maybe going fishing
again oh and Mom would be fixing up
something in the kitchen fresh biscuits
or hot apple
pies and I spend all day long in the Bas
torturing rats with a hacka and pulling
the Wings off of flies those were the
good old days those were the good old
days the years go by but the memories
days and those were the good old
days I can still remember good old Mr
Fender who ran the corner grocery
store oh he stroll down the
with a big friendly smile he'd say howdy
when you walked in the door always
treated me nice gave me kindly advice I
don't know why I set fire to his place
oh I'll never forget the day I bashed in
his head well you should have seen the
look on his face let me tell you now
those were the good old days those were
the good old days