[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast hi everybody it's Jason clom
it's the comedy on vinyl podcast and
live via Skype is Harry sheerer thank
you so much for being here my pleasure
and by here I I mean there right right
specifically you are actually here you
just sound very strange in person this
is um so normally obviously we start off
you know I give a year I give an album I
give an artist um I wanted to just talk
with you about your influences and also
I mean here's the thing you've been
involved with so many of the albums
we've talked about on the show already
uh any of these that you want that you
you're up for talking about I'd love to
talk to you about too well um the only
one that I I mean I I've played with a
bunch of people but the the one that I
can talk about with some knowledge is
the uh one that I had most to do with
which is a great gift idea the the one
credibility gap album that I thought
really represented uh that group at its
best um but the you you also asked me to
talk about uh if I if I had an album or
two that had influenced me yes and uh
the answer to that is a definite neon uh
capital letter yes uh specifically Stan
freeberg presents the United States of
America oh good good uh that is it is
easily one of my favorites that we've
been introduced to that I've been
introduced to through the show uh you
know I had a collection before we
started the show but as you can guess
you know you know a couple hundred
episodes later I've been exposed to a
lot of new stuff and that is a very that
is still a beautiful album yeah I mean
you know there were as you know and as
I'm probably the the listeners to this
podcast know there were really two
different kinds of Comedy records in the
in the Heyday uh of that genre one was
recorded standup routines uh which were
recorded live usually with an audience
uh and the other were these produced
records uh that sort of started with the
uh from to my ear with the recordings of
the the Goon shows from Great Britain
that traveled over here uh and then
freeberg started making these parodies
of uh pop hits in the 50s with a big
band and and with full production and a
lot of sound effects and basically he
was a refugee from Old Radio he had he
had done the last Network radio comedy
show he replaced Jack
Benny and uh when he got kicked off of
radio the capital you know the CBS Radio
Studio was about uh uh I'm calculating
now about a eight blocks walk from the
capital record
Studio he just moved his act over there
wow that's the thing I'm pardon me and I
you know I'm I'm actually this is this
is pertinent because I'm I'm right now
researching the perfect sample chapter
to write for the comedy on vinyl book
and sort of realizing what I what I just
got myself into by picking the sketch
comedy chapter because while freeberg
you wouldn't people don't instantly
associate with Sketch I mean most of
this album most of that album is a
sketch album even even with all the
music on it y yeah it's basically it was
uh the most grandiose imaginable project
it was a uh Prospect for a Broadway
musical uh done as a comedy album right
so there were sketches and there were
songs and and freeberg idea was okay now
let's move it to Broadway which uh
bought him about four or five years of
absolute misery uh but I mean this was a
record that the minut it came out having
been a fan of freeberg
anyway I this was just such a revelation
and I and uh many of my friends uh you
know quickly memorized all of the all of
the songs on the record and would just
you know sing them to each other and
bother everybody else with it's you know
and I don't know if in 50 years if
anybody everybody's so many different
acts have tried to do let's do funny
American history because why wouldn't
you it's an Amer thing to do uh but it's
I don't know that it's been done as for
lack of better word as tight as this
album well you know freeberg came at it
I think with a a
distinctly to my ear and I I got to know
him uh later in several different guyses
I mean I was
uh I I I spent a month um doing a piece
for the New York Times magazine about
him which never ran wow
but we we spent a lot of time together
and then years later uh he got around to
doing the long delayed part two yes and
uh do Butler had his one of his great
members of his cast had had passed away
and of all things he called me to do a
couple of Parts on that record so I saw
how he worked uh with his uh ex-wife who
was his his late wife who was producer
and
collaborator um and so I I think going
back to the the first record um that he
approached doing comedy about American
history with something that most people
don't bring to it which is a great sense
of of absurdity and silliness and very
little ideology right yeah so it had a
broad appeal because you didn't have to
buy into a certain construct to enjoy it
it was just taking it was just taking
taking people off their off their
pedestals a bit and saying well these
really were real people and they
probably acted just like us but they did
this other stuff too and which is more a
comedic than a satirical uh approach and
I I I've always sort of thought that
that's the perfect perspective to take I
mean I understand that you know if
you're a saturnist you you're you're by
Nature going to skew things and uh
although I mean I don't know maybe
that's not true maybe that's that's an
inaccurate way to to describe it no I
think I think a sauris brings a ique uh
and I don't think Stan brought a
critique I think he just brought a
a in a way he was the successor to Jack
Benny uh in more than time slot because
his comedy was based more on just let's
just make the assumption that these are
people like us with all of our flaws and
go from there as opposed to oh these are
a different breed you know these are
heroic and uh
people you know who don't scratch
and you know pick their noses and all
that stuff and I think he just brought
that which is a which is I say basically
a comedic view of history or of of you
know current events or anything I mean
um I I don't think one is better than
the other but I thought that that that
that marked Stan's approach to it which
was you know let's just imagine what
these people were really like uh take
the wigs off and see who they really
were yeah uh I thought that was you know
uh certainly he had he he was not blind
to certain realities I mean take an
Indian to lunch is one of the best
skewering of uh the American approach to
the native population that anybody's
ever done and it's two and a half
minutes and it's you can hum it yeah so
yeah what's wrong with
that yeah and I I guess if it's not
specific like you say it's it's not Saar
because as you say it doesn't but but
it's
it it has those ele it's it doesn't saiz
anybody in particular but it does take
that it's it's it's a weird line to walk
where where like you say you're making
everybody human and then that's where
the comedy comes from but also you get
to still pick apart some of the biggest
hypocrisy in all of American History
it's just very dense that way yeah yeah
and it you know it it's
it it it gives the Indians the
honor and the privilege of being human
too right which was the radical thing to
do at the time you know when they were
the Savages and the Redman so uh you
know he he was a very surprising guy I
mean because of his role in in making
fun of pop music and and then making fun
of American History um people who were
his big fans really thought he was a
much more radical person than he was you
know he was a very devout religious
person I think his dad had been a
minister wow so he came from a whole
different angle uh but he had this um
you know I guess what what influenced me
the most was that he harnessed really uh
serious musical talent to his
comedy yeah no I mean that is that is
the one thing where where I've always
every time we we talk about freeberg
work whether it's that album or whether
it's a child's Garden of freeberg which
we just did recent
um I I've always you would know better
now that I mean you did a piece uh is by
the way is that piece available anywhere
no oh my God I I don't I don't even know
if I have it oh my goodness they had
assigned a piece uh you know this was he
was just leaving he had left comedy he
he had left recording uh side of comedy
and had gone into advertising for pretty
much full bore and pretty much invented
uh humorous advertising right uh and and
was making a lot of money and was you
know revolutionizing the advertising
business uh taking the the the the piss
out of uh clients uh as they're called
making fun of them and enriching them uh
because it made people like the the
client and therefore the product that
was his theory um and the New York Times
assigned a piece about freeberg and
making that transition and they had
assigned it to A A A friend of mine a
freelance writer named Michael Leiden
and Michael uh it turns out was busy
taking
LSD mesino County at the time and
couldn't be bothered and so he called me
and said you know would you like this
assignment and I said
sure uh because I was doing freelance
writing in those days so I I picked it
up and and spent all this time with free
and sent the piece in and I was
really I was coming at it from a um an
irritating kid point of view which was
you know sort of disappointed that
freeberg had U left the world of comedy
and and satirical comedy behind sure um
and and so I was you know sort of homing
in on that but not unpleasantly I mean
we really did spend a lot of time
together and the piece goes into the New
York Times magazine and the rejection
says this piece assumes that people know
who freeberg is and I thought well why
did you assign it didn't know who he was
you know you assigned it with this angle
of you know why did he go from Comedy to
advertising right and you're there's
there's an assumption there that the
that the pronoun is represented by
somebody that people know yeah wow so
yeah oh my god well and I guess and I
apologize so I I I uh I kind of drifted
there but my the purpose of asking you
does that exist is a I want to read it
but since it doesn't probably exist well
that sucks but it sounds like an amazing
experience what is your perspective on
on the way and the reason for him
tearing apart pop comedy the way he did
cuz there's nobody possibly more
potentially Adept at doing it but it
sometimes it reads is like I can't tell
if there is some bitterness there or if
it's out of pure love or if there's a
mix he hated rock and roll absolutely
did okay he hated rock and roll he came
out of you know the earlier kind of
music and thought that rock and roll was
he he viewed rock and roll the way most
people who were fans of of rock music
now view
hipop just put it that way um so he came
at it with you know the view that this
was barely music it was radically
oversimplified and and and pathetically
under under talented and um that he he
did have a critique yeah that was the
thing with with the music paries he did
have a very strong critique um and and
um that could to Rock Fans read his
bitterness um but he he didn't limit it
to rock and roll I mean he he did a
wicked parody of Harry bellante
pseudo Caribbean Banana Boat Song you
know which was basically kind of tinpan
Caribbean alley um and he he also tore a
new one for uh a guy who was making a
huge number of uh hit records in in the
mid-50s Mitch Miller with these horrible
uh Reverb drenched uh Unison singing uh
male choirs um and uh the one that he
picked was the Yellow Rose of Texas and
just you know right ripped RI ripped it
up one way and down the other so it
wasn't just rock and roll he just was
was hating what was on the or was uh
picking apart what was on the Hit Parade
but he did have a special animus for
rock and roll that's what's just so
crazy to me is that he's clearly was
clearly a brilliant comedian and clearly
had this sharp eye towards what a very
like not single-minded but very focused
when he put together something but also
he's got this just grumpy old man
aesthetic to him that just blows my mind
compared with that he he he wasn't he
was he was a a traditionalist you know
in a lot of ways especially and and
musically too but you know the thing
that pervades the the lp the the United
States of America volume one as it was
called even when it came out right uh is
the perfectionism he was a total [ __ ]
perfectionist yeah and I the conclusion
I came to when I wrote the piece um just
I remember was that that's what drove
him you know he he had had a little
fling with television that I think a
couple I think ABC gave him a show uh
for a little bit um
but the only place where he could get
the budget that would allow him to do
things on the with the Perfection that
he craved was advertising yeah he went
there for the
perfectionism man that's oh that's CRA
you know and it's so F that's the other
thing too about this album I just I just
grabbed the the lp just to take a look
at it just to see uh I guess just to
make myself sad because I'm not sure how
many of these people are still around
frankly who are who are on the album um
but the just the sheer production value
on this like in terms of sound effects
too which is one of just it's just one
of my favorite things about sketch or or
great comedy albums it's just so
beautifully put together so not and I
again I don't know how much of that was
him but again I'm sure at the end of the
day the final say was you know that Echo
should be you know less Mitch Miller and
more me he was he was you know from
having been around and having watched
him do the the second record uh I think
there was not a choice that he was not
involved in yeah he he that's what he
loved you know was making all those
choices to to get to something that he'd
H in his head and he wanted to uh
replicate it out in the real world I
just love that this is a time period and
I'm not trying to to be too heavily
nostalgic but this is a time period
where you had that as an option well you
know what I can write a thing and it'll
be an LP and this will be a thing that
maybe maybe as many people will buy as
bought the first family that' be great
but you know you can only hope
uh just that this was an option well you
know there are these little little
windows that open up from time to time I
mean uh
10 or so years later the window opened
up again uh forced open I guess one
could say by the fire sign theater sure
uh and and we walked through that window
uh or crawl through that window long
enough to do the record that we did The
credibility gap at at Warner uh and then
it closed right up again um so you
know you can't look at any Med my
feeling is you can't look at any Medium
as as your home because
of the uh
opportunities come and go the window
opens and closes for anything that's not
uh
resolutely um of the- moment commercial
uh and sometimes it
people in an industry like records or
later on Radio FM radio or later on
cable TV sometimes they're at a point
where they don't know what the formula
is and that's the magic moment and then
when they figure out the formula it's
goodbye right right uh was there was
there another album that you had in mind
besides this one because it did sound
like you said you you might have had
another one that influenced you kind of
heavily as well
well this this was the most influential
but I mean I mean I I I grew up on Bob
and Ray so anything that they put out on
record was was you know uh I I never
thought their records quite reached the
Apex of of their work that the the daily
radio output did but I thought in I
think inside Bob and Ray was the one
that got the closest because it was
basically just a collection of great
radio sketches okay um you know and and
there again um to me
marked the the move forward from
freeberg in a way because freeberg was
still harking back to that world of of
Comedy audio comedy where maybe you even
had an audience but you certainly had a
big band had a lot of cast of characters
and and Bob and Ray moved it into a
little Studio where it was just them and
one one sound effects guy uh and they
were the world uh of all these
characters and that you know that sort
of the more modern approach to doing uh
audio audio comedy um yeah they they
influenced me totally yeah you know I
mean I guess the more I think about
because I think the one album of theirs
we did Phil Proctor picked uh the two
and only uh which is a great album but
it's also I think it's if I'm not
mistaken it's their Broadway show it's a
live stage so it's a different
experience than what you're talking
about which is sounds like just 100% the
precursor to what podcasts have now
taken for granted as if you want to do
comedy it's two people in a room y but
almost never sound effects so I mean
they at least had that over on yeah yeah
they had sound effects they had you know
they had a a great engineer who was a
sound effects man and also was the their
music guy you know found all the all the
great theme music for everything they
did um and that was you know they really
did invent that uh uh starting out in in
on the radio in Boston in the middle of
the afternoon entertaining Boston
Housewives and then and then moving to
New York and
and the two and only is great because
you get to hear how well they could work
at audience right um You Know It All
Those
Years closeted in in radio Studios of
various sizes of smallness um did not
mean that they could not work an
audience and they that that that album
shows that they could but I mean what
what their bread and butter was was
sitting across from mics in in a room
and and I think inside Bob and raised
the name of the record very obscure
record but that's the one that I I
really loved did I mean I the Assumption
might be since you've done so much
musical comedy that freeberg was the
bigger influence but did you ever
listening to B I mean did listening I
I'll just say this uh just get it out of
the way watching watching you and all of
the folks that you're associated with
made me think when early on that I could
do improv like everybody else about 15
20 years ago we all thought we could do
improv from watching you you guys did
you from listening to like a bob and Ray
did you're like oh crap I can do this
was there was there ever a moment of
that oh God yeah I mean that was what I
wanted to do um and when I got with this
group which was originally on the radio
in Los Angeles called The credibility
gap um we were doing three 10minute
shows a day and I thought I this is 10
years after I'd been you know listening
to Bob and Ray thinking God I wish I
could do that now I was doing that um by
the way of improv you know
um neither
Christopher well I I can't I'm I'm G to
maybe say more than I know but I don't I
think I think this is true uh neither
Christopher nor Michael Nor I had uh
studied improv uh taken an improv class
uh been in an improv group uh fancied
ourselves as improv artists uh spinal
tap came came not from a desire to do an
impro movie MH but from a sense that the
only way to make this movie look as if
it's a documentary for Real uh was to do
it uh improvisational yeah
improvisational style well to sorry it
was a choice that came out of what we
wanted the movie to look like not what
we wanted to do if it had been a movie
that had come out of the Second City and
this is in no way to crap on them or or
what they do and how they teach people
it would feel it wouldn't feel so
natural I mean there might even be an
element and I don't know I'd have to re
it's been a while since I've seen it but
there might be an element of it feeling
very simple I mean again even even the
the type of improv you're doing I could
be wrong but it doesn't feel like well
here's the game here's the setup here's
the this this to this there was not
there was you know what what we because
we as I say we we hadn't I had been a
fan of the of of several improv groups
had seen a lot of their work and knew a
little bit about how they work um but
what we were just we were we had tried
writing a script and uh realized that
was not the way to do this movie um and
so the we wrote uh an outline of what
happened in each scene and so and and
this has been sort of the through line
for Christopher's improvisational movies
ever since right the job of the
performers is just to tell the story of
that
scene period MH uh you know and so be
that person in that scene telling this
story and uh it's not about games and
it's not I mean the one thing that I
think we all uh took from um what we
know about improvisational theory is
it's more about listening than talking
yeah uh and and that but that's true of
that should be true of acting anyway
should be all acting um so you know
anyway we've wandered off of com well we
can get back very quickly because this
is making me think of in Terms if if if
I was to look at if somebody were to
tell me at this point oh credibil most
of the guys from The credibility gap are
going to make a movie about rock and
roll and at the same time if you just
said the guys from National Lampoon are
going to make a movie about
college the immediate thing I think of
is is x-rated it really does doesn't
feel like like you guys must have had to
tone yourselves down to because it's so
like just listening just if I think
about a great gift idea um and actually
side note I actually really like floats
I but butk I really do enjoy it but if
we're going to talk about a a great gift
idea there's some really harsh stuff in
there that you maybe just couldn't maybe
wouldn't translate to a film I don't
know but you know well did you ever hear
uh um Bronze Age of radio
yes I have but only the once and I you
know heard great about the harshest
thing you'll ever hear us do was on
Bronze Age of radio um and um it was
sort of indicative of of what we got
away with um in in that era which was
there was uh somebody you know
everything we did was was based on a
news story that was what it all was
generated by and there was some some
news story long forgotten about somebody
complaining about a commercial being
racist and okay our response was you
think that commercial was racist listen
to these and we just had a [ __ ] field
day with okay here are the most racist
commercials we can
imagine see what you think of these okay
yeah and they were done in this style
that and then because we were very
um interested in form
as well as in uh satirical content um so
there was a second level of the joke
which was there was a guy channel 13 in
Los Angeles uh used to show old movies
on Saturday and Sunday nights and um and
in between you know in the commercial
breaks rather than showing regular
commercials like you see on television
uh there were these weird different
commercials uh
I figured out I you know I I I always
follow my nose where this stuff happens
oh this looks weird why is that it was a
guy who I don't know if he was hired by
the station or if he bought the time and
then turned around and sold it to these
these advertisers but he went out with
his little little 16 super 16 camera and
shot these commercials for these various
retailers and then he narrated the
commercials himself with his big boys
name Fred May and and and the opening
sort of teaser line or the the end
tagline was done in very heavy slap Echo
by his wife Gloria oo I like the boots
you know this stuff so and you'd see
four of them in a row that would be a
commercial break it's four Fred May
commercials in a row for different
little establishments so that was the
the form of the racist commercials was
for Fred May commercial for you know it
was and it was just the strangest but
you know outrageous and transgressive in
every way
imaginable so that there's
that well there's this that's another
thing too that being born of a certain
age I'll never be able to quite relate
to is that there's this moment again
around this period around the same time
National Lampoon's doing stuff where if
I listen to it if if if I'm I guess if
I'm in a super sensitive mood I might I
might miss the satire if because again
because it's just so full bore it's just
full [ __ ] steam ahead on some of you
know a lot of it is just to make us
laugh sure and you know I I I don't know
if four people who listened to that
sketch when it was on the radio said to
their their their smoking companion wow
those are that's just like those
commercials on channel 13 right you know
but it it it gave us an organ izing
principle for doing this transgressive U
idea and that's you know in a way um it
it's it becomes irrelevant whether
anybody gets that level it's just that's
what we needed to kick us into into high
gear and and and get us to do the piece
and um you know when you're doing uh two
a show or two a day um that's what you
need is just right you know oh how would
we do this oh I got it we'll do it this
way and then you go how do you do
something though that is potentially so
high-minded as hey guess what guys we're
going to take down racism but at the
same time is just it's just a big [ __ ]
about for a while too like there's a
real it's a it's a tough line to walk
isn't it it is it is and it and you know
you have to you have to trust yourself
that um and your audience that they know
where you're coming from you you can't
be too dainty about saying now remember
please we're not really the
right uh so um but you know that's
that's that's what I guess what we
carried I and the people I work I've
been working with uh all the way through
I mean the the head of marketing this is
again veering off for a moment the head
of marketing at the alleged Film Studio
that released spinal tap said to us like
two weeks before the movie came out guys
don't you think you have to like in the
first 30 seconds of the movie wink to
let people know you're kidding oh my God
yeah literally yeah all four of us we
all four said Unison no we don't thanks
U Christ so that's but that's the same
thing you know no we're not the racist
so you know um you have to trust the
audience that they and I don't know I
don't know if the
if if uh one could do that well it was a
product of its time and and you can't
ever say okay well we couldn't do that
now
one might never get the impulse to do
that now but um whether you can trust
the audience in the same way I mean I I
assume you do I still make comedy every
week and I assume that the audience gets
it and uh I I'll I'll transgress from
time to time myself but um you
know in in in that era if you were
making fun of a racist you could have
him talk like a racist yeah and you
can't do that
anymore yeah it's
on the other hand I got fired from uh a
radio station in Los Angeles in 1975 for
saying the word penis on the air uh are
you for what really yeah yeah and it's a
long story why it was it was it was as a
part of a joke as a part of a s parody
of of something that was very popular on
the radio in those days and the general
manager of the station actually said
when he fired me listen I could have
understand if you had said [ __ ] or [ __ ]
but penis
now of course Howard Stern gets half a
billion dollars for saying penis every
day but you can't have a racist talk
like a racist wow that is uh there's a
lot going on there too much to delve
into I guess well it's it's my law of of
conservation of taboo uhuh there's a
there's a standard amount of Taboo in a
society but it moves over time to
different attaches to different things I
guess it's true
I it's up to tolerance it's up to you
know media it's up to uh personal
preference I suppose but yeah that's wow
um and it's also up to Mark Ferman of
course yeah
naturally do you okay so I I do want to
ask you about something this actually I
was just thinking about this H I don't
know why the other day I was just
thinking about how people are
complaining about Jimmy Fallon's Tonight
Show and I understand everybody's
complaints but then I immediately got to
thinking about your Johnny Carson on on
on a great gift idea which is you know
if you want to talk about scathing it's
pretty wonderful it's I mean if I'm not
M mistaken it's the whole half of the
album right uh or just about it's 13
minutes there we go okay that's right
okay very long though and but uh
obviously infinitely listenable but
there's this you're I mean you had this
opportunity to [ __ ] on an American icon
and I'm and I'm obviously but I want to
know what the impetus behind it
was um
besides the fact that I think most
people know that Johnny Carson was
secretly a lot like that behind the
scenes maybe more than what you're
actually portraying but well yeah much
more a much meaner person from
everything we can find out now yeah um
it had it had um like most of the
sketches on that record started out as a
sketch on a radio show which meant there
was some news story behind it I think it
had something to do uh Rickles was the
guest on in that sketch um a man whom
I've come to like and admire greatly by
the way in the in recent years Mr
Rickles but um I think it had something
to do with
somebody evincing surprise that Rickles
had uh attacked them when they were on
The Tonight Show or made fun of them
when they were on The Tonight Show or
something and so we just thought what
what what do you expect and it was just
okay um but I I don't know if that was
the I it definitely involved something
to do with Rickles in The Tonight Show
those choices were made for us and then
we just went okay so uh let's let's do
one where you know there's a guest on
from this uh gay organization and then
brickles and you know and we know what's
going to happen um and I think that was
it I think it was a a person from G I
don't know anyway that's what made us do
it um and then there was all of the
sort of builtup sense of of Carson as
this very Middle Road kind of I mean by
that time he had a clothing line like
anybody wanted to dress like that um and
he had this you know
survi uh uh sidekick who you know who
laughed too hard at everything he said
Ed
McMahon um and that very kind of
Clubby scene Showbiz scene that that
show
embodied um it and you know as a as a
student of Comedy or lover of Comedy My
Kind of mildly suppressed outrage that
Johnny had just stolen most of his bits
from his
betters uh he'd stole from GLE and he
stole from Winters he stole from Steve
Allen uh all of his best known bits were
basically total lifts from um those
other guys right uh so it was just
seemed to me time yeah yeah and we done
it on the radio it was kind of good but
we thought man we could do a really
great version of this for the record and
uh we had a wonderful engineer at Warner
Don Landy
de uh brilliant guy and just a lovely
person to spend hours and hours in a in
a studio with um and I I gave him
certain technical challenges to uh uh
accomplish with that piece uh we
actually hired the guy who sweetened
most of the sitcoms really yeah so he
comes in with his laugh machine and we
get to watch that at work wow and um say
you know okay we want a little like a
naughty titter here he okay good and
then he covers up his little machine and
switches out his little little tape um
they're not really cassettes they're
they're cartridges of some sort little
mini cartridges and then he plays this
weird keyboard that he's got and as he
plays the
laugh he kind of half silently does the
laugh along with it so he's he's like
he's like a singing organist except on a
laugh it was [ __ ] amazing wow God
that's so and for the record it might
now be my favorite Carson once I was
finally introduced to it I it's just
there's some there is something about
your impression that's just I don't I
don't know what it is it just it's like
there's this extra filth to it maybe
maybe there's also this sense that there
was such a formula to it all sure to his
jokes uh that's you know in in the
monologue and in in his comebacks it all
has a a a grating sameness to it which
is one of the things we were pointing
out uh and uh uh so there's that and
then um
I don't
know if this fed into that because I'm I
I would have
to review the
chronology but we certainly had a a very
uh unpleasant experience with The
Tonight Show I was gonna ask okay yeah
um we
were this has to
be chronology yeah maybe maybe maybe
this happened before um we were doing uh
live show credibility gap and um a
talent uh coordinator from The Tonight
Show came down to see us had I think
he'd been
invited to see you know what in our live
act could work on The Tonight Show and
uh and we had a lot of different kinds
of sketches and he said and we one of
them was a fake daytime talk show called
the Danny Wade show where
uh the uh DC Comics had just uh uh come
out with u an anti-drug thing and so uh
the sketch was uh this horrible Bland
daytime talk show the Danny Wade show
you know afternoon in Cleveland local TV
talk show and the guests were Superman
and
Batman plugy anti-drug thing and um so
that was the sket C that the talent
coordinator from the tonight's show
thought we should do on The Tonight Show
we were saying really take off the talk
show you think that's no no really
that's it so we go there and he and and
he says um calls and he says can you
guys come to the studio just to do a run
through the day before for
camera we said okay and we get there and
he says now look it's just for camera it
doesn't it don't you know it doesn't
even have to be a performance you can go
through it like you know double triple
speed they just want to see who's you
know get get the shots
mhm okay so we just rattle through it
without any performance to it at
all and then he comes ashen-faced and
says
guys um I'm sorry but um Johnny was in
the control room uh during that and uh
he he's he doesn't want that on the show
well wait a minute you said you said you
said boy oh boy yeah that and how I mean
okay I'm assuming this is your shot I
mean I know at The Tonight Show means at
the time this is your shot yep and it
just Falls the [ __ ] to the floor oh my
God yeah so that may have that may have
influ piece on the record yeah yeah well
no that's that's that's understandable
um Jes but the piece was written before
that yeah but it may have impelled us to
say you know if if if the and I don't
recall whether there was any discussion
about whether the whe here's Johnny
should be on the where's Johnny should
be on the record but if there was that
might have slightly put a finger on the
scale you know the assumption is when
you were writing the Carson thing that
you're writing this with no fear is that
absolutely the case because none of you
were you know a-listers you're you're
just you I mean you're doing radio doing
albums is it I mean is it just
completely no fear that you're writing
this
with yeah
yeah I sound a little ruul as I say
that yeah um
yeah but look I mean I I I I live that
thing to to this day I mean I've been
I've made fun of most of the people uh
uh in the New York Media news scene and
and then when I had a a serious
documentary few years back about the
flooding of New Orleans um I actually
allowed myself the privilege of being
shot that uh none of them would give it
the time of
day well I mean that's I was yeah for a
second I was going to say do you miss it
but obviously you don't obviously I mean
I know you're you're well known for
having principles and uh and and I love
that as a comedian and a Satur is that
you can still do that and still also be
funny it's it's hard well I mean
fortunately I have a day job sure so uh
that that cushions the impact of a lot
that that phone will stop ringing you're
a receptionist that's your day job right
if I'm not mistaken just doctor is not
in um but you know it it it's it's not
an easy line to walk um and um I guess I
mean look I had I had
uh at the age of 35 a taxable income of
zero MH uh um but I never had kids right
and it it does you know um if you're not
making the the decision for other people
you're just making the decision for
yourself it makes it a little easier if
if you're if you're having to uh take
that risk and it's uh your kids's
College uh on the
line uh things are change things are
different for sure uh you know I I I was
thinking about this and thinking about
just The credibility gap and the fact
that I mean uh you know in in in Reading
up a little bit more about your
influences realizing that uh you know uh
you know you you acknowledging uh fire
sign's impact and I didn't even realize
you had been in one of David osman's
albums I wish I I had I had no idea
there is this at at this period there's
a lot to do with either making fun of
oldtime radio or I mean you guys
specifically like to take apart old film
strips like picking on that kind of
stuff like there is this this that's
another thing about this era of Comedy
where uh post-war America was
just you know in your subconscious and
you I guess you probably had no choice
but to spew like that up onto like you
know onto an album and make fun of that
I I'm I I just I don't know I I'm I'm
because I think we all take it for
granted as this Nostalgia thing but I
think it must have been something
different for you as you're making it uh
you're purging these things that were uh
poisoning your brain as you were growing
up MH you know um I mean look this is
this this gets into uh more serious
stuff but I mean this was an
ERA uh
where we
were turning around and seeing
everything that we had
imbibed as uh growing up uh as
being kind of brain poison yeah yeah and
we're reacting against it uh and so um
the image that that sort of stays with
me from that is that people would go to
midnight movies to uh laugh at the uh uh
film shorts versions of uh
Batman uh that had been made 10 15 years
earlier uh and laughing at it at the at
the simple mindedness of it right uh cuz
we were in the middle of a hideous
complicated
um
war
and
something clicked for me the first time
and this is now some years later the
first time I heard a um a high official
who was either in that cohort or just
slightly older say with a straight face
we know who the bad guys
are and I realized okay that era is over
we're back to taking this that that
programming seriously right that are
that once again it's proved that comedy
and satire doesn't
work uh yeah you're right that was dark
that was Heavy uh yeah I boy and I guess
the thing is the more I think about it I
think about this era of making comedy um
again working mostly without a net to
use a [ __ ] overused phrase but I mean
I'm I'm I'm of a generation of people
who's wearing that garbage they grew up
with on their shirts constantly and I
count myself among them I'm not
necessarily proud but I'm I you know I'm
a zombie in some ways and I try to fight
it but I do want to know like well you
know and then the funny thing is at the
same time like I'm now speaking to a man
who whose voice I've been listening to
for most of my life mhm and who's been
involved with the best of and maybe I
mean I understand your opinions about
the later years but I mean uh you know
the best of the comedy that I grew up
with as a kid that also had this equally
pop culture like I had a literally had a
Teenage Mutant Ninja Simpson shirt don't
ask me what that was that was a
wonderful bootleg but you know uh there
is this fight and I'm I and I I don't
know what the moment's going to be for
me shouldn't it have been 911 maybe but
I don't know what the moment's supposed
to be for this generation of comedians
to do something
new well you know I I I don't know um I
think that
uh the
um the the
um the thing to me that's that's always
going to be new is um to
just do without the formula you know I
mean I look at uh the comedy movies that
get cranked out now and it's it's no
different in a way than than when I was
coming up you know there's a formula and
some of them succeed and some of them
fail but that doesn't dissuade the uh
people in charge from believing in the
formula even though it's batting average
would get you back kicked back down to
the minors
um and you know you
it's always easier to sell something if
it if it uh partakes of the formula I
mean we got turned down by every major
studio in Hollywood when we were trying
to pitch spinal tap yeah um because it
didn't wasn't the formula and and even
down to when the movie was about to come
out and um and and you know this is not
to say that the formula is bad NE sure
um
the um first ad that the studio wanted
to put out for spinal
tap was basically a u to put it
charitably an adaptation of the ad for
airplane the ad for airplane had an
airplane fuselage tied into a knot the
wanted to do had the the neck of a
guitar tied into a knot ah of course and
said you can't do
that um but they wanted to sell it as if
was the the going commercial formula of
the time even though it wasn't uh that's
how hard it is even when you've gotten
to make the thing that's not in the
formula they want to try to convince the
audience that it no it really is yeah um
so it's that's ever new is just to go
against that you
know um I feel like I've gotten down us
down to dark path so let's go back real
quick to either either maybe another
Comedy album that you loved a hell we
can talk about freeberg again I don't
care we can talk about what I I am just
curious a bit more about your influences
because you're one of the you know I'll
give you the other one yeah um which is
um which is amazing and I I amazed a
friend of mine by playing a couple of
tracks from it uh maybe six months ago
and said guess when this was made he
couldn't even get within a decade or two
of imagining it was made in 19 59 and it
was
uh I forget what the original name of
the record is um it's most of it has
been gathered on the best of sellers um
Peter Sellers but the original record is
is called something else anyway there
are are two pieces that stand out um
that are just
astonishing um and again
[Music]
um the production that's what my friend
couldn't believe was was the lushness
and the Grandeur of the production which
was done by a certain Mr George
Martin oh yes right I'd forgotten he did
those albums before yeah okay yeah yeah
that's one of the reasons that um and
the the two
pieces they're
um one was a supposed film tour of a um
un relatively unimpressive neighborhood
of South London called balum but it was
done as if by
Americans and Peter sers does this Great
fake American narrator balham gateway to
the South and um it's just this
wonderful silly travelog of nowhere uh
done in this uh Broad American fake
American approach but with great music
um great sound effects Peter does all
the voices all the characters and um
that's a and then
B is a piece called so little time um he
plays Nancy and I don't remember her
last name but she's an interviewer from
the
BBC and she's interviewing a guy very
much like um
Elvis Presley's manager uh Colonel
Parker yeah this is a
major and uh he's um he has a stable of
young rock and
rollers and he and he's he one of these
guys and he brings one out twit Conway
say hello and twit Conway is this
gormless as the Brits say uh 18-year-old
kid who's been chosen to be a rock and
roll
star and there this three-way
interview um and um it's it's just
fabulous and it's you know it's about
that era of rock and roll where people
would pluck you know so unlike today
where people would pluck kids
with mini min minim minimal talent and
sort of Groom them uh to be whatever the
market is looking for and rock and roll
Stars at the moment totally nobody could
understand that now no no unrelatable
yeah but it's bril stuff bril stuff and
his and he does as I say all the
characters but the you really feel like
you're listening to three people having
a real conversation and it's and and the
um the uh sort of the iconic moment in
it she she asks him uh twit a question
and
uh he um he gets the answer
wrong we're we're just good friends is
his answer and the major is Thomson
assist that is the answer to a different
question the answer to this question it
is I just want to
be I just want to be an all round all
round Entertainer
enter it's just just wonderfully done
much better than I did it but it's just
Unforgettable stuff I'm going to have to
hunt those down because that's ah yeah I
mean again and
I half for Peter sers and half for
George Martin but that's yeah yeah wow
uh you know there's so many I I took so
many notes and I'm half half proud of
myself for not bringing up the stuff
that you get have to talk about every
time you're interviewed but I I am just
looking here very quick you know I do
want to ask you only because it's on my
mind and I have been interviewing Phil
Proctor basically one album by album by
album for fire sign about the
production um when did you first hear
fire sign
well um I heard before fire sign F
me Peter had a a radio show on kpfk in
Los Angeles the radio station of the
trites and the
stalinists depending depending on which
year you were listening it was one one
of the other um called Radio free Oz
yeah with um Paul J
Robbins and um so I'd listened to that
this was what before I got back into a
show business I was teaching school and
I thought found it a fairly mesmerizing
show um to to plant this in time they
ended each show with a
Raga tonight's Raga is tonight's raaga
um and then
um fairly soon after fire sign started
doing a show on
kpfk and fairly soon after The
credibility gap started doing our show
on krla we were on am they were on FM
and I realized that our our Fates would
be somehow intertwined when a
u Christmas one year a uh guy from
Chicago came out and wrote a
review of our radio show very nice
review of our radio show and then said
and not only that they're coming they've
come out with this new record and then
he reviewed the fire sign's first record
as if it was us I real
okay because we're four guys on the
radio they're four guys on the radio
we're doing you know sort of weird
comedy they're doing weird
comedy you know that's not a horrible
compliment at least uh wow fine it's
much better than the one I I I I keep as
a reminder of how the audience is
allowed to have a much broader taste
than one might have when somebody came
up to me once and said you know you guys
are my favorite comedy group you and
chich and
[Laughter]
Chong yeah well I mean they're allowed
sure no of course I mean I've I've got
I've got cheich on the wall but I've
also got weird and I've also got Mike
Nichols and Elaine May I've got a very
strange wall of record
stuff now Have you listened to their
records lately oh uh it's been I would
say maybe a year but not that long it's
amazing how much of their material has
to do with psychoanalysis oh yeah and
how and how that dates no that is true I
mean there's yeah and I say that as a
fan but I went back and listen to it
about a year ago and I just was stunned
at oh my God this is all about life on a
you know this is all about shrink World
M I've also got my wall one piece I'm
very proud of which is the only comedy
bootleg this bootleg company ever did
and it's a Groucho bootleg oh yeah it's
it's the weirdest maybe kind of super
ugly cover but it's the only comedy
bootleg these guys ever did in the 70s
and it's it's what's on it is Radio uh
no it's it's actually I think it's
mostly hijack clips from movies uh maybe
one or two I don't think they did any I
think yeah I think it's just mostly
movies not the boring stuff um cuz
there's just bits and pieces there are
there are some compilation albums that
you can get that's got stuff from uh um
oh my God his talk his his game show
which is now escaping thank you you bet
your life so it's got weird random
things it's they call it the Marx
Brothers but it's mostly just Groucho
being silly uh but it's a good one um
well well that you know that was really
interesting because people
assumed that the Marx Brothers in the
movies were basically I mean there were
a lot of really good comedy writers who
wrote those movies and so it was sort of
a leap
for uh you to see grouo in that in that
late uh in his career later in his
career game show context and realize um
this is him ad
living he's he's a funny he's a funny
[ __ ] even without those those
great writers around him oh yeah oh yeah
God I love and it's and there's always
of course that just that little twinkle
where you can tell he's a bit of a perve
but not in a gross way like he's just
he's a dirty old man but in the most
delightful way possible yeah um well
those eyebrows helped yeah yeah that's
absolutely true that is true um well I
don't want to keep you any longer so and
I don't know when this out this will
come out I will say though this is the
200th episode we've ever recorded So
it's very nice to have you be a part of
it well thank you um but is there
anything you've been remarkably
persistent I I I hope I hope not too
much so no no it's been fun um is there
anything again I don't know exactly when
this will come out but if there's
something urgent you have to promote I
will put it out sooner no no there's
nothing nothing urgent something
something big is coming but not not very
soon okay so if people go to Harry
sharer.com is that just the best way to
it's the best way to live yeah I agree I
100% agree uh everything's are uh I'm
I'm assuming you're on Twitter I'm never
on Twitter so I don't remember who's
there and who isn't yeah I'm on Twitter
um I'm not on Facebook I I think
Facebook is evil but um uh I'm the Harry
sheerer on Twitter okay um and I'm I'm
I'm I'm active on Twitter good I like
Twitter um you know um for people who
who can write jokes or in a joke form
Twitter's Twitter's great yeah know um
people get afraid of it though they're
afraid of burning
material oh well
then um I'm not I just don't have the
material yeah no it's but that's I
always to me it's always my my
inspiration is always what's going on in
the world has been you know that's what
I do so uh there's always more of that
and especially this year good Lord the
material is being delivered to your
house fresh
daily well thank you and thank you for
being persistent just as a human and as
a comedian it it's it's important and it
makes me very happy to know that you
know guys like you and again guys like
Phil Proctor are still you know being
bad asses in their own way I uh thank
you again for doing this thanks J
obviously you're welcome to do it again
uh if you have the time thank you guys
for listening and as always have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
our blogs read our tweets watch our
videos and read our books please
subscribe on iTunes and if you like us
give us a five-star rating and a nice
review you can find us on facebook.com/
Comedy onvinyl Twitter at comedy onvinyl
and find everything else at comedyon
vinyl.com a major portion of comedy on
vinyl has been underwritten by standup
records please visit standup records.com
for all your comedy needs and tune in to
the new standup channel available on the
Roku where you can also find select
episodes of this podcast
[Music]
in 2012 stolen dress entertainment
brought you the featurelength
mockumentary looking forward the story
of one 24-year-old man's presidential
campaign 12 years in advance of
Eligibility and 16 years in advance of a
good slogan now in 2016 in anticipation
of an historic election season stolen
dress entertainment brings you the
sequel looking forward 2016 14 of the
story's Central character will present
video blogs bringing you their side of
the story on the day following the
election in November the strangest most
unorthodox film sequel in history will
be completed visit lookingforward
movie.com to see every video as it is
posted and to watch the original film
for free subscribe to the channels you
like retweet the characters and share
your thoughts on the looking forward
page on Facebook looking forward
2016 one campaign in pieces