hey everybody Welcome to Comedy on vinyl
this week we have Scott ochman and it is
awesome uh also I wanted to announce
officially that our guests for the
comedy on vinyl live podcast coming up
on May 28th which is a Monday at 7:30
p.m. at improv Olympic West here in Los
Angeles uh is David Anthony Higgins and
Jeremy gusin it's going to be amazing
David Anthony Higgins of course was on
Ellen he was on Malcolm in the Middle
and he's also in one of the great
underrated comedies of all time the
wrong guy it's great it's a wonderful
film uh we are definitely going to be
talking about that even though we'll
talk about whatever album he wants to
talk about um but yeah uh David Anthony
Higgins Jeremy gusin who is obviously a
regular they're both going to be on the
show uh Mike will be there as well
please get your tickets at ticketweb.com
and uh they're only $5 a piece you can
get a two for one deal if you show the
event uh invite on your phone or printed
out at the door uh make sure that you
RSVP on the uh the event page on
Facebook Facebook which you can get to
through our Facebook page facebook.com/
comdy onvinyl thank you so much and
enjoy this episode from the nari film
company uh hair Adolf
hartler uh good afternoon ha hartler
harler how are
you now this this is a strange name it's
narzi films yes we well we well that
does have anything to do with Nazi does
it no are you kidding V they are worst
enemies we are against them we always
were I had
a
kidding well I I I've heard that in my
own home we we hit a Jewish
Family well uh I've heard that there
were many Germans we hit them for a
while and then turned them over to B St
you know sir what did you do personally
during the war oh well I was a baby
during the war I was maybe four or five
years old it was terrible I mean I
didn't know what what's going on I you
were so confused sir just a moment
little German little German Tykes for
confused well sir it's hard for me to
believe that you were a little German Ty
because you look to me to be a man of 60
65 years old oh well you know we had
nothing to eat and I I've aged terribly
all right everybody Welcome to Comedy on
vinyl this week we're doing uh Carl
Riner and Mel Brooks live from the camp
film festival and our guest this week is
Scott Aran hello Jason hello all the
ships at Sea um so why did you pick this
particular album I know you said you
didn't listen to on vinyl first but no I
listened to it on tape which is an old
format that
uh I I guess it actually is tape I don't
know it's literally like tape that you
would you would put through a machine
and it would it would uh sounds would
come out of it oh is that how that
worked yeah it's uh it's pretty it's
pretty old I know you mainly work with
vinyl but this is a pretty old format
sure sure sure um casses your Superior
sound quality and M actually I I may
have
heard I'm trying to remember but uh the
first track I ever heard from it was the
uh 2,000-year old man track uhhuh and I
heard that as part of a different set I
might have had that on CD but it that
probably was tape to but that was uh
part of the American
comedy box set I believe I don't know if
you've ever seen that or I have seen
yeah yeah most of it is
pretty uh undistinguished MH or classic
in a way that wasn't really I wasn't
really relating to you know like I can't
remember what's on there but stuff to
the effect of say who's on first is on
there sure it would be you know just
kind of a recording of Who's on First
and I wasn't really you know responding
to it but then that track was on this
box set and I immediately just really
sparked to it yeah and I I think the
reason I picked it
is not because it's the album that I've
listened to the most um out of Comedy
records cuz that would maybe be um Bill
Cosby himself probably or something like
that but I I think I picked it because
it has excuse me it has the most direct
influence on what I do right now now it
it's really a lot like what I do on the
podcast and and what I'll be doing in
the TV show sure so and I I think that
that
was kind of unconscious in my mind until
recently recently I started thinking
about these records and I realized oh
wow this is
exactly what I have been doing yeah I
didn't even put two and two together
until you brought it up and I'm just
holy [ __ ] this is Perfect 2 and two
equals 4 that is now we all realize but
at the time who knew no nobody you know
it
was but yeah I I I picked it for that
reason mainly because I think it's had
the most um influence on my work um so I
think that what I responded to it back
when I first heard it back in probably I
think I heard it 1993 1994 mhm um my mom
I don't know if you have this experience
do I don't know do you have parents I
have at least two so if you ever develop
an
interest um or a hobby or or something
of that effect um my my parents will
then try to give me Christmas gifts or
birthday gifts relating to that hobby
sure so I think back in
1994 when I first heard it I think I was
I had an interest in comedy I hadn't
started it yet but I had an interest in
it so that's why I got that box set yeah
um and what what I really responded to
it I remember is The Improv nature of it
yeah the um the fact that Carl Riner is
trying to trip up Mel Brooks yeah and
Mel Brooks is trying to overcome
questions that he's just thinking of on
the sure yeah and you can really hear it
on the record I mean I think that these
records are so successful
because um they're not just recitations
of like a script that those guys wrote
right yeah yeah yeah it's a stick but
not in the same way I mean it it it
doesn't have to repeat itself every time
I mean the most recent one they did was
I think it was a year 2000 it wasn't as
good but you know they can still do it
yeah and you know I mean take Abid and
Costello doing who's on first sure okay
so they worked out that routine they
probably worked on it in their live you
know routine over the years but they
honed it down to a script sure and it's
a really tight script and they perform
it as a routine on TV shows they did it
in movies yeah but it's there's
something lacking in the scripted part
of it that really shines through on this
record because these guys are making it
up as they go along yeah um and when I
when I first heard it it was at a really
influential time it's it's really right
before I started doing
comedy um I heard
this which made me go out and buy the
box set of all the records of course um
I Heard
or I saw an Andy Kaufman special on NBC
that they I forget why they were um
airing it but I I really had no idea
about Andy Kaufman's life or or career
other than he was on Taxi was that the
one did they interviewed you was it late
enough that Jim Carrey was interviewed
in that one I think it was Jim Carrey
was Interview that's the first special I
ever saw about him too yeah I had no
idea who he was really other than he was
the guy on tax so it was relev or
revelatory rather I keep mispronouncing
that word that's fine I do too I say re
but yeah that my my I was my parents
would tell me yeah of course Andy
Coffman did that [ __ ] and I was kind of
pissed off that they didn't tell me
anymore right cuz he didn't really I
mean he had he had a couple of specials
I think which you can still get but he
didn't put out a comedy record or
anything and that's mainly how I
listened or or saw comedy cuz I didn't
have HBO sure um you know Comedy Central
wasn't really a thing at that point you
know so so I I saw Andy Kaufman I saw
Bob and David do their live show leading
up to them getting Mr show uhuh and it
was called the cross Odenkirk problem
okay and then I and I listen to this and
those three things I
think I would say the cross Odenkirk
thing and the Andy kopman thing had more
to do with what I was doing back then
when I first started and I sort of
forgot about these records sure and we
did a um uh BJ Porter and I who were in
something called called the Fun Bunch we
we did something influenced by these
um where I was the Mel Brooks person and
he was the Carl Riner guy interviewing
me but that was just one bit out of a
lot of bits that we did back then so I
haven't really thought about it very
much but when I started thinking a few
months ago about these records again I
realized holy [ __ ] this is exactly what
I'm doing right now yeah um so I listen
to him again and it's it's really kind
of
fascinating to listen to back when I
first listen to it I always imagined I
would be the Mel Brooks guy sure sure
you know being the funny guy who's
coming up with and riffing with stuff
off the top my head but now it's
interesting doing what I do now to
listen to it and be paying attention to
Carl Riner a little more and seeing what
he's doing and how he's leading Mel
Brooks into stuff and which is kind of
what I do on the podcast yeah I noticed
more and I should we should mention even
though there's no way they haven't
listen to yours if they're listening to
mine but comy bang bang is obviously the
podcast and the the IFC show there's so
many ways yeah when does wait when does
the show start on IC IC show starts June
8th June 8th okay um but uh I told on
that show yes on that on that show you
know if people haven't heard it it's
basically I'm the host character and I'm
interviewing Real people but then I'm
also interviewing characters which is
what Mel Brooks does on these records he
doesn't just do the 2,000 year old man
by the way which maybe a lot of people
don't know but he does several
characters on each record the only one
that he did um the 2000 man for the
whole time was the fourth one and maybe
they did a fifth one out I think since
then so but the 2000 year old man was
the uh most successful stand out and
then they did a film of it a short film
which I think did some shorts yeah if I
remember correctly they also did it and
speaking to the improvisational nature
of these they did it um on several TV
shows like maybe the Steve Allen Show
I'm not sure but they they had to script
it for that yeah so it just Mel Brooks
hated doing it supposedly and it just
lost everything that kind of made it
special I bet about it um but if you
haven't heard my show I I do want to say
this if you haven't heard my show it's
me talking to real people and then
talking to characters a lot akin to what
Mel Brooks does on this and my role on
it is
to we never know where it's going we
never plan it out so my it's my role to
either uh lead it and steer it into a
direct
that I think is worthwhile exploring and
also sometimes to trip up the person or
to press them on a on a point sure and
make them come up with something in the
moment which is I think what makes my
show so unique yeah yeah you force them
in a lot of ways I really love that
about the show uh sir are there any more
secrets you're ready to divulge about
why and how to live 2,000 years well one
of the big things that's kept me rolling
along singing a song is uh garlic
garlic has kept you alive how can garlic
keep you alive well garlic keeps you
alive because well you know how you die
don't you the scientific reason how you
die is that the angel of death
see Rings your apartment Bell and you
let him in and bang you know comes comes
in and says okay muray this is
it and and so how how does garlic how
does garlic help usually comes at night
right so before I retire I'll eat myself
a nice pound and a half garlic
then I lay down in bed and I pull up my
crazy
[Laughter]
quilt and I'll uh starting to retire and
snore and how does the garlic help well
the angel of death you know comes in he
comes over to me Taps me on the shoulder
I say who is
it and usually he goes woop he takes
right off door well that's an
interesting Theory sure you know about
the kiss of death right sure he not
going to kiss me I'm full of goet but I
mean you're that's one thing that I was
thinking about listening to this as well
Carl Riner who we've seen play plenty of
characters I mean this is not he's a
straight man but he's got enough of a
character he's willing to laugh you do
similar thing on your podcast he laughs
a lot more actually in the second and
third one it's really interesting if you
listen to the first one he he almost
Riner kind of sounds like he
is worried the whole time you know
because if if people don't know the
background of these
records this was something they did at a
party which you know back in the would
have been the late 50s I think cuz this
came out in ' 61 maybe yeah um parties
were the original podcasts yeah I don't
know if people remember that but people
used to have parties instead of Hosting
podcasts so um so they would do this at
parties um where it was just kind of
like a party game where Carl Riner would
to Mel Brooks and ask him a weird off
ball off ball Oddball question offthe
wall and Oddball question um so they'd
be they're a couple of off balls MH um
and and Mel Brooks would launch into
this and so they they were um doing this
at a party and Steve Allen was there and
insisted oh you got to make a record you
got to make a record and they were
saying no I don't think so it's too
inside sure no one would think this is
funny it's too Jewish was another thing
that they T yeah and then George Burns I
believe came up to them and said are you
making a record and they said no I don't
think so he goes okay I'm going to steal
it
then and which is a common thing back
then you know of course so they said oh
[ __ ] we got to make a record so they
went and made this record so if you
listen to Carl Riner on the first one I
think this is before it's a proven thing
before he knows if any anyone will think
this is funny or not so he sounds very
worried and trying to steer it and
trying to rain it in and trying to
control it a little more which um I I've
been there so I know exactly especially
when you don't have a lot of time um
you're constantly trying to rain
something in and and make it not go off
the rails too much you know like if you
only have 15 minutes with a person
you're constantly trying to get him back
on track he sounds like he's constantly
trying to get Mel back on track but then
the second and third records he laughs
more he seems more at ease with it it's
been it's a proven thing and which is
sort of where I'm at now where I can
just kind of like relax a little more I
tend to laugh at the bits a little more
and um yeah it's kind of an interesting
difference it seems to I mean obviously
it's an amplified version of you too
what where where do you come yeah
exactly it's where does it come from for
you I mean is it just you [ __ ] around
with your own sens of humor or you how
are you amplifying you well I mean I
I've I've said I've said this recently
but um I do view the
character that I do on the show as a
character um it is an amplified version
of my own personality obviously my
personality sometimes leaks in like I
can I can hear it on the show if I ever
listen to them which I try not to sure
but um if I ever listen to one back I'll
go oh that's me dropping character and
actually having a real moment okay
um for instance uh we're recording this
the week uh uh Bobcat go weights episode
came out and sometimes I I um if I have
someone on for the first time I'll tend
to do a lengthy interview with them I
think that one lasted maybe 30 minutes
or something before I bring a character
in um just to acclimate them to the show
so not too much craziness is happening
right from the start so when I T when I
do the real interviews with someone and
I've known Bob for a long time but I'm
not you know as comfortable excuse me
with him as as other people I tend to um
be a little more real and and be a
little more I am sort of like a good
interviewer searching for an inn sure to
make a joke or to lead the conversation
into a a humorous Place yeah but I do
think that for the most part if I had my
brothers I would do the show with people
who get it all the time yeah and we
would never talk about anything real it
would just be fake bits the entire time
but you can't always do that cuz the
show is different every week I don't
have you know paa tonkins is maybe the
closest to a person or or James adomi is
closest to a a regular and even he only
does it every month or so so you know I
have to work with different people every
single week so it's a little more akin
to a talk show yeah which is interesting
for me because it's a um I mean it's
that's where the format sort of
developed of talking to real people
mixed with fake people because if I had
a group of people like Paul F or James
or Seth Morris who were on every single
week I think the show would have would
have gone into a different direction
where I just talk to crazy people every
week yeah yeah yeah yeah and then the TV
show probably wouldn't have happened
because that's a big part of the TV show
is the celebrities that I can get on the
show and and involve them in the
craziness okay
um is
is this was this I doubt it but I mean
was it your first exposure to Mel Brooks
or is it just your first exposure to
this side of Mel Brooks no I you know I
mean I I think you know I grew up in the
7s I think I grew up in the 70s let me
check yeah I grew up in the' 70s okay um
so you know I I was aware of Blazing
Saddles I was aware of of Young
Frankenstein I think I probably saw them
edited on TV a lot so like I knew who he
was and I you know Space Balls came out
and I I remember when it came out just
thinking oh you're parodying Star Wars
now you know it was as I recall it was
like three maybe four years after Return
of the Jedi came out and at the time I
just thought that was an eternity like
you know now of course like Robot
Chicken is still parodying Star Wars you
know it doesn't family guys do you three
full parties of yeah so it's you know I
don't know what my problem was at the
time I still have not seen Space Balls
uhhuh because I just was like that looks
corny and it's not going to hold up so I
think I think I had a thing against not
against Mel Brooks cuz I always knew to
respect him but I I was just not
interested in him sure so when I heard
this I got very interested in him I went
back and Revisited Blazing Saddles Young
Frankenstein The Producers all those
quickly became some of my favorite films
sure and so yeah I mean it was it was
really what made me sort of ReDiscover
him and they they say that this is like
the most Mel Brooks of anything he's
ever done mhm like it it it really is
you know in in Blazing Saddles or
whatever he has a script he's works on
it for months this is just pure like his
mind operating at a level of instinctual
comedy which is just amazing to behold
it's probably it's probably the closest
picture you're going to get to what he
was like behind the scenes of like your
show shows as much as people said he was
a raging dick like it's still probably
the funniest he's he is um is uh well
then I guess the like do you at all miss
having comedy albums just physically in
your hands is that something that was
ever important to you it was I mean it
was very important to me I the first
record I ever bought was Bill Cosby
himself yeah um and the Foot Loose
single nice um but so so I I was really
into
that and I didn't even know it was a
movie until I was maybe 15 and my
teacher showed it in the class really
strange really but um I listen to that I
I listened to Billy Crystal's marelus
record over and over and over awesome um
and uh you know Eddie Murphy and I
I someone got a hold of me recently an
old friend from high school to let me
know that he had my Joe
Piscopo Eddie Murphy uh Honeymooners rap
12 in oh my God that um that uh he had
borrowed and um so and I play a lot of
Comedy music on on my show so I
definitely do I listen to Dr Demento
every single week Weird Al Yankovic
veryy into it's I mean it's one of the
major Thrills of my life to actually
sort of know him now you know I mean if
it's one of those things where it's very
common to say if I could have only told
myself when I was age whatever but
that's one of the big ones for me of of
I was so upset when I couldn't go see
him live mhm in 1984 I think for his
in3d record [ __ ] yeah I was so upset my
parents wouldn't let me go for some
reason MH and just to like be able to
say hey you're not only you going to see
him you're going to hang out with him
you'll get he'll be on your TV show you
know it's a major thrill for me so do I
do I miss having records I do but at the
same time um I'm around so much comedy
right now that that personally I don't
miss cuz I just don't know I mean I I
still get records from all my friends
and stuff and it's out I mean comedy is
out there more so than ever if you want
to get it but I just personally don't
have a lot of time to to I I have the
Richard prior box set of all of his
records I haven't listen to a single one
I've had it for seven years maybe I
still have not listened to any of them
so that makes sense you have a chapter
here sir entitled your mate controls
your weight would you explain that
that's quite true I think it's
self-explanatory but I will you want me
to Yes it isn't self-explanatory you
mean if you're happy you gain weight yes
uh no not at all oh contr my dear Fair
no uh actually uh as far as controlling
weight is concerned let's say you have
uh a bulldog for a wife now you're going
to keep your nose and your mashed
potatoes at dinner and you're going to
eat your strain beans and you're not
really going to pay too much attention
to it you don't want to look up let's
say you're married to uh one of them low
leaders you know one of those 16 year
olders or some something if you've got
the guts to do it I never have I'll
follow him for a block or two and then
that's it
you the
end for
um son of a [ __ ] I did it again I had a
[ __ ] complet oh you such a good
question all right so here we go did I
promise I was talking about uh oh here
we go I got it here we go yeah all right
obvious I'm just going to sit back I'm
going to let the magic happen so much
you're just going to hit me with it and
and we'll just uh reel it okay all right
I've forgotten it again no but uh uh are
there I've talked with a few people
about specifically like sketch comedy
albums this I mean this is obviously
improv there there there's sketches I
usually think of sketches as something
that's written yeah but um are there any
cuz again you're in the comedy world are
there people releasing sketch comedy
albums that I'm not realizing because
that's something that I miss personally
I just saw yesterday that this group The
Midnight show who does a UCB yeah uh
they're releasing one awesome um
I talked about doing one at one point
actually as records wanted me to do One
MH and um it just uh is not something I
can focus on right now but um yeah I
mean I tried before before I had uh The
Comedy Bang Bang podcast I actually
recorded one
episode of a more
sketchy podcast uh with um Paul rust and
Neil Campbell uhhuh and those were we
had some sketches but we mainly had
ideas for sketches that we would Riff on
and you know a good sketch is like 2 and
a half minutes 3 minutes we would do 14
minute of course long 15 minute long
sketches where we never even got to the
game of the sketch until minute 8 cuz it
was just us riing and being idiots and
doing anti-comedy so I'm definitely
interested in the form I used to listen
to the Monty Python recordss a lot and
um but at the same time I mean a lot of
times those existed because it was
difficult to get to see sketch back in
those days sure it's not that difficult
now I mean you may as well just like you
could almost
say that any group would put out 12
funni or Die videos that's an album
right there you know what I mean so is
uh if if you were to do one if that does
happen would it be all improv or I don't
know I mean there's something
about that's the thing is is right now
if I wanted to do a sketch I could do
it um on the TV show or or for fting
your die or something like that so but
at the same time when I was doing a a
sketch
show a few years back we wrote all these
amazing sketches for it that just we'll
never see the light of day you know like
Bob Odenkirk is a guy who he writes a
great sketch he puts it in a drawer MH
and then
he will pull it out at at a certain time
actually on the uh the fifth episode of
of my show he does a character on it
that he has been thinking about doing
for 20 years I believe holy [ __ ] he's
had this idea for 20 years he's talked
about it with a few people oh my God he
happened to talk about it with the
birthday boys who are a sketch group and
uh two of them are writers on my show
and they brought up oh Bob has this
character that would be perfect for your
show and so we asked Bob to do it and he
just you know he'd been sitting on it
forever that's insane he did that for
the Jimmy Kimmel show too where like
he'd been talking about this one
character he wanted to do of a jack
Lan um guy who has a lot of energy who
exercises all the time like an 75 80y
old guy and who
then you off a bunch of his makeup and
he's wearing old age makeup and that's
why he has so much energy and it's all a
sham I forget exactly what it was but
but he talks about that sketch forever
and then he just kind of ran out of
places to do it you know we tried to get
a sketch movie going and all sorts of
stuff and he ended up just doing it on
the Jimmy Kimmel show cuz he's like I
don't want to waste this idea so he just
did it there that's hilarious but um I
would almost rather do a sketch movie
the great thing about an album though is
you can record it really easily you know
I have the podcast company which we
could record it there I mean Mike
detective is a lot like a sketch record
Mike detective is a a podcast that we
did last year we did 13 episodes I think
um a serialized 5
minute um 5 to 10 sometimes minute
episodes I mean so that's like if you
listen to those back toback that's like
a sketch record sure it's produced like
a sketch record it's very influenced by
them um but yeah maybe I mean who knows
the great thing about about it is I
would probably put it out through though
as a podcast through my company ra and
then turn it into a record or something
like that people wanted to buy it they
yeah God that' be amazing have you had
the opportunity to meet Mel Brooks or
Carl Riner no the closest I've come is
there's a producer who runs uh red hour
Ben Stiller's um production company
steuart cornfeld who's a great guy I've
worked with him on a few projects and he
used to be Mel's
assistant maybe that maybe uh not as
good of a job title as I he may have had
but I think it was assistant so he's
told me a lot of stories about him but
that I couldn't even repeat but um
that's the closest I've ever been I I
love Mel Brooks I would love
to um I mean he's not you know working a
lot nowadays but I would love to just
meet him and has he done a podcast I
feel like he might have done a few I
just I would like to hear I've never
heard of him doing a the last thing I've
ever I ever saw him do was that dick
Cavit conversations with Mel Brook's HBO
show that was on about a year ago okay
all right which Carl Riner was in the
audience and stood up and like asked Mel
a question and they spent like five
minutes on Carl Riner I was like that's
what I want to see I want to see Carl
Riner and Mel Brooks talk to each other
not dick
CIT all dick Cavit would do is like tell
stories that someone else told him yeah
you know oh we're getting a uh message
from the uh oh oh no I'm fine thank you
so
much this sounds like an episode of
heer's Playboy club but a you want
another drink
H um uh did you ever make any friends
over comedy oh oh yeah meaning when I
was a kid yeah I yeah yeah I mean
obviously now but yeah I like listening
to albums together watching anything
together well when I was
15 well when I was
14 I I my best friend who was a couple
years older than me we we uh met in
theater mhm where we were doing a U
production of Carousel Rogers and
Hammerstein's Carousel so I met my best
friend there and we had very similar
interests um in terms of Comedy we were
very this is 1984 1985 so we were very
into Saturday Night Live um which at the
time was the 1985 season with Billy
Crystal yeah the mentioned Billy Crystal
and um Christopher Guest and Martin yeah
so we would
reenact that all the time we were
constantly doing the synchronized
swimming hey you hey you I know you I
know you we were doing that we were
doing Harry Shear voices we were doing
Christopher Guest stuff I mean Billy
Crystal for all the you know whatever he
is now yeah I was majorly influenced by
him when I was 15 I would do all the
Impressions that he did yeah would walk
around you know I I was in speech
competitions I would I would
do voices we had to do something called
extemporaneous I believe which was like
they give you a topic and you Riff on it
for for 8 minutes and I would just do
like comedy it would I'd slip into
Impressions Impressions that Billy
Crystal did or impressions of like
Reverend Jim or you know stuff like that
so we were really into SNL we were
really into Letterman who's probably my
second or he's he's probably my biggest
influence on on the TV show yeah um so
those two things and we were into stuff
like the hitchers GU to the Galaxy we
were really into
um uh but the th you know I would say
those two things were the big things for
us we would constantly watch SNL and
Letterman every single night did is it
do you think it's important for people
uh learning comedy to copy the the way
you did I mean does I feel like it must
happen for everybody you know when
you're
[Music]
15 you know I was also doing speeches
where I just basically they would call
it hi or humorous inter turp which was
you take a script and you you do the
script so I was doing like Mighty Python
and the Holy Grail just like doing
impressions of all of them you know but
when you're 15 or you're growing up you
don't really know well I mean that's not
there are a lot of smarter people I
think but at the time
all I knew was I really loved comedy I
don't know that I thought I could ever
do it sure but you you don't know that
hey you know you're not supposed to just
like imitate people you should actually
create your own stuff and and that's not
to say I didn't I definitely I had my
own Public Access TV show awesome I was
super influenced by Letterman and
probably ripped off his cadences or his
sardonic nature but but um definitely
created my own stuff for there but um I
you know I remember
reading um an interview with radio head
when they put out okay computer and they
said that they were basically imitating
some other band I can't remember who it
was they were trying to do an imitation
of that band yeah and it came out they
couldn't imitate the band so it came out
the way it came out right and that's
sort of what art is in a way I mean
everyone's influenced by something and
you get ideas and you try to sort of
imitate for a while and then it just you
develop your own style what did you do
2,000 years ago to entertain each other
Wing well no were there were were there
comedians oh sure sure we we you
remember any of them 2,000 years ago
primitive days let me see I remember one
comedian gave us some laugh boy we were
hysterical what was who gave us some
good laugh Mari the nut what what did he
do oh did he give us a laugh a tiger
came in the cave one afternoon Saun it
in Uninvited naturally nobody asked for
Tiger to walk in I here right tiger came
in and Murray you know the the Joker the
tumbler you know the nuts he jumped up
and he grabs the tiger by the table goes
and he went yaha yaha yaha and the tiger
turned around and ate him up in a minute
and then we get
hysterical we left that J that the best
joke we ever had well sir that's not
very funny that's well why did we have
RKO then that's all we had yeah but I
mean that I would consider that that was
the best we had M took a that was
entertainment but I would consider that
in the realm of tragedy rather than
comedy how do you differentiate between
point of view to me tragedy if it is if
I'll cut my finger that's tragedy it
bleeds and I'll cry and I'll run around
and I'll go into Mount Sinai for a day
and a half I'm very nervous about
it and to me comedy is if you walk into
an open sewer and die what do I care
that's comedy I see that's your my
finger is important see want to stick to
the album but if if if you would talk
for a second about how you got involved
with Mr show and what the first steps
were to just becoming well I you know
like I said when I started um those
three things the the Kaufman The
2,000-year Old Man and the and the Mr
show thing happened around in the same
summer as I recall okay or the
same right before summer mhm probably in
March or something I think I still have
the the flyer to the Cross Odenkirk
thing I think it was in March um those
all occurred around the same time and
and the reason they had such a big
impact on me I think was because at the
time I was I was I'd moved back from LA
to La rather MH from um doing musical
theater across the country oh all right
um which is what I thought I was going
to do I went to school for it I studied
Shakespeare I musical theater and I was
kind of trying to do Regional the or
make my way to Broadway or whatever I
gave it up cuz I thought it was kind of
boring yeah um cuz I mainly because I I
uh hated changing clothes uhhuh um I
hated putting on makeup I hated changing
clothes I hated anytime anyone else was
talking in the play um which then you
know I got into standup which is like
you wear your own clothes you talk about
yourself and you can drink yeah yeah you
know
so i' moved back to LA
I was trying to be a writer then I knew
I wanted to work in movies or TV or
something so um BJ Porter and I wrote a
pilot a television pilot like a 1H hour
Beverly Hills 902 and0 but funny pilot
which um kind of turned out to be sort
of like the OC the OC sort of turned out
you know but at the time no one was
ready for it it was like you got to
be you know if they wanted you to if you
were doing an hour to be you know a
drama basically so
um so I was kind of [ __ ] around I
didn't know what to do and I had a u
friend that I had done theater
with whose roommate was Karen kilger
who's a uh a standup and so she I would
go hang out with her every once in a
while and she
would I remember her introducing me to
Odin Kirk at a at a bar and he he said
um I don't know why he took he he he's
he's very uh he always
takes kind of an interest in people he
always like that's one really
interesting thing about Bob is like if
you just meet him he'll be very
interested in you and want to ask you a
bunch of questions so he asked me oh I
said I was trying to be a writer he's
like oh what do you write for I was like
nothing yet I just you know I've written
plays and I've you know have this script
um I didn't know who he was I didn't
know he wrote for SNL I didn't know he
wrote for get a life and all this kind
of stuff so I was kind of hanging out a
little bit in the comedy scene but um
when my friend Mala
said hey you know I read your script and
I don't really like it um you know it's
like halfway between a drama it's like I
don't like the drama part of it yeah but
you're a really funny guy why aren't you
writing funny scripts sure and why
aren't you why aren't you doing comedy
and I was like I don't think I could do
comedy I I don't know you know I I had a
sense of humor that everyone found to be
annoying which which was
is is to say that what and what I found
out is that um people found it annoying
because
people people don't like people trying
to be funny right like basically I had I
had uh I was a waiter mhm
a Chinchin here in LA and all the other
waiters whenever I acted like what I do
now they would get annoyed and say stop
trying so hard or something okay cuz
people I don't know if you noce this
people hate funny people they do yeah
they hate people who are actually funny
sure until what happened was I started
doing comedy mhm I started doing comedy
and all of a sudden I could say oh I'm a
comedian they went oh that explains why
he's acting that way and then no never
had a problem with think you're an
[ __ ] until they know you
professionally okay all right that's
interesting so in any case I I just I
always I I got this feedback from
everyone that I just was annoying and
that my sense of humor I was like my
sense of humor is too out there what I
find funny I don't think anyone else
would find
funny um so I don't think I could be a
comedian she goes well okay my roommate
is in this show they do it every Sunday
night at The Comedy Store you know why
don't you just go up one night and try
something mhm um so BJ and I talked
about it and we came up with this bit we
we weren't really comfortable being
ourselves but we we thought we would do
a bit which was we were a fake um improv
group who we took a suggestion from the
audience and then it just I I forget how
but it devolved into BJ [ __ ] me in
the
ass um
so I and I remember doing practicing it
a few times for BJ's girlfriend at the
time and we show we showed it to her and
she just was like
well all right that's not going to go
well and uh and that and I literally
thought it would not go well but for
some reason we have this belief that it
was really funny uhh so we did it and it
really did well um it it it you know
just like this because no one knew who
we were and they thought we might have
actually been a really bad improv group
and it I remember when the sketch turned
and it turned into and everyone got it
just this amazing waves of laughter um
and and then we got asked back to do it
you know two weeks later and we became
regulars at it um so that's how I sort
of got into comedy and which leads into
Mr show which is Bob Odenkirk who I'd
met at that bar who probably didn't
remember me cuz I was just some idiot
who said he wanted to be a writer he was
at the second performance that one two
weeks later that's awesome because it
was people doing the show it was it was
the people in the scene as we called it
it was your Dana Gould your Janine
graffo your David Cross John Anis Bob
Odenkirk Margaret Cho um so every Sunday
night everyone we knew who was in comedy
would be there yeah hanging out watching
if they weren't performing they would
watch the people so Bob was in the back
and um
I forget exact oh I do remember that bit
it was the one where
BJ ended up peeing in my
mouth at the end of it to humiliate me
and
I spit it out and was crying and I said
I hate you I hate you and I I would run
out of the room that's usually how our
bits ended is me saying I hate you I
hate you and then running out of the
room so I ran out of the room and I had
to I had to basically run out of the the
belly room of The Comedy Store which is
upstairs so I had to run
downstairs then go around to the main
room of the comedy store and then run
back up through the back and stuff so I
was out of commission but BJ he ended
and he just got to walk back into the
crowd and Bob was in the back and he
came over to VJ and said hey um that was
so funny um do you guys um do you guys
want to maybe write for my TV
show um and you know considering cross
noen Kirk who by the way I left out
seeing them made BJ and I kind of go oh
wait our senses of humor are maybe not
that far off from what could be good
because they were doing stuff that was
sort of what we would do around the
house to amuse ourselves and we were
like oh and that in the Andy Coffman
thing and the 2000-year old man thing we
were like oh there's stuff out there
like what we're interested in right so
to have him ask us that was like oh you
realize you're the reason we're doing
this for the past two weeks you know so
and you know it took I still I think it
took still two years for him to make
good on me writing on the show but still
at the time it was like a huge boost I
think from then on it was like our
second show went really well Bob asked
us to write on a show at that point I
think it was like I considered myself to
be a comedian yeah Jesus God listening
to you describe those sketches um
reminds me that there there is something
about your humor and the humor of your
podcast where despite the fact that you
are going through the paces of yes hand
and all that that [ __ ] you do break a
lot of the rules in a really creative
way is that important to you is it
conscious it's interesting I
[Music]
mean I part of the part of the issue for
me um as a performer
is the
UCB improv uh or the UCB school out here
in LA
improv didn't come around until
2005 I believe okay so um and most of
the Improv that that was out here
previous to that I didn't really respond
to okay um but I really responded to the
UCB School of it so part of the issue
for me as a performer is I didn't by the
time UCB came here I was already a
35-year old man and I taught sketch at
the in the first you know when the
school was the first sketch teacher you
know so I thought it was weird and I'd
been on Mr Show and i' you know I've had
sketch shows I thought it was weird to
take improv classes know I still think
like I still think about oh I should
take some improv classes but but I just
feel weird doing it of course you know
around 20-year-old kids you know what I
mean and I would have to go through
level one I mean everyone has to go
through all I I hate those people that I
hear about who are kind of famous who
come in and go can't I just go right to
level three I don't want to be around
beginners right no I mean you have to
you know so I've always felt weird about
it mhm
so and I always sort of Envy the people
like you know Paul rust or Neil Campbell
who were really young when the school
first opened they went up through the
the the ranks and they they took level
one immediately and now they're cuz I I
see the freedom in their performance
that is so fun yeah um that I wish I had
that background so I don't have that
kind of background you know so when you
say breaking the rules I like have a a
general sense of what the rules are of
improv right but I think a lot of my
style especially earlier on in the show
was about breaking the rules about doing
bad improv as I said you are a member of
the new wave school that's right try to
do the new wave pictures now what is
your picture about it's it's what is it
called by the way rape
what well could you tell us a little
about your picture some of the how does
your picture open well we started to
with a with a new wave we uh the camera
Waits until there's a good wave coming
in and looks like a new wave and you
filmed it we filmed that wave and then
the wave breaks and when the wave breaks
there's two people on the beach raping
each
other I see and what are you trying to
say in your film we're trying to say
that there's much immorality in our
society
I see and you show this by uh by showing
a lot of rape and filth and dirt and
people love to see the immorality so
they know not to do that I I see but
very ethical and moral is there anything
in the film that would be well other
than rape I mean you can't do a whole
film no no no then there's the near the
end there's Contrition where the uh all
the raped people feel that they have
done a dirty thing them is there a hero
in the picture oh yes the avocado man we
have an avocado picker who comes to a
Grove of avocados and the people somehow
know he's symbolic of goodness and the
avocado cu the avocado is good yes and
he walks through the Grove and the all
the people are very contrite and they
cry about the their rape and their
Terror and they follow him to the church
to pray for their salvation I see so
Happ and on the way to the church the
Turkish Army comes and rapes them all
[Applause]
because we like to finish a picture with
a rape you know yes so it ties it up but
that there's something in anti-comedy
that I really respond to that that Neil
and Paul and I when we did that podcast
I mentioned that was all about
anti-comedy of like a good sketch is 3
minutes well we're not even going to get
to it for eight right right we're going
to we're going to [ __ ] with each other
and try to um derail everything mhm and
make each other laugh until until
finally one of us brings up the sentence
that we said would start the sketch you
know what I mean so and that is really
really funny to me there's some and
that's a lot what this record is to me
is um Carl
Riner trying to steer it and then Mel
Brooks trying to derail it you know and
that's that's what a lot of great comedy
is is is derailing each other is you
know when when Carl Riner on this record
says did you know
Michelangelo um you know you know Mel
Brooks
saying oh yeah I hated him is derailing
it in a way you know what I mean like
because you expect him to go oh yeah I
knew him he was great I always had a an
appreciation for his talent you know for
but for Mel Brooks to go yeah he was the
first guy to use a roller only on the
backgrounds you know it like so good you
know it that's what a lot of Comedy is I
think so so as far as breaking the rules
I don't have as firm a grasp on the
rules as I wish I had you know but
um but it you know yeah it is a little
bit a little bit of that definitely it
seems like those are a different set of
tools for if if you need them though to
be fair I mean not to say that we don't
always have something to learn but I I
feel like listening you know it it your
style of humor is its own thing I guess
I can understand you saying you want to
do you take traditional improv if you
thought you'd be comfortable doing it
but it what to you is the appeal of of
I feel like a lot of what Andy Kaufman
did as far as you know anti-h humor like
you say is is obviously the severe end
of what they're doing on this album and
sort of there's a discomfort aesthetic
but is that do you think that's the
reason it's done is it done to challenge
people is it artistic or is it just done
I don't know there there a number of
different reasons you could do it you
know another another a couple of of the
other records that I could have picked
um are Steve Martin's records which were
also he my friend
back in high school those were the other
things that we listen to all the time we
listen to him in his car driving around
all the time and that's a lot of anti
comedy or what I view as as anti-comedy
so um what is its role I
mean you know it
it I think I think a lot of times it's
just kind of like breaking you get tired
of doing the same old thing you know and
Steve Martin could have I don't know
that that he could have been a regular
comedi yeah com you know I don't know
that he could have been an observational
comedian I I don't think his brain works
that way you know what I mean and as
much as I've tried being an
observational comedian I've done standup
um I I gave it up I didn't give it up um
I still could do it but sure but I my
interests don't really lie that way
because I'm I'm a little more interested
in in stuff that is different than that
you know so I don't know I don't know I
mean Kaufman just was on another level
of stuff that you couldn't even conceive
of anyone doing at the time yeah you
know um and and certainly my my humor is
not at that level I'm you know very
influenced by other stuff doing kind of
a letterman meets peeee pasti on the TV
show and you know but still trying to
make it my own voice you know yeah so is
there any level preparation for the
podcast other than here's the name of
the is it even that far I mean you know
I was thinking about this this a lot
because of this record and I was you
know reading um when I was Rel listening
it to it to do to do this um I also read
a bunch of articles about it and just
tried to get back into what I really
liked about it and um these guys I mean
you when I say that Carl Riner sounds
like he's trying to Corral something in
the first one I think that they had like
little pre-planned bits sure um
that worked really well at the parties
that Carl was trying to get Mill to do
because he knew we're making a record we
got to get these pre-planned bits going
a little bit and so to answer your
question I think that my show used to be
a little more like that okay um when I
first started having characters on it it
was because I'd seen the characters do
these bits on stage so I'd seen Andy
Daly do um this character in a 10-minute
bit mhm so I think one of the first ones
we did was the
uh that I
remember really well is the guy who
wants to commit suicide by buying a
heavy coat and going into the ocean I
can't remember his name but um I think
I'm pretty sure I'd seen that bit on
stage okay so early on I was sort of
doing what Carl Riner was doing on the
first record which is trying
to ask the questions that will set up
the bit yeah yeah um so like iin for
instance Brett Gman I brain thing even
though I'm acting with mock uh
indignation I'd seen that bit several
times I knew it backwards and forwards I
knew when to interject and and act like
it was upsetting to me you know so early
on in the show it definitely was a lot
more like that but
then and and sort of goes hand in hand
with the fact that I don't have any
formal training I I sort of was like I
don't know how funny I can be I'm I
should be more I I knew because I'd been
on Jimmy paro's never not funny that I
was a relatively gregarious guest sure
sure and so I figured I could I could be
that as a host I would just be kind of
funny every once in a while but I I do
remember the moments and I think it was
it was on that um heavy coat one with
Andy daily where I started just really
asking pointless questions to him
to try
to supposedly to try to flesh out this
story but in my mind to derail him and
to make him come up with things that he
wouldn't come up with and there was some
weird magic about it where I started
really focusing on the coat and where he
bought the
coat and he would he sort of answered
the question he's such an amazing
improviser he answered the questions for
a while but then like turned it back on
me like why are you so obsessed with the
coat I feel like we're getting off on on
a on on I feel like you're focusing on
the wrong part of the story CU he's
talking about how he's committing
suicide and I just remember listening
back to that
one and it may have been the first time
I tried sort of doing that and because
he's so skilled I felt like it was
something I could do and I I remember
that being a big moment in the in the
podcast for me of oh this there's some
intangible magic that happens when you
go off script A little yeah um
so rounding back to answer your question
now I would say 0% of it is is planned
yeah um the usually what will happen is
say Bobby moam the other week came in we
didn't talk beforehand he just said hey
I'm going to do your show at this time I
said great I'll see you there he shows
up we all sit down I say so what do you
want to do he says I think I'm going to
be an orphan I said great let's start
and we press record holy crap and
everything that you hear on that is all
improv Jesus all us not knowing where
it's going to go he didn't plan anything
I I think the most he I I don't want to
speak for him but probably the most he
planned out is that he was looking for a
father or something I don't even think
he knew his name I think that's
sometimes you forget to even come up
with a name when you're doing that so to
when I was like so what's your name and
he said uh orille it's like fival but
one less like that's not planned that's
him just being
hilarious um so so none of that is
planned the most I think we'll ever do
is every once in a while a person will
come on and have a vague idea of some
beats that they want to hit mhm um and
I'll try to remember to hit those you
know but but a lot of times we don't
even get to them yeah so um it's a
little more planned on the TV show I
would say um because we're in a so under
so much of a time constraint 3 minutes
basically for each character that we
have to have a vague idea of where it's
going but even even on that I was just
watching the sixth episode today and
James domian is on that one doing hu
Hower and we had no plan on that like
I've worked with James a lot I know hu's
game I know where to lead him but we had
no end to it we had no beats for it we
didn't have time to do it I remember I
was working constantly and James just
showed up and we're were like okay what
are we doing [ __ ] panic in our eyes and
then we did it and it it ended it ends
up really funny we came up with a really
funny outbeat to it but all the all that
stuff that you hear of like hu Houser
turning into a Crobot on the on the
program and stuff like that none of that
is planned and that's the that's the
reason that I continue to do the show I
think is because the sheer joy and
finding stuff like that just can't be
matched I think you must have known many
great men in your time many any great I
knew the Great and the near Great sir
did you know rembrand van Ryan we call
him rembrand you knew him yes you know
rembrand was one of the first to use the
roller
what how could you possibly the roller
you mean the little roller yes only for
the background F brand didn't eat much
you know he used to money always went
for paint and the money always went for
paint occasional gu and then paint and
paint and paint and then I gu and paint
and I gu and paint and then for a long
time just GS
how about Michelangelo did you ever how
about him is that all you care to say
about him yeah nice fell used to come in
the store once in a while Michael Ang
was one of your customers oh big
customer did he ever pay you off in a he
used to cuff him a lot oh really put on
a CU did you think of taking has never
had money well didn't you think of
taking a piece of his art it would be
worth I thought it stunk who knew why
did you think I would gladly taken it
why did you think that of course there
all people flying around you know it
wasn't like a nice picture of somebody
on a
pony wasn't nice they were naked too yes
you no naked you can't hang a naked in
your living room they do now now well
now they're modern and
diry then we were clean and cute I think
I've honestly asked you every question
we normally ask people you normally well
let's get to the abnormal questions the
strength on kinky what are you
into what ah God I just wonder I have
asked Mel Brooks to come on the podcast
and no it's not going to happen I have
asked is there any like dream guest like
for you on your show either as a
improviser or actual guest
well um pee Herman was a or Paul rubben
was was a huge one for me yeah um that's
another big influence on me when I was
again 15 is when that movie came out
peew big adventure and um he's a giant
influence on me so and I I chased him
forever it took two years for me to get
him on the
of me bugging his publicity rep mhm and
finally it all came together so that
that I think is the most nervous I've
ever sounded on the show like I think
you can audibly hear
me um my my voice shaking at certain
times you know and it doesn't help that
it's in front of a live audience you
know as well which are you know I I
enjoy doing the shows in front of live
audiences but I'm certainly more
comfortable in the studio so so that one
I was very nervous for um we tried to
get David Letterman on Between Two Ferns
the special we just did that didn't end
up working out um but he's a giant to me
that I'll I'm sure I will never get to
talk to I actually just went to a show
for the first time a few weeks ago
really um for as giant um of an
influence he is on me I never I always
wanted to go to a show and I never made
it out until a few weeks ago oh [ __ ]
this is 30 years for him isn't it yeah
holy crap yeah damn so that's that would
be huge for me I remember um I remember
I always wanted to get certain people on
the the live show the live standup show
and I was like I was obsessed with
getting Rodney janger field at one point
and then the minute it pops in my head I
like started to try to explore how to H
have it happen and then he passed away
right away um you know I I Seinfeld was
a big influence on me before his TV show
like I was really into his comedy for a
long time um so you know people like
that I mean you know I I just I have so
much respect for comedy and I grew up a
huge comedy nerd and so you know Bill
Murray would be huge you know I'm I'm
basically throwing out names of people I
will never get to talk to it's okay it's
okay I like knowing who people's
influences are cuz there there are
people who haven't heard of a lot of
people that I love you know and it
weirds me out uh I'm trying to think who
I mentioned last time to one of my I
would mention somebody like uh I've
mentioned Frank Goron to an impression
Amy Phillips was on
I first heard her on your podcast
because of her [ __ ] amazing lies of
Manelli and I brought up Frank gor and
she had she didn't know know you know I
was surpris it's always interesting when
you see something like that it it like
because I knew Frank gon as the Riddler
yeah growing up and that's all I knew
and so to see and you always just assume
oh he was an actor who grew to fame as
the Riddler then you see him do his
Impressions on um I probably saw him on
uhic no not Ed Sullivan and it's like
hits you like oh that's why he's the
Riddler it's like Jim Carrey is the
Riddler because he had this thing going
on yeah his Impressions were really
amazing Amy Phillips for not knowing who
Frank Goran was you know there's plenty
of people I didn't know Ernie Kovac
before I started this podcast to be fair
yeah I I watched a bunch of him when I
was probably 20 never could get into it
for some reason yeah even though I would
thinking back some stuff we do on the
show is probably very kind of Ernie Kish
yeah some stuff we do on the TV show um
but for some reason I I never could get
into it it's hard because it's
experimental comedy so it that's that's
it's almost like you have to be there
sometimes too to go oh that's what he's
reacting to yeah and realizing that it's
the first time anybody was doing any of
this stuff nobody was playing with
chromy at the time yeah but there's a
lot of stuff like that like the movie
Jaws where I didn't see that until I was
maybe 27 years old or something and I
just assumed
it's going to be like Ernie KX for me
where I'm going to watch it and I'll
have seen the parodies of it and the
movies that are influenced by it so much
that it won't have any effect on me but
like Jaws is still great and I was like
oh this is amazing yeah like you always
want something to
transcend that sort of thing where it
and really hit you where where it can
another huge influence on me was Bob
Hope yeah I live on Bob Hope Street
actually which was a giant thrill for me
his neighborhood but um he was probably
growing up the guy that I was really
influenced by and
actually when we when BJ and I started
doing our Duo act it was a combination
of Bob and Bing MH uh and Martin and
Lewis those were the two old school uh
uh touchstones that we had so it was a
cross between those two things wow and
Kaufman cross Odin Kirk that's awesome
um so it was us trying to to put both of
those things together but but we even I
remember um we had one routine where we
were um where I talked about how my
grandfather was an Entertainer during
World War II but he was for the other
side and so we both
reenacted he was in a Duo act as well
and so we reenacted this Nazi um
Vaudeville act oh God and uh we sang a
song um that uh BJ wrote and and Evan
schl wrote the music
to and like we straight up ripped off
something in road to Utopia I think it
is or road to Rio one of those movies
but I think I think it's road to Rio I
think they uh uh hope and Crosby start
with a dance routine and we just
straight up like we were like in the
middle of the routine I have a little
musical theater background I was doing a
little tap and stuff and we were like
okay we need to do something here what
do we do and so we watched RoR Rio and
they do this hilarious bit where
um where Bing puts his hands down like
he's going to give Bob Hope a lift and
have him do a flip uh and Bob puts his
foot on it and then they jump up in the
air about one foot off the ground to go
hey awesome and it's really really funny
we're like let's just try that and you
know we did it and just straight up
ripped it off but at the same time you
know they were ripping it off from
someone's shoe so you know of course but
yeah really into those guys yes yes it's
very exclusive Community yes why is it
so exclusive well we don't allow
children for one thing I mean a whole
city without children we do have
children what do you do with them we
send them to
Hartford well who takes care of them
Jewish and Italian families people who
like children you know we're we're not
crazy about children you know I see I
see uh are sir are you married uh yes I
where do you live I'm very happily
married I live right in Connecticut
Connecticut you have children I have six
darling children I'm sorry four make
that four four yes I have four where are
they sir uh they're in Hartford living
with an
Itali lovely Italian couple taking care
of them for us do you see them often do
you visit them oh yes of a Sunday of a
Tuesday of one of those days I I might
just Moi over to Hartford and high a
gang you know and then speed right back
to Connecticut Connecticut you mosy over
in speed back yes if you were to this is
the final question the one I'd forgotten
uh if you were to recommend this album
to people which I assume you are since
you did oh yeah why for somebody who's
never maybe even listened to Mel Brooks
or never obviously never heard the album
what's what's the reason you would say I
mean if if you want to hear a comedian
just at the height of his intelligence
coming up with
stuff so quickly that you wouldn't
believe it
um you should definitely listen to this
I mean and the other part of it is
unlike a lot of standup records a lot of
sketch records it is improv I mean it's
the most it's the thing that's most akin
to certainly my podcast but a lot of
podcast out there where it's just people
riffing and thinking of stuff really
really quickly and the reason I picked
the third one out of all of them and I
would just say listen excuse me listen
to all of them but the reason I picked
the third one is I think it has the
highest ratio of bits that really really
work and and for me the most classic
lines in it I think the
the line where Mel Brooks describes the
difference between tragedy and comedy I
didn't know that came from this album
until that's crazy it's so great and it
sounds that actually sounds like it may
have been something he'd said before but
the fact that he pulls it yeah really
quickly mhm um and all based on a
suggestion from Carl Riner I mean it's
not like they had planned that out of
like oh let's go into the comedy tragedy
bit it really was just like
like and and maybe it was maybe it was
Carl Riner knowing that he that Mel
Brooks had this in reserve or something
and like setting him up and just teeing
him up so that Mel Brooks can knock it
out of the park but but this record has
the most the the highest ratio I think
of just bits that really really work as
well as it has the best non 2,000-year
Old Man characters that um Mel Brooks
does I think the
um I think actually the the second
record the 2001 year I love the third
best poet that's really akin to
something that we do on Comedy Bang Bang
but um I love Dr Felix weird is great it
really is like the by the the first
record Mel Brooks is trying a lot of
different types of characters and not
all of them work the I I know the um
Fabiola is like a minute and a half and
it's him doing a um basically an
impression of a 60s Coffee House singer
and all the only joke to it is he's like
hey that's it you know there's there's
no joke to it but by the third record he
figured out what works I think for him
and so all there's four tracks on it and
on all four of them he's playing
variations of of the 2,000-year old man
just with different voices so I think
it's the best one out of all of them
just for that reason and so I mean to to
me it's
just they're some of the best best
records of all time just because there's
stuff on them that you would never hear
anywhere else and it's all just because
they happen to have a tape recorder
running and they are incredibly quick
yeah thank you so much for coming here
my pleasure and plug things that need to
be plugged please sure well I mean I I I
want everyone to watch The Comedy Bang
Bang TV show it starts June 8th on IFC
um when does this come out if if I'm
going to try and edit it and put it up
tonight oh great okay so
uh very soon there will be an episode
streaming um at IFC I think on the 24th
there will be our second episode
complete episode will be up there with
Amy Po and um uh Andy Dy and David
Kenner awesome and so if people are into
comedy and I I imagine you are if you're
listening to this our very first episode
on June 8th has Zack alfanis Andy Daly
Will Forte Thomas Lennon Gillian Jacobs
me and Reggie Watts um as well as some
other people so it's it's really every
single episode
um you'll see what a comedy nerd I am
because they are packed with comedians
in it and and I believe our eighth
episode I have Dave Thomas from SCTV
he's playing my father like it it
working on this show I got to meet so
many amazing comedians I got to put so
many amazing comedians in there there's
like places where will Arnette pops up
doing a couple of lines and then he's
gone you know I mean normally normal
shows would have will arette that he'd
be there the entire half hour like my
show I just Tred to fit as much comedy
as I can into it I have great people who
would would drop by and do me a favor
and um so I think the show is really
special um fans are really going to
enjoy it fans of the podcast I think
will see that it's a lot like the
podcast but it it's it's a TV show I'm
really really proud of it and I think
people will really enjoy it that's
amazing that sounds so exciting uh
Twitter you are you just Scott oerman
yeah the normal a and go to earwolf.com
Comedy is it Comedy Bang bang.com or the
path Comedy Bang bang.com is out there
ALS yeah earwolf.com also you know and
listen to the show every single week I'm
still going to continue to do the
podcast uh if I could do it during
production of the show I can continue on
you know so I definitely it's very
important to me I got the TV show
because of the podcast so I'm going to
continue to do it sure that's awesome
thank you so much for coming my pleasure
Brian thank you and I will also very
quickly say uh come to the live episode
of this show which is going to be uh
Monday May 28th 7:30 iio West buy your
tickets online please and uh who's the
guest uh David Anthony Higgins great and
uh also my buddy Jeremy uh gusin who was
awesome and say hi to David for me I
will we're old buddies ask him about the
wrong
guy you hosted did you not host the
showing of that at okay Sant family
that's where I got to meet him for the
first time oh yeah yeah
got to meet Dave Foley and almost [ __ ]
myself great yeah yeah yeah's he's a
very nice guy yeah that movie is amazing
watch the wrong guy everyone get a DVD
of it brilliant if you can find it yeah
all right thank you again thanks and
everybody have a good thing how does you
feel about the the motion picture
Stanley K's Motion Picture judgment end
durble
unfair uh why did you consider it unfair
well because he didn't tell the whole
Truth uh uh what was the picture about
really about a misunderstanding really
wasn't it I mean look you have uh you
you send people to Camp don't you in the
summer we sent a few people to Camp I
don't know what the whole fuss is about
well sir um sent some nice people to
Camp sir did you did you know mostly in
the
summer how did you feel about Adolf
Hitler personally oh well I I I thought
that he made some terrible errors losing
the war was a big
error made a couple of blunders
[Music]
there comedy on vinyl is recorded at
Fort awesome studios in beautiful
downtown Burbank California our producer
is Mike Warden our host is Jason clom
and he's also the editor comedy on vinyl
is a stolen dress entertainment
production you can check out all of our
other podcasts books videos other audio
stuff probably some writing at stolen
dress.com and please check out comedy
onvinyl at facebook.com/ comdy onvinyl
twitter.com comdy onvinyl and please
subscribe to us on iTunes rate US highly
and spread the word thank you so much
for listening to Comedy on vinyl this
week and have a very good thing
like a
man I said to a Mary and your look she
said that's my man and whispered in
my let bra dangle Dingle dingle
dangle got gold R right through the
mangle over