hey everybody thanks for joining me this
week uh this is a special bonus episode
uh so bonus uh that I it's the day after
our last episode with Sarah pook uh this
episode is with Kelly Carlin she talks
about growing up with her father George
Carlin uh her history as a writer and a
performer and her new show A Carlin Home
Companion uh which is going to be at the
Acme Comedy theater this weekend May
18th at 8 p.m. it's 135 North laa in Los
Angeles 90036 why not give you all the
information um I will put all the links
on the website but definitely go to
kellyc
car.com uh which uh will have everything
you need follow her at kellyc Carin and
enjoy the rest of this episode obviously
no clips um because it's just me talking
uh with her and it's a lot of fun uh a
great episode so enjoy it hey everybody
thank you for joining us uh this week I
have with me Kelly Carlin hey I'm here
thank you for being here it's my
pleasure I feel like I'm in the Cocoon
of Comedy
nerdness yay that's the best possible
compliment I could possibly get
excellent uh and the uh it it was nice I
got contacted
at uh I was asked if if I would like to
have you on my show to which my answer
might have been are you [ __ ] kidding
me but I instead said yeah great that'd
be nice wonderful so yeah so um you were
doing let's start off you're you're
doing a show right now now yeah I've
been doing it for about 2 years now holy
cow really yeah is it is it are you
developing it or is it the same thing oh
no no I'm done I'm done developing it
we're going to New York in the fall with
it amazing yeah yeah no we started
developing it in uh around this no
actually way earlier this time of year
uh in 2011 okay uh in
February uh well basically how it
started was in the fall of
2010 mhm uh Louis black invited my
myself and my husband on a cruise ship
that he was he was doing a comedy Cruise
like this he was just like he didn't
know if he wanted to do this or not but
he's like [ __ ] it I'm going to bring
people I want to hang out with on this
cruise ship and it was like a normal
size Royal
Caribbean 2,000 people craziness but
they were going to have 400 hardcore
Lewis Black fans come on board and then
he invited like six or seven of his
standup friends to come and just kind of
rotate each night someone opens someone
features someone headlines it's crazy
and then he had a couple of daytime
slots that he needed to fill and he said
and he knew I was a Storyteller and he's
like can you just come on and like I
don't know play some videos of your dad
and tell some family stories right right
and I'm like sure anything to get on a
cruise ship for seven days with leis
black Kathleen Madigan John Bowman Ted
Alexandro John Panet wow um uh uh I
can't a couple other people I can't
remember uh it was insane it was insane
fun so I literally like the morning of
like I had a couple of compilation DVDs
of my dad's and I was like okay what are
we going to do here I don't know we'll
do Johnny he did a Johnny Carson thing
we did this and I just kind of did like
40 years of my dad's whatever it was and
then I was like all right 1960 uh my
parents met in Dayton Ohio okay remember
that story and I like told the stories
of that I tell and that my dad had told
before for and like told in his Memoir
and told at cocktail parties and things
like that right and um people freaked
out about it I bet like totally freaked
out about bet I bet I would I would have
I don't know lost my [ __ ] and I was like
wow really I mean like all week long
people were like oh my God this is the
best thing all week and thank you and
the comics were like laughing and crying
and oh my God and and then like all the
agents and managers were like hey kid I
think you got a show here you could you
could to with this show you know and
Evergreen Evergreen kind of a show and
so I came home and I was like you know
it's like I I didn't like plan on like
my first big creative thing after my dad
died being my my life story with my dad
I mean it was like you know you're kind
of hoping to like you know find your own
voice in your own Direction
littleit but I thought hm there was
something about the idea
of going and taking this to my dad's
fans MH and knowing that this was I kind
of think of this as like the George
Carin farewell tour of course yeah yeah
yeah and that really warmed my heart
like I wanted them to connect with him
on a deeper level and get to see all of
who he was and so in February of 2011 um
I was hanging out with Paul provenza now
at this point and he said
um do are you do want to do anything
with this you know and I'm like well I
don't know maybe he goes well if you do
I want to direct it wow I know exactly
right and I was like well if I have Paul
prenza directing it then I know I'm not
going to make a total [ __ ] [ __ ] of
myself because for me he is like the
highest of Comedy tastes there is sure
and uh so he basically within a month
had me booked at Just for Laughs in
Montreal Wow Wow in July coming up so I
was like oh okay well I guess we're
doing this thing holy [ __ ] yeah so I
started just going down to the comedy
magic club in Hermosa Beach and using
their little side room the lounge MH
because Mike down there had always said
to me if you ever want to workout
material or anything come down use the
lounge and I just once a week got up on
stage and just started recording and
telling stories and writing and writing
on my feet and I'm really a writer
writer first of all and so right one
night I just decided to write on my feet
and just see what would come out and
like 2 and a half hours later I was
like okay I do not work that well I do
not work that way I'm clearly my
father's daughter in that way I have to
have it down and then organized yeah and
then by the time I got to July um in
Montreal I had it in decent shape but I
didn't have it fully memorized okay I
hadn't had really actualized it so I had
2third of it on music stands on stage
right stage left which I would kind of
go back and forth and then in the middle
I would come and do scenarios and scenes
and do the acting part of things and
then go back to the narrating or
whatever and um and then after we did
that prens and I got together in the
fall of 2011 and that's when we really
developed it we carved it shaped it had
5 hour sessions where you know it was
like therapy and he would smoke a lot of
pot and I would cry a lot oh my gosh oh
my God and I I would just you know and
tell him stories that had nothing to do
with anything that would ever be on
stage but he was like Gathering it all
in and he was kind of the synthesizer of
it all Co okay and so by November of
2011 it was it was basically in the
shape it's in now and really the last
year and a half has been me getting
stage time I mean I had I'm not a
standup I've been doing storytelling
around La for 10 years which means 10
minutes of stage time every other month
right right pretty much that was it yeah
so I've been getting this kind of I've
been getting this amazing education
about being on stage so that's like my
personal fun with it now is the script
is pretty much set yeah and now I'm
learning how to actually live breathe
and eatting [ __ ] on stage right right
right you know I think typically if you
hear if you hear about somebody who's
maybe trying to tell the sort of story
you're you're doing they might do a lot
of research but it sounds more like
you're just you're telling the stories
you already know that must be what
people are connecting with completely it
is the Carlin family stories and and and
it starts off really the first half and
it's a it's two acts it's a 90-minute
show with an intermission and the First
Act is really kind of me up to age 12 so
it really is the family and it's my
shaping years and what my dad
experienced and and a good portion of
that is the stories that everyone wants
to kind of witness and feel and hear
about our family during those times it
was the straight 60s
the crazy 70s basically and um and then
the second half of the show is is I'm
always playing videos of his and his
videos are kind of bouncing off our life
together or my life at the time so
sometimes they're direct
chronological you know kind of comment
about what's going on interesting and
sometimes it's more of a
thematic thing coming in you know either
in contrast and conflict with what I'm
trying to deal with at the of my life
with or it's supporting it in some way
so we kind of play with the video in all
different ways that's incredibly cool
yeah it's fun that's uh did you uh if
you don't mind I I wanted to talk to you
but we always talk about people about
their first comedy influences but you
grow up in a comedy house I mean I think
that that that that question is answered
immediately perhaps but yeah it well it
it pretty much is I mean in some ways
mhm um I mean the very first time I saw
my dad on TV I was a somewhere between 2
or 3 years old and my mom was very
excited Daddy was on TV and she got me
all situated in front of the television
set now of course this is 1966 most
likely so your TV was a piece of
furniture in your enormous count console
thing as you all remember I don't know
if you do you're a little young but um
uh and I guess
uh I have no memory of this but I guess
what happened was Dad came on you know
introducing George Carlin and my dad
came out on stage I don't know if it was
at Sullivan or what it was and I
proceeded to scream and cry where's my
daddy where's my daddy and run out of
the room
no yeah I can imagine that' be traumatic
because yeah suddenly my dad was about
you know 4 in tall and stuck inside of a
box oh my God the only person he scared
that night that's pretty much pleasure
to the country and then holy cow so I
mean was it that's so weird from then on
I mean it must have been a a lot more of
getting having to get used to that kind
of thing but yeah I mean I do remember
being a little older and and knowing
he'd be on that night I remember him
being on the delar ree show one night
which is a long time ago and and and
starting to feel the pride and
understanding that my dad did something
special yeah and then but that really
started cementing in more when I was
like 7 8 n years old I tell this story
in my show of the summer of 72 getting
to go on tour with my dad my mom and I
went on tour with him and it was Kent
State Summerfest Carnegie Hall those
were like three of the highlights we
went to lots of other places but that's
when it really became clear to me that
my dad was a God to people it was
1972 you know and um and that's when it
hit me
that that he was something special and
and of course he always made me laugh I
mean you know um but there were awkward
moments too you know being a little girl
in an audience the only little girl in
the audience when your daddy says the
word [ __ ] on
stage at a certain at first I was
unconscious of how probably
uncomfortable that made other people
feel right and then when I got to the
age where I was realizing oh H I bet you
people are uncomfortable about this
right now so that I think somewhere
inside of me I was like oh I've got to
act like it's really okay right I'm
really cool with this you know when I'm
realizing maybe I'm not supposed to be
so cool with this right who knows but uh
but yeah I mean so so certainly dad was
an but for me it was you know TV I was a
TV kid I up in front of the TV so uh
Lily Tomlin for me was the first person
that I S I guess Lucy mhm um Lucille
Ball but Lily tommen was the first one
who was doing stuff that was like oh I
want to do that yeah I mean she was
playing a little girl right on TV you
know and it was like all the little all
the funny little girls in the country
could do that character sure sure yeah
of
course so good so I think my my first
you know besides Ethel Merman I think
probably Edith am was my first
impression so good that's amazing do you
um were you again we you don't have to
be I hate I don't I want I don't want
people to feel like they have to have
been Comedy album buyers but was it a
thing in the house to to buy a lot of
comedy albums or no my dad was really
into music my dad was a big big music
person he had an incredible music vinyl
collection that he was colle he
collected during that time and that he
told me were was going to be my
collection someday and it is mine now
it's at my house so I have the' 60s 7s
and I have Al his Jazz records too um
and I know there's comedy albums in
there he didn't play me a lot of comedy
albums he played three things that were
really really important to my education
mhm Lord Buckley yes of course the
2,000-year old man of course and uh Ruth
Draper wow yeah those were the three
things that he wanted to make sure that
I got an education on he probably felt
that the rest of it the culture would
take care of sure um and I mean and I
REM remember some Bob newart some
Cosby but I don't know if that was later
I heard that earlier stuff you know but
we as a family certainly watched you
know if people like that came onh we
were watching them on TV um uh but you
know uh Mary Tyler Mor show was an educa
you know sure love that laugh in uh Bob
newart show of course and uh and the K
berett show I mean k berett for me was
another of course huge hero huge hero of
mine and uh and watching my dad be able
to Cry tears of joy when Tim Conway and
Harvey Corman would be going at it in a
sketch toe to- toe yeah you know you
knew something was going on because it
was making my
dad laugh in a way that you know only
true comedy can can make you laugh you
know that real spontaneous love of the
moment and appreciation of it yeah yeah
was it a thing was it only sharing or
was it did he ever intellectualize it
with you or for you never
intellectualized it never ever never had
those discussions did he have that
interest that you know of was he I mean
was he picking it apart
ah boy you know I don't know being a kid
I really don't know that sure he if he
did he was doing it on his own or maybe
with friends but I don't know if he was
picking it apart I know he was he was
definitely a student I mean certainly as
a
child um Spike Jones and Danny Kay were
the two big influences on him um and but
no picking intellectualizing analyzing
it no it wasn't that wasn't part of the
game it was just a spontaneous enjoyment
of the art yeah definitely did you ever
find yourself at some
point doing it yourself and sort of
realizing you grew up in an environment
that allowed you to examine it better no
no not at all no I was uh an
unconscious uh kid I mean you
know it our house was there was some
years in our household which were very
very chaotic so for a lot of years it
was survival time there wasn't a lot of
time to be um even thinking about any of
that kind of stuff I knew for me
that and I was just writing about this
the other day there's something about
that place that Carol Brett or Lily
Tomlin or Lucille Ball would take me
there's that expanded feeling when
you're having enjoying a moment of
comedy and I knew I wanted to give that
to other people sure that's all I knew
about it that was as much as I knew that
I wanted to be a part of that that
magical expanded feeling however that is
or or that expanded feeling that I knew
my dad was creating in a in a live
audience
situation um as a teenager then for me
you know I was in high school 78 through
81 so Saturday Night Live was Valhalla I
mean it was Saturday night you you'd
gotten your money together so you could
get enough weed for the
weekend and hog and DA's ice cream had
just been introduced into America [ __ ]
oh no it was bong hits hog and Daws and
SNL man I mean you know and it was it
was it was the original cast of SNL it
was it was they were everything and then
there was Monty Python on
PBS and that was it those two things
were everything and affected I hung out
with some very funny people in high
school so all of our humor was
completely filtered through that it
wasn't standup it was sketch comedy and
one of our dads had one of the first
beta cams in LA and we took it for a
month and shot sketches every weekend of
just bad bad but fantastic sketch comedy
that we just would literally right in
five minutes like okay let's go do it
right now so good get our costumes and
whatever you know and um
and I wish it had survived I really do
it was all on VHS or something but that
was and for me like that's what I
thought if I was going to go anywhere
that's what I thought I would go towards
yeah do you do you remember the first
thing that you do you remember writing
like when you first decided writing was
something important to you or um you
know it was I was one of those people
that got caught up in
my confusion of my life in my 20s and
didn't have a lot of time to develop at
all anything except for survival okay uh
at age 18 I met a man who was 11 years
older than me and we did a lot of
cocaine oo wow wow so my although I was
interested
in I'm wanting to pursue and I did a
little bit wanting to pursue some acting
I didn't realize that I had no concept
of myself I had no idea of who I was
didn't realize that I probably should
have been at the Groundlings probably
should have been auditioning for SNL and
going that character comedic actress
route because that's really what I who I
wanted and what I wanted to do instead I
was in a very bad relationship and and
in [ __ ] up part of life yeah my dad
did which I show in my show my dad did a
pilot for HBO in 1984 called apartment
2C okay and I have a copy of it holy
[ __ ]
and I said to him I want to be in it and
he and his writers wrote me a part as a
Punk Rock Girl Scout who comes to his
door to sell him cookies oh my God and I
show the scene in my one in my solo show
and when I went to look at it to put it
into the show and I'm watching the
footage and I'm
thinking God I had I had no training at
all and I had I had really good good
comedy instincts yeah and a friend of
mine and I'm not name dropping or
anything but it means something to me my
friend Lorraine Newman who's now a good
friend of mine saw that and said to me
why the [ __ ] weren't you doing this work
right you could have been in the cast
like right then and there and I and it's
like I didn't I had no concept of myself
at that age of course what happened at
that age was is I did that thing and it
sparked something in me but because I
had no real training and because I was
George Carlin's daughter which I felt
like I didn't never wanted to be put in
a situation where there was nepotism or
anything like that I didn't feel like I
had earned my my my stripes and so I was
still knowing that I wanted to do that
and everything but didn't quite had no
concept of it at that point either and
it took me a couple of more years to
kind of get my way out of the marriage
and all that kind of stuff and I ended
up going actually back to UCLA and
getting my Bachelor's degree um but I
look back on it now and I it really has
been happening to me lately because
about 3 months ago Second City there's a
show at Second City called
TMI um and they invited me to come and
do sketch comedy with them and they do
their show and I had a blast doing it I
bet and it was like 30 years later why
am I doing this now but um yeah you know
would have could have should have
right I'm doing it now what can I say of
course yeah um
did you I mean uh as far as developing
uh a writing voice uh did you ever have
I don't know did you ever have any kind
of conflict like you said being quote
unquote George Carlin's daughter did you
have any conflicts as a writer yeah it
you know the big Shadow thing was always
there it was tough um when I I met my my
husband that I my husband that I have
now my one and only husband no my my
second husband but really the the love
of my life Bob Mcall he and I started
writing in the early '90s uh started
writing sitcom spec scripts and that was
like enough outside of my dad's purview
that it felt safe to do that okay so we
wrote a bunch of spec scripts we ended
up writing a b movie that actually got
made it's Rose mwan is in it it's called
devil in the flesh oh yes of course and
we wrote it as a total tongue and cheek
comedy but you know it's be movie
Thriller we would like wake up in the
morning say how are we going to kill the
grandmother
I don't know how should we kill her
today we had a blast riding it um but
you know it was the The Shadow thing was
always big with me and um it's always
been hard for me kind of the official
Hollywood thing it was always terrifying
for me I never knew where I could fit
into
that um had a lot of issues around it
and then when my dad did his fox show
the George Carlin show Bob and I pitched
him uh pitched him an idea for a show
for an episode and he loved it and ended
up pitching it to Sam Simon and who was
running the show at the time we weren't
allowed to pitch it to Sam Sam did
wouldn't even allow me barely allowed me
onto the onto Warner Brothers he he
didn't like he's got a thing about
nepotism he really okay he you know he's
he's an interesting guy I'm leaving it
at that and bless his heart he's I know
he's dealing with serious health issues
right now um
but so we pitch it to my dad my dad
loved it and my dad pitched to Sam and
Sam loved it and my dad said oh Bob and
Kelly happened to pitch it to me yeah we
want them to write it so we ended up
writing an episode and having a blast
with that and everything like that and
we you know it's so funny how [ __ ] goes
down we ended up getting invited at the
time I mean this is like 95 I guess it
was at the Time Warner Brothers had this
amazing sitcom writing program yeah and
we got invited
to go and interview for it awesome which
was awesome right and but see I'm George
Carlin's
daughter and the thing about being
George Carlin's daughter is [ __ ] the man
right right and basically in my eyes
sitcoms and Warner Brothers were the man
right never mind that you know you get
on a staff somewhere and you write one
or two scripts of season and you're in
the room and you get great health
insurance and you're getting paid about
25 Grand
episode and you're in the club yeah and
that yes eventually you can go on maybe
to write a feature whatever you want mhm
I I didn't think about any of those
steps I just thought of the [ __ ] this
boy club [ __ ] the man [ __ ] sitcoms [ __ ]
this [ __ ] [ __ ] town I'm a real
[ __ ] artist right and I didn't
exactly say that word for word in my
interview but I'm sure the subtext of it
was there uh-huh uh-huh because um we
didn't get invited
in oh my God even though we had you know
a great Matt about you spec script we
had a great Seinfeld and we already
written an episode for a Warner Brothers
show right right yeah so um I did that
yeah and I've been apologizing to my
husband ever since right right we're
still married still loves that's good
and he gets it he gets it um but yeah
there's something about being a Carlin
and wanting to do it on your own terms I
guess and you know my dad he he was a
very lucky man you know he he had
moments like that in his own career
where he I mean he tells great stories
about when he was going through the
change going sounds like he having
menopause my first he's going through
the change you know um he had been
booked like a Playboy club or something
like that real straight place and he is
already done with these places he's got
the contract and he's got to do it and
he goes on and they're making him go on
because if he doesn't go on he doesn't
get paid
and and he'd already been fired from
Vegas I think at this point and um I
guess at one night he just laid
underneath the piano and read like the
little thing like I guess a little tag
just read that to the audience for a
while you know so I guess that was kind
of my phase of that you know I just was
like [ __ ] you [ __ ] you Hollywood [ __ ]
you
mainstream I'm a I'm a Carlin and even
though I don't I have I have no right to
be doing this because I have no nothing
to stand on because I have no work in
the world but I'm going to reject
you I I just love that that story
doesn't end the way you expect if only
because at his hardest in that scene
he's a child so childlike that is the
most brilliantly completely he's doing
performance art actually you know is
what he's actually yeah and that's
what's so beautiful and I and I and I
don't again I don't want to turn this
into a whole let's examine of his work
but obviously you're doing a show about
him and so his work is going to come
into it so I've always had questions
yeah that I you know which I probably
can't answer it's okay ask them but uh
but you're going to have a perspective
on it yeah uh uh the the change that
you're talking about
specifically where suddenly the hair is
tied back suddenly he's in all black
right suddenly he's reflecting something
he's never been before he goes for I'm
talking about your [ __ ] versus your
stuff too real really laying in oh
you're talking about that change that's
the CH that's the change that I I was
talking about the straight man the
counterculture George of course right
but that you're talking about the second
of course Counter Culture Georgia is the
one that I think I first and I related
to cuz I'm what I was in high school
when I first started listening to stuff
and absolutely beard and long hair yeah
you're talking about the change that's
the change that always sort of like hit
me so hard because as a as a kid I'm
growing up with class clown that's the
one my parents gave to me so that I
listen to it over and over again right
you know memorize seven words you know
all that good [ __ ] okay so I've always
been curious about and it's my own
ignorance for not going on Wikipedia but
I'd rather get it from you yes you know
what did you see that brings about that
sort of yeah that's a very [ __ ] the man
oh absolutely absolutely you know what I
mean even though some people The
Simpsons even gave him [ __ ] about it but
you know like it's still very well no I
mean you know I think basically in um in
1987 he turned 50 mhm when you turn 50
things happen in your life right you
really do see there's definitely less
time yeah ahead of me than there is
before me and his mother had
died uh a few years before that his
mother was a huge shadow in his life I
mean literally the day she died when we
came home from the funeral he was a
different he was a changed man W there
was a burden lifted off of him yeah um
and I think uh it was the end of the80s
yeah we had just been brutalized by
Ronald Reagan for eight years it was a
very difficult time to feel like a
freeth thinker in this country of course
and um and the [ __ ] was was just
front center for the country to see you
know there was no more hiding it you
know there was no more dancing around it
um you know
it I mean it's just exponential nowadays
but uh you know with the Iran Contra and
all that stuff it just all started
unraveling basically and and I think for
Dad between all of that that cultural
stuff his own personal turning
50 um and and he talked about in
particular Watching Sam Kennison yeah
screaming at the
audience and thinking why is he
screaming scaming because you have to
scream nowadays to get through to people
right because there's that much noise
mhm and um he had just you know he was a
man and I so get this because I so have
this inside of me I I'm constantly
wanting to evolve myself sure constantly
what's the next Horizon that I'm I want
to move towards the minute I get
somewhere it's okay this is great now
what yeah yeah and that's who he was too
lucky for us he was always finding his
next personal Edge and he just started
doing material that was just so much
more on the- nose
commentary directly you know about what
was going on and not feeling any need to
take care of the audience anymore right
there was something about that he he was
learning that and probably also I'm
guessing because he'd had enough decades
in this business and he knew he had he'd
already survived I mean like you know
and I talk about it in my show the late
70s early 80s he I play a clip of um
Rick Moranis from SCV doing an imitation
of my dad I've have not seen this clip
it's really great oh my God and it's he
does this thing on beets the vegetable
beets and he's like beats beats beats
beats you know and it's like the
ultimate you know in at your Naval kind
of observational humor and it's and it
and it I think it my dad was in some
ways very thin skinned and I think it
like kind of like destroyed him in some
ways like oh [ __ ] and the way I talk
about it in my show is it's like you
know he he was the straight guy was a
successful straight comic and then he
was the counterculture God he and prior
went out and changed the world and set
the stage for all these other comics and
um and then he he somewhat became an
institution mhm and he became in some
ways part of the establishment for these
young guys coming up and SCV and SNL
were just different creatures to him he
didn't he didn't he loved it but he
didn't get it you know it wasn't his
thing it wasn't his generation and I
think he realized oh I'm I need to
figure out who I am again so he that's
when he started to and that's when the
stuff stuff you know he started to kind
of build in that time and I think the
peak of that was the late 80
I think he talks about um the um what am
I doing a New Jersey show I think that
was the first one where he really came
out and had some things to say to the
audience and that we were all kind of
like o yeah wow this isn't going to be
cute and funny all the time you know
he's got there's a there's an edge here
there's an anger here and I think he was
really freed by that I think he really
was really really freed by it and then
jamming in New York
which I believe is is except for modern
man that one piece I really believe that
whole show is such um a tour to force of
his voice which he ended up building on
for another however many years 15 years
um but man that is just it's pure
perfection that whole show yeah and and
I and he really I mean he said and I
think he even said it to John Stewart in
97 you know that after 30 years of
comedy he realized he'd found his
artistic voice he' really found it
finally and he knew who he was
completely and he didn't give a [ __ ]
right anymore what anyone thought about
him and of course he did because he's a
comic wants people to laugh but um he
freed himself of something there that's
insane yeah it's just so it sounds like
it shocked you just as much as it might
have the tyal I mean it shocked and it
energized me because I was
um I always loved when he spoke a truth
and it shattered something in the room
sure there's something about that that's
so thrilling and so I
mean I think it's growing up at the
times I did and of course him being my
dad and and witnessing the country and
the way it went but you know truth
tellers have always been important in my
life and to have my dad be one and
telling a truth that and telling it in a
way that's poetic and funny and and
worldview shattering all at the same
time [ __ ] man it's it's it's exciting to
be in the audience when it's happening
and it's exciting to know it's my dad
doing that and and it and it gives every
one of us who want to express that in
the world great hope that we have a
platform to do this too sure and that we
want to dedicate Our Lives to that yeah
do you
I it's easy for an audience member for
somebody who is especially who is a
standup who gets to do a new hour every
year or every couple years whatever it's
easy for me to demarcate someone's
Evolution yes um harder maybe impossible
if you're the person doing it maybe a
little less hard if if somebody who's
related to them who gets to see that uh
but for yourself do you do you do you
get the opportunity to take a step back
and actually are there demarcated points
where you can look at your own Evolution
as a writer oh God yes I mean I I'm
um I got my Master's in Yi and
psychology so like my evolution is like
all I ever think about I mean I'm a I'm
a Storyteller that talks about myself
I'm an autobiographical Storyteller so
I'm always trying to find the narrative
through line in my life story and I you
know doing this show I did another onew
woman show in 2000 which really was the
first time I sat down my mom died in '97
of liver cancer and that completely
changed my life sure and of course and
but that's when I really knew it's like
oh you can be hit by a bus any day like
[ __ ] or get off the pot Kelly like if
you want to be a writer performer then
[ __ ] go do it you know stop sitting
around going well when will someone tell
me that I'm okay and I'm
lovable um and so I spent about 2 years
and just really walked through my life
and and and looking at my own life now
looking back on it now in this fine year
oh my God I can't believe it's
2013 um I mean I really see that I was
always putting my toe in the water and
checking the temperature and going a
little further in and then getting
freaked out and getting out of the water
sure and and I was really I was a
frustrated artist I was someone who was
in my home writing a lot thinking about
a lot of things but terrified to go out
in the world with it MH um never wanted
to be a standup never ever saw that as
something my dad even said to me I don't
want you doing that really yeah which is
a little difficult to hear sure I mean I
made my dad laugh all the time so I knew
it wasn't that right but a part of me
thinks well maybe it was that but I get
that he knew it was a [ __ ] up life
it's a life on the road is tough he saw
what life on the road did to our family
and what he had to end and he had an
audience he had an audience when you
don't have an audience it's a whole
different Road and then on top of that
being someone like him's daughter you
know I'm sure he didn't want me going on
stage and some drunk [ __ ] going hey
bring the funny Carlin out right oh that
would have been a fun moment I would
have thought I'd come back for that
though maybe I would have um so I never
wanted to be a stand up but I knew I
wanted to be on a stage say
something to people and impacting people
yeah and and doing it in a way right um
and so I I did a lot of tow in the water
and then back again tow in the water
back again and um wrote this onew woman
show in 2000 sent it to sent the script
to my dad it was really about my mom's
death and I had this kind of real
Awakening like oh like this amazing
Awakening I mean I guess you could call
it a spiritual awakening but really like
a a s sense of who I am and what my what
I felt my purpose was and and really
this experience that I had around my
mother's death and the intensity of it
and then also growing up in this kind of
crazy household that I grew up in and
being able to it was called driven to
distraction okay and the thesis was
basically like you know so many things
distract us from who we really are until
the very thing you don't want to happen
comes in your life which is the death of
something or something big and then you
can no longer really distract yourself
from it right and then you realize oh I
need to really live my life that's kind
of was the thesis behind it so I sent
the script to my dad and
um you know I hadn't thought about this
then but now when I look back on it I
can really see you know when people talk
about my dad and prior I really see that
they each occupy two different
universes because although you think you
know my dad my dad never talked about
his life on stage right I mean early yes
okay Tippy was on in there and and I
believe I said the tippy did a number 10
52 whatever what all what is um you know
and he he pulled from his life but he
never talked about his wife he never
talked about his drug addiction he never
talked about any of that prior on the
other hand oh yeah oh yeah would be
living his life and six months later
he's on stage telling you what it's like
to be on fire running down his driveway
right right you know I'm more like prior
uhhuh so my show was like that that yeah
and so my dad read it and he was very
uncomfortable with it oh no very
uncomfortable I didn't say anything in
it that he hadn't fully admitted in
public a doing too much cocaine that
there was a lot of arguing in our house
there was nothing uh you know Earth
chattering going on but he felt I think
he felt a lot of guilt about those years
and it just made him uncomfortable and
he said so but he also said I would
never stop you you're an artist and you
have to do this you know and of course
being the beautiful only child that I
was I was like I canel my run and I
ended up only doing it three nights okay
so once again I put my toe in the water
temperature fell a little warm this time
I thought better get out because it's
making daddy
uncomfortable and and that's when I
ended up going to grad school and kind
of taking a whole different direction in
my life uh in 2001 and then I got out of
grad school and was an intern for 2
years and literally the people that
started coming into my room as clients
MH were right ERS and standup comedians
and actors of course of course yeah and
it was like oh I'm supporting these
people's dreams helping them get out of
their own way and yet I'm the one who
wants to be out there on stage again
right and that's when I said okay I've
got to I've got to I've got to I've got
to really go for this um and even during
that time I did a lot of Storytelling at
the time my dad came to see me once do
it and uh he said to me Well you
certainly know what you're doing doing
up there yeah like okay Dad said that
I'll take it I'll take it um and then I
started working on a memoir because I
knew that this crazy life story I had
this journey MH being a woman trying to
find my voice sure growing up in the
shadow of someone who had a voice all I
wanted to tell that story very much so
and it included my mother and father my
childhood and all that kind of stuff and
I told my dad I was working on a memoir
and he was like really
really you know and so I went and I put
it on a shelf and I really knew now that
was
2006 I knew I said okay you know what
I'll just figure out something else to
do until he's until he's gone yeah and
then when he's gone I'll go do my work
right and it's like a horrible thing to
say m and yet I didn't want to make him
uncomfortable I didn't want to step a
and
yet I look back on it now and I think
well would have that have stopped him
right you know did he did he care what
people he was making uncomfortable about
the things he was saying on stage ever
sure no not really um but you know it's
a different generation it's a different
I grew up differently than he did he's a
man I'm a woman he didn't have a shadow
like I you know there's all that other
stuff but
um you know so I feel like I kept
pulling myself back and hiding and and
going off and doing doing other work
that interested me and was important to
me and I think ultimately is serving me
in my life 100% but
um but you know it's like I you know but
but the weird thing is too is that I was
thinking about this driving up here
that before my dad died I didn't know a
single comedian personally interesting
that's interesting didn't hang out with
them yeah Dad didn't I mean I know dad
knew them and talked to them and had an
influ inced a lot of
them um and I knew he'd go into clubs
and he'd check out people and he was on
the road and I knew and he had phone
conversations and relationships with
young Comics coming up I didn't know any
of that until after he died by the way
because I was living my life and dad had
his life yeah um but I didn't know any
Comics wasn't even part of the comedy
world but that was Dad's life and yes I
had some sort of little halfway entree
into it but not not my world not my life
right never went to comedy clubs in fact
hate comedy clubs to this day I'll go
see my friends every once in a while
right but literally the day after my dad
died these comic started calling of
course and now and and really because of
Rick Overton and Paul provenza and
really provenza because he is this kind
of connoisseur of Comedy um I am now it
was so incredible that first year
between my dad's fans and the comics how
they embraced me mhm I would not have
survived without them and because of
that now I feel like I'm doing this work
and it's a whole different entree into
it you know I know I have to I know I
have to show up I have to have the goods
right I have to have my craft I have to
do the work but I get to have a
different conversation with them now and
I and I and I'm I'm really honored by
that conversation really really honored
that I get to be someone who
gets to meet his fans and and talk to
him and gets to to be with the comics
now on a different level you know that
you know they they I'm yeah I'm George's
daughter but he's not here hovering I
mean he is always hovering God help
us but he's not physically hovering
anymore you know I wouldn't show up
going hey you know whatever um you know
I feel like I've been embraced into the
bosom of of these comedy
you know ladies and gentlemen such a
Beau a bit to kind of wiggle your way in
there though you don't it's not enough
to be oh no anyone's daughter that's not
enough not in this [ __ ] not not with
comedians so that's I mean that's what's
impressive on its own I mean it has to
come somewhat you a minute ago you're
talking about the shadow but at the same
time a second later you're talking about
would he do this you obviously there's
obviously something about him that you
emulate is very important to you to live
up to yes
a standard a huge standard and a lot of
people maybe in your position
wouldn't the bitterness would maybe be
overtaking them you know what I mean and
to and to learn uh so much about
yourself uh especially creatively as a
result of just everything that you've
gone through and again still to appeal
to Comedians and impress them is you
know it's a big skill you know I think
the thing that my dad embodied and and
therefore I embodied and my mother it
too real I'm and and comics and everyone
who knew my mom uh would stand behind me
on this is we're an authentic family
we're just authentic people and I think
that in comedy that is everything yeah
it is I mean especially nowadays it's
it's all about being authentic sure and
um and I think
that
uh I think that serves me more more than
anything else in my craft learning my
writing craft is important learning to
be on stage has been is is is an
incredible experience I'm having right
now and and improving my writing all the
time um but being comfortable in my own
skin sure and really trusting myself and
knowing that I belong and I deserve to
be here just because of the fact that
I'm willing to try hard and to show up
and do the work um and that I have spent
a lot of [ __ ] years working on myself
of course I mean you know therapy up the
[ __ ]
yaoo
um and uh and so I you
know and it's but it's always a
balancing act too you know because you
it's the ego is such a little [ __ ] MH
because it'll start to believe the press
or believe what you know oh I'm part of
this group now and oh look who's in my
phone book and oh look who I hang out
with and oh look who I can just call and
look who texted me and this and my funny
thing is my dad was always um star
struck yeah and I'm always Star Struck
too so a part of me is always like oh my
God that's awesome that's so good though
but the other part of me's like Just
Breathe Kelly just [ __ ] breathe
they're just another person they [ __ ]
just like you
do and um and and don't and and you just
got to remember to kind of come back
into your own
skin say that we're all humans here
we're just being real and um none of
that Okie Okie energy I call it the Okie
energy do you I mean I'm finding at
least from talking to a lot of people on
this podcast I mean this is 62 some
episodes now uh I get the feeling and
this is just positive makes me happy
that the tears of the clown comedian is
slowly maybe going I mean if if a man
again it sounds like like you said it's
you had you're a real family he doesn't
sound like a man who tearing himself
apart constantly and just you know
filled with self-hate you know what I
mean that's such a thing people really
feel like they have to do that to be
that you you know to be funny yeah I
think he certainly you know he didn't
have a daddy mhm I think
he he had a you know his had some demons
in his family absolutely
um I I think he was a man who was very
driven sure extremely driven
perfectionistic uh and and over the
decades you know but also a man who had
Consciousness had the ability to finally
witness himself and evolve I mean that
is how one evolves is you you you start
to be able to see your own behavior in
an objective way so that you can change
it I mean that is I think the definition
of of evolution of Consciousness sure
and um so we had that great ability so
he was always working on himself but you
know
um yeah who doesn't [ __ ] have demons
who doesn't have Darkness but I think in
general I know at the end
he
um you know he he had found God we were
at the um the Paley Center in Beverly
Hills and they were doing a tribute to
him one night it was just a few months I
mean it was maybe like six weeks before
he died wow and I think you can even go
online and find it yeah it's incredible
there was maybe 150 it's a really small
theater at the Paley Center maybe 150
people in that little theater oh God and
he was I saw I saw in him that he got he
was an elder Statesman mhm that he was
the wise Shaman in the room mhm and that
he was comfortable with that and that he
was like this
philosophical guy and I saw peace in him
really did see peace in him and I know
that his personal life I know he loved
my mother dearly but they had a lot of
baggage in their relationship from all
those years I know that when he Met
Sally uh Wade and were together until he
died that he had a lot of joy in that
relationship and I know he was tired of
being on the road and traveling but he
was always hungry to do the next bit
right right he I I mean I have his
computer there's probably the makings
of two or three more HBO shows in there
in very raw raw form but there are files
and files and files of stuff that I
really haven't even looked at yet um I
mean I look at it every once in a while
and just get overwhelmed by it all and
think what am I supposed to do with all
of this my chest gets tight oh my god um
but I don't know
the you know I I I do really though
believe that people that comedians the
more I learn about comedy and I thank
Paul prenza for this because he's really
made me a student of Comedy getting to
watch people
um I look at what it's about and I
really see that people say to me you
know what's what's it like hanging out
on them like they are the
smartest and kindest for the most part
the smartest and the kindest people I
know yeah comedians yeah they're really
sensitive souls for the most part but
they're so [ __ ] smart they can't keep
their mouth shut about what's wrong on
the planet or in themselves because
they're always digging and figuring out
what's this mean what's this mean what's
this mean and and putting it out there
in such a way that um they're
questioning it so that we can question
it sure and and they're funny and
they're funny on top of all of that
because I think I do all that other
stuff I mean I call myself a thinker and
a communicator yeah and an instigator
but I'm not driven to like get the laugh
all the time yeah you know um but I get
that drive of like so there is something
about there's there's an unrest MH
there's a famous Martha Graham quote
that my dad sent to me probably 10 years
ago and it is that an artist is Never
Satisfied there's always an unrest in us
there's always the minute you do
something there's what's next yeah and
so that Darkness I think is absolutely
essential for a comedian for sure you
know um whether you have to like hate
yourself and be like killing yourself
with drugs and alcohol and and scary sex
all the time right I hope you don't have
to be doing that I don't think you don't
have I don't think you do no yeah I
don't think so um but you know there's
always that in every crowd for sure yeah
um I want to make sure that we we uh get
in uh that you can tell everybody more
about the show where they can find you
online oh yeah yeah yeah so the show is
called a Carlin Home Companion
and um of course it's Kelly car.com I
mean that that just that has my whole
universe in it um I'm actually uh doing
the show in two nights uh at the Acme
I'm doing it a lot at the Acme Comedy
theater in Hollywood that's my new home
uh in the
fall we just booked the theater I'm
going to New York City it's crazy I'm
doing and this is even crazier I'm doing
a theater called The Players Theater
it's on McDougall Street in the village
it's in the same building is Cafe W
uhhuh Cafe W is one of the places my
Daddy went to in the early 60s and did
hooton nannies holy cow with you know oh
Lenny Bruce and Jo bz people like that
so it's in the same building so I feel
like I will be an emotional [ __ ]
wreck uhhuh uhhuh uhhuh and I feel like
the Carlins uh the Carlins are coming
home that's awesome in October yeah so
so I'm very excited about that and then
the other thing that I do weekly that
I'm really proud of and actually where I
I really have helped me to discover my
voice is my is my podcast which I do
which is called waking from the American
dream which I completely took that title
from my dad's bit uh that great line he
says which is the reason they call it
the American dream is because you have
to be asleep to believe in it and when
he said that I went [ __ ] he did that
again that
poetry world view shattering [ __ ]
thing he
does um and came up with that title uh
you know years years before my like a
year after he did the show and then I
just wanted the title for something and
started doing a documentary and then and
then he went and died my whole life
[ __ ] changed of course and so now I
do have the podcast but I love the
podcast and um I have I found my voice
there I do it's really cool as I'm sure
you found yours here maybe I just sit
and listen to people talk and say yeah a
lot that's what I've discovered about
myself but you're in your bliss see
that's what podcasting is about being in
your [ __ ] Bliss oh absolutely no this
is the best thing that's and then other
people like have a similar Bliss kind of
Zone and they come to your podcast
they're like wow that's my Bliss too
yeah it's starting to seem that way so
yeah it's pretty cool um are you on
Twitter oh my God I'm a [ __ ] Twitter
[ __ ] Kelly Carlin and everyone makes
fun of me because the [ __ ] uncore
thing but I didn't know what Twitter was
I thought you had to have like a little
space between your two names because
that's the way you do it in the real
world I didn't know the Twitter verse
was a special Zone
I love Twitter I'm on there all the time
and uh I have way too many tweets um so
please come find me on Twitter and play
there that's really where I hang out
this has been amazing thank you so much
fun thank you for letting me talk and
your great question asker and I I'm a
rambler I'm very good at that I will
give you that you're great thank you so
much for doing this my pleasure this has
been a lot of fun everybody thank you
for listening and as usual have a good
thing
[Music]
comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom visit stolen
dress.com to listen to our other
podcasts read our blogs read our tweets
watch our videos and read our books
please subscribe on iTunes rate US
highly and write your reviews you can
follow us on facebook.com/ Comedy
onvinyl and Twitter at comedy on
viny over at the bottom of the pot
himing he got ripping mad his eyes were
Bing out he jumped up the
piano and loudly he did shout who threw
the overall in Mrs
Mor nobody spoke so he shouted