[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast I don't know what we're going to
call this but uh let's just get started
everybody Phil Proctor is here with me
Hi H yes I am welcome to comedy on vinyl
we don't have to look at the camera it's
just their uh camera yeah there's a
little camera Jer who do you think you
are big brother yes I thought that was
thought that was obvious I mean I'm
going out of my way to like you know
detail your career and uh I what I'm
trying to figure out what makes you you
call this a
career um Jeremy yes hi Jeremy gusin hi
frequent guest friend of the show
pleasure to be here as always Greg
Benson hello infrequent guest but a
guest nonetheless high frequency gu
exactly right that's absolutely true um
and and one of one one of the more deep
conversations we've had on the show so
thank you for you know coming back hey
my pleasure I'll try not to get too deep
today speak in a higher register yeah so
he yeah but you were willing for some
reason yeah to talk about every album
that that fire sign made or at least
we're going to talk about the first as
long as I can still remember them I
figured might be a good idea you know I
am I am working on my Memoirs and
working is is really the the operative
word there because it's it's uh I
collaborated with a guy named Brad
shriber I don't know if you know Brad
He's a comedy writer and an old old
friend of mine and uh he wrote the first
draft based on my ramblings like I'm
going to be doing with you guys today
and uh and then I got it back and I
looked at I said well this is funny but
it's not my voice so I have to I have to
make it my voice my voice well you know
and and also whichever voice you choose
to use of course there's spelling
mistakes you know and and and
misinterpretations of certain things
that I said and things happened so it's
it's a full-time job and I'm still
unfortunately or fortunately as a case
may be so busy in my professional life
and my personal life which I'm don't
talk that that I I'm finding it really
difficult to sit in front of the laptop
or put the laptop on my lap and you know
and get dive into it again but slowly
but surely slowly he turned into his own
you know and I'm figuring you know all
these people are coming out with their
Memoirs you know singers and actors and
all and and uh Jane Fawn for instance or
other people they say oh yeah it took me
10 years to write it and this and that
you so I don't feel so bad I figure
maybe next year it will come out in some
form or another probably by the time I
get it out it I'll be able to just send
it to your brain you know you can just
download it right into your cerebral
cortex you know or in my case maybe the
reptilian brain which is more suited to
the kind of life that I've LED you know
you're pretty good with you know
predicting future technology so I
wouldn't be surprised if that's if
that's not the the next thing I know uh
Peter Bergman and I when we were touring
uh were invited to connect with Marshall
mclen because he wanted to add more
comedy to his lectures and of course we
worshiped the man and his his genius and
foresight and one time uh he and oh and
and I only mentioned this because so
many of his predictions are still
manifesting you know uh but he invited
us to his uh to his office that's not
the word they use they Ed some English
word up in Canada at the University that
he was teaching at all of which I is is
in the distant future I have to to
Google it to give it it was Google
University up there and and his quarters
and we're in his his Chambers and he's
got a livery servant there white guy but
you know dressed with the with the the
uh the Tails and you know white gloves
and everything and he's serving us tea
Remains of the Day just straights of the
remains of servitude you know and or
colonialism and uh and then he he brings
out because it's Canada two Cuban cigars
or three Cuban cigars he gives Bergman
from a safe that he's got there wow and
and he gives his and he lights them up
and we're sitting there and talking and
then all of a sudden bang bang he
planted loads in holy [ __ ]
you have oh my God so that's my my fond
memory of of the Marshall who that who
passed away soon thereafter from smoking
Cuban cigars I guess and great loss he
put put the load on the on theong yeah
right but you know he's that's one of
the people that you wish was still
around going like see I told you so or
even like you ain't seen nothing yet you
know you
know but he's gone and son the deputy
Deputy mclen my Marshall son uh he is is
keeping his dad's Legacy Alive by or had
been by publishing stuff that he had
written comic stuff that he' written
anyway uh I I mention that only because
uh there are going obviously going to be
some kind of platforms I already believe
that the whole social media thing is is
a precursor of telepathy sure you know
and and and help now my Memoirs are a
lot about telepathy you knew I was going
to say that I did I can feel it because
I've had actually open that envelope
under your chair oh no it's the King of
Diamonds oh my God thank you and it's
got poop on it oh my God that was my
poop oh amazing trick how you pulled
that right out of your ass no out of my
ass so anyway uh telepathy plays a great
deal and Serendipity one could call it
uh in in in my history my personal
real history and some of that will come
out during this our rambling
conversations because it I'm going to be
telling you the way things really
happened uh that that led to the the
creation of the fire sign theater into
the albums into our our career together
uh so we can start as you suggested with
waiting for the electrician or someone
like him yeah because I know you've been
waiting for the Proctor or something
like him to come and talk to you about
this uh that title came from Peter
bergman's experience in uh Amsterdam
when he was uh with the fool a group
called The Fool which was artistic
performance and and creative uh uh
costumes and paintings and psychedelic
car paintings and uh that the Beatles
Affiliated themselves with at a certain
point they used to drive around in one
of their the Fool's psychedelically
painted limos Etc ET and Bergman was was
the story which I I can only kind of
remember like most most of what I'll be
talking about was that Bergman was up on
a rooftop getting high because he that's
how you did it now all I had to do was
get up on the roof and you were high
because you just breathe in the air and
who marijuana everywhere so he's up on
the rooftop getting high and suddenly
there is a
blackout in in in his area of the city
oh not in his brain oh no oh no no come
to that point no not that enormous
Bergman brain no no there were seldom
blackouts in that brain although I'll
tell you about a famous one that
happened when when I was present but
anyway there was a black out there and
so they were indeed waiting for the
electrician or someone like him to
restore power and that's where that
particular title was inspired uh uh to
to to to be created uh my connection
would you like to hear how I became a
member of the fire sign theater that'd
be nice I anyone is interested okay than
thank you
for I was I was pursuing the a career as
an actor in New York uh having graduated
from Yale in the class of
1962 uh with a ba in drama and a BS in
life and for those of you who don't know
Yale is a university in New Jersey
University the way no new something it's
in new oh that's right that's right it's
con hav
I was thinking of the other people from
Yale are very well connected to yes they
are and I was also in you know secret
society secret society uh one which I
can mention unlike Skull and Bones if
you mention that I have to leave the
room know no I was in scrolling key
which is the Bohemian Society second
oldest society and Austin Pendleton was
in that Society that's one of the
reasons I got in and and Bob grman who
did the airbrush you know uh album cover
for don't crush that dwarf hand me the
pliers go got right there and he was
Peter's roommate at Yale Peter was a
class of 61 when I was at Yale and
working in the dramat acting the dramat
we had Sam Waton uh uh uh Peter hunt
Richard Maly Jr uh skip hennen uh Frank
jasi some of these names Tom Lian uh uh
pet I said Peter hunt uh who who
directed uh just a minute who directed
uh Saturday Night Fever De John batam
John batam and and all these incredibly
talented people and Peter Bergman and
and Austin Pendleton and uh and we were
just the hottest thing on campus Because
the drama school was was kind of full of
the Old Guard uh the the the teachers
and the the head of the uh a guy named
Canon I think was the head of the school
at the time School of drama I remember
he came up to me after a show that that
I was in there and said Phil you got a
real bomb here a real bomb and because
in the old theatrical vernacular met hit
but in the newent oh it stinks and I
went like oh this you know something's
got to give right and and it did Connie
Welsh was a teacher and the way that
they taught acting there to people like
uh uh Dan travante and uh Joan vanar
whom I I all got to work with and a
bunch of other right before Merill
Streep showed up by the way uh but there
were a lot of oh and John gu was in the
school that's how I got to do Musa
that's another story that the mar
perform I mean it was great talent great
wonderful people but uh Connie Welsh
would would get these these kids from
the Midwest uh like etop pin's daughter
who was also there at the time and would
basically strip them down now I don't
want you to think about about ETO pin's
daughter being stripped down because she
was a big girl and it wouldn't it would
not be it's not a good image to start
this discussion with but anyway she
would basically uh try to reduce
everything to a technique that would be
taught to all vocal technique physical
technique you know uh uh acting
technique and it was all technique
technique technique and and the way that
our generation what our generation
brought to it was you know [ __ ]
technique you know it's me you know here
I am I'm going to do my thing I'm
naturally talented I want to learn you I
want to experience as much as I can
learn from others and do it and do it
and do it and so and that's what
happened right afterwards that that
whole older way of working went went
away but not to say I didn't she had
some wonderful exercises and and I
learned a lot you know from from her and
from the class uh but it was still a
very oldfashioned way of approaching the
the theater and it didn't it had very
little to do with personality with what
you brought to the table they they kind
of frowned upon that uh when I went to
Dennis and some summer theater during my
years at Yale and spent a summer in rep
there with people like John shuck and uh
and visiting actors stars coming in to
play with us we did a rep a reparatory
season so You' do a you'd be doing a
play learn a play doing a musical and
learning another Musical and it was
great training at the end of that John
John Davidson was there also who became
a great pop star he a very handsome
young man with a great voice was before
he went on that's incredible he
ter there's a new show now on the on the
uh uh the Food Channel called that's
inedible have you seen that yet all
right anyways believable it's also
unwatchable but but I digest all
right uh so I at that time uh working
with all these these people uh it felt
like a little microcosm of what the the
real world was and uh uh and I worked
with Peter Bergman on two musicals that
Aus Pendleton wrote Tom Jones where I
played the lead character and Tom Tom
Jones The Musical Tom Jones The Musical
was they're allowed speaking directly
out before the movie wow really wow and
it was brilliant it was wonderful I bet
it was just like Hamilton like yes it
was it was like Hamilton except there
probably weren't any U uh uh well anyway
it was it was true to the story of Tom
Jones but it was like Hamilton and and
it was directed by Bill Francisco
brilliant director a and uh and a great
experience big big hit and then it was
followed up by Booth is back in town
which is a musical about the booth
family that Austin Pendleton wrote and
Bergman wrote the lyrics for both yeah
awesome so that that was my first
collaboration with Peter uh all right so
I uh read for a soap opera in my senior
year oh I got I got an agent from the
stuff that I did Lucy croll agency
and big agency and I was sent out to
read for a soap opera Edge Of Night the
part of a juvenile delinquent named
Julie Curts all the boys in the soap
opera in had female names and all the
girls had strong masculine names cookie
Pollock was my girlfriend so Julie CTS
was a juvenile delinquent and cookie
Pollock was my girlfriend she was a
knockout too uh anyway uh I I I I read
for this thing and they just introduced
the television camera and taping you
know to it to it so I read for a camera
and uh and I I had some time to kill
before I got on the train to go back up
to New Haven and they were building the
PanAm building on top of Grand Central
Station so I stood there on Park Avenue
or Fifth Avenue whatever p park I think
it was and watched this thing for a
little half an hour and I I I started to
walk back to the train through the
station and I hear will Philip proor
please report to the station Master's
office and I stopped you know and people
are all walking around me and nobody's
responding so it must be me well Philip
I repeated it so I went to the
information booth I said I'm Philip
Proctor where's the station Master's
office and she said over there so I go
over and there's there was open area
with all these conductors sitting with
telephones and desks and he says to me
your agent wants you to
call I went that doesn't wow is this a
somebody filming this so so I went to
the pay phone that's that was a little
booth where you put you know a dime in
the I pay for my phone I don't mean like
they're not they're not no I'm paying
every month for mine but anyway and and
and it's my agent she says you got the
part [ __ ] and you start next week
$365 a show and blah blah blah blah blah
and I went holy crap I'm I'm on a soap
opera I got a soap opera uh which I did
and uh and so the next thing I did was I
went out and bought contact lenses
because I I wore glasses at the time and
uh I wanted to be able to read the
teleprompters because you know you have
to learn all these lines H and I've
never done anything like this before so
that was my first big break and I did
that for a while uh and how long did
that go on for me it was about a year it
was it was I remember the the head
writer came up to me one day and say
Phil we got a storyline for you you know
cuz they were developing the character I
said great he said you're going to be
murdered what am I going to tell my
mother something like job security in
this business but don't worry you'll
come back in flashbacks during that
trial right I was a Revenant right I was
the Revenant the ghost that comes back
after he dies uh great movie by the way
so uh so anyway I had that experience
but and and then I got cast in a show uh
portrait of the Artist as a Young Man
and the barroom B monks two short plays
at the martinque theater where I met the
producer John Randolph who became one of
my greatest friends the god The
Godfather of my daughter Kristen and a
lifelong friend uh and John was one like
Dalton Trumbo was part of The Blacklist
he one of the the actors who was
blacklisted during that ridiculous
horrible period in Hollywood and uh and
he was in an avowed communist you know
and socialist uh and and he uh had a
wonderful s return to the business just
like Trumbo did and ended up starring
with Jack Nicholson in PR's honor and
he's a very recognizable character actor
if you he was in he played in seconds
also uh he was the the before guy and
second but anyway if you if you Google
John Randolph not his real name you'll
see you'll see his face you go oh that's
John Randolph so and he was honored by
the city as he major I me this city for
his work in the theater and anyway so he
he was a a mentor for me and uh and then
after that I got a show a musical called
the Amorous flea
uh what does this have to do with the
fires side there you may be say well
you'll find out so the Amorous flea was
at the York Playhouse I was working with
amelda de Martin and uh uh uh Lou Parker
who was an exod villian great funny
funny man and later Frank Parker who was
one of the teners on the Arthur Godfrey
show oh my God and seal cabitt who is
Carl ballentine's wife the great comic
magician Carl Balentine and who else did
I work with there uh Jack Fletcher a
very funny you know kind of a gay
comedian uh and they played this the
wicked servants and Lou Parker was the
old man it was a musical based on moer
school for wives and it really worked we
we just sold out we terrific run all
kinds of great reviews and uh both
amelda and I won promising personality
award Awards theater World Awards and we
were presented our theater World awards
at a at a party in Greenwich Village
Bloom was the guy's name who started all
this and there are books you you've seen
them haven't you no maybe not theat the
theater world uh every year there was a
book published by this guy of all of the
plays of that season Bradway up and then
all the awards and blah blah blah and my
award was presented to me by Paul
Newman who was looks much bigger on the
screen I have to say uh and Paul Newman
for those of you who don't know he's the
guy who makes the popcorn you like so
much and salsa delicious salsa and salad
dressing alfredy Newman's Uncle
exactly star of cool what me worry yes
anyway and I used to my first one of my
first girlfriends I mean you know
serious hooking up girlfriend was a girl
named Nadia leer
she was Russian her uncle was Don kosak
who who created the Don kosak choir the
Soviet Army chorus records and
everything which I I learned Russian
from partly and uh her uh house her
third floor walk up in the Greenwich
Village overlooked a courtyard where
Paul Newman and Joanne Woodward his wife
used to lived and they used to uh drink
beer
out on and smoke out on their patio and
we could look down and see them there
small world it ends up that he presents
me with this award great all right so
but here now here we go they decided to
take the show to Los Angeles MH and they
booked the Las palas Theater which is
off of Sunset Boulevard just below
mitchelli's uh and across from muso
Frank near muso Franks and when I was
there I stayed at the moneto
which is still there it's a hotel
residence for visiting actors came out
to do television shows and movies and
stuff and we had you know a a kitchen
apartment and every I had a kitchen
apartment and everything uh CU I didn't
know how to drive when I came out I grew
up in Goan Indiana on a bike and at the
time that I then started going to camp
blackpoint in the aderan deex which is
connected with Alan Stevenson School
where I went to school and and learned a
lot of music and the violin and
everything was in the orchestra and all
that uh uh anyway that that about the
time that I started going there and not
to Goan for the summer everybody learned
how to drive my my best friend Dayton
Dallas became a stock car driver wow
okay and when I got out there again I
went out to the to the uh Goan whatever
it was and watched him race and
everything in insane but I I did not own
it and I grew up in New York you don't
have to drive in New York no I got my
got my dri was born and raised in
Manhattan I got my driver's license the
day before I left for college and if I
didn't pass I probably would never have
gotten it yeah yeah I I didn't uh I
finally realized when uh uh well I
finally realized that I you if you move
the letters of Los of Los Angeles around
it spells legs on
sale okay and you've got to have a car I
tried to walk once from uh where I was
in Hollywood I got an apartment on Vista
delmare View of the sea mhm no
no view of the smog me I had a little
apartment there walking distance to the
theater Las palas theater and uh I used
to have breakfast I had flannel cakes
had muso Franks in the morning you know
and I had a great little routine but I I
once I tried to meet a friend on the
Sunset Strip and I tried to walk there
and there the I walk and then there's no
sidewalks you know and and and there's
nothing but like exhaust in and I was
exhausted before I I got there and I
said okay I guess I got to learn to
drive jeez Phil you you should have just
used your smartphone to call an
Uber you weren't thinking no I clear I
wasn't thinking futuristically enough
these are the days this isn't the days
by the way of real smog I feel like we
should real SM whatever we got now no
[ __ ] stuff yes they say in the 70s it
was the worst in Los Angeles right and
that's when I was I was in the late in
the mid 60s so it was it was bad but
anyway uh I took driving lessons I
learned how to drive and and uh and I
got an apartment up on Beachwood Drive
overlooking the entire city and I could
see the sea and I was settling in for a
great run and oh boy I'm a California
boy now in Los Angeles and I think I I
may have even done some television shows
or something and uh no I didn't I hadn't
done TV shows at that time and and the
phone rings and it's my agent and I had
gotten another part in a musical called
a time for singing which I auditioned
for months before uh apparently out of
500 people who'd read for my role they
were stupid enough to cast me and it's
it's a wonderful musical based on the uh
beautiful novel and the film how green
was my valley oh okay which if you
remember is a a story about a Welsh
mining disaster that wipes out an entire
family yeah which would make a great
music so I should have known but
Alexander con is producing you know my
first Broadway show uh no it wasn't my
first Broadway show uh I had I had
understudied in a time for singing uh
after that's right that was between
between uh uh a race of Harry not a race
of har that was between uh portrait the
artist and the the music Musical that
got me out to LA I I had understudied
Ralph the singing
Nazi and that and that show had gotten
me uh all kinds of of national tours and
everything because Richard Rogers
directed us W directed everybody who
went into that show and so I got to work
with Richard Rogers and then I was cast
and as an underst study I was in the
show I was one of the the guests at the
uh at the big ball in their house
and I was a Nazi Soldier and you know
the typical Austrian German you know
casting and and and I was paired with
Richard Rogers mistress who was a
formidable blonde tall wellb built uh
gorgeous and nutty as a fruit
cake she was a schizophrenic in those
days they call her schizophrenic
multiple personalities Godly knows uh
but but I I would be at living with her
uh in the background while the little
scene is going on before the kids start
singing so long good
night and we come in to saying good
night good night good night and but
before then we're we're with our
champagne glasses chatting in the
background all Gussy up and some night
she was perfectly normal and we'd have a
nice conversation and other nights she
would would be talking to her
Angels yeah and and and would just nod
and look at me and great listen to her
angels and then maybe share something
that one of the Angels had told her you
know uh but I was in a Broadway show you
know and and hanging and it was it was
great and that's uh and that's another
story because that's where I met Henry
jagam because we all used to hang out at
a place called dowy which was just up
from Broadway H and Shelley Winters was
there and Chris Jones and oh God I I all
of the many of the young stars from
Broadway uh were hanging out there after
the shows and you know letting off steam
and Henry jagam and I became bonded uh
and at that time I was also dating Karen
Black and I introduced Karen to Henry
which and Henry immediately boom that
was it I said well good night you
know Henry and Karen right locked brains
and we're go you know we're getting into
and was because of of of uh Henry that
Karen was brought out to Los Angeles and
had a career in the movies because he
helped her get started and he cast me he
had cast me in a play that he was
writing at the actor's Workshop uh
actor's studio writer Workshop called
the snowball tree which comes from the
Russian songen Ken Kena which is my
snowball tree my snowball tree my
snowball tree my tree which other people
might know is the Tet theme is is it is
it is it really yes it is that now makes
perfect sense you go awesome the technis
theme I never who would have thought it
infected that game the tetnus theme is
slightly different it's a virus isn't it
okay so so anyway and and I did that
with Karen Karen Black and Bonnie badila
and Richard PRI and Charlie deerock and
yeah yeah who hasn't heard of Charlie
dear character actor with a funny little
face great guy uh and and uh uh and
after that he got he Henry ended up in
Hollywood and he worked as an editor on
easy Ridder now easy ryer is going to
come up in a minute and you'll see why
how do we get to the Fireside theater
keep listening right so so Henry is out
there with with Bob ravelson and Bert
Snider uh the BBS Productions and uh and
and they were the guys the bankrolled
easy writer and a couple of other really
great great movies and they uh uh bankr
Henry's first movie a safe place and I
got to to screen test with Candace
Bergen and oh God all these hot chicks
but he finally got Tuesday Weld to do
the part cuz he'd written it
about so so I co-starred I was intro and
introducing uh I co-starred with with
Tuesday W and Orson Wells and the late
and beautiful Gwen Wells and Jack
Nicholson in Henry's first movie a safe
place so a lot of seist people is what
you're really getting yeah you see them
all the
time not enough but yes oh yes so so uh
uh where did all this happen in in the
chronology right now uh uh I'm I'm in uh
La doing the musical and I'm called back
to New York to do uh time for singing
and so I had to give up all of my my my
future life my beautiful little life
that I created for myself in legs on
sale and go back to why no work all
right so I'm in New York and uh uh and I
do the musical which goes out of town
and what's his name gar Champion came in
as a as a as a doc script doctor and
worked with us later I worked with his
wife in Musa at the Mark Taper
uh along with Sher North and uh uh and
one of uh one of Fred of stairs dancing
partners Chase what was her first name
Ginger Ginger Chase terrif let's say
ginger Chase right and I got to meet
Fred is stair who also is a tiny little
man you know oh yeah oh what a thrill to
meet him came backstage to meet me Barry
Barry Chase Barry CH I think it was uh
but she wasn't Berry chased I'll tell
you that uh so anyway uh so so this is
the jumble of my life uh but but at the
time I'm in this play and it closes it
it because it opened to mixed reviews
but good reviews and it was a beautiful
musical with wonderful wonderful music
and uh George Hearn was one of the
actors in it who went on to great great
Fame and success and and it opened and
then there was a newspaper strike so had
you know lines around the block during
the previews and once we opened there
was no way to advertise it didn't have
the you know the the kind of advertising
reach in the 60s that they've got now or
public media or anything so we had a
very short run and closed uh and but I
went immediately into another play I was
cast as an understudy to Brandon
dewilder in a race of hay Men by Evan
Hunter which was 's take on the
generational Revolution that was
happening you wondering how I got to the
Fireside theater so but so uh so I'm
understudying Brandon now I had been
faded I had been asked to understudy
Brandon when I was a child actor I
started as an actor when I was nine
years old on a show called Uncle Danny
reads the funnies which some other
famous actors and actresses were on to
we would basically read the funny papers
from The Daily News every day for like
10 10 or 15 minutes in a tiny little
studio in Dumont Studios uh smaller than
this space we're we're we're recording
in now and uh and ad lib a lot of it ad
lib it and have fun so uh Elliot Gould
was one of the guys by the way who also
did this child actor uh so now oh gosh I
got I'm got lost now in my trail oh yeah
so uh at the time going to alen
Stevenson School starring as female
leads in Gilbert and Sullivan operettas
because I was a boy
soprano Phyllis and Pirates of penance
and uh something else in
ianthe I'm getting the characters
confused Mabel in Pirates of Penzance
Phyllis in
iany uh anyway and I'd been asked oh
yeah and my second grade teacher Mrs
Green was a very good friend of Helen
Hayes who was at that time you have to
explain who Helen Hayes was
she was like the the the the diva of
theater you know and Helen Hayes was
doing a show called uh Mrs mcing on
Broadway and Brandon dldo was playing
the little boy in that and she because
she knew I was a really good actor uh
Helen Hayes asked that I audition for
Brandon's understudy I would have
replaced him and I was believe it or not
shy at the time I didn't take that
opportunity so here well what 20 years
later I'm under studying Brandon dlda
and we became extremely close friends uh
one of the reasons that we did was he
was a a Viper he was a a wonderful uh
dedicated pothead and he and and so we
would we'd go up in in the Henry Miller
Theater I think where we were working
after rehearsal and and later after the
shows we'd hang around and we go up to a
dressing room an unused dressing room at
the top of the a staircase and we'd get
stoned and we turn on the air
conditioner so you know get the stuff
out so it wouldn't and at the end of the
run I remember looking over at the air
conditioner and realizing that the air
conditioner was actually not in a window
it was on a window sill so what it was
doing was just recycling you know no
wonder we got so high up there you know
but but but then Brandon and I stayed
friends and he was teaching himself to
play guitar uh because he wanted to
change his career and so I I hung out
with all these great musicians uh and
and uh especially the international
submarine band Graham Parsons we used to
go down and hear him play all the time
and we jam and it was it was it was
groovy man and and we' put hash and
cigarettes so we could smoke them in
public and all that and we took acid
together and Brandon had a beautiful uh
uh home up in Vermont we go up there and
we get Get Stoned on acid and walk
around talk to the deer and you know and
he was married to the sister of one of
my classmates from Yale okay I see how
this is going to tie together fire sign
that sister gave a hand job to David
Osman no is this not right
sorry totally logical I'll put it in the
footnotes or the hand notes if you will
so anyway uh Brandon towi at one point
Brandon says after the show closed he
says I want to go back out to to LA and
resuscitate my ACT my film career I said
great he said let's drive out together
fine I had a a great apartment on uh
West 11 Street just up from the White
Horse Cafe where Brendan Bean used to uh
give Bean
jobs and uh thanks for setting that up
and so I I think I sublet the place to
some to a stage manager that I worked
with on on on Broadway I also did a play
off Broadway called a race of Harry no
called called a uh oh gez what was that
called well Sam Waton was in it and John
Cullum was in it uh and it was directed
by
uh a wonderful no I I better not I can't
I can't that's another I'd have to do a
little research to bring that all back
Howard de Silva ah his name appeared
Howard de Silva can you explain who he
was no how I can't give you now no he
was with the group theater oh oh my God
yeah which later became the grope
theater when they when they went off off
off Broadway but no he was with the
group theater and he directed us and uh
and it was the stage manager of that
show which was called thistle in my bed
it was a
Welsh folk not another one folk play God
almighty this Welsh thing that that that
that uh by good Powers her name was
goodin powers powers yeah oh yeah goodin
Powers you never heard of her in your
life and isn't that Mike Meers new
spin-off series and film getting goodan
pow needle that's a really obscure pun G
Gertie Grand getting ger Gertie
grandal's needle oh you don't know that
it was an early early early comedy I
mean 12 Century you know English getting
Grandma girton's needle mhm Google it
I'm Googling getting Grammy gon's needle
say that 10 times straight all right so
anyway uh so Brandon says let's go out
let's go out to Hollywood and uh I took
my my new uh found powers as a driver
and we drove cross country together uh
Amazing Adventures actually have
cassette tapes that I recorded along the
way of that oh god really what am I ever
going to do with those first I have to
find a cassette player and that's number
one so they have find somebody who knows
how to use it so we get out to Hollywood
and Brandon connects up immediately with
Peter
Fonda and so Peter and Brandon as one
does why not you know you want to groovy
man so and he was he's in Hidden Canyon
he's got a beautiful house in Hidden
Canyon and uh and we would get and he
was going through a a marijuana
possession trial at the
time and so we would attend his Tri
every day you know to support him and
then go and get
stoned in the car while he's holding up
the pipe that they had and saying
claiming he didn't I no I've never seen
this
before and this would before DNA too
right so yes this is before DNA existed
ladies and gentlemen so just good old
Lord yeah come a long way didn't exist
so anyway so we we're the Three
Musketeers and we're having a great time
together and one day uh and and Peter's
working on a little movie idea he's got
called Captain America and uh but Marvel
Comics which was nothing at the time
wouldn't give him the rights to use
Captain America so he retitled It Easy
Rider okay which which and you know what
an easy riter is don't you I do an easy
riter is a boyfriend of a prostitute
there who living off living off his
woman there we go he's an easy riter uh
I didn't know that and I I sent sent an
email to Peter a couple of weeks ago
saying did you know that and he said yes
Terry Southern told him that and that's
where he got the title I said son of a
[ __ ] all this time I didn't know
amazing uh so anyway we're hanging out
and he wants to do some research on the
youth Revolution here we going around to
the youth Revolution and so we went down
to the Sunset Strip uh during a
demonstration against the curfew that
the city wanted to impose on young
people on the strip
and that became the Sunset Strip riots
holy [ __ ] and it became the Sunset Strip
riots because the LA Police cordoned off
one end of the Sunset Strip and the
sheriff's department cordoned off the
others and they just did a pincer
squeeze and pushed everybody into the
middle So that obviously there was going
to be unrest you know and and then they
started wailing on people at the time uh
I had a I was working also writing for
the East Village other an alternative
newspaper in New York and I was there
whs Coast correspondent so I held up my
my press card which had a big eye on it
and the cops just Flo around me like a
KN through hot butter but they beat up
uh uh they they they arrested Fonda and
they beat up
Brandon but I was fine but
earlier in that demonstration we had
done a sit down strike where you know
the the cops were starting to move in on
us we said hell no we're not going to
move and we all sat down and I sat down
on an open copy of the LA Free Press
which was you know the Revolutionary
newspaper at the time pulled it out from
under my ass and I had sat down on Peter
bergman's
face there is a picture of kpfk newsman
Peter Bergman interviewing returning
Vietnam war vets holy sh and I have a
copy of that CU a fan sent me a copy of
the paper awesome well I go holy [ __ ]
Peter Bergman kpfk newsman he's out here
and so I called him the next day and he
said oh yeah I'm The Wizard of Oz I said
I know but what are you doing these days
he said no no no I have a talk show late
at night counterculture call-in talk
show for 3 hours or something 1200 to 3
or 11: to 4: I don't know
and radio free Oz huh be Radio free o
radio free Oz was called Radio free Oz
and on kpfk he said why don't you come
down and we'll you know we'll play so I
go down and I meet David asman and Phil
Austin who were both work worked at the
station and we discovered we were all
fire signs Peter and David are
sagittarians I'm a Leo an Austin's an
Aries got God forbid and and we all
started improvising together on the
radio we found that we had a comic Knack
we had a lot of things in common we
loved old radio we loved the Goon shows
yeah goon shows I was going to say
actually Peter sers actually after
listening kidding listening to the
electrician that was one of my first
thoughts I'm like there are some goon
voices in there and I'm just like so
that doesn't doesn't surprise what what
got you started improvising you say you
started improvising on the radio were
you just hanging out like how did that
just start well I had done radio improv
with Victor Miller back at Yale who had
had a show Victor Miller wrote Friday
the 13th [ __ ] and and he became Prett
impressive and he's still he he sent an
email out the other day saying I can't
believe it I'm still having dinner out
on Friday the 13th I bet I bet right
because it just boom it just catapulted
him and he actually wrote on a soap
opera for years and years and years and
years and he's actually now
collaborating with Peter Fonda on a
movie idea because Peter and he his
family and Peter's family were house
Neighbors at one point it's such a small
world amazing so so
anyway uh I had done radio comic radio
improvisation uh at WN whatever the Y
station was
wybc it was H and uh and I don't know if
I ever did that with with uh Peter or
not but always had a knack for for that
remember my my comic yep gooner scripts
brilliant and Peter worked with Spike
Milligan really in London on not so much
a show as more a way of life it was a TV
show that he did uhuh uh because Peter
Bergman he he
was he was drafted no he was due to be
drafted but Lyndon B Johnson intervened
and put him into a special program uh
arts program over in
Berlin with Wow people like uh uh not
David mammo but another famous writer
like that this back brain I have to deal
with but anyway he was saved from the
draft and yet the first time that I
reconnected with Peter before sitting on
his face was back in New York in my
apartment on my third floor walk up uh
and brown Stone on West 11 Street I had
hooked up with Susan anspach before
anything happened to her career she had
been told by Helen Hayes that she's got
to go into show business because she was
so talented and and she went to some
Catholic University Helen Hayes came out
to speak to the students saw her work
and said girl you got to do it you got
to go for it and somehow I ended up
sleeping with her you know the next day
or something so I I wake up in the
morning with beautiful Susan anspach in
my arms and there's a knock on the door
and I said knock on my door and I go and
I open the door and it's Peter Bergman I
hadn't seen him since Yale and he's in
an army uniform and he's got a
guitar and he comes in and we all have
breakfast together and he sings you know
folk songs and wobbly songs to us and
tells me something about his life a
little bit about it and disappears gone
until I sit on his face and this is like
the best Cohen Brothers
idea I've ever heard in my life man was
a magical Sprite who didn't exist except
in these moments good God God so anyway
uh we we discovered we had this Knack of
improvisation together and we did a a
piece called the Oz Film Festival uh in
which we all portrayed multiple
characters uh and showed movies on the
radio you
know and Austin he played a an adult
filmmaker and Jack love I think his name
was and uh and he showed an excerpt from
Blondie pays the rent on on the on the
air and of course the the the the
phone's lit up with people saying you
can't show a dirty movie on the radio oh
God and then they they lit up again with
people saying how can you censor people
for showing a dirty movie on the radio
he said you know and and we said uhoh
we're on to something uh the art of
sendup because see Bergman he he had the
Gift of Gab but he also had an ability
to uh AB absorb and become the
characters that he was interviewing so
like if he interviewed a shaman a Hy
Shaman uh a after the guy was gone he
could he would then become the Hy shaman
on the radio and could talk to people
and tell them things and read read tarot
cards and all this so he I saw that he
just absorbed these things and instead
of saying like the shaman told me he
would say he would become the shaman and
and be the shaman and I would shame on
you Bergman you know uh and and so he
had this enormous following uh he
created a thing called the
lovein uh which was held in allean park
I played a Russian poet called Yuri gnov
which means Yuri [ __ ] because gavno is
[ __ ] shitty Yori shitty George or
something and uh and I read a poem in
Russian you know one of my Russian poems
translated you know to the crowd of
thousands of thousands of people who all
were fans of Peter bergman's radio foras
and came to this first lovein he created
the name and everything and and and so
we had this phenomenon going
on and uh and we created an
improv oh yeah we we were asked to uh we
kind of created a name for ourselves as
the fire the Oz fire sign theater okay
and so we were asked to perform in the
student lounge at UCLA and we said
perform what are we going to do so we
created uh we we we put on it's all the
art of put on we became an expatriate
Eastern European comedy troop theater
theater troop and we were trying to stay
in in in America because we had escaped
from
communism and and we had we had a play
that was a big success over there called
waiting for the electrician or someone
like him but because we didn't speak
English we had to do it kind of like as
a MIM so we did some crazy improv there
of waiting for the electrician all right
well then I get another call from my
agent I'm cast in Henry jum's movie or
actually the way that happened was that
fire sign was starting to get traction
but we we but nothing had really
happened for us yet and jagam had been
given this movie so I got to audition do
screen test with all these famous he
wanted me to play him in the same part I
played before in the play he wanted me
to play in the movie snowball tree now a
safe place uh and was before Tuesday W
was cast so as I say I got to to uh impr
to do screen test with all these famous
famous people uh being buzzed what's
happening no problem Jamie I can't take
it Melinda Peterson I have to take it a
minute and uh uh famous people and and
then and then uh I get cast in the film
and uh it takes me to New York so I had
to put the fire sign theater on the back
burner MH and I went to New York and we
shot most of this stuff uh on locations
when there was an apartment in the East
Village that we shot a lot of the stuff
at and uh but most of it was in the boat
Park and in Central Park and that's
where uh Orson Wells did all of his
scenes as well and there's a wonderful
book that Henry put together called my
my lunches with orison have you read it
oh it's fantastic it's fantastic and he
tells the story there of how he got
orison to get in the movie because it
was jago's first [ __ ] movie he didn't
know anything you know he had no track
record or anything like
that okay fine and uh and and he met
jagam he says he looked like a big
purple grape cuz he was in he used to
wear like Viet Kong pajamas he was
always an enormous man you know weigh
350 pounds he had to have especially
reinforced chairs for him you know to
sit in and things or he Splinter them
amazing character but anyway and and and
J and and he said can I see a script and
then we said well there isn't really a
script you know I believe in
improvisation but you know I've done it
as a play and there is a play you can
look at he says well I'm not used to
working without seeing the script and he
said you're a first-time director all
and he said what do you want me to play
he said I I want you to play a a rabbi a
kind of a mystical magical Rabbi
character and he thought for a minute he
said can I do
magic he was an ad magician right and
Henry says
sure that's what you say
so he says okay I'll do it wow that was
magic right there absolutely and so
Henry put in all this magic which is you
know in in the in the movie now now the
one story I want to tell about the movie
before I uh uh uh I I tell you the next
step of the the electrician how the
electrician happened
was there was a scene in the play where
Tuesday Weld she picks me up and I think
I'm going to get hook up with her okay I
think I'm going to get LA and and she
instead she takes me back to her
apartment and she shows me she takes me
to the bathroom and there in the bathtub
covered with ice is a dead dog and it's
her pet her dog has died and it's a
weekend and ASPCA won't pick up on the
weekend so she wants me to put the dog
in a suitcase and take it down to the
ASPCA and and and I say okay so I put
the dog in the suitcase and and she
she's having a seance with a bunch of
her friends up on her roof uh while I go
and and get in the subway and take it
down
but when I'm in the subway as I tell her
when I get back to the Seance I was
trying to get some lettuce out of my
teeth in one of the the bubble in one of
the gum machines there had little
mirrors on them and some guy stole the
suitcase Puerto Rican guy stole the
suitcase now apparently this really
happened to somebody oh yeah okay so I
come back and I'm tell her that and I'm
all upset and she says that's okay all
right so in the
movie Henry's debating now how are we
going to do that should we have a
stuffed a fake dog uh should we have a
maybe just a fur coat with ice on it uh
or should we have a real dog very
well-trained patient real dog it's more
to it than that he gets a real dog and
he thinks it's funny if it's a St
Bernard so this beautiful big St Bernard
is on on the set in the apartment and
they tranquilize it and they put it in
the bathtub and he got his his tongue
coming out and he's snoring and they put
the fake ice on it and it's a real one
shot we open the door you know POV of
the uh the caraman in the back of the
bathroom and oh my God I see the thing
and she says whatever she says and I
stammer whatever ever and and cut and so
then they give the dog the
antidote the dog
died Jesus Christ and the next thing we
know they're carting this beautiful
carcass out rolling this carcass out it
was the 13th time the dog had been
tranquilized for a movie or a commercial
oh holy [ __ ] it killed it and when Henry
looked at the rushes the next day
he said it didn't look real so they cut
the whole plot line wow and they
replaced it with a magic box this made
the film even more impenetrable than it
was
already a magic box that Orson Wells
pulls a rainbow out of which if you ever
see any of Henry Henry Jam's movies
rainbow pictures and that's the opening
logo of his film company yeah he was
just honored and rightly so by the
independent film uh U by the in what
would they call the independent film
Society uh as Indie director of all time
you know because he really he has
cranked out so many films I've I've uh
appeared in three of his films now a
safe place and two others with Tana
Frederick who is his his latest uh
Discovery and his wife and a very
sensitive actress uh quite quite a
wonderful partner for Henry and they're
they're turning out their his own little
Studio turn he's independently wealthy
because his dad was in real estate his
father's story is a wonderful story and
he wrote a play about it called uh the
last train to gdau or something I can't
remember the title right now but but it
had a real long run it's going to be his
next movie and it's the story of of
Simon jagam uh how he got out of of uh
Poland was it Poland or Russia anyway
how he got out of Eastern Europe
uh it's it's a wonderful I I don't want
to get into the whole play because it's
it's quite a complicated but fascinating
real story anyway uh we're now at the
point where I'm wrapping the
movie and there's something else that
happened here I have to figure this out
yeah I'm rapping the movie and and I'm
closing down my apartment in New York
because I know I want to go back to
LA and I hooked up with a girl named
Diana du who Brandon had introduced me
to when we were living on Lash
Lane right near uh Yamashiro down from
Yamashiro Lash Lane near the Hollywood
Bowl we had a great apartment there and
Diana stayed with us for a while
so I connected up with Diana after the
movie was over and she was living right
across from Maxis Kansas City in the The
Happening part of the village and I uh
so I I I bunked with her and her
girlfriend uh and basically had an
affair with
her uh the other one watched I
guess and and she
Diana had invented electric clothing
she had opened a fashion boutique or
design Factory called expera
puritanos which was part of Puritan
Fashions uhhuh and she
took uh translucent plastic strips that
would hold a charge and glow and she wov
them into dresses oh my God so that
there would like be like a stripped a
stripped disco dress uhhuh cute short
dress with these panels black and black
and white panels and with the use of a
potentiometer on a belt she could
control the movement of the lights
around the dress so it could Flash and
move in Rhythm to the
music so it was all the rage on the
Disco floor and she had a tie for men
and a belt for men which I used to wear
so I'm living with her and I actually
it's the only job job I've ever done I
did publicity for her publicity
releases uh and we had the be wonderful
Affair and we're hanging out with
everybody at Maxis Kansas City who is
anybody and a certain point in
relationships you reach a point where
you go like well this relationship is
over you know and for whatever reason
you just say this it's over and
we both came to that same
conclusion and the phone rang and I
picked up the phone and it was Peter
burkeman and he said Phil there's a
ticket waiting for you at Columbia
Records we want to fly you back to LA we
got a record contract with Colombia and
we're going to be doing our first record
waiting for the electrician or someone
like
him and I said Diana
I love you bye-bye and I the only thing
I regret was I left my guitar with her
because I was learning to play the
guitar a guitar which had been given to
me by a winner of the 60 of of was it
named That
Tune I think it was there was a young
man who uh they played me in my shadow
and he correctly identified it and then
he played it on the guitar remember this
was all rig these were the rigged and
and he became a friend of mine in New
York and gave me a guitar and so for a
while I learned to play the guitar
particularly the D Minor
cord I was I was living in the village
and into the D Minor cord H but I left
that guitar with Diana now Diana
du Diana du later changed her name to
Daisy Duck and she and and when a safe
place open
uh in New York and was playing in
La uh I had a party at my house and
Henry was there and a famous French
director uh the one who directed Jane
Fonda in in that wonderful science
fiction movie Barbarella Barbarella oh
shoot yeah okay and and he back to Jane
Fonda and yep and he had cast Gwen Wells
to play like uh a deaf mute girl or
something in a French film he was doing
he was at the party with Henry and Diana
showed up with a duck in a
diaper as Daisy
Duck D What I Call Daisy Duck and she
later
married my childhood friend from Goan
Indiana Ricky
Curtis who lived down the street from my
grandparents where I stayed every summer
who aged to hang out with all the time
and the Curtis family was a musical
family and would tour around playing
clubs and things and Ricky was a genius
guitarist and he wrote Southern Cross
for Crosby Stills Nation wow beautiful
song and
he had been drafted and was a Bombadier
in the Vietnamese War and it really
crippled him became a heroin
addict and uh but he married mared Diana
they got married and moved to
Florida and I still haven't done proper
research on this I'd been told that he
had died of an
overdose but you never you never can
trust these things I've been told many
times that people I knew were murdered
or died or this or that and then they
show up like the Revenant you know alive
and well it's just gossip you know it
could be just gossip I hope it is yeah
but anyway when I flew back to La I of
course had no place to live so I crashed
at bergman's pad and Osman and his wife
Tiny uh who was rather tiny uh were also
there and Austin and his wife Ana Lee
lived in uh Laurel Canyon and I think
Peter was living in in Laurel Canyon
area too he had a beautiful duplex house
with an open Atrium and we we slept up
on the little beds in the
atrium and Peter and his
girlfriend uh oh what was his
girlfriend's name Susan no that's Denise
Susan was Brandon's wife uhuh uh that's
all right I always get them confused
yeah before we get there I I don't want
to cut you off but I know you have a
call schedule so well we have to find
out what the girlfriend's name is a
Lauren do you want to she's the one we
thought was murdered do you want to do a
wrap up and say this is how we got to
electrician and then next episode we'll
just go over the electrician yeah all
right let's do it because I don't want
to cut you off but I know you know sty
so
St terrible Brooke yes that was my next
guest Brooke
asalan it's also your next guest and
Brook and
Brooke she's a piece of
work Brooke is a gorgeous zoptic
force of nature who was Peter's best man
you know I mean she she and Peter he he
he and she were a a great couple they
traveled to Turkey together where she
practically you know caused a revolution
because she was so pretty and Peter was
doing research for a play a movie he
wanted to write and uh and Brooke later
when they split up married Simon uh John
Simon a mutual friend of all ours and
moved to
Woodstock and and John Simon is a
Pianist musician uh of some Fame and and
and and when I after I did a safe place
I remember I traveled with a girl I had
fallen in love
with uh up to Woodstock to visit them to
visit Brooke and then many many many
many many years later I had affair with
Brooke and uh and you just have to pass
it along pass it along pass it along and
and and Brooke was in a way responsible
for Peter's death
because I was doing a one-man reading of
Don kote with the LA guitar quartet
which I've been touring around with
Hawaii and various other parts of the
Canada and the United States and I was
doing a performance of that I think it
UCLA and I invited Peter to see it
because he'd love it you know and and he
had revealed to us that he was suffering
from a form of
leukemia and we were still writing
together because we were trying to put
together the the Proctor and Bergman
story and and various other things for
for a publisher who was
interested and I said come and see it
show the show it's on satday night he
said well no he said I want to go up and
visit Brooke he was trying to rekindled
his relationship with Brooke and Brooke
is a professional nurse now and so she
was giving him advice about then helping
him so silly Bergman drives up to San
Francisco where she is spend some time
with her drives back gets a terrible
cold and the next thing we know he's in
the hospital Melinda and I were at this
time at our time share on Kawai
with some wonderfully funny Canadian
friends of ours one of of whom it
teaches the ergonomics of
dentistry in in uh Vancouver and is a
mystery writer which is how we met him
at the mystery writers International
mystery writers Festival in uh Owensboro
Kentucky another
story and his wife is a sex therapist
and travels the world lecturing and
teaching people how to do it or not
to and we're there on Kawaii and we've
invited them to share our our lockoff
with us because there's so much fun to
be with and we had some sexual problems
we were working out no and
uh and it
rained every day but maybe two during
the two weeks that we were there and the
one week we were there with them
torrential biblical rains thunder and
lightning and lashing rain and flooding
and and Bergman died during this time
and I'm trying and my
phone my
iPhone the microphone stopped working so
I could hear calls but I couldn't talk
back to people and I had to call on the
on the regular phone that was there and
and so all the interviews and everything
that I had to do relating to Peter's
passing and the fact that he passed away
I was in Hawaii I couldn't have been you
know farther away from all of that
but that puts a a Topper
to to a a long wonderful history with
Peter uh including touring for many many
years as Proctor and Bergman doing
syndicated radio shows nationally
syndicated radio shows
uh performing all kinds of shows from
big old a big huge stage touring show
that we did based on TV or not TV uh all
the records that we did independently of
the fire sign theat is Proctor and
Bergman which I'm still receiving
residuals for and really a wonderful
wonderful long lasting
partnership uh and Peter was responsible
really for it all and
certainly uh created
the concept of waiting for electrician
or someone like him because when he was
approached by a producer named Gary
Usher at Columbia who had gotten wind of
us through Phil Austin Phil had done
voices for an astrology record and
another record I think called Duckman I
think it was called duck Duckman yeah uh
and Gary Usher talked to Peter through
connection with Phil said I want to do
an oz fire sign theater record and Peter
said no no you want to do a no par I'm
misspeaking myself he said you want to
do an a radio free Oz I want to do a
radio fre Oz record and Peter said no no
no you want to do an oz fire sign
theater
record and Gary say anything you
want so that's why that record got made
but we we had to lose the name Oz
because Disney ah was doing a thing
called Return to Oz at the time yep and
so there huge success
so we got a letter we're still talking
right right we got a letter signed by
Mickey yeah and Goofy his
know and Fireside Theater which was also
a theatrical book club interesting and a
radio show where they did plays
firesight theater so so there we are and
the next chapter of this Audio Drama
will be uh going into the studio for the
first
time and uh at
Columbia and the studios were old radio
Studios M at Columbia square and
starting to lay down the the writing
that we created for our first
record and uh where it went from there
sounds good well thank you for being
here obviously as always Phil glad to be
here Jeremy can I sleep over yeah I
don't want to have to drive back this
you know we got have a pajama party
We'll order some pizza we'll do each
other's
hair I'd pay good money to see that
Jeremy and Greg thank you guys for Abad
just sit and listen all right thank you
guys for listening and watching and as
always have a good thing have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if if you like us give us a
fstar rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook.com/ Comedy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedy on vinyl.com
[Music]