[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
[Music]
podcast hey everybody we intended this
to be a discussion of uh of how be in
two places at once when you're not
anywhere at all guess what happened not
that Phil has this wonderful notebook
and that's for the next hour you're
going to watch him talk about his 1967
calendar everything yes his calendar
everything that happened in 1967 when I
say everything I mean everything his
haircuts are detailed my accidents his
accidents rain every time he knocked
down a carport lots lots of great stuff
so that's what you're watching we will
pick up on this album shortly but enjoy
The Following episode
recording and uh you know but we do not
have to get started till you're ready
but I'm ready uh I'll never be ready so
we can start whenever we want you have a
bunch of things
there
well when do we if you want tol what
we're doing I don't want I don't want to
anybody oh my God the year is 1969 the
album is how can you be in two places at
once when you're not anywhere at all the
artist Z with an S the fire sign theater
spelled properly on the on the album
cover this time my guess that's right
for a change Phil Proctor and Taylor
Jason Taylor Taylor is here drinking a
beer Phil's also drinking beer but he's
slipping through some papers well not no
these do your taxes you're doing your
taxes no no no no no this this is yeah
this
is my the only record I have of what I
was doing from 1967 to 19 68
sure around the time that
we were starting to write how can you be
in two places at once when you're not
anywhere at all it's mindblowing and oh
here's a public notice for free food
from the
diggers
okay that's the best diggers this this
is like a Holy Grail mhm Holy Grail and
and oh here here was the this what did
you know you had this I did but I I
decided for this interview tonight
because I can never remember anything
that it might be wise to see if I could
find some tracking of what I was doing
then uhhuh and this these years yeah are
so extraordinarily full that it it
absolutely is blowing my mind here for
instance I just opened to July
II and it says the
lovein Oz
uh and I guess this was the famous no
then what was it I don't know what other
11 you you might have done in Ju Chad
and Jeremy
8:00 uh dating game for I I was so busy
so you were you were a ringer on The
Dating Game for a long time weren't you
I was on The Dating Game I did three
times and I won every time wonderful uh
and and I could only take one of the
trips I one of the times I won was with
Deborah not Winger Wall-E Deborah WALL-E
who was one of the flying nuns oh and
although she was not that nun-like in
person and I want a trip to Switzerland
which is my my home country it's where I
came from my family the the Amish part
of my family the yters come from Baron
Switzerland I couldn't go because I was
doing something with the fire sign
theater sons of [ __ ] you know but if
I if I had to do it over again I would
have said guys I'm going to my home
country going to Baron and it's a one
once in a-lifetime experience because I
haven't been back there since although
I've been to Switzerland and I said I'm
going let's Rec confabulate let's you
know if we're if we're performing let's
change but you know somehow we couldn't
or I couldn't or whatever right but
1967 I did bird at
kpfk on New Year's Eve I was studying
with a guy named jacqu Honduras with
Brandon dlda and Peter
Fonda I performed Ernie the Wonder
healer on kpfk with Peter
Bergman uh and I watched a my
performance in the Amorous Flea on
KC or NE it says here because we had
recorded it in the theater at uh uh on
Las pomas okay I guess a little while
before uh it goes into various things
here I got cast in generation with Bob
Cummings on the 20th of January and you
got a haircut Peter visor cut my hair
Peter visor was another celebrity okay
hair it was Peter Fonda's stylist and
Peter had his haircut the same day I did
a dating game the same day I demolished
Brandon's carport
Brandon dewilder was living on West
Wanda mhm in Benedict Canyon I live on
Wanda Park
Drive and he has he had a great house
with a Turret on it and a kind of a
turnaround uh that another friend of
mine later lived in not even knowing who
Brandon was and that particular day I I
was driving because I was I learned how
to drive kind of I was driving a big old
V uh um station wagon mhm because I
figured there'd be more car between me
and an accident and I parked the car up
next to Brandon's house forgot to to
turn the wheels in didn't do the
emergency brake properly and as I'm
walking down to go into Brandon's place
I see the car rolling past me my God it
hits this open carport at the end of
Brandon's place and completely destroys
it it just fell down
completely now Brandon who was always
stoned didn't bother him a bit he was
insured he said fine he thought it was
amusing and so we went on with whatever
the hell we were getting stoned I
guess it rained on the 23rd it rained
and it says here smog device and
insurance oh good I guess I didn't have
insurance when I destroyed his and it
says saw blow up and Austin Pendleton
was in town okay I saw Mike Nichols The
Graduate uh Curtis Roberts H generation
ctis Roberts was our producer for
Generation uh I had my first rehearsal
with Les Brown Jr Bob
Osborne who's famous now for all of his
you don't know who Bob host Robert
Osborne yeah yeah the host of
TMC movies oh of course okay there we go
the time when we with him as an actor he
amazed us with his an astounding
knowledge of the Academy Awards and the
movies all right perfect right it was
perfect love it all right uh and on the
27th Brandon and his wife's child was
born Jesse Ian dlda 6B 7 oz okay all
right next night party party time uh
then I flew on the 29th to Palm Beach
Miami and Palm Beach where we
rehearsed generation with Bob Cummings
and uh his daughter Melinda Cummings
that's right uh and we played first we
opened uh in Palm Beach at the Royal p
panana
Playhouse so if I can stop you mid uh
early February of ' 67 because you're in
Florida you miss the night of the provos
I did on kbk where a guy who was kind of
rubbing Peter the wrong way because he
said oh I'm in with the provos and Peter
had been in with the provos in Amsterdam
two years earlier he was like well [ __ ]
you're kind of nudging into on my
territory there and he came on uh on uh
radio fre o and did uh did did a did did
a sort of Yes Man thing he came on and
said this guy from Provo said he
represented Provo said he had some
electronic music to play and he uh
proceeded to to play an open reel of
commercials that were taped off of
commercial AM radio and uh they started
taking some phone calls and people
started calling in and saying we dumped
some joints in in uh the the library
book drop at A and C and at the end of
the after after an hour and a half
somebody broke came some some other
people in this Provo group came into the
studio took out Peter moved him into
another room and proceeded to sign up
removed him they didn't they didn't kill
him today's you know vernacular you have
to be careful what you say very polite
uh Peter can you please go along with
our little our our little Happ here
prank and go into the other room and
they signed off for the national anthem
eight times right and then shut down the
station that's right oh my God that's
right that was a very famous and
Infamous event at kpfk how how late in
the year are you okay so you said this
is around the time when you start
writing the first album correct not sure
I'm waiting to see find out on the 13th
of February I appeared at the Coconut
Grove Playhouse and I mailed $125 to
Chase Manhattan
Bank excent
1967 it was a fortune Peter saved all of
his his receipts in case you're
interested saved him in the archive
which is now taking up space in the fire
sign archive very important thank you
Peter oh here I have we saw in Miami
Frank Sinatra perform at the Eden Rock
apparently
uh and then we had a day off good good I
mailed
$354 56 to Chase Manhattan Bank
whooo okay 26 we played in Fort
Lauderdale at the opening season of The
Parker Playhouse built by Zev buffman
okay who had sent me out previously on
other tours with goober for and gross uh
Music Circus on the East Coast doing
plays like Brigadoon with Pat o no uh
Phineas rainbow with Pat O'Brien and
Brigadoon and other other things and
many many many many many years later I
performed on the same boards at the
Parker Playhouse still produced by Zev
buffman in the BBC Murders okay which
was a hybrid radio show of the original
radio BBC Radio broadcast written by uh
uh what's her name a chrisy aatha chrisy
oh yes I remember okay I think I think
we talked about not on this before
performed by my wife Melinda Peterson so
that it was on it was in 67 that's
wonderful that I did that end of run
okay Cheryl oh yes we met Les Brown Jr
and I got along like two old brothers
and we were driving along the street in
Florida somewhere one of the cities and
in an open convertible rented
convertible and there were these two
really knockout girls walking along the
street on the sidewalk and all of a
sudden the two girls stopped in their
tracks and turned and looked at
us and we
stopped and went over and said hi who
are you one of them was named I guess
Cheryl height trying to remember there
were and and they were both stewardesses
they were Steward
ey and we entered into a relationship
with them uhh that continued for many
many years when I was uh living in enino
renting a house with Jeremy Clyde this
this wonderful crazy house uh with the
Olympic side swimming pool and the uh
bomb shelter and the tiki bar and the
Flaming uh the ape cage and the Flaming
uh Fountain what world did you live in I
lived in the world of Jesus Christ
[ __ ] Hollywood man of the late 60s
sexual Revolution man yeah but and we
had these you know these topless parties
which is easy for us uh by the pool
every weekend and it was gorgeous it was
just great it was such a wonderful
wonderful time we kept our pot in the uh
in the bomb shelter some local kids once
broke in and and we we we the cops let
them out but we we talked to them and
said no no no don't do that now you get
get your own pot you NY kids and uh uh
in any event how did I get there from
here I don't
know these girls ended up living in in
the house Helen height that was her name
okay Helen height a stewardess I love it
and Cheryl I can't remember her last
name but she later became like the mayor
of New Mexico or something the mayor of
some city in New Mexico really she did I
swear to God and they were they were
living there okay plus as well shiron
mccan who later was the psychic girl who
told me about the the gang line shooting
oh yes right they all lived there in
this complex that we had cuz it was a
huge house with you know seven or eight
rooms and 12 bathrooms and a pool to pee
in and everything it was just it was
great so anyway I flew to New York City
and my dad flew to Caracus says my dad
flew to Caracus I stayed with my mom on
the 11th of March and my dad flew to
Caracus I don't know why ah all right
and and I oh and I stayed with Diana du
who invented the electric dress and who
had been Brandon's girlfriend before me
uh okay it's it's kind of great hearing
you talk about her and then seeing her
name written down just in very is this
crisp not this has not been it doesn't
look like this has been cracked in 50
years I'm telling you this stuff just
amazing all right what is St Patrick's
Day I deposited
$878 okay happiness in the flashing Loft
this is when I was with Diana
du the the ventor of the of electric
flashing
clothing oh there was a lot of flashing
going on in those days and then called
California and there was a human
being the human the human be ringing a
bell who hosted that cuz it wasn't it
wasn't a Bergman joint and this when is
it March it's March March 26 67 minut e
no that's no that's it that's Peter's
that's Peter's being this is the one
okay so it's if you if you've been I
wasn't there no well wait a minute
though I was in Diana do at the time I
see okay so but if you were in Florida
and New York and everything but I
thought you played a poet on stage ah
that was different that was in the first
Lin but that's the first Lin no no it
wasn't the first Lovin was the Lovin
which I think I mentioned earlier I
played yavas luu which means I love you
in Russian yavas luu and I and I was and
I was dressed up like a Russian poet
with you know orange glasses and
everything and I did some kind of poetry
with irian
accon uh in any event exper puranas was
the name of Diana's company oh yes sir
remember you mentioning yes yes all
right what else Annette Grant H moving
cleaning apartment sublet Helen height
there she is Cheryl oh here's her name
Cheryl B what does that say B uh that
does look like maybe bro BR R NE BR is
that possible BR well we'll never know
we'll never know and I met up with Ken
burough my My Pal Ken burough look all
these people who later married Erica
Jang still happily married to Erica Jang
now what's this Max's oh yeah Maxx's
Kansas City is where we all hung out and
it says Max's bomb
food I don't know what that moved I I
closed up my beautiful third story walk
up Brownstone in New York on West 11
Street just a few doors up from the
White Horse Cafe okay and moved into
that was yeah 312 West 11 Street and
then it says unemployment oh I went to
the
unemployment oh those are the days Helen
Hayes audition for West Coast rep don't
oh at the Helen Hayes theater audition
for the West Coast rep April to tell the
truth paraphernalia show taping Anette
Grant
rain uh got me and I was there okay all
right let's see what else after strike
ended the after strike ended on April
the 10th what after strike I don't
remember that Cal before the bomb
reading a play by John
wolson okay all right right uh I'll stop
this in a while because it's probably
boring to everybody else no it it is
interesting though and it's also what's
great is it's proof that your other
memories weren't complete [ __ ] like
some say is written down not complete
[ __ ] ah and here it says the coast
calls that was the day that I told you
I'm sure I talked about this I did a
nice little drawing about it that was
the day when Peter Burgman when I I knew
that my relationship was over with Diana
and it was time to move on and I got the
call from Peter Bergman saying there's a
ticket waiting for you to be picked up
in Columbia record the the fire sign
that was the 16th of April 16th of April
1967 ladies and gentlemen this is the
beginning of fire calls on paper it I
need to take it was can you take a
picture of that for me uh what button uh
it's on the screen right there that one
that's just that's I think my nipples
are hard like it's it's just one of
those things it's very like this is like
Ah that's one
of 67 but but we fire sign had already
we' already been doing stuff sure yeah
yes but this was like the record the of
course yeah this is let's see of the
fire sign the world knows Lan Kings
goodbye I flew out on the 22nd and then
I have
Cabaret and mcbd just oh God know oh
Susan
anpo there was Susan
anspach oh I see a lot of little do I
don't know what that means there Susan
on she was obviously turned into a bunch
of dots like uh Mike TV but here we go
the 26th I flew to
californ and met up with Peter Bergman
at 8:45 in the morning he drove me to
his home 26th April yeah April 26th k
rla
a okay and then UCLA there it is
bronislav compos
I apparently played a character named
Bron SLO compost which I forgotten well
if it's Friday the 28th of April this
could be your first fire sign live
performance fire live performance so do
you remember this performance did you
did you were you pretending to be
Russian throughout no not Russian
bulgarians Bulgarian yeah and we yeah
and we they were you know all speaking
with accents of some kind of sort you
indeterminate
Eastern and and and because we knew that
they didn't understand what we were
saying when we
speaking we did kind of a mime improv
okay and at the Student Union right
student union and it worked and then I
have let's see after this I have uh
barbar
Smith okay krla Oz Sunday the 30th
Sergeant I played Sergeant Gary Croft
combat aogo
okay good good does this one exist
Taylor are these
all so much recording S I just
transferred all of David's tape so if
any these were the first recording
sessions drop pictures off at Blake
Blake I apparently I read for Blake
Edward for the party didn't get the
party I'm so sorry interesting uh but
anyway skip meaning I don't know what
that means but we here we were starting
to record okay Barb Smith W so may we're
in April oh beginning of may may may I
feel like I feel like I should ask since
you since you narrowly Barb
Smith since you narrowly missed working
with Peter sers did you ever meet him no
no I met his daughter remember uh
Victoria sers when she opened a hor
house on our street that's right I think
you have mentioned this before yes you
did but I never met never met him so
that was
like you do you know yes yes please
pleasure Fair pleasure on the seventh
now you know Dave Osman has a connection
to it because he was married to uh
Patterson uh I think that was her
married name after she left David but
her husband Patterson started formalized
started the the commercial pleasure
fairs but that was where we first
performed uh wedding for the electrician
or someone like him
and I see all of the the people I was
studying with with if this is indeed
correct with uh Honduras were there
suzu Diane big Sue John R John H etc etc
Brandon dlda and pet Fonda story meeting
11 recorded Sunday May 7 another day on
the 9th MH uh
meditation Cyrus's Place mhm ye Fair
cancelled mhm okay KLA Oz oh Dave Crosby
this was the day that David that that
Peter overdosed on
brownies Peter overdosed on brownies on
May the 14th Mother's Day Mother's Day
Sunday May
14th we were doing radio fre O show live
and and Dave Crosby was our guest oh my
God and and Brooke was there there Brook
Anderson and Peter had eaten too many
brownies and started crying no during
the breaks oh
no and so Brook drove him home and and
and Crosby said well The Wizard of Oz
has just taken off in his big
balloon so so Phil you and I will have
to carry on in the happy Old Land of Oz
and we did we we improvised and then I
have here Dave Oz man's kpfk on the 15th
don't know what that means eyes recorded
voice track mantras oh mantras and the
chakras and here we go the the mantras
and the chakras right yeah uh the uh cut
track from electrician a cut track from
electrician and then 18th here it says
recorded the first part of electrician
wow what dat it says the 18th of
May then I have dried to Pasadena in a
steaming G
and my car died oh no and I got a
haircut another haircut this is so
California if I can just jump ahead
three years when you were on uh radio
hour hour on
kppc there was a moment when Bergman
started this improv about uh being a a
drug taker a drug tester for the US
government he would he he started he
pretended to pop some things and Austin
says now you you're you're a federal
agent and you're in charge of the the
and Beren just cries and falls apart and
everybody is laughing their asses off
and this is why to to the guys in the
room this was so funny is because
Bergman was intentionally going back to
oh he was replaying his his meltdown his
meltdown I was a
big yeah you got to use your use your
art you know all right car hair cut then
I have Henry Jam's eating Affair I don't
know what that means but Henry jagam of
course I did his movie a safe place
Cinema midnight Midnight feet feet feet
oh I don't know I don't I don't know and
let's see oh and there's there's Barbara
again uh and let's see okay uh lots of
pictures here we go okay all right we're
busy again M uh Bob
Klein it's a Sunday wrting for the
electrician okay and it says into Gemini
we apparently moved into Gemini was
making notes of that album picture Mark
gotle Mark gotle did a oh that's
interesting there a couple there are a
couple of shots that right well I I I
can't remember but there are a couple of
snapshots that survived from that you're
all just wearing kind of kind of you
know
hipsh uh uh David's wearing like a white
turtle neck or something and you're all
standing by wall sounds like it but this
was the bunch of photos which taken were
later I found it writing writing writing
on the 27th of May the lovein yavas SL
Soviet poet there we go at alian Park
27th of May 1967 there it is that was
the I guess all the others were dress
rehearsals okay so the lovein at alian
Park was on the 27th of May 196 7 got it
yavas luu and the elid symphony
performed on the last Radio free Oz on
the
28th and then right right right I
recording music and then Peter leaves
now was that when he was going off to
Turkey to do his research on the movie
with Brooke oh it could be or that could
reference to it says didn't happen Okay
so that's probably referencing going to
KLA dropping kpfk I don't no it says
Peter leaves take car to Peter didn't
happen on Memorial Day why can't I
remember it all right Beach day good
great uhhuh recovery day Brooke had an
accident Volkswagon accident on the 4th
of June and we were
recording at at Oz recording at 1:00
a.m. I don't know what this all means
and then kpfk Grant Brooks and Dave
Osman I don't know what that means ah ah
Bill
McIntyre the theater of being Richard
Harris
party Bill McIntyre she let him continue
is this the party where he left the cake
out in the rain that's all I need to
know well I guess this is the first time
that we connected with Bill M so it's
Tuesday 6th June okay and here Peter and
Brook to Turkey ah on the eth Thursday
the 8th of June so they left on the
Thursday the 8th of June for turkey and
and the next day two days later I had my
aura reading and I have the tape of that
aura you do too cowardly to listen to oh
no I had I remember my lower chakra was
blocked but hey it still is it's all
right uh bu aren't we all built porch
don't know what that means okay what
else Ice Station Zebra okay uh I saw a
screening of Ice Station Zebra on June
the
12th now reason I'm laughing about that
is Ice Station Zebra yeah is that you
know okay I've been doing I've been
working at in pal
Springs uh raising money for Des Art
performs by performing old radio
Recreations of old radio shows and Ron
mesac and I have been recreating the
who's on first routine costell well R
this was Ron maac's big movie MH I stage
zebra which he talks about all the time
because he was working with uh uh uh oh
gosh famous now with many famous stars
and one in particular Rock Hudson okay
hson and I never realized that I saw a
screening of it I have to tell him on
June on June the 9th oh my God I tell
you the world is so amazing I'm pretty
sure we're going to do two episodes
today one is one is Phil's notebook and
the other
is it's okay this is great I love this
and then yes I was hired to go up to the
montere Pop Festival on the 16th of June
and to report live to
k rla radio yeah as a roving reporter
and we've got those air checks yeah oh
you do yeah I met the masas and the
Papas there okay uh what does it say
phon in report on the radio flew back to
to LA on the 19th uh wrote an article
for uh I what was it called City I I I I
was writing for the East Village other
at the time I think that's what it was
but I don't know it says something else
open City I I wrote an article for open
City uhuh Phil Oaks hanging out with
Phil
Oaks and here's another lovein another
lovein Wednesday June 21st summer sols
is lovein and did I play there the 60s
were awfully confusing Elliot mince
kpfk I guess that's where I first met
Elliott uh and then we had a a vday
press conference VD
Day I I'm not sure what that means
Friday the 23rd was VD Day okay
everybody checked each other for the
class every day I did another dating
game or maybe it was the first I don't
know Chad and Jeremy at o don't know
what that means uh another love another
lovein ladies and gentlemen on the
second of July second July
Sunday okay dinner with Les Brown Jr uh
day at home okay it's getting less busy
oh Jeremy's n
in see I told you was there are happy
times back there uh Jeremy's nude in was
on the 8th of July MH okay mhm and I
have Carol in parenthesis well you know
I do like that remarkably there's so
very few notes about what when you're
actually writing the album so in between
being naked and getting very high
somewhere you're not getting very high
staying staying okay very highing very
high staring very high all right now
this this is odd because Oz Dave Phil
and Phil that's me y uh 7 o'cl jacqu
dinner at
see this is this kind of little electon
little Electrical uh markings moving all
across the week of exactly sure what
what that means because those are
obviously lost days C and J Chad and
Jeremy MH 7 o'cl Oz okay we did the AZ
so 7 o'clock
Oz krla Oz 13th of July this is a
Thursday are we still talking is is Oz
still a five day a week
thing I guess it was and I guess I would
show up occasionally and then there's
the Fantasy Fair Fantasy Fair on
Saturday the 15th of July do you know
what that is no I was going to ask I
don't either all right all right Carol
and Kathy I know who Kathy is Kathy uh
here's Kathy let's see oh Kathy Coy
Kathy cozy yeah whoops where's Kathy
cozy she's in the car yeah there she is
in the car well in the car in the
gatefold ladies and gentlemen of the of
the uh how can you be album uh Nick is
in the car with Kathy Kathy cozy my
girlfriend is mine not a gatefold
version now know there's you only Kathy
with the K is there only okay all right
this is Kathy with the K so maybe and I
did the dating game again on July the
18th Jeremy all right Phil Oaks loveing
Rumble Jeremy Clyde Fiddler's for all on
Oz I guess oh there's Kathy with the c I
guess I learned how to spell her name in
the view Gary Usher is in town with the
contracts oh here we go oh my God Monday
the July for for electrician wow the
24th of July all right now what happens
then my birthday was on the 28 that's
all it says happy birthday birthday mhm
nothing okay uh the hate
tapes David away 30th of July the hate
tapes what are the hate tapes I don't
know noide IDE something for tayor we're
not going to be able to Google these ah
but here's Pastor Flash oh on August the
1st Tuesday August 1st it says
Shakespeare audition okay Bank call call
my agent go to the bank and Pastor
flash got rid of Proteus turned it down
oh I turned down a play okay 6 to1
electrician aha Thursday the 3rd of of
August of August then saw an
agent wrote the oh columia contract
contract Friday and Robie Shankar at the
Hollywood Bowl we saw a Robbie Shankar
concert on July 4th wow at July August
4th at at at the uh Hollywood Bowl and
the next day M Peter returned from
Turkey from Turkey H with a leg and a
piece and some breast all right then I
went to
uh let's see what this is another nude
in hippie I guess so always uh okay move
to Phil move to Phil Austin oh yeah I
briefly moved to Phil Austin's that's
right he lived in in Laurel Canyon as
did Peter nearby anyway and I moved in
with Phil and Anna Lee that's Monday
August 7th yep oh and this is the famous
interview with Robbie
Shankar at uh on August the 10th we
interviewed Robbie Shan car and
apparently we put the realtoreal tape on
top of the car and drove away no it is
the Lost Ravi Shankar interview what was
it what was the what was it what were
the contents of it what was your
fascination with it other than it was of
the time I'm curious now like what was
this interview like he was a
phenomenon and and his music was both
meditative and stimulating mhm at the
same time and he represented as the
Beatles later espoused he represented a
a blending of the East and the West the
cultures of the East and the West the
meditative culture uh the ancient
culture of India and the East China and
the rest and the the
musical uh
inspiration
of basically meditative
music like Peter used to play whirling
dervishes music on his show and Peter
was was in into medit meditation
meditative music from the very beginning
uh Peter's relationship to spiritualism
was I think somewhat
spurious but it was well-intentioned
yeah and uh and he did share that
cultural
uh Enlightenment with his
listeners and respected it and
interviewed people who really espoused
it so uh it was part of the uh New Age
awareness and the opening of the culture
to a more Global psychic uh and
psychedelic perspective okay which you
know it still influenced us to a great
extent all right back I was just look to
see how if you know how long that that
interview us says here farewell to
Phil's summer
camp oh he's going to go off and do his
uh it's 67 and he has to go off and do
army army oh Austin was in the Army too
both both he and Bergman were oh okay
all right pick up Kathy and go to
Jeremy's now Cathy's relationship with
Jeremy Clyde was that she had been in
England and it hung out with Jeremy
Clyde and and Chad and the Rolling
Stones and Donovan and his wife and all
those people and she was absolutely in
that scene and really introduced me to
that whole wonderful scene that's how I
got to know all those great people uh
this says Oz views the news on 13th of
August and uh last weekly show last
weekly show in answer to your question I
don't know if that means five days a
week or just all right let's see what
else happened here this is about the
time when we consider going to the magic
mushroom maybe let's see what happens I
caught a cold on the 15th of August
great all right let's see what else
dinner with Tom Clyde I don't know these
people meeting with Jeff gold at Kathy I
don't know any of these people call
cashes weathers beep no idea but here's
the number here's the phone number I try
it opening of Sirrus series Spectrum B I
vaguely remember that lunch with Beverly
no idea all right 18th The Jokers Jeremy
and Stephanie good luck okay 19th Jeremy
all right all good getting busy again
here here we go Bob Klein Bob Klein
became a very famous erotic photographer
okay and I think he's still doing
incredible erotic Sunday 20th of August
Oz we did the problem solver show oh
we've got that 28th of August got that
got got the last two hours of it good
and a
leback Phil's first
wife dinner at the Highlands Great uh M
2:00 to 5 fire sign sound effect session
for us do you see how casual it all was
yeah it wasn't like okay and we're going
to make the record no he like and what
are we going to do today oh we haven't
done the sound effects yet oh okay can
we get some studio time yeah sure man
you know who knows all right standard
radio I don't know what that means CBS
don't know what that means all right
lunch the universal Peter's place for
dubbing an interview okay fine uh
Kathy's birthday spelled incorrectly on
the 26th of August Kathy is now you know
married to John Sebastian okay and has
many beautiful children and all that uh
Jeremy Dy analie Kathy Carol Richard
Volkswagen rehearse scene H Don Schwarz
move to
enino Ah that's when I moved in with
Jeremy on the 29th of August and then I
did The Dating Game the next day
at so did you get paid to do the dating
game I have to assume yeah so okay like
an okay amount of money every Union
member was paid to do it sure yeah it's
great okay and it I don't know if I I I
don't know what happened there Sunday in
New York scene at Paramount
what 4:30 Sunday in New York was the
first movie I ever made uh and it was a
scene with Jane
Fonda in a rowboat passing by kind of
kind of with Jane fond MH and it says
here Sunday New York scene Paramount boy
I have no idea what that means there's
Bob Klein again okay getting near the
end of this uh
Volkswagen Furniture
Mar Jeremy returned Jeremy returned from
England I guess kpfk Katherine cozy it
looks like her handwriting yeah she was
in New York I guess so Kathy wrote in
her New York address she was at 135 East
61st Street and her number was and her
phone number is B B8 0894 Butterfield 8
butfield that was the old days when you
had Oz meeting and writing session Billy
James huh next day I sold my car so it's
like it's September of 67 and you are
still considering yourself the Oz fire
sign theater is what I'm seeing you
haven't taken out oh yeah right you are
right o in all these little little
moments okay ah on September the 11th I
was cast in who's happy I think it's
who's happy now who's happy Gordon
Davidson directing it Paul Aaron at the
aminon
theater wow
and and here we had another session from
2 to 5 oz Columbia Wednesday the 13th
session Wednesday the 13th and 11 I had
a who's happy rehearsal I was under
studying
wonderful actor's name I can't remember
and that's it oh no there's a a lost
week whole lost week seber
17 really higher really getting up again
on the 24th where I had two accidents oh
[ __ ] because of course you did two
accidents after a week like that Jesus
Christ and then there's more blank space
and then there's the Dylan
tape and Don Stewart who I just read an
a an obituary for
my God
uh car broke down first rehearsal Dylan
tape did you get another car cuz you
sold your car by that time I don't know
what car I was driving or who or if you
were insured Dylan tape I do
remember I have a tape
somewhere of Dylan being interviewed MH
and he is so
absolutely ahead of everybody there mhm
and you know and
so re revealed and so present and
so talented MH that it is amazing and
it's a realtoreal tape that I've got
somewhere I might have transferred that
and I don't even did you transfer it you
could I don't even know I I'll look for
it anyway and my car broke down of
course that's California all right here
what's happening here that was the the
the public notice of the free food at
the Hamilton the diggers rehearsal Randy
Kirby oh yeah well Don
Stewart the first television show I ever
did as an Entertainer was called Talent
63 on CBS Don Stewart was the singer on
that show uh uh I did a comedy song
called The Entertainer written by Johnny
Meyer and uh a magic Act was done
by uh oh God who was the crazy lady on
laughing with the the funny hair thing
oh Christ not Ruth Buzzy Ruth Buzzy okay
oh wow Ruth Buzzy and uh funny
heavyweight
comedian this is embarrassing Fatty
Arbuckle no not Jonathan no no no very
famous became very famous
he did an act a magic act her name was
shakuna and and what was his name did
Dom Dom deise oh Christ wow all right
Ruth buzy and Dom deise okay Dom deise
and what's her name did this crazy magic
act and that was part of talent 63 Don
Stewart had dated my cousin Barbara in
New York which is how I first got to
know him he attained Fame by playing a
major role in the SOA for for 16 years
MH and he had a magnificent voice and he
would tour around singing and Performing
when he had this great Fame which gave
him you know the opportunity to do it
and he died of lung cancer in Santa
Barbara and as I was going through all
of my stuff for my
book my
Memoir my fortune it's a thick stack of
papers ladies gent that is a very thick
s uh I've read it it's astounding it's
astounding I I can't remember it but
it's astounding I wrote it and uh and in
any event I found his autobiography now
this was a picture great that I also
came across which was a this time the
Nick danger time because this gentleman
here Grimm what was his first name David
Grim David Grim plays the organ
on on the record what I think we're
looking at here is like uh fall 69 and
you got uh and that's Jimmy guio jimmyo
in there too who created Chicago managed
Chicago there's a photo s our manager
photo session for the back of the single
yes uh forward into the past what it
called right and and we were in the uh
microphone room mhm when this happened
and then I have another picture which is
I think
it's later isn't it yeah that's like 7
you look when you look at Austin now
later so that's that's the picture
that's more pertinent to what we were
doing all right so let's finish out this
year I had two accidents great I don't
know what that means Dy and tap okay
rehearsal 10
to7 I still haven't written down the
name of the guy I was under studying oh
his name will come to me he's famous to
Las Vegas
fine uh on the 3rd of October 9 to 12
electrician Bergman work
on new playright series began oh began
work on the new playwright series ah yes
this was at the Mark Taper Forum MH and
because I was
understudying this
actor uh oh b b it'll come to me uh and
and they spotted me they said well we
can use this kid and some other stuff so
I started working in the new playwright
series uh with Gordon Davidson and oh
some other wonderful directors and
playwrights like Jules feifer and David
Mammoth and D Shephard uh I mean these
incredible emerging playwrights and I
got to work with my uh old girlfriend
Karen Black in one of them and a whole
bunch of other wonderful people anyway
and at the same time we were we were
doing electrician oh and on the 4th of
October I worked in the morning on
electrician you get Jack AR and I was
cast as Jack argue in Musa by John G
Jack argue is an anagram of John
G I had gone to Yale with John G and he
had written this extraordinary play
about himself really of trying to emerge
in the world of Vietnam and the
psychedelics world the crazy sexual
Revolution world and they had cast a
fellow named Joe RI in the the lead role
but Joe didn't have any background as an
Ivy League person and I of course had
gone to Yale so at lunch and I was in
the the chorus of
Musa along with Phil Austin M who was in
the Repertory company at that time and I
remember the
director oh oh I can't remember his name
so talented and John G told me to stay
for when they took their lunch break and
they offered me the part and it was
opening in like five days or something
they said you think you can learn it I
said yeah I can learn it I could those
days and I did and it was a great
success for me and it became a mainstage
production and we and it was a great
success and I worked with uh Sher North
and I worked
with go Champion G Champion's wife uh
who had worked with whose name was
what who had worked with danced with
Fred a stair and I met Fred a stair
through her I'm Sorry by poor old mind
anyway everybody if I can stop you
there's a collection of jnu plays that
includes Home Fires I believe Musa and
copout that I bought which is amazing uh
even just reading it if you're not see
seeing it being played even just reading
it it's extraordinary it's really um
it's like part of the DNA of fire sign
it's the age that age of a really
amazing absurdist comedy theater yeah
really was very amazing stuff uh anyway
we uh was his wife margerie beler then
margerie Champion or Carla Russ mar mar
Champion okay there we go Mars Champion
okay uh and I'm still trying to remember
the name of this wonderful director but
I'll I should have been better
prepared I'll never be better prepared
anyway we opened great success uh it
says rehearsal MTF and then 8:00
performance of Musa what was
MTF I don't know all I can think it's
Monday Thursday Friday but it I perform
and then says radio for question mark
and I mean my God busy busy busy happy
rehearsal oh my God I was still doing an
under study to for happy for the happy
thing holy mackerel how did I do all
this fire sign session oh my God
meditation columia Thursday the 19th of
October October okay I had my flu shot
on October the 22nd that's we had a fire
sign edit session on the 23rd of
October uh I rehearsed happy no I
performed happy at 8:30 Bill McIntyre
and Biff Biff Maguire Biff oh Biff a
famous performer at the time
Biff dear God uh next time I'll be more
prepared no let's see uh Halloween the
Oz Halloween show oh yeah yeah a long
standing tradition after that October
29th rehearsals for the S this is
definitely you're at the magic mushroom
I had a haircut on the first of November
opening night of who's
happy which I wasn't I was just
understudying that guy all right Oz
writing session if you ever scan this
and and and reproduce this it should be
called Phil's haircut book that's we
should call it an
accident Phil's haircut and accident
accident book all right Suzanne to San
Francisco great here's Cheryl again
Boon Cheryl Boon Cher Boon Harold height
Helen height and chery Bo okay now we
know travel to fres
tunnel to Fresno very important Sunday
the and I have a picture of that 5th of
November I have a picture of that last
tunnel to the the last tunnel to
Fresno okay the next day we did a tech
and Musa
opened uh okay who's happy rehearsal I
guess brush up that's for me understudy
understudy and for those who don't know
though the last tunel of Fresno let's
cuz again at the magic mushroom yes at
the magic mushroom right one thing the
the One play that we have a complete uh
script for but do not have a recording
of well we have 10 minutes of it but
you're never going to hear it because it
sounds like it was recorded on one one
mm tape in a Tunnel underwater in a
different state from an Edison cylinder
oh I remember that
session all right on the 12th we
recorded The Sword and the stone ah or
we performed The Sword and the
stone okay and on the 13th we had a
session for electrician rehearsal in
tech for Musa and I've opened Musa or
Musa or something how do we do all this
Musa Musa Musa seems like such a loose
schedule for doing electrician though it
seems is it is it just at your
convenience like how did it
go I can't tell I don't it was organic
yeah it was organic everything kind of
like flowed together yeah it was it was
there wasn't nothing was
formalized with the kind of of rigidity
that you know people think is required
to create art sure sure you know it's
really more has to do with the talent
the the focus of your talents uh as as H
my favorite line in Hamlet is the
Readiness is all whenever you're there
you're there and you do your thing you
learn from it you contribute to it and
you carry that with you and move on to
the next thing having had that
experience and that learning and that uh
uh gift yeah really reward now on the
26th of October we performed Phil's
November we performed Phil's Indian play
perfect timing for Thanksgiving that was
a Thanksgiving play right uh I had a
rehearsal for Musa says last time Ed
Peron that's the director okay Ed Peron
brilliant wonderful director I had so
much fun working with him who's happy
right at PE
rain riding at pets 8:00 both nights
Wednesday and THS P after rehearsals of
who's happy okay all right we're getting
to the end here December by the Light of
the Silvery aha Sunday the 3 December
the 3 and that was uh the UR material
for the giant ratra okay which we also
then performed as a little play at the
Ashgrove uh okay let's
see uh rehearsal Universal Darren
McGavin I don't know what that means how
is he reading with Darren McGavin at
Universal what was Darren McGavin like
the only reason I ask is you always hear
rumors yeah funny funny all I'll take
funny I'll take funny rehearsal of who
happy something with Jane drus who's
happy kpfk benefit December the 9th
Saturday the 9th oh oh okay so it's uh a
live show somewhere and we've got some
photos of that okay and I think you did
uh this is your trip yeah so Sunday the
10th of December it's marked this is
your trip so that's that's what you were
calling uh freak for a week freak for a
week yeah which we've done before yeah
so Sun Saturday the 9th you perform it
live in front of an audience and then
Sunday the 10th you do it again on Oz oh
okay good uh let's see what else write
at Pete's on the 12th reading o'clock
right pictures by John Rose o oh that's
good to know Thursday the 14th of
December John Rose photos I wonder if
that's that wonderful picture I have
with the nude and and the set of By the
Light of the Silvery I don't know I
don't know uh
right uh movie question mark what does
that
mean no no idea all right here we go
right in Phil isn't
here so he is we'd ask him he can't talk
end of who's happy
Oz 17th of December that's a
Sunday uh okay so had you gone seems
like he'd gone from daily shows to now
doing once a week is that what is this
what correct yeah at this point radio
for o was once a week Sunday nights on K
live from the magic musroom how long
were these shows three hours three hours
okay okay this is an interesting week
December the 20th it says 7:30 run
through run for your life mhm I don't
know what that means and it says Barbara
Hershey whom I dated
briefly and then the next day it says
Michael Bell and Jay Ward and Jay Ward
100 bucks 100 bucks was that when we did
the J Ward
commercials I wish I knew more about the
J Ward commercials don't we all yeah we
all did commercial for fantastic
cigarettes among other things with J
Ward we shot it at J Ward Studios where
the old moose used to be turning around
all the time Sunset Boulevard all lost
lost really just gone that's writing
Kathy's back good okay uh
party
uhoh
tape Sunday the 20 31st tape that's the
last at wood December happen it that is
1967 ladies and gentlemen I give you n
1967 he remembers it and he was there
what the and I wrote it down and I still
can't remember so run for your life TV
series from 65 to 68 oh with Barbara
Hershey with Barbara Hershey with Ben
gazara I was in it you were in it all
right well there we go so we've
explained that and then I dated Barbara
Hershey briefly after that all right
then well done I mean I'm just saying
what a cutie she was with David kerine
at the time who I also had a strange
history with I was for a second going to
say for I thought you were going to say
who else had a crush
on no okay I just thought i' check you
was a man's man no newon no n
grasshopper man's man now I also made
notes about
1968 next year mhm you do not have
another notebook like this am I
understanding correctly this is the one
I don't godamn my notebooks pick up
again in like to that's the year to have
one for I mean that's a that's a lot of
like that's a beginning of a lot of [ __ ]
and I'm amazed at how artistic I was you
know and all the well
happened in
1968 the USSR invaded Czechoslovakia the
monkeys were hot Martin Luther King was
killed the Civil Rights Act was passed
uh my lie Massacre happened Robert
Kennedy was
assassinated when we were performing
Pope Paul banned the pill uh wow
so stupid uh the cray Brothers the cray
cray Twins were arrested oh that's right
the White album was released the first
appeared uh and what's this oh yeah we
had there was an hbomb test color TV was
starting to catch on TV dinners were the
rage and what does this
say Pigman Mac I don't know what that
Big Macs big oh the Big
Mac could be the pig Mac who knows maybe
Big Mac Big Mac happened now so that's
when we were writing this album which I
think we'll talk about in a future I
think I think it might have to happen
but can I tell you this was great
because this is we didn't plan on this
but come on like that's I don't know
like it's it's definitely archival yeah
exactly definitely AR typical and
archival nobody is going to and I even
surprised Taylor I know I know our
archist
Jesus Christ now you got some dates I
mean put it on the arc were any of these
dates ever solidified in your brain
before now this is uh this is good stuff
I mean when I was I was really getting
into trying to spelunk Phil's history
probably for the first time when I was
doing the dear friends package and
that's when I that's when I found out
that he didn't have the the 1970
calendar anymore which would have God
damn it yeah um so yeah um getting dates
for these things is amazing yeah this is
that's making me very so hard that's why
in in my in my
Memoirs I I do like a disclaimer at the
beginning saying you know that it some
of these things may have not have
happened half of what I remember never
happened said Mark Twain what is reality
said the Fireside theater so I do a
disclaimer good you know what though I
don't know hey we've yeah we've proven
it's not all [ __ ] I was right it's
you know there's a lot going on here um
what I want to do two things um a I want
to thank both of you for doing this cuz
this is always fun we will I promise you
you people at home we will do this album
I promise it'll happen we will do the
album um Taylor thank you for archiving
you kidding like that's huge I they just
threw [ __ ] at me that they saved and I I
I took some notes on it thank them for
saving it I would love to see this
scanned but I mean that's honestly I
mean that should be should I put it in
the in the stuff for Taylor hey buddy
hey um uh so okay let's let's do a
little bit of promotion stuff at at the
very end here uh go to Firesign
theater.com there's not fire sign
theater re I'm correcting I just make
sure you know that it's theater with an
re not an ER oh but can't you also find
it I think we set it up for an ER Nick
danger comes on and chastises you and
says I spell my name re y yeah but but
we really should have put in theater
with an
e but we didn't do that a son of a [ __ ]
well what $12 get yourself another just
go ahead buy another do oh okay and
since we're promoting things you can
still see me and Jamie Aloft doing uh
Boomers on a bench yes okay with that
cat as a guest star hi Kitty hi Kitty
yes uh boom is on a bench just Google
Boomers on a bench we're on Facebook and
we shot four more for of them uh just uh
two days ago MH and uh it's slowly
growing in popularity because it's so
weird I mean it's like you know Bob and
Ray for the 21st century two old guys
sitting on a bench but we will be
performing live again at The Tutor House
in Lake Arrowhead as part of the
American Parlor song book radio show
syndicated throughout the country uh uh
JP hon and his wife Julie vanen uh and
uh
and we are uh contemplating the next
step in what we might do with this
particular uh venue I'm also promoting
at the time my participation in elron
hub's Battlefield Earth oh yes Wow audio
book 47 and half hours holy of audio
book oh my God
150,000 sound effects Jesus Christ 67
actors already you know we're sweeping
the awards yeah already gotten a dozen
awards for for acting and production and
for the longest thing ever yeah and it's
it's really fun because you you it's
it's not the movie right okay right the
movie is in your mind and and these
people that I've been working with over
there at Galaxy press they really do
know how to do audiobook production M
and when I the reason I first got
involved with him besides the fact that
I was a science fiction fan of harb's
writings was that I saw that they cared
about production and that they were
doing Foley and that they were doing you
know original sound effects and they
were doing an original musical score key
yes you got me let's let's play that's
wonderful so I did scores of voices for
their uh first Audi book series which is
basically the Golden Age of Pulp Fiction
and then my dear friend Jim mesan
directed this Monumental production and
cast me in a couple of fun roles that's
so you know it's just just the way it is
uh in movies I have a film out now I
don't know where it's playing it's
called The Love addict okay and I play a
kind of a a central
more anchored role uh in this sex
farce uh and it's it's an interesting
film and a fun film so uh the love love
addict is what it's called if you see it
somewhere go and support it it's you'll
enjoy yourselves and uh beyond that I'm
working my butt off uh putting pictures
into where's my fortune cookie that's
right and I'm enlisting the help of this
genius to to make the book uh Prof usely
Illustrated good I'm excited as we said
and also uh I am working on a proin
Bergman script book called Power which
is the
transliteration of uh our our absolutely
brilliant uh radio series back in 1991 a
great piece produced by Ted Bonnet for
uh the heat uh NPR series with John
hackenberry and I'm telling you
returning to the material and hearing it
again and transliterating has been an
absolute joy and I'm I'm finishing it
for Peter cuz he and I were working on
it before he passed away okay and after
a period of mour I said got to bring
this to light yeah it's morning again
the sun will rise on this great project
and you will also be able to get the uh
64 minute uh uh CD or download of the
show that Ted It produced that's great
and I'm also then going to to
transcribe uh a a uh Cabaret version of
americathon really which is the version
that was witnessed by uh Neil Israel who
had directed me in tunnel vision and who
said I want to make this into a movie
yeah and uh I despaired of ever being
able to do anything with it although we
have some tapes of course of the shows
but uh I found that Neil had done a
transcription of our performances and
it's a big old script but I'm going
through it and transcribing it and I'll
as as it reveals itself to me I'll see
what format I can put it in yeah but I
have a contract with bare Manor press
for both power and for americathon wow
so those will be the next projects that
will come to print cool at the beginning
of next year uh I'm and David Osman is
working on a project for them for Bare
Manor press which combines the scripts
of the
Odyssey uh saucer which he wrote with
with Phil Austin and what's the other
one well those are going to be hopefully
combined in a sort of Dell double uh in
the uh double OB verse where it's a two
front covers uh saucer and odyssey
combined in in one book and then David's
finishing up the fighting clowns story
that's it the fighting clowns in
Hollywood so extraordin story of our of
our writing years doing these things for
which as he said he he decried to me
there's no pictorial evidence that we
ever did this right right cuz we were
basically sitting in you know offices
writing we were over at the MTM Studios
really David who we called the colonel
at the time was sleeping on the couch in
in our Studios I was going through my my
first
divorce yeah I think it was my first
divorce oh my God what tumultuous times
and we were writing this really funny
[ __ ] you know which should have become a
movie yeah and could have become a movie
if they had CGI right in an instant sure
oh yeah but anyway maybe somebody will
read it and go hey we should make this
now of course all so the next thing I'm
doing yes I'm flying to Maryland on the
5th of July mhm and I will be performing
in a three-part PBS historical series uh
the story of Francis Scott Key after the
song okay uh it's being it was created
by and is being directed and produced by
a fellow named Phillip J
Marshall and I've been cast as in the
role of The Eccentric Senator John
Randolph of Rowan Oak who spoke with a
very high voice for all of his life
because I had some kind of a disease
that created AR rested development his
voice never changed and he could never
grow a
beard okay so they're going to have to
do some heavy makeup on this boy I'll
tell you that and he was very flamboyant
he would show up on the floor of the
Senate uh this is on the beginning of
the 19th century uh 1800 to
1833 uh in in uh uh uh riding
clothes uh high heeled
boots riding boots and and Spurs a
riding whip with his two white Afghan
hounds at his side who were controlled
by his lover and his favorite slave
Juba wow and he'd Harang them with his
shrill voice for eight hours sometimes
for the vast causes about slavery
against slavery and how to deal with the
change
should they colonize them and send them
away or should we integrate them into
our
society and he was working with you know
all these extraordinary men of his time
he was in a duel with Henry Clay really
where he where his coat was was shot a
hle was shot in his coat but they both
were gentlemen and they didn't kill one
another H clay like to shoot man oh they
all like to shoot oh it's so tragic if
you listen to Hamilton I can't afford
see to see it but I've been listening to
it just makes me cry while I'm driving
which is probably dangerous but but you
learn again how many of their sons were
killed in these senseless duels and then
Hamed it himself oh awful awful time but
anyway I'm really looking forward to
this it's being done in an interview
format okay with Recreations awesome so
I get to recreate the duel with Henry
Clay but basically I'm going to be
interviewed by by Philip Marshall as a r
Faith M as a ghost so I've returned from
the dead for this interview and I'm
aware of that yeah and I'll be talking
about my life from my perspective all of
which is drawn on all the historical
writings of all the people involved and
I tell you it's going to be fascinating
it will be aired during Black History
Month in February of 2017 that's great
and it fell into my lap because of my
dear friend Gary Sandy who was the boy
toy on WKRP oh sure and Gary and Melinda
my wife and I have done many many many
radio shows live radio performances
together become very close and he was
cast as president uh Andrew Jackson oh
perfect if you go to the website Francis
got key after the song you'll see a
picture of
him all decked out you know as Jackson
with the little glass and everything
brilliant he looks brilliant well the
guy who was originally supposed to play
my role dropped out and so Gary so Peter
philli said Gary who should I get for
this he said Phil Proctor Phil Proctor
not only does he have the same first
name as you but he could do he'll he'll
act circles around this you'll love him
and it turns out that philli knew the
Fireside theater perfect and he said
Phil Proctor the Fireside theater he
said yes yes so I called him up Bingo
got the job wonderful so I'll be going
back for that and I'll be shooting on
the uh uh 6th and the 7eventh in the
studios in Maryland Baltimore Maryland
and then I fly back to I fly to
Connecticut to join my wife and her
family for a memorial service for her
darling mother Shirley who passed away
last week about three days shy of her
90th birthday wow wow so there will be
one hell of a celebration with the seven
siblings and all of their family that's
how you do it wow and it's worked out
just beautifully that I'm doing this gig
in the east
coast that's wonderful so that's what
the little busy boy is up to right
now um I guess incidentally then people
can follow you at Firesign Phil on
Twitter I could yeah I I suppose
although I don't contribute to Twitter
that much it's better I guess to go to
Planet proctor.com there will be a new
edition of Planet Proctor released on uh
Independence Day July 4th all right okay
yes and uh other than that are you
present on Facebook I have a great
presence on Facebook I would I would
recommend if anybody wants to follow me
even though I can't befriend them
because I've reached my limit uh you can
certainly
enjoy my posts and my wonderful crazy
friends posts by just seeking out Phil
Proctor on Facebook yes Taylor do you
want to promote yourself anywhere or do
you want to just stay quiet well I've
been perfecting Fusion oh [ __ ] shouldn't
have said it Taylor Taylor this is a
secret I don't have uh you're on Twitter
you're very funny on Twitter thank you
you used to be followed by Stephen Fry
before he quit Twitter again oh that's
true no maybe I still am maybe that that
account is just a a Dead Mystery account
he's just following more and more people
Sid fud on [ __ ] has moved to Los
Angeles I haven't seen him okay I know
somebody who's who like Co I just found
out recently a friend of a friend like
co-created the show he's on and I'm like
well how do I now meet him because this
needs to happen yes uh anyway I don't
know what you guys are talking about an
old British homosexual uh wonderful
gentleman what do you mean isn't that
aim moronic uh good question I I'm
British am I am I gay are you British am
I gay everybody's gay but only in the
sense of happy oh some of the okay this
is a long discussion that we could have
I'm sorry you can't have that word back
we've taken
it uh you can go to stol and.com for all
of our [ __ ] go to lookingforward
movie.com where you can see my political
mockumentary sequel yes uh that is now
at about 5 hours long if you want to you
want to talk raw footage so much good
[ __ ] ladies and gentlemen thank you so
much um well thank you guys for
listening and watching and as always
have a good thing
[Music]
comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
five-star rating and a nice review you
can find us on facebook.com/ Comedy
onvinyl Twitter at comedy onvinyl and
find everything else at comedyon
vinyl.com
[Music]
Jason clom here uh I'm of course running
for president for 2020 and 2016 this is
a blog or video blog or Vlog or V blog
this is Bobby hober Clint Westfall Derek
melon welcome to Fire and range with
your pal trip Markle Harry I'm Rea blur
where Trace empan CEO of Phyllis Masters
Rebecca Penn you may know me as the
poison pen Kyle Frank figure for my
inaugural oh God Alex Parkhurst here
welcome to long to cook my name is to
Long Scott Apple can we vote in 2020
2020 being prepared is the essence of
being uh of having prepared looking
forward Hope war which is available
exclusively in paperback because hard
covers as you know are elitist Define
quit for me it is with a heavy heart
that I enter the campaign again pleas
please please tell me the truth you're
not you're not fooling me are you
where's the where's the nearest airport
welcome to
I'm I'm a Onan improv show what happened
with the
campaign nothing it's gone Kanye West
has decided to run for the presidency in
2020 and I really wanted to just kind of
wait to announce you know that I'm back
in the race which uh here here I am I
guess it's official I'm back in the race
we are now getting ready to hire our
first intern and then you died like
theoretically I would move up one step
closer you know I'm sorry are you
assuming you would be the vi my vice
presidential candidate as as my intern
one of my client's kids is going to is
kind of backrolling his campaign
Magnetic Tape is what the whole
cinematic experience is all about dun
we're going to paare this with Coca-Cola
what's the point of overthrowing the
government right if there's no Earth
left to live on you have to have
an ID it's ridiculous we need to know
who you are in order to camp this guy
over here with his leather come on
really guys did you clean up the mess on
the floor what mess on the floor I I
produced the uh The Real Housewives of
Madison
County very very sad if people in Africa
eat this uh they die Master Vapor that
piece that got to the bottom of like
hula hoops being anti-semitic that was
groundbreaking it's called in the line
of fornication
my editor is very excited about it
[Music]