[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
podcast okay the year is 1968 it is the
album yeah it is I'm sorry I'm so sorry
did we not I'm having an acid
flashback 68 okay the album is waiting
for the electrician or someone like him
the artist is a fire sign theater and we
have a quarter of that group right here
again Phil Proctor thank you for being
here again wait a minute I I am a
quarter you are a quarter but I'm not
worth a plug nickel anymore okay so so
how many times is your face on this
album cover let see one we this was an
album cover we didn't have any control
over really okay and it's called a naive
collage
uhhuh uh and you know cuz they didn't
know who we were sure and we didn't know
who we were were and so they made this
naive collage I REM I vaguely remember
the the uh photo session and and of
course I I distinctly remember the
clothes because we were all uh hippies
at that time and whatever that meant I
mean you know hippies invented them we
weren't Bongo playing you know
turtleneck black like we weren't beats
no we weren't beats we were we were
hippies but we weren't hippies we were
we were uh we were all educated and
clean Yeah clean educated young men
shoes had proper radio voices we had
radio voices we smoked pot you know I
mean we we embraced the the cult the new
culture the the youth culture and uh and
I remember part of that was the clothes
yeah you go out and you look for the
coolest clothes you could find and uh a
different clothes you know you have to
wear ties and coats and things so we're
all wearing our Our Kind see we have
things around her necks little things
and I and cool yellow glasses cool
yellow glasses those are good yeah yeah
I think I I think Peter Fonda turned me
on to those in fact and Austin's in
these great white pants yeah I know yes
white pants and Osman he's he's only
wears a well both Bergman and Osman are
still wearing their Square you know
glasses but uh but that's okay the minds
behind the glasses were certainly not
Square they
were elliptical or something oh I just I
God I was the
baby the papoose the lower left hand in
the lower left hand corner I was the
papoose so anyway naive collage and then
uh these interesting strange things on
the the other side uh but it was okay
and at the time that we did this correct
me if I'm I'm wrong we were managed by
uh Fitzgerald by Jimmy guio who was the
manager of Chicago
among other acts and a fellow named
Fitzgerald Larry Fitzgerald I think his
name was was our particular manager
person who of course Bergman destroyed
by removing his stomach or something I
mean I remember he finally just stopped
he says I can't do this because we were
four hippies we were
unmanageable you know Fireside theater
if if it ever had found someone lion
tamer or something who could have
managed us I think our career would have
been uh quite different uh but in any
event here we were surprisingly making
our first
record and I can tell you how I I
believe I became involved in this uh and
I'll try to get it right as opposed to
the last time we talked about
it because it's interesting fewer
elephants this time please interesting
uh and if I repeat myself uh and you
want to compare it to the last time it
might that will be interesting too it'
be like a three-dimensional chess game
you know did he move the pawn that last
time over here we'll just edit out those
parts of your brain which are no longer
correct Taylor jessen our archist and a
wonderful producer uh uh is uh here to
help keep me on track if you will so
here I go uh I had come out to Los
Angeles in a musical comedy called um
the amoris flea which was based on moer
school for wives written by Jerry Divine
who H had was a writer who had worked on
Gang Busters on the radio he's a radio
writer and he had adopted this into a
absolutely Charming funny musical my
co-star was Aela de Martin I was working
with Lou Parker who was a f famous vaud
villian and a wonderful actor and seal
cabitt who uh was a great
farus and uh uh Jack Fletcher who was a
wonderful funny gay actor in in the
musical comedy
tradition it was a wonderfully cast
piece and great fun to do uh and and
later Frank Parker when we came out to
LA who was on the Arthur Godfrey show
it's like the ten on the Arthur Godfrey
show he he took over one of the roles
and I got to know him so I had loue
Parker Frank Parker seal kabat who was
married to uh oh a great comic magician
big tall funny comic magician uh name
will will come to me later famous on T
on television all the time anyway it was
a great cast and we we settled in for a
run at the Las palus theater in
Hollywood mhm uh I didn't know how to
drive so they put me up at the mono
which was where all the the actors would
come in who were doing uh roles in in
television shows it was a it's still
there and it's a a hotel with kitchens
and you know your rooms have kitchens
and I was walking distance from muso and
franks so in the morning I'd go and have
a flannel cake at muso and Franks and
I'd hang around Hollywood and then I go
do the show and uh melli was right up
the street afterwards we go to melli for
drink and everything was very successful
uh but in the middle of the run when we
were kind of going like yeah we made it
we're settling and I had by then I I
moved into an apartment on Vista delmare
which means a view of the
sea
no and then later up Beachwood Canyon I
actually because we were going to settle
in for a run okay I'll get a nice little
house apartment on Beachwood Canyon
overlooking you know the I can see all
the way down to the ocean
the Hollywood Sign yeah just above the
Hollywood Sign below pardon me the
Hollywood Sign so I'd say the Hollywood
sign and all of Cal and all of Los
Angeles and then I get a phone call from
my agent in New York Lucy croll agency I
had auditioned for a musical in New York
called the time for singing uh and out
of like 2,000 kids who auditioned for
this they chose me and it was they
wanted to do a a reading of the musical
next week on like
Monday and they want you to be there and
they'll fly you there and everything and
I said but I show I'm and no one to
study so it was like horrible and it was
my my first but definitely not my last
uh uh contact with conflict in this
business oh my God the conflict you know
talk about being in two places at once
and you're not anywhere at all you if
you could be in two places at once
you could have a hell of a career in
this business but you always are having
to make a choice should I do this guest
starring part in this television show or
should I do this commercial which might
mean a lot and the times that that we
all make bad choices you have no idea y
but occasionally make a good choice and
occasionally you know you made the bad
choice you see the other person it's
like well look at them all that success
oh look at them so so anyway uh I
my agent resolved
it my producers found a replacement for
me and I was able to fly back to New
York and do this musical time of singing
which of course was a wonderful musical
based on uh a mining disaster where an
entire family is wiped
out how green was my valley beautiful
beautiful book beautiful movie MH
beautiful uh musical Alexander con
producing Gerald fredman directing uh
George Hearn was my old one of my older
brothers uh Shaney Wallace and tessio
Shay a legend of of Irish and English uh
musical comedy uh White Hall gang stage
stuff a wonderful cast iore Emanuel
wonderful people and uh a a beautifully
mounted expensive musical Ming Cho Lee
did the sets which once ran over over
one of the dancers patty melt no Mound
Patty Mound what's her name Patty Mound
ran her right over because he was moving
around with the big wall and I like
Patty m p she should have been named
Patty Mel we on Broadway or off bro on
Broadway on Broadway and we we uh we had
the whole thing we went out of town we
we tried it out in Boston there was a
huge fire in Boston I remember being on
the roof of the theater watching this
fire during intermission with the some
of the chorus girls and uh and at that
and then uh G Champion came in and he
was our our doctor he helped doctor the
show a little bit I got to meet work
with him and we had lines going around
the block they loved the show because it
was both heartwarming and heartbreaking
music was great and uh uh and then we
opened and we and the main reviewer
Frank rich I think his name was
something like that main review didn't
like the show New York New York Times
didn't like the show MH and so Alexander
Cohen brilliant producer uh was going to
do a great publicity Blitz with all the
good reviews MH and there was a
newspaper
strike and that was the end of the show
oh my God end of the show suddenly
nobody was coming to the box office
because they might have read that review
or they didn't know it was happening and
they know and and there was no such
thing as word of mouth in the way that
there is now you know it there was no it
would it nobody could tweet or you know
or Facebook how wonderful what great fun
they had at the show what a great show
it was and the amount of time it takes
for the word to travel in New York and
things already closed there been
something else that's already closed so
we had an adamated run did this all go
down in two weeks six weeks something
like that something like that two we you
guys have your uh poster up at Joe Allen
gosh I don't really know I don't know
all all the good ones that closed early
are well then then we're there then
we're there and we did do a cast album
oh a cast album we recorded it and uh uh
which was wonderful so you know a lot of
good came out of it and and it was a lot
of fun for me but then I thought well
what the hell am I going to do now so I
uh I connected up I see if I can get
this right but it seems right right I
connected up with a a a girl I'd met
when I was hanging out with Brandon dlda
and Peter Fonda uh in in
Hollywood
uh around this time okay and was that
when the Sunset Strip rot happened
November 66 that was yeah 66 so that was
when I came back oh that's yeah we've
got we've got to the bit where you you
sat on bergman's face okay yeah okay so
it's like November of 6 is when you
start sitting in on Radio free O Okay 65
yeah okay so here's what happened yeah I
got it now okay the show closes forget
Diana do we get to her later it'll be
worth waiting for uh with a teeth like
that Jesus Christ
oh please she she invented electric
clothing but that's another story
so the show closes I immediately get
cast as Brandon to Wild's understudy in
Evan Hunter's
uh comedy and I Ed the word Loosely a
race of hairy men which was his attempt
to explain that there that there was
going to be a youth Revolution not
terribly
successful and uh so Brandon and I who
had been faded to meet because I'd been
asked to understudy him when I was a
child actor and he was a child actor in
a play called Mrs MC thing which starred
Helen Hayes back in the ' 50s I guess it
was or maybe even the late 40s I don't
remember uh he I understudied him and we
became friends just like that and he was
a head he loved to smoke P so after
rehearsals we used to go up to a
dressing room at the Henry Miller
Theater I think it was where we were up
in to a dressing room in the top of the
uh uh theater and we turn on the air
conditioner and we smoke pot and get
stoned this is the air conditioner that
did not work no it wasn't that we we we
discovered at the end of the run that
the air conditioner was sitting inside
the window that's right the window the
window wasn't open so it was just
circulating the smoke right like good
stuff no no we were we in this this
malestrom of smoke so anyway we became
great Pals it was not a great success
this play and it closed but Brandon and
I uh had had a friendship he had married
a girl
uh who was the sister of one of my
classmates at Yale Susan ma was her name
really cute little girl and he had a
bengi uh and I used to go up to his
apartment on the west end I guess it was
and uh smoke pot and hash and and he he
was trying to reinvent himself as a
musician mhm and uh and he was a good
musician he could sing so he was he had
taught himself the guitar and so he'd be
singing all the time and I'd sing along
you know fun uh and and I met all kinds
of interesting people like Graham
Parsons uh and we used to go and listen
to the international submarine band all
the time with grah Parsons and all these
other great musicians and uh it was a
very interesting little New York Life
that I had
[Music]
boy I'm tired of pushing West how long
ago we leave Goan about two hours ago a
we ever going to stop quite down boys
wagon my fellow
settlers we stand here at the edge of
civilization on the banks of the
Mississippi River looking West at our
destiny what may appear to the
fainthearted as a limitless expanse of
godforsaken wilderness
is in reality a golden opportunity for
humble God-fearing people like ourselves
and our families and our children and
the generations are coming to carve a
new life out of the American Indian
welcome white brother engin dra the
wagons up into a circle why you always
do that we get better reception that way
do you mind if I put this antenna up on
Yonder Peak that's our sacred Mountain
this is our sacred antenna it's shaped
like a cross made out of aluminum uh got
any aluminum and then he said uh he
wanted to go out to to resuscitate his
career in the movies and so I had uh
taken driving lessons when I was doing
the amoris flea because you can't walk
in Los one night I tried to walk from
one place to another and I practically
was asphyxiated SM almost carbon
monoxide you know and there's no
sidewalks that's the thing that gets me
one of my favorite lines from La story
like I watched that as a New Yorker and
thought it was funny and then I moved
out here and I realized it was Art and
it's just one of my favorite things he
picks her up and drives three houses and
then stops she goes well that's it
couldn't we have walked and
then are you
crazy you move Los Angeles around the
letters and it spells legs on sale or
sale on legs for that matter as opposed
to Manhattan Woody Allen's movie
Manhattan where he runs to her apartment
you come about oh man so anyway uh so
Brandon and I drove across
country uh to come out to LA and that's
where we met up with Peter
Fonda and that's where we got involved
in the Sunset Strip Riot and that's
where I sat on Peter bergman's face and
that's how the fire sign theater started
all right
so uh we he were basically just doing
radio kpfk and again I'm going to call
upon uh uh Taylor to help me with this
uh and we became
successful uh the fire sign theater
became a very successful part of Peter's
radio Frias show and uh he did the first
lovein during that
time and I played a Russian character
called yavas luu which means I love you
Russian Uh Russian poet and was part of
all that Madness and uh
we I think we we we improvised together
at
UCLA in in the Student Union doing uh
this uh a crude early version of waiting
for the electrician yeah improv might be
right what I've got the earliest like
fire sign flyer that I've got is from
April of 67 and it's it's Peter Bergman
and the Oz fire sign theater no no no no
no it was not advertised as Oz fire fire
sign theater it was the Bulgarian yeah
Bulgarian players players in Exile in
Exile yeah but it was Bergman plus plus
yeah so that's how they were marketing
it everything that we did on the radio
at that time was as Anonymous as
possible okay because we we all now all
who are we uh Phil Austin uh David Osman
Peter The Wizard of Oz and myself uh all
met at uh kpfk realized we were all fire
signs which was bizarre and uh and and
found that we had a knack for
improvising together and playing
different characters this radio was
perfect so the
anonymity of it was more important than
the identity as the Oz fire sign theater
or you know an ensemble of players sure
so uh that that was part of that
mystique and or mistake if you will and
and so the Bulgarian uh improvisational
theater in Exile whatever it was
performed uh appeared with Bergman who
was the the draw and we
improvised uh a a play called waiting
for the electrician or someone like him
most of which was in mime because of
course we're bulgarians we don't speak
English to good and uh and then after
that no here we go now I have to figure
this out well like in April you've moved
to krla by then yeah I that's right we
moved to a commercial station AM station
yeah and were we doing the magic
mushroom at that no that's not until you
didn't do it live from the mushroom
until September so you're still in a
studio like somewhere in Pasadena until
September still pretty Anonymous nobody
knows your faces yeah except the people
who come to see us perform live cuz we
did at the magic mushroom no no this is
before the magic mushroom yeah yeah
nobody really knew who we were uh and
did we get a uh did we get the offer to
do our first album before we did the
magic mushroom well this is the part
where Austin drops from his uh from his
Cloud into the room and corrects us all
and says no no fire sign was mean
bergman's idea apparently he went with
Bergman to a dinner with Gary as
and Gary wanted something okay Gary user
was a producer at Columbia and Phil
Austin had worked with him in the
astrological album right and didn't he
do a comedy album called Duckman or
something yeah the single Duckman single
duck man so Usher was tangentially
through
Austin uh uh connected to Bergman and
they had a dinner and he wanted Peter to
do an a radio fre album okay and Bergman
said oh no no no we're going to do the
Oz fire sign theater album okay and
Usher said
okay which was The Fall of the House of
Usher and and so we a a deal was
percolating now I guess I know I went
back to New York so I think that what I
decided was my career is now going to be
out here yeah and uh I had become
estranged from uh uh uh uh Brandon
because Brandon was a uh there's a name
for somebody who smokes pole a Viper he
was a Viper he really loved to smoke
people under the table and to me that is
never the that was never the purpose of
of smoking pot yeah or hash because then
you you can control your hive yeah you
know uh is is that the point of any drug
to win I know same with alcohol
same with alcohol you know you drink so
you're happy and I mean then you switch
to soda water or something yeah when it
turns into a unless you're an alcoholic
or a Viper you know which case it's like
I can get higher than you can you know
yes and and and it's fine because
Brandon was a Sweet Soul and a wonderful
person and bright and funny and and
happy but but I would become dull and
and dazed you know and it wasn't fun
anymore and so we we kind of drifted
away does the idea of getting the album
or the album coming up is that what
feels like the career is about to happen
here's what happened that's my question
this is what happened I ended up living
with Diana du and and we had a a lovely
Affair together and at a certain
point I knew that it was over and that I
had to go on with the rest of my life
and at that very moment when we're
having this conversation the phone rings
it's for me it's Peter Bergman and he
says Phil there's a first class ticket
waiting for you down at Black Rock which
was Rockefeller Plaza CBS building
whatever uh we want we need you to fly
out because we're going to write and
produce our first record and all we have
is the title waiting for the electrician
or someone like
him I said
okay off I went yeah and uh and I I was
living then in Peter's house he had a
house in Laurel Canyon and David and his
wife Tiny were living there
too the house had like an
upper walkway or something an upper
shelf or and we we slept on this shelf
well Peter the house was downstairs and
and his girlfriend Brooke as
melian we're we're downstairs you know
and we got a picture of Brook somewh oh
and I later I later got together with
Brooke too and we had we had some time
to together right whatever picture you
have is not as good as the one he's
thinking of that's the thing that I want
to see and and and uh Phil was living in
Laurel Canyon married to anal and who
was in English girl uh so he would come
to these writing sessions and we sat
down and we started writing and it was
the first time that we we wrote together
really because we were just basically
improvising I've just got all of David's
Radio free Oz archive and I'm digitizing
some of these reals from magic mushroom
era for the first time yeah boy and
you're talking about the fact that you
give a line away at at one point from
the album and you say oh shouldn't give
that away yet that's on that's on the
album so this is this is awesome in the
middle of the time when you're like
writing and recording the album somebody
uh they I can't remember which line they
quote but David quotes a line and then
recuses himself oh you haven't heard
that line
yet well uh the the the the contract
that we
had allowed us to record at Columbia
Records in
Hollywood uh at Columbia squ mhm and the
studios that we recorded in were old
radio Studios oh so good they were
Studios that you one of the studios was
was a audience Studio that I think Bob
Hope had performed in among you know and
and the another Studio where we recorded
forward into the past which was our
single about oldtime radio was a classic
uh radio Studio of the 40s 30s 40s it
had the control room had one of those
slanted
glass oh yeah Acoustics oh the Acoustics
were brilliant I mean and and it was
cozy you know and it was just like
dripping with uh memories I mean you
know and and and extraordinary to to be
dropped into that environment cuz all of
us of course we're radio babies we grown
up listening to the radio and loving the
radio uh when I was in New York
because of my dad's connections with
things I went to radio shows fairly
regularly I sat at in Arthur Godfrey's I
saw Arthur Godfrey's show my God but I
was in the in the uh sponsor's Booth to
see it awesome I went and I saw uh
Archie Andrews at Rockefeller Plaza NBC
NBC Studios uh full audience you know it
was like a theater performed that they
performed it in and I remember the
actors coming out with umbrellas because
it was supposed to be raining in one of
these scenes who that's cool you sudden
I went oh it's radio but woo you know
and and uh and of course in New York
because my my mom and my dad who both
could have been actors they were both
extraordinarily handsome people
beautiful PE my mother was very very
beautiful and she was like a more
beautiful Angela l B really and my dad
was a very handsome leading man type and
he he was kind Robert Montgomery but
more handsome and both of them could
have and would have pursued a career in
theater and films but at the time uh
their their parents wouldn't let them do
it you know and my dad in
particular uh was his father Robert e
Proctor who had been a state senator
Ator would help to expose the klex clan
in Northern Indiana wow he was a state
senator in Indiana and and a judge and
later became first started as a railroad
engineer I have a lot of railroad
engineers in my family then onto a judge
state senator and then his own private
law practice he wanted my dad to be part
of this law practice my dad was an
Outdoorsman very athletic and and uh
uh naturalist a naturalist at heart and
he had gotten into like I think it was
Arizona State University his father went
down and literally dragged him out of
there and put him in Notre Dame where
he'd gone to school where my dad went on
to become the president of his class but
he was damaged by that sure and and then
he entered my his dad's law firm and
eventually got out of that and went to
New York and became part of mcnut long
Co Proctor and Lee now mcnut
Paul V mcnut was the former ambassador
to the Philippines very powerful man and
he was a Democrat like my entire family
on my father's side and uh was going to
run for president and he wanted my dad
to be his Vice Presidential nominee so
be to rest up before the convention he
went on a cruise and during that cruise
he had throat
irritation what's this came back is
diagnosed with throat cancer and died 3
months later and my father's political
Ambitions were quashed after that
although he remained active in
Democratic politics in New
York uh for most of his life but uh all
of this background led me to a point
where when I was suddenly engaged with
the fire sign theater I had had all this
tremendous
experience uh in and and I was a child
actor at the age of nine on television
live television in New York as well and
I had an excellent education at Allan
Stevenson School where I learned to play
the violin and I could sing and I played
female role female leads in all the gber
Sullivan Productions so I you know I had
the stuff and and my parents supported
me because they were they would have
been delighted to have done the same
thing and they were all musical we all
sang and harmonized together my mom
played the organ she we had an or Oran
in the in the house and so there was
music and entertainment uh we lived at
139 East 94th Street and uh in apartment
6B and in apartment 6D across from us
was a fellow named Max Gordon who was a
Broadway producer and owned the Village
Vanguard and the Blue Angel Jesus okay
and so I would go over to parties there
and I'd meet Henry Morgan Margaret
Hamilton which
which of the West uh uh oh you know I'm
not even sure how many famous people I
met cuz I was eight or n years old you
know but but again we were in this show
business environment the St Club you
know Frank Catra I mean we saw all these
great entertainers Broadway shows you
know Mary Martin in P South Pacific and
you know and I mean I and and uh Anie
Get Your Gun and okoklahoma
and all of this so I had this wonderful
wonderful exciting background in all
this stuff and that's one of and and I I
was I was absolutely delighted to to get
into Show Business it was easy it was
fun why is it that you're drinking Timmy
me boy because it's bad for my Hollow BS
I got a chance to see things in real
black and white I despise electric pink
you know Dr Tim is Keeper of the Sacred
tablets yeah have a tablet
[Music]
oh nice paisle
horsey give the nice horsey some sugar
[Music]
cubes well Dr Tim everyone's gathered
for the daily Miracle here's your
microphone ever since the son took
LSD it's been a fundamentally better Sun
more pink and green electric
blue let's hope it comes up again
today here it comes he's done it again
it's coming up it's coming
up it's pain uh and uh so with with fire
sign what was different about fire sign
was nobody had to hire me I could
control it I was in like this little
safety zone working with these great
guys and now we'll get back to Colombia
and we're working in these classic
Studios with Engineers who are basically
uh state-of-the-art Engineers for the
time and one of the the jokes that uh
one of well I should say jokes one of
the the funny things that happened was
when we were recording this album
MH we we we we went out for a break in
the Columbia building and they were
taking out old sound effects uh uh props
to throw away no no no no God marching
men wind machines little
doors we're going to throw them away and
we said no no had we we need these
and that's when I started my career as
Darth Foley you know how much how much
of this did you get away with what the
stuff yeah oh we they gave us
everything throw it away and the door
that we had ended up with Stan freeberg
really because of Fred Jones this ZIP
into the future here so
anyway this album uh we we didn't have
we didn't have the contract that we got
later because of a fellow named John
McClure I'll talk about about that but
at this album we were just you know like
spoken art actors doing something
different yeah uh with comedy but nobody
had done anything like this and we
hadn't really ever done anything like
this right because we weren't doing the
magic mushroom but we all knew when we
wrote the album that we were going to do
a radio show that unlike anything that
had been done before we're going to do a
soundscape and and we were going to and
we and and we could design it any way we
wanted and of course so there's the one
long story waiting for the electrician
right and then there's the story the
three little pieces on the other
side not that we designed it that way it
just was organic and it happened that
way yeah we were writing about the
topics that were uh in the culture at
the moment that we were a part of that
interested us and that we could parody
yeah cuz we that's what we were doing on
the radio we were parodying we were
insiders slightly parodying the the very
culture that we wanted to be a part of
you know and wasn't there kind of a
pressure overweening everybody you have
to have more than one cut on one side
you can't have oh yeah all of the
designs all of the design remember we we
were revolutionary in the sense that we
wanted to create like a story on one
side no you can't do that you know you
have to have little
things because basically you know uh uh
other other than certain isolated story
albums like the the crepitation contest
and things like that which came from
Canada right uh or the bozo records or
you know Adventures for kids and stuff
like that for the most part comedy
records were recorded routines right the
best of the recorded routines uh and and
they'd last as long as they lasted you
know cut cut cut cut cut and and they
were designed to be played on the radio
if they could and all that stuff fine
but that's not what we wanted to do and
uh uh and and luckily because we had
this understanding management company
behind us Jimmy guio and Larry
Fitzgerald uh they volunteered it was
almost
magical the there was a day they were
working with an orchestra for something
for Chicago I don't know what it wasn't
Chicago but an orchest
at columia and they brought us in and
they they orchestrated and and played
recorded some pieces for this album
Amazing you know the D the traffic thing
they recorded these Transitions and all
yeah all this crazy stuff where did that
how did that happen where did it come
from I don't know because we were all we
were just like part of this of this
magic we were we were in the in the
stream of this event that was happening
I think
Jimmy
understood what we were trying to do so
did Gary Usher and they liked it and
they said this is this could go
somewhere this is interesting this is
like they're a band you know they're
they're making comedy music they're a
band and and they brought their
expertise to that and supported us in in
ways that absolutely totally surprised
me yeah I didn't and yet at the same
time it it was expected it was kind of
like muh yeah yeah you know this is what
we want to do and we're doing it and and
they're helping us so it must be right
right there were no barriers to what we
were doing did you do was it sort of
like was there ever we're just going to
do this or did you ever say can this be
done or you just assumed we never said
done it was it was we were we're going
to do radio on record yeah and we're
going to make it interesting enough that
you'll be able to listen to it a lot of
times you can listen to it again and
again and again it's not going to get
tired you know uh and and of course one
of the predictive things about this
album and this title which Bergman
basically had come up with because he
had an experience in Amsterdam when he
was researching
LSD uh and and
psychedelics uh with the fool which is a
group of performance artists and
musicians who later Allied themselves
with the Beatles had had that one elet
and did a lot of artwork for the Beatles
yeah uh painting their limousines and
things like that uh he was up on a roof
smoking something and uh there was a
blackout in the city and that's where
the idea of waiting for the electrician
or someone like him to get things going
again huh became a part of you know he
tells the story on one of these on one
of these um radio freeas in the fall of
67 and it's like he tell he says that
first line out loud we're all just
waiting for the electrician and somebody
but I can't remember his name next to
him or someone someone like him yeah so
it wasn't even all his his initial but
what's what's so startling about this
is that main story is about an Eastern
European country mhm that is in the
midst of a revolution yeah okay
and that really happened first in Poland
and
leesa was one of the main uh forces in
that Revolution and you know what his
job
was he was a ship's
electrician it's amazing oh yeah there's
a lot of amazing stuff that that has
happened like that so my memories of
actually making the album were pure fun
yeah and uh the recording sessions David
actually did I think both David and I
took movies right of the of the early
session was that where that happened I
haven't got any home M well well anyway
it was it was easy and fun to do it and
and then we had the great pleasure
because we were producing it mhm uh you
know I mean we were the creative
producers sure Hands-On producers we got
to mix it I was that was my next
question actually okay and that for me
was a complete Revelation now when I was
at Yale from uh
58 59 to 62 something like that my
scholarship job was editing a program
called Yale reports uhuh and that's
where I learned tape editing ah and what
I did as he well knows was that uh they
had all these famous people Henry
Kissinger and Poets and writers and
critics and know all being interviewed
for this this half hour radio show and I
had to cut it down to 27 minutes or
something like that so I would take out
their uh Speech impediments the you know
their their Habits Like s and us and
butts and pauses and repetitions my God
and to to get it down to time after out
certain phrases and things that had
already been highlighted to be removed
wow uh and I kept them
all oh no and so at the at the end of my
semester i i i i i over the course of
the semester I edited I've been editing
them together on a real and I and the
ultimate result is called Yale distorts
and it's on one of our albums it's it it
ended up being you opened one of the
dear friend shows with and it goes
things like you'll hear you know the
hostess says so Mr Kissinger how did you
feel at that exact moment when you had
to make the decision well you know that
the it was it it was a and and the uh
but but the the well you know let me try
to say if I could and and you know it I
don't but uh so and
that and so it's made up of all those
wonderful rhythmical it's the way
politicians actually speak now and and
also what's so interesting is some of
them there's this guy with their French
accent where I got my old French accent
from he was a teacher of mine he used to
do things like yes but but but you know
but but but but so you know there each
one of them had a different kind of an
of a speech pattern yeah it is
absolutely a classic early tape I mean
it's it's cult it's culture jamming from
from the' 60s and it's themed it tells
us
it tells the story it starts to go off
on the sex tangent yeah I edited it
together oh yeah and oh no we should cut
that out you know like that I should I
have to listen to it again I have the
original tape somewhere but of course it
probably break to pieces if I unless I
bake it you know uh so uh uh we we did
this album MH and we went we mixed it
and the mixing was four guys at sitting
at the the the mixing board uhhuh
you know our our engineer would help us
now remember at that time we had how
many tracks
107 you have four oh really four [__]
think of that it was four than eight 16
and we were pioneering
multi-layered tracking right so what
would happen is we'd fill up our four
tracks and then our brilliant Engineers
one of whom was named
Dremel drel Dr ml dribble uh would would
what they call pingpong they take the
two tracks two of the tracks that we
done sure put them on the other tracks
somehow and clear the two tracks so we
can put more stuff on okay yeah yeah
okay that's brilliant and yeah it was
and it allowed us to to uh uh realize
our audio
Vision if you
will and uh uh and uh uh evolve it
during the you know during the course of
of our mix and everything later of
course
they the tapes became much more they had
more tracks on them 12 track tape for
instance and made it easy for us and
then I remember was so funny to me the
the reels got bigger and bigger and
bigger till there like a hundred tracks
and the reels were big the tape was like
you know like a
lasagna no no more little thin things
big things to take and you had to take a
machete to cut it you know and and and
then it all went away it became digital
everything went away it's like it got so
big and we were getting smaller in
relation and then suddenly we were all
small yeah everything was small uh but
but during that time the the pleasure of
being able to mix things in to take a
track that we laid in which was you know
like an A A Walla track a background
track where we all could not help us we
always saying funny things right do you
like
horses I have one I don't mean to cut
you off but there's one thing that stood
out to me and it's the craziest it might
be the longest piece of backward masking
in an album ever yeah in the airport is
it the airport or train station my
brain's not working right now what is it
the election the electrician piece the
first like four minutes of that where
it's you you think you hear the
background of airport yeah that's what
it sounds like but it's backward masking
the entire time yeah you know what's
happening there that's taken de directly
from one with the Andre jman uh sound
effects records from like
6263 what happened in that original
album which they L later recycled
endlessly and dear friends they had
somebody page
Andre you can't hear it on the fire sign
album because they they like Mosaic it
out somehow okay yeah so every time they
say his name
it's is that what I'm hearing that's
what they were doing at that point [__]
yeah well see that's which is Goofy I I
really I really should have listened to
the album before I came in but my but my
life is so full of of stuff that's
happening now of course it's really hard
to go forward into the past right that's
why we're here to do
things I apologize that hard drive that
is what you missed earlier was the two
qu back and theyve only recently met but
this is IPA and fire sign of
the the fire sign theater created a um
an opportunity for people to coales and
to you know to to meet one another on an
interesting intellectual and emotional
comedic level uh to this day it happens
I did a play reading uh uh a couple of
days ago and one of the
uh people who was there is the head of a
local Jewish theater this is this is a
play in which I play David Irving MH a
holocaust denier ahu and and all
everything I say in this play he's an
Englishman is in his own words from his
books and his lectures okay it's
extraordinary and he absolutely is a
Believer he absolutely believes in what
he's an historian he wrot of these books
and he basically says that AST is a
fraud you know and he proves it's
impossible to burn that many bodies and
you know where the piles of coke that
they needed to to fuel the fires and
anyway so I did did this this wonderful
interesting Play It's called stubborn
things and trying to get a production of
it in town which I think they should and
by the way there's a movie coming out
about David
Irving which I know only a little bit
about but so this this because the
reason is that he
was publicly um humiliated in a court
case uhhuh because David Irving has such
an immense ego that he was he uh sued a
guy who wrote a book saying that he was
a
fraud all right to to you know to to uh
protect his reputation and during the
course of that trial he was of course
revealed as a
fraud interesting how a trial can do
that manipulating information and doing
you know dude did not not learn about
Oscar wild so fascinating story uh and
anyway one this one guy uh fire sign fan
he comes up to me afterwards he says I
can't tell you he said you changed my
whole sensibility about comedy you got
me on the path I went on and blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah and I said okay
write me a
check and and and it's it's very
comforting and it happens all the time
in surprising ways you know when I was
married to my my second wife barbar
singson and I was in Oslo for the first
time and we went to the m Museum the
scream Peter Bergman right the
picture help me out of this head that's
right help out of
head so we're standing looking at you
know the scream and there's this lanky
guy and this hippie girl next to him and
and I've G I'm going oh oh oh he's going
to say something to me and he comes up
he says excuse me far sign theater and I
go
yes and it was another one of those
International connections where I went
oh my God what a wonderful effect you
know we've had on
[Music]
people comedy on vinyl is a production
of stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit ness.com to listen
to our other podcasts read our blogs
read our tweets watch our videos and
read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
f-star rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook.com/ comdy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedyon
vinyl.com Jason clown here uh I'm of
course running for president for 20120
and 2016 this is a blog or video blog or
a vlog or of a Blog this is Bobby hober
Clint Westfall Derek Mendelson welcome
to Fire and range with your pal trip
marle Harry I'm Rea BL
we Trace empan CEO of Phyllis Masters
Rebecca pen you may know me as the
poison pen Kyle Frank figure for my
inaugural oh God Alex parkst here
welcome to uh learning to cook my name
is to Lear Scott Apple can we vote in
2020 2020 I don't know being prepared is
the essence of being uh of having
prepared looking forward hope more which
is available exclusively in paperback
because hard covers as you know are
elitist Define quit for me it is with a
heavy heart that I enter the campaign
again pleas please please tell me the
truth you're not you're not fooling me
are you where's the where's the nearest
airport welcome to I'm uh where I I'm a
onean Improv show what happened with the
campaign it's nothing it's gone Kanye
West has decided to run for the
presidency in 2020 and I really wanted
to just kind of wait to announce you
know that I'm back in the race which uh
here here I am I guess it's official I'm
back in the race we are now getting
ready to hire our first intern and then
you died like theoretically I would move
up one step closer you know I'm sorry
are you assuming you would be to V my
vice president candidate as as my intern
one of my client's kids is going to is
kind of backrolling his campaign
Magnetic Tape is what the whole
cinematic experience is all about duncle
we're going to pair this with Coca-Cola
what's the point of overthrowing the
government right if there's no Earth
left to live on you have to have an ID
it's ridiculous we need to know who you
are in order to camp this guy over here
with his leather come on really guys did
you clean up the mess on the floor what
mess on the floor I I produced the uh
The Real Housewives of Madison
County very very sad if people in Africa
eat this master Vapor that piece that
got to the bottom of like hula hoops
being anti-semitic that was
groundbreaking it's called in the line
of fornication my editor is very excited
about it
[Music]
hey there and welcome to fire in range
with your pal drip Markle now there's
something I'd like to discuss with you
today concerning eco-friendly gun rights
right and that's biodegradable Weaponry
the government uses uh a lot of plastics
chemicals oils and we really need to
refocus our efforts towards things that
are more
biodegradable now that candidate I was
talking to about Jason clam has spoken
against us on this issue not only is he
considering a lottery for gun ownership
and that includes biodegradable gun
owners but he's also said no 100%
absolutely no personal ibds improvised
explosive
biodegradable devices and so we just
thought we would whip a little something
together to send this uh Mr clam a
little hello from Vermont say hello
Lance hello that's a hello from Vermont
we took
ourselves 100% biodegradable cloth
diaper filled it with naturally found
Goose crap Lon CRP my crap Lance's crap
just a touch of nitroglycerin a Mentos
and some Diet Coke and we buried it B
there in the backyard so there you go Mr
clam a little bit of a hello from
Vermont oh boy okay well uh this has
been fireing rain your Mar