[Music]
I'm Jason clom and this is the comedy on
vinyl
[Music]
podcast at one point there was this this
Vietnam War veteran that I met who told
me probably the most chilling story
about being a fires sign theater fan now
fires sign theater records were sent
over to n as children's
records and so this guy was working in
like the radio there found it and said
oh my God you know listen to it oh oh my
God and he was he a pothead and he told
me this story he said in N there were
the Alis and the heads okay and he said
one day we're out in a bivaak and uh I'm
all the guys are sitting in this this
half track this truck uh ready to go out
to wherever the hell they're going and
me and another friend of mine were lying
on top of the truck on the canvas uhhuh
getting high and they are all drinking
beer and they hit a
mine everybody in the truck was killed
because their spines were compressed by
the explosion and the two guys were
thrown up in the air and landed in rice
patties oh [ __ ] and survived oh oh my
God I said you so we saved your
life Wow who would have thought that you
know comedy record could save your life
my god wow because because what the
record did for him was it affirmed that
he was different and still smart and
funny mhm you know that he could be
different there were other people who
were different sure so and that's what
I've heard from almost everybody who who
got that yeah the high the High Altitude
bombing you know uh High attitude
bombing the fact that we you know that
we we could uh we were on a level that
certain people got and other people
didn't it went over their heads High
attitude High attitude bombing uh and
and to and to this day I run into people
in all in all various walks of life and
of success and things that that tell me
about it and it makes me very happy yeah
I got to ask you this when you were in
the process of writing electrician what
exactly what you're talking about is
what's hitting me is that this is
American radio theater mixed with a
heavy new American Theater and European
avangard theater and when you were
putting this thing together is that
something when you were trying to go
from point A to point Z in electrition
the long piece yeah that was something
you were specifically keeping in mind or
you just trying to make yourselves happy
and that's something you all had in
common no Taylor you're absolutely right
it it was something we had in common and
I think it it could be best expressed by
our admiration and love of the Goon
shows yeah uh the Goon shows for those
who might not know it uh were a
surrealistic r was a surrealistic comedy
radio program that went on actually for
quite a long time through the war
English yeah British on you're doing a
couple voices on this album am I not
mistaken there's a
solid by the goons and the goons
included Spike meligan and uh Peter sers
and Harry seeum yeah there there you go
the Goon shows he's holding up some
books of the scripts the Goon shows
right and if you don't know the go shows
Google them and listen to them they're
they're amazing and there's never been
anything like them frankly fire sign
theater was inspired by their surrealism
their extraordinary inventive use of
sound effects their the the the the the
far out musical uh uh um musical
expression of the
characters with with voices that were
exaggerated and yet uh char
characteristically identifiable in
amazing ways very cartoony I guess one
could say but surrealistically cartoony
like Mad Magazine at its best you know
and panic magazine so that surrealism
was something that zany silly surrealism
was something that attracted us all plus
the fact that they tell a story yeah in
a half an hour uh Peter got to work with
Spike Milligan in in London in uh
working on something called not so much
a show moreal way of life if I'm not
mistaken and uh uh and I unfortunately
never got to meet Peter sers
although her her do his daughter had a
uh a bizarre uh impact on my life
because uh Heidi F she was Heidi F's
best girlfriend Heidi fle The Madam of
Hollywood remember oh I do so Heidi F's
girlfriend uh bodyguards dog ate my
bed and wow and this all happened
because I don't need to hear any more
sentences in my life those words have
made the English language have Justified
the existence of the engl anyway go made
my head hurle
it see see Ivan NJ uhuh who was later uh
uh punished for being a bit of a pimp
himself married Irene Sue who was a
beautiful Chinese American actress uh
who was the wiki wiki girl on The
Campaign on one of the gas station
campaign okay where they had the
wikiwiki islands where you get your gas
on the Campa I please don't ask and and
I I met her like everybody else in my
life through my first wife Sheila Wells
who knew everybody and we used to go to
these parties at Genie Martin Dean
Martin's uh uh uh ex-wife's place where
I met Elizabeth Taylor uh Ringo Star uh
David Bowie uh Natalie Wood uh recogniz
no they're all wearing masks Jack Carter
all the comedians uh I mean everybody
everybody met everybody and among those
people I met Irene and then she married
Ivon uh and uh they live I live uh in
Benedict Canyon and on the street right
over is where they lived on Hutton Drive
they lived on that street and here's why
this all happened Irene Sue when they
got divorced stayed in the house and
became a real estate agent and she was a
friend because of Ivon of Heidi
fces and so she rented a house on our
street which was uh rented before that
by a guy I went to Yale with a director
I went to Yale with and before that by
the producer of the fire sign theater
movie
Zachariah who still lives across the
street from me because he's had three
houses and he was the Larry cubic was
the manager of Arnold
Schwarzenegger and I have a picture of
my wife barbar being lifted out of a
pool by IR oh my God and before that
this guy named uh Sylvester
Stallone okay who actually lived on our
street for a while too later because the
the top of the street there is a
compound that was owned by Kirk Koran
one of the wealthiest men in the world
MGM MGM Grand MGM movie studios and he
rented one of his places to Sylvester
and Sly used to like to drive really
fast down our crummy little Street and
complained about it so karian built us a
street for
$500,000 about 12 years ago with a flood
control Channel and everything so that
Sly could drive his little car fast down
the street you know it's all it's in my
Memoirs I mean how do you how do you
explain these things I I'm
crying so Sylvester Salone ate your bed
no no no Sylvester my bed but but uh
when we were having work done on our
house uh we were expanding our house up
into the hills the inspector was also
inspecting s's house because although he
was renting it he was doing
renovations and one day that the guy
comes down and he's got he looks like
like the cat that ate the canary he's
got this funny little grin on his face
and said well what's up Ed you know he
says well I was just up at Stallone's
Place actually had a kind of a western
acent I was just up at Stallone's place
and he says uh he hired his Scenic
designer to do all of his interior
Renovations and and he said it's all
going to fall
down and then we had an
earthquake and it all fell down and
that's when he moved to Miami you
remember but we had our street so we
didn't care you know all right so so
where the hell am I let's go back in
time
now uh uh Holly it's all right they're
speaking Chinese we we do that's right
yeah yeah right we we do
this and uh uh and and we were able to
be as totally free as crazy and zany and
surrealistic as we wanted to be because
who knew I mean who cares uh we weren't
thinking commercially right we were just
doing what we had already been playing
with and and were having fun with and
had and all of us kind of had this
agreement that this is what we should be
doing you know uh none of us thought
we'd be where we were and or given an
opportunity like this or be paid to do
something like this amazing and to be
given that much Freedom yeah oh my God
it was so exhilarating uh so I gladly
kind of
surrendered a a a normal career to this
adventure yeah and yet once we sent this
record out of course nobody really knew
who we
were and so it had its effect but it
wasn't
until uh the uh uh what can I call this
the the emergence of FM
radio which was the the lucky thing that
happened happened at the same time we
were doing this making stereo records
suddenly could be played on the radio in
Stereo wasn't just you
know and not only that college stations
could play because they weren't
commercial they could play a whole side
of a record yeah yeah yeah and that was
revolutionary suddenly people started
listening to it also the the kind of
stuff that we did was the kind of stuff
that made if you were listening if you
were listening to the radio and suddenly
fire sign theater came on you went
what's what's that cuz there was never
anything like that on the radio before I
was going to say I mean you're not just
mining the goons were you you're like
actively Eugene unesco's in there and
John gu yeah these are these are people
with and yeah and I I did at the same
time that all this was happening Phil
Austin is wife and Lee were part of a
Repertory company down to the Mark Taper
Forum MH and I was still I still had an
acting career and I had a good Agent out
here and everything so I got in a play
uh uh at the Mark Taper Forum under
studying a role MH
and they found out kind of like you know
oh he's good and so they pulled me out
to to be in this uh what they call
Monday Monday Mondays at the taper it
were there were short plug
by new playwrights like uh Mammoth and
Shephard and G and one of the plays was
called Musa no I did that in college did
you did you play Jack argue no I wasn't
argue I was his roommate well okay well
I was Austin was my my roommate uh so I
was called to be part of the
company and at one point uh at lunch
break I could see at Peron the director
and John G kind of in conference and I
knew John from from
Yale and they said Phil could you could
you
stay for you know during lunch and I
said sure and I said they're G to
they're going to ask me to do this role
they're going to give me the role and
they said Joe RI who' been doing it who
was fine but he wasn't he he wasn't uh a
y he didn't and it's all about John G
it's about his Yale experiences things
like that his is east coast Elite Yale
thing sure and and that was me I at
least I knew it m and so they asked me
to do the rooll and it was like four
days to opening and he said can you
learn it I said yeah sure I could and I
and at that point I could you know big
role too big it's got huge monologue
yeah huge monologue and and we worked on
singing the penny you know Peron and I
worked that out and I performed that on
local television later and everything
but it was a natural fit for me and and
I really you know took off with it and I
got to work with uh and then it was so
successful they made it a mainstage
production wow so I got to work with
Sher North and uh later Chase uh Barry
Chase who was g
Champions is that right let me just say
well Fred of stairs partner uh somehow
connected the GU Champion to married to
him at that point maybe I don't know and
I met I met Fred AER through Barry Chase
he came to see the show and he came up
the dressing room afterwards I was so
thrilled and there was this sweet little
man there this little man hi oh my God
FR is there you
know and and you just want to take him
and pirouette him want a pouette that's
tapped together as so anyway it was it
was a great thrill and really fun and
Austin was in the Repertory company now
you did the scene where he where I
commit suicide or he commit suicide I
commit suicide yeah yeah I'm in the
upper bunk he's in the lower bunk we're
putting on clown makeup uh in in N yeah
well he you played Phil Austin's part
wow isn't that wild that's so cool it
was so cool that I was working with
Austin in this thing too so so we're
kind of this record is out there and uh
and and and we had a contract for only
that one record so our contract's coming
up and it's like you know well what's
going to happen just talk to your father
he's groovy yeah I like pop well then
baby how come we find you in a classroom
today why weren't you hanging out in the
parking lot relating with the rest of
the kids and teachers I I don't smoke
can I go now yeah do your
thing hold it leave those books
here Malcolm X John Lennon come on in
and dig your mother oh mama I can't now
I got to go do my homework I I I mean I
got to meet my connection you can't fool
me you're in one of those underground
study cells aren't you no it'll kill
your father I didn't breastfeed you for
14 years for this come here baby but Mom
I'm not hungry straight Nick do yourself
a favor be groovy now sit down turn on
and tune in the TV but Mom I don't want
to watch television oh you're so
weird and now direct from The Paisley
house on Capitol Hill man we take you to
the Gathering of the tribes which is
already in session a fellow named John
McClure at uh uh Columbia who was in
charge of the spoken arts division MH he
went into a meeting and he held the the
album up and said you can't you know
they were going to drop us he said you
can't drop the guys this is they're
Geniuses this is they're they're going
to go on and do wonderful things we've
got to you know they're they've got to
be our artists so he said here's what
I'll do I'll offer them a spoken Arts
contract which will have a reduced
royalty but they won't have to pay any
studio time all right so that they
spoken art so they can go in and they
could you know work on a on a different
Rhythm and by God that's what they gave
us wow you got a [ __ ] around contract
that's fantastic and that's that's where
we beautiful and in in our this was it
the second album uh let's see no how
could you be into place who once was in
danger and all that we did we talk about
that last time we'll talk about that
another just just bits but uh that's
another I mean that's another all
incredible yeah story but yeah ask me
anything else and I'll see if I can my
my two big questions were a I'm not
mistaken those are goon voices and B the
backwards Mast but you exped some of it
I'm still a little confused as to the
backwards masking cuz it was it it's it
only sounds like it they're just
weirding I don't know what literally
what they're doing maybe it could simply
be something as physical as picking up
the tape away from the heads at that
point we did do we did do a lot of that
stuff because we you know we they didn't
have the sophisticated
computerized sound systems that we later
were later developed so we would do
things like when we did on Boo's I think
it was Boos we did Thunder electronic
Thunder I'd have to go up to the echo
chamber room and bang physically on
whatever those things were you know that
that created
that with my fists you know and and uh
and of course part of the fun and the
challenge of all of that was uh being
asked to invent uh ways sound effects to
invent sound effects
and both both that I got a lot of that
stuff also from going to um Hollywood
toy store really yeah because they had
they had a gun for instance which was a
I wish I still had it a replica of a
M13 or with a a tape Loop of a of a of a
gun on
it I use that many times but I would
always seek out whatever elect
or electric sound effects toys and
things were out there I think we hear a
lot of these in in uh Mar in January of
68 when you do a life in the day as a
magic mushroom show you're doing fake
commercials for cartel toys that's right
that which led to a a dwarf and remember
I found an electronic bird you
know I have one of those you have one of
those yeah I do it was a Christmas
decoration but it does that exact same
thing you're talking about what happened
to the the stuff that you rescued from
being junked uh we we kept it and used
it for a long time until you know I
guess we but as they say uh the Nick
danger stuff I bet you came in real
Handy oh yes oh yes and and and later in
our stage shows we built special stuff
to you know approximate it to make fun
of to allow the audience to have fun
with seeing sound effects uh and and
Stan freeberg as I said because of our
association with Fred Jones who was one
of our greatest engineering production
collaborators uh he also worked on
Stan's albums they engineered Stan
albums and and it ended up in Stan's
office and in Stan's repertoire that's
amazing my God yeah so who in cuz this
is out of like all of and I love all of
your guys albums but this one is is I I
there's something about this one I just
think is just perfect and it's one of
the ones I heard early it wasn't the
first one but it was one of the ones I
heard early and it it's really amazing
because even though the first side is
three different tracks it's all one
bit Loops into the next right after the
atom bomb comes it goes right into
smoking The Joint right I mean it's
there it's seamless so I mean like even
though it is three tracks it's still
it's a side a and it's a side B it's
this side right you're right you're
right they that was something
which I guess we all agreed on early
that that even the albums the first four
albums are all connected one to the
other to the other to the other uh a
quad rology and and and and I think that
was part of the extenuation of that idea
which again nobody had ever really done
before no I mean they were musicians
were just doing concept albs you know
and to think like a non-m musician could
make or especially you know a comedian
could make something that's non you we
actually were hired to work on the birds
one of the birds conceptual pieces which
was what do you remember what it was but
draft morning I think so and then later
Chad and Jeremy's uh uh cabbages and
Kings uh and
and because I had a girlfriend named
Kathy
cozy uh who's now been married to John
Sebastian for decades related to Patty
mou by any chance not related to Patty M
make sure uh uh she had been John
Sebastian who wrote the uh theme to
Welcome Back Cotter that's right if I'm
not which starred another girlfriend of
mine Mar oh wow
actually it was after Kathy cozy that I
took up with Marcia
stman gets
around I sure
did it's in the
Memoirs I'm sure so I'm excited for that
so
Kathy had been in England and she knew
it's how I got to meet MC Jagger through
Kathy uh we when they were mixing uh
cabbages and no pardon me Goats Head
Soup I think it was here I was sitting
in on the session with them I have some
of his clothing in my closet still
please it's so weird so anyway but but
getting to know Chad and Jeremy Jeremy
Clyde and Chad hanging hanging
chad they we we ended up sharing a house
together Jeremy and I because he was
living in this big estate in enino owned
by Dr Adolf the
radiologist and there a dog out there
neighbor's cat that's a gray cat I could
probably let her in no one's
horribly she's vocal very vocal I love
it uh so
so let her in so Jeremy uh oh anyway
this is like a 4 acre estate in Nino
with a tiki bar a flaming fountain that
ran down all the way down to the bottom
of the staircase big an ape cage
and limic side swimming pool and a bomb
shelter it's where we kept our pot mhm
sure and
uh that place became you know a a a
harbor for hot and cold running girls m
and no cats we didn't have any cats no
no and and Jeremy and I were still
friends I see him when I'm in London as
often I can and Chad and Jeremy have had
a great resuscitated career uh and been
touring all over the place you know with
their big
hits uh so there was another benefit of
of all of that you know these
friendships and people and everything oh
God and it was through through
Jeremy that I met shiron mccan shiron
her name was Sharon at that time one of
the girls who was living with us uh and
really cute little blonde from
Atlanta and uh many years later well I
don't know if I should get it of all
this we can get into it next time yeah
if you want we can save some things I do
have one question about bside I have one
question go back to this who Who's
Playing Lord
kitner and did all of that coughing
happen in one
tap and did he do it in one tap that is
insane
and like this is how sad and like kind
of like a sad freaky fan I am I've tried
doing it to see if I can because you
know like it's just to see if I without
trying to ruin it just to see if I can
make over he's I mean like when he gets
to the end he is heaving Berman it's so
impressive sounded like somebody
actually fell too I how much physical
acting was going on far as me just
that's one of my favorite that's what's
great oh he broke the glass yes yes yes
now which I think that that was all part
of the first live the first live take
well you know when when we started we
wanted to do as much of the production
live as we possibly could okay because
first of all that was what we knew
remember we've been improvising on the
radio live all four of us sure and and
and we all came out of some kind of
theater background remember I met Peter
at Yale when he was writing the lyrics
for two musicals I starred in written by
Austin Pendleton oh yeah Tom Jones and
Booth is back in town M and uh so we all
came out of a theater tradition even
David you know not as much as Phil whose
mother taught acting at Fresno State
University that's amazing so Peter and
Phil and I had a a a theatrical
background David had somewhat of a
theatrical background but when we worked
together we wanted to to use that energy
uh uh when we were recording yeah and
then we would add overdubs and sound
effects and things later because we we
had solid tracks solid lead tracks and
and uh uh and and our and our energy and
our chemistry was you know on the on the
record yeah my God you know again that
cat is it's perfect we're talking about
sound effects and we have a cat the
best hi Kitty look at this big old guy
that's a big cat I have a cat as big as
that honey G I think that cat's even
bigger than mine this episode oh he's a
beauty weird I love it what's his name
or her um it's it's a neighborhood cat
so we've gone so far to call it gray cat
gray cat hi gray be hi gray I want to go
out now thank you I wanted to come in
now I want to go out thank you oh
they're so funny uh yeah so that's
that's another aspect of of of what this
was all about yeah and again once you
lay down really strong lead
tracks you could you know add the music
and add the sound effects and add the
background Walla and add all of that
stuff uh with with ease you weren't
under pressure makes sense to do it and
and that's where once we realize how
easy that was to do and and that it was
possible to actually put it on a for
track tape right you know it's
stereo we we did it yeah yeah and and
the learning curve was very fast yeah
for everybody when's the first time you
met somebody who' bought it oh yeah
great well it's a great question I don't
think I have a great answer I I I'm not
sure I could remember that uh I I don't
even all I guess I can I can say that
the uh Fame that came to us and the
celebrity that came to us was very
personal
mhm people would come up to us as
individuals or in a group and say you
know you guys saved my life or wow when
is the Revolution going to
happen a lot of that you know but but it
was all very personal it wasn't like
adoring crowds who want us to sign
records at a record store that came
later sure sure uh so it was subtle I
guess that's the only way I can put it
it was subtle and uh and my life it's
literally like meeting wizard raas what
are you saying yeah being a fanboy I've
been a fan I'm a fanboy from way back
and I'm I have the I can say I've
embarrassed the [ __ ] out of myself in
front of Douglas Adams and lots of
people and what you what happens is
you're not quite sure how this person in
front of you did this magic thing yeah
it's true you how do you get into
beginning to ask the question of what
what the the line I love that one line
yeah where did that come you you
don't and when it's when when you're
part of an opus like we are uh you know
it's like well I played the second
violin on that piece you know and and it
was all written down for me and I played
it you had a good day yeah I had a good
day and we added some Echo to it and
it's great you
know but but uh you you you did make me
think of something else about all that
which of course I immediately forgot
uh right but but it has something to do
with
uh uh the yes I I know what was I doing
because you're asking me if people you
know how people uh I'm I'm going to try
to put together some more pieces here I
said I was living with Jeremy Clyde but
before and was it after that that I
lived yeah I guess it was after that
because you see I I was still pursuing a
career as an
actor now when I did the Daniel Boone
show what year was that do you remember
that Jesus Christ you don't remember
that I I played a French character in
The Daniel Boon in in the Daniel Boon
show so it's a Disney TV show it's
called No Bless obl yeah with Fest
Parker and and Rosie GRE and all those
guys great are we talking late 50s or
late 60s no no not late 50s it was in
the 60s somewhere you can still get it
online I mean no bless o b i play a a a
French pastry chef who is pretending to
be the king King of
France see so that so that he can you
know do what he needs to do in America
and uh uh but I'm not exactly sure when
that was it was during fire sign theater
career it certainly was before uh I did
the Henry jaglin movie a safe place see
one of the reasons why I have so much
trouble remembering all of this stuff is
that I have all these concurrent careers
going on yeah I mean it's quite
extraordinary uh in one way it it it's
wonderful and and was very satisfying
and allowed me to to be in two places at
once when I wasn't anywhere at all and
to use my various talents but on the
other hand I was never identified with
one thing and that's what creates
celebrity sure see if I if I'd had a
television series or if I'd even done an
appearance on Star Trek or something you
say
oh you know I could go to ComiCon but as
it is you know I'm Howard on the rug
rats you know so you know okay which is
still pretty damn good damn good 14
years but still if I go to ComiCon
nobody cares you know it's not like oh
you were on Star Trek you know I I find
that kind of woefully ironic that
there's something called Comic Con and
you can go largely unrecognized yeah
where in the hell is the Comic Con for
Comics right but like you know somebody
who's created I don't know Batman versus
Gumby whatever Batman versus Gumby that
they're working on that you don't know
who will win no really it's be good all
that clay inside the
mechanism when are they going to when
are they going to do something with
plastic
man um he pops up every once in a while
does he Plastic Man very rarely I love
plastic in cartoons but not not even now
Plastic Man uh Frank Miller uh did a
sequel to The Dark Knight uh the the
graphic novel he did a second one um and
uh man is actually in it the rubber
Knight or
something that's a that's a stretch well
that's an adult device that you you
don't has variable speed so good at
getting derailed what I want to do is no
it's fine it's fine I I want to say
though like I listening to it today
because I obviously heard it before but
I decided to take uh Jeremy's advice
from when he like really got into fir
sign was listening to it with some nice
quality head taking your [ __ ] time
because I have a lot of problem with
that when I'm listening to Comedy alum
I interviewed guest DW overy
blind favor because it's genuine theater
of the mind you know um and so he said
same thing you know just sit there and I
took my sweet time with it and it's just
so much of a different experience and I
think you know if we're going to
recommend anybody obviously yeah immerse
yourself in it please do listen on
earphones it's true for one all for one
and all for one all for
let me hear it for me you're under
arrest hello my it will be pleasant to
have you here I've not had any company
in this dank and dismal cell for 40 long
and miserable
years I was imprisoned by faceless
people for a crime of which I had no
knowledge and certainly did not commit
but what of that in me spare time I have
been pursuing me Obby which is writing a
great prison novel in the beginning I
wrote with an ink composed of of me own
blood however this would not make an
acceptable carbon so I acquired an
electric typewriter I am proud to be
able to present you with the first
edition of Mis Saga of eternal torment
profusely
Illustrated titled leather
thighs guard guard I want to see my
Ambassador easily done he's in the next
cell use the telephone I don't have a
dime here use one of the pages of me
novel
[Applause]
it's no good they're tapping the lines
when we uh were giving the opportunity
to to do quadrophonic
mixes uh on eight track tapes
for everything you know is wrong mhm
what was the other one Boos oh I think
we're all Boos on this bus
did I do the bozos thing for you the
last time talking to Siri yeah oh yeah I
see you were talking about like popping
up in weird ways that's exactly it right
if you ask Siri why does a porrige Burg
lay its eggs in the air you get this
okay now listen we have to acknowledge
that we lost Gary Shandling today I know
I I mentioned it before you showed up
and and and we also lost uh a Ken uh oh
no I can't remember his name it's all
right he's dead doesn't matter uh [ __ ]
sag president sag president yeah who I
who I worked
with who I worked with on several
committees you know uh in any event but
Gary shandley now Gary Shanley went his
own way yep and uh my friend Paul Wilson
worked with him on the uh this Larry
Sanders show and then later on on the
Gary Shanley show and a very unique
comic
who uh actually was offered like to
replace Johnny Carson at one point in
his career really y wow and instead went
into cable he was a Trailblazer he and
he and he created a parody of Carson you
know and it was brilliant brilliant
wonderful funny as hell and and and so
he he has had a cultural effect as well
because he was a Trailblazer into the
whole idea of doing comedy on cable
creating a series on cable creating a
you know character that was both real
and not real at the same time crossing
the lines Fernwood tonight yeah you know
all of that kind of stuff and it's
surrealistic in its own way it's all
it's all subtle and surrealistic so uh
he he made his Mark in a unique way and
of course I haven't really investigated
this as much as I'd like to maybe I will
later but he apparently survived a
terrible automobile accident which and
and died and came came back from the
dead and that's when he took a more
unique path because he realized that
this is life is a gift and what am I
going to do with it yeah see
so here's to you Gary yeah
absolutely on that happy note how do
somebody pick it up pick it up Phil me a
happy note you know it is a happy there
are a couple there are a couple of
moments when fire sign almost had a TV
show or almost had a feature
oh yeah but that was tough it was just
luck it was luck and it was it was life
and death also
because we we had an opportunity to to
do a film which was going to be called
eat uh it would it it would start with
uh the fire sign theater in neon and one
by one the letters were all short out
until just the E8 of theater was left
and then the camera would pan in down to
a diner and it was going to it would
start in the diner that had a flashing
light that said eat on it and our
producer was going to be a guy named
wacko his nickname was wacko Jerry Jerry
Brian Brian and uh Jerry's girlfriend
was
una and they went to before before we
were going to start the production of
the film and everything they went to
Hawaii for a vacation and he drowned
there Jesus and that was like by the end
of my father's career you know that was
the fire sign there wasn't that person
there to say I'll take come on let's do
it pick it up you know and later on we
had another opportunity to do that
writing a screenplay of
Ulisses uh a contemporary screenplay of
Ulisses for U Phillips what was her name
was it Michelle Phillips was no anyway
for some heavy weights in Hollywood
and uh and that also because of two
producers who were a little
crazy uh didn't go all the
way and you know when these things don't
happen and if we don't didn't have the
ambition to do it which we
didn't uh then your career goes in
different ways there were other
opportunities that I was aware of that
the other guys didn't understand that
would have helped him
move us forward what we were asked to do
Parts in Death Race 9000 or whatever
that
2,000 yes and I said we should do this
and it was all like oh there's no money
and we G no money and money and the
money and the money you guys would have
been so good in that of course of course
and the other thing was uh don Shay who
later started new line Cinema he was a
Pioneer on early cable television uh I
don't I don't know if it was night
flight that was something else but any
EV any event he was early Pioneer and he
wanted to do a Nick danger movie
starring Chevy Chase that's right well
there's no money in it yeah you didn't
have any money yeah and and believe it
or not we were hippie we're poor hippies
everybody we needed to make a living at
what we were doing there's four of us
yeah see it's not like you know okay
I'll get give me $10,000 and I'll do it
and you know and then I can I can get by
for a couple of months no it's four guys
you know 2500 a piece well it'll get me
through you
know and I can't do anything else I just
have to you know uh all of that the
economic part of it is something which I
think if we'd had strong management
would have would have been uh overridden
sure because a management company if
it's worth its salt it is funded it has
money y just you know and just like a
big agency they can put money into their
artists to help them because they're
going to get it back sure and
tenfold and we never never got into that
kind of a Groove with anything so you
know there were there there are
certainly distinct reasons why fire sign
didn't get farther than it could have
after a great beginning but culturally
we've had a strong success and and a
good effect yeah so that's kind of the
reward we we uh we have to to look to
and I must say I mean my own career was
certainly not hampered by Fireside sure
because the reputation that uh that I I
was able to carry With Me based on my
involvement with this kind of incredible
U creation has you know allowed me to uh
to get jobs where somebody would say oh
good I want to work with Phil you know I
know he can do this I would honor to
work with you and that's you know very
rewarding sure I mean for what it's
worth uh even if fire sign as you know
as a as a big stepping stone didn't blow
up in that same way artistically to
continue to be as good as you were and
then to obviously to get better and
better and better better your art did
not suffer for that no we we were we
were given uh the the evolving tools
technologically to to uh grow ourselves
yeah and to learn
and uh and we worked with some brilliant
people I I mentioned Fred Jones again uh
we worked with some absolutely brilliant
Engineers uh who helped us create our
vision yeah through new technology and
it was it was great well I think this is
a good place to end it because we are
going to we're doing the next album
whenever we can all get together so many
questions still ask you but we you must
throw them into the next next the bucket
for the next album the next one is what
how can you be into places at once is
that okay yes yes what did we talk about
the last time dwarf nothing you didn't
we
got got hiding under tables in
restaurants we got it was
fantastic and I mean like and I'm sure
as soon as we cut this there's going to
be eight million questions I have to ask
but I mean this really this is my
favorite uh this is my favorite I mean I
love all of them but this one I just
think it's it's so perfect like I've
even tried like I tell my students to
listen to at least the first side of
this just because you know what what are
you teaching abnormal psychology yes I I
teach uh I teach self flatulation and uh
shepherding how to stay insane insane
right which is a good class for it
really is but I mean like you know I
heard a couple of my my 13-year-old
students talking about you know the
whole Native American thing going on
with uh the Washington football team and
things like that and and they were like
yeah it's disgusting it's disgusting and
I said you know what I got something for
you to listen to you got
it and it's amazing because I don't
think they get all the references but
they will the winning of the West the
Massac yeah oh my God yeah
right this is this is the first fire
sign album that I got turned on to this
is what made me eventually become you
know involved with him the way that I am
this got me involved because side two is
a funny nightmare I am I'm a funny
nightmare person because that first it
scares me and then then I just hold my
head the whole time going wow this is
the best thing ever and electrician is
like that about halfway through like
life you get you're getting rugs pulled
out all the way along but when you get
to let me hear it for me you're under
arrest smam it's your that owned me for
life and it got me on to uh it made me
want to listen to the rest of the stuff
yeah and little those little little
throwaway almost jokes like I'm give
give me that gun but father I don't have
a gun here take
mine like those dumy dumy dummy you're
all little and and because this thing
switches on a dime from one place to
another it's that great and you talk
about that improv uh uh soul of it it's
there because as soon as you think
you've got that picture in your head you
drop something on literally on top of it
right next to you that you didn't
realize was there which you know you
can't do or at least I've never seen it
done on improv on state sure you can
only do it your mind well you get a
little bit of it like when you see
really good people at Groundlings or UCB
specifically because you know like all
of a sudden somebody will just say it
was like yeah but then get off the
submarine right like oh but it was such
a nice tea party I didn't realize that's
true you know but it's not the same
because you've built a complete picture
in yeah we we suck you in and then we
spit you out if you will it's true and
this was this one I just I mean and it
happen so quickly and effortlessly the
way on on the third track on side one
the um 38th of kondo the way every piece
of the scene suddenly you're cutting to
the other point of view in the scene and
because there's like two people in a
scene you're cutting to person B and
they start a scene with person C and you
cut to C's point of view and suddenly
they're in apparent teacher conference
with somebody else who goes on the next
thing who goes on the next thing you
can't do that you you can barely do it
very good good point Taylor and I I
think what it what it really boils down
to is that we were children of radio who
then and and and
movies okay and remember there was a
marriage a CO Coalition between movies
and radio they' put movies on radio and
they and and radio shows would become
movies I've got a great uh um radio
version of it's it's mury and the man
you got it the first it's almost
verbatim the whole thing unbelievable I
know uh and and and then television came
in so we were like really media babies I
mean we were the first generation to to
experience this evolution in in media
yeah uh in my book I I refer to myself
at one point as a Comedia n m
because really I grew up with changing
media and and I think that that's one of
the other things that that the other two
guys well three guys excuse me uh
everybody uh assimilated and and had in
common because this was an opportunity
to commingle these sensibilities for the
first time in one medium Y and reference
all the others yeah and you see play
with it even more especially when you
get to something like uh um dwarf when
you've got a movie on television right
and you're doing it on radio you hit all
three of them all at once and really the
bottom line is it's a record it's a
recording and that was what gave us the
freedom yeah CU we can do anything we
want on this people can take it home
listen to it privately yeah and we have
no restrictions other than to to create
you know realize Vision yeah boy was
that
liberating so liberating okay I I'm
going to recommend people buy this on
vinyl but Taylor maybe you can tell us
best is is it where is it still in print
where can we get it and money actually
goes to fire sign well go to Firesign
theater.com we are
selling uh not one but two versions of
this on CD including we still have
copies of electrician from mobile
Fidelity sound that's a great mix uh the
the people of the9 and 80s who cared
about getting Master recordings or not
doing it not doing it at all they'd get
the Masters and that's the best version
you will ever hear of the first four
albums um so get get that I say go to
Fir the.com and get the mobile Fidelity
version of electrician give your money
monies the fire better so we can make
fine new products like a DVD please do
that um
thank you so much this thank you so much
I I love sitting down with you and
listening to your stories because uh I
love sitting down good good well I'm
glad day we get the nice seat I'm an
[ __ ] I'm taking the other nice seat
every time this is Jeremy's office I
feel like I'm I'm that's fine I like it
this Jeremy's in sanctum we're
surrounded by pictures of comic great
everywhere and you're up there too don't
forget yeah there we are yeah yeah yeah
yeah but oh my God it's it's wonderful I
got I got all the good ones and if you
get bonus points if you can name
everybody up there the the the one
second from the right is the hardest oh
yep Harry Lang he knows of course he
knows he knows Harry langon most people
don't get Lloyd but if you can get Lang
in you oh yeah see my my dad used to
take me to the silent movie theater in
New York and uh uh and that's of course
I was in Laurel and Hardy were my
favorites but heral lyd was was right up
there with them yeah and I mean all of
them they were all revered by us WC
Fields later but you know the Mark's
Brothers I I grew up on East 94th Street
the Mark's Brothers grew up on East 92nd
Street in Lexington yes amazing yes I
went to high school on East 94th did you
Hunter you went to Hunter no kidding
Elementary School and High School wow
mhm that horrible brick Armory yes the
brick Armory yes no windows high school
with no
windows why would you need
oh my
God it's a great school though yeah it
was a great school you're honey for the
windows all the
time all right so see we could go on
forever we did go but it's okay it's
okay so great but thank you guys for
listening thank you guys for watching
and as always have a good
[Music]
thing comedy on vinyl is a production of
stolen dress entertainment it is
produced by Mike Warden and is hosted
and edited by Jason clom our theme song
was composed and performed by Richard
levenson please visit stolen dress.com
to listen to our other podcasts read our
blogs read our tweets watch our videos
and read our books please subscribe on
iTunes and if you like us give us a
festar rating and a nice review you can
find us on facebook.com/ Comedy onvinyl
Twitter at comedy onvinyl and find
everything else at comedyon
vinyl.com Jason clown here uh I'm of
course running for president for 2020
and 2016 this is a blog or video blog or
a vlog or of a Blog this is Bobby Hava
Clint Westfall Derek Mendelson welcome
to Fire and range with your pile DP
marle Harry I'm Rea blur
we're Trace empan CEO of Phyllis Masters
Rebecca pen you may know me as the
poison pen Kyle Frank figure for my
inaugural
Alex Parkhurst here welcome to learning
to cook my name is to Scott Apple can we
vote in 2020 2020 I don't know being
prepared is the essence of being uh of
having prepared looking forward hope
more which is available exclusively in
paperback because hard covers as you
know are elitist Define quit for me it
is with a heavy heart that I enter the
campaign again ple please please please
tell you're not you're not fooling me
are you where's the where's the nearest
airport welcome to
I'm where I'm a onean improv show what
happened with the
campaign it's nothing it's gone Kanye
West has decided to run for the
presidency in 2020 and I really wanted
to just kind of wait to announce you
know that I'm back in the race which uh
here here I am I guess it's official I'm
back in the race we are now getting
ready to hire our first intern and then
you died like theoretically I would move
up one step closer you know I'm sorry
are you assuming you would be the V my
vice presidential candidate as as my
intern one of my client's kids is going
to is kind of bankrolling his campaign
Magnetic Tape is what the whole
cinematic experience is all about dun
we're going to paare this with Coca-Cola
what's the point of overthrowing the
government right if there's no Earth
left to live on you have to have an ID
it's ridiculous we need to know who you
are in order to kill
this guy over here with his leather come
on really guys did you clean up the mess
on the floor what mess on the floor I I
produced the uh The Real Housewives of
Madison
County very very sad if people in Africa
eat this master Vapor that piece that
got to the bottom of like hula hoops
being anti-semitic that was
groundbreaking it's called in the line
of fornication my editor is very excited
about it e
[Music]