preponderance of people are
idiots hey my name is Chris Porter
listen if you're not laughing at these
jokes cuz you don't think they're funny
fair enough but if you're judging me and
you own an iPhone you can go [ __ ]
yourself it's the same Factory little
kids make iPhones and then when they're
fingers get too pudgy they move them up
to ey
pants where you from Chris I was born
and raised in Kansas uh did Kansas uh
trouble you at all did it make you it
does it come out your comedy still it's
been a while yeah I'm sure I mean yeah I
haven't lived there in 13 years but I'm
still from there I uh definitely my the
way I view the world is definitely a
something I picked up in Kansas I want a
burger made from a cow that was born and
raised to be a
burger that is why that cow existed was
the need for
Burger I don't want a cow with hopes and
dreams I don't want to taste Joy all
right I want a cow that knew the [ __ ]
deal I want a cow that walked by The
Slaughterhouse every day like is it my
day today the day no Cal be be over
[Applause]
here screaming from the cosmos was a
magical time I was just coming off Last
Comic Standing
which was probably one of the bigger
points of my career so it was definitely
you know screaming from the cosmos is
definitely an encapsulation
of you know that time period ax body
spray is a regression
as a society and everyone knows somebody
that uses it you do right before you
walked in here tonight they're like hold
[Music]
on I'm
ready but no one had left the car yet so
now all your friends smell like date
rape
I asked my friend why he did it I go why
do you do that why do you cover yourself
in that [ __ ] he said I don't want to
smell like pot and
beer why
not you know we've got pot and beer
let's
advertise cuz I'm going to tell you
something the girl does not like pot and
beer she's not going to like us at all
I don't I haven't watched it in a while
uh when I do watch clippings of it I you
know obviously I'm like wow I could have
worn some different
jeans
um I just see a kid having a lot of fun
is what I see when I see screen I see a
guy that literally in the middle of a
giant cluster [ __ ] of success where he
didn't really know what was going on
kind of encapsulated a moment of it
sweet jacket though that was nice I
still
lost and alone's the new one uh it
was kind of my answer to ugly and angry
which was my album
previous
um you know it's just it's a weird
managerie of of jokes uh some really
funny stories in there and the great
thing about lost lost and alone is
there's you know a good chunk of it is
just happened at the show it's not even
really you know it's called the girl in
the cute noise and you know it's just
something that happened and then it was
magical enough that we kept it one take
one take one take Chris that's right man
oh man that's got to be a lot of
pressure though do I mean doing an album
like that cuz I mean I I would want like
10 takes of not screwing it up well you
know uh I don't you know I don't record
the record till I'm ready so I guess by
the time by the time I get to record an
album I'm so tired of that material
anyway it's almost like a giant goodbye
party and if you're going to bring up
politics at your friend's party you
should do everyone else at that party a
favor and instead of bringing up
politics just pull out your dick and
shove it in the
jello because you will get the same
reaction that you would have gotten had
you broughten up the election
everyone's going to look at you and go
what the [ __ ] are you
doing we're trying to have a good time
here why would you do
that but at least if you stick your dick
in the jello your friends have a story
for
later so tell me what's coming up next
for you uh let's see I'm recording a new
special in August and uh other than that
I got a whole spring tour lined up so
and then you can be found uh uh Chris
Porter comedy.com or I am Chris Porter
on any of the social
medias sorry I farted did you I did it
thanks