[Music]
I'll never quit I'll never admit cuz I
love
it the Son of Sam I'm gun in hand ready
to
go I'm in the clear long as I don't
appear sad in public
[Music]
that's as far as I know thank god dad
set the bar low because someday the
ripples going to hit the
[Music]
wall someday the ripples going to hit
the
wall somay the ripples going to hit the
[Music]
wall
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah you what it takes to put on the
brakes before
Collision if you or I do or die know in
[Music]
between you won't survive a moment alive
television I know I'll never come down
from the things I've seen I never knew
it not being young would me but now
someday the Ripple's going to hit the
wall
someday the ripples going to hit the
wall somay the ripples going to hit the
wall and I know someday the ripples
going to hit the
wall how could I be a dream date you
don't even think of me when you are
[Applause]
swing and a p is why I exist or so they
tell
me the fear that God is here you not
feeling the
[Music]
pain too disease to ever be pleased with
what's healthy every day the length of
the streak is perverting your brain
strength and weakness could never be a
per sh
it's a day the re's going to H the
wall I know I know I know I know it's
day the's going to hit the
wall yeah yeah yeah yeah someday the's
going to hit the
wall I know som the ri's going to hit
the wall