it's nice to to be in America um because
you have like far more liberal freedom
of speech laws uh so I can I can I can
tell the jokes here which at home make
you know qualify as like hate speech
um so have a good night you
know yeah now I recently joined uh
Montreal's Gates trade Alliance um we go
around the city beating up the bisexuals
you know
um I don't know I think it's okay to
tell these jokes you know
uh how'd you get your
start uh very first set ever was a high
school project did 5 minutes at an
amateur night outside
Toronto and then the next set was I
think four years later was taking a year
off between undergrad and more school
and so I I went to a movie and in the
mall where the theater was located there
was also a comedy club advertising an
open mic and I had nothing to do I was
just writing jokes anyway for all this
time and uh yeah I used to go watch
standup when I went on vacation or
something to New York or San Francisco
or wherever or LA but it wasn't
something that I did at home or took in
at home it was more just uh garbage pale
kids money python things like this but
it wasn't stand-up comedy really what do
you find funny what do I find
funny uh I suppose I find funny
When people's expectations are not met
it's a weird thing going around for
standup quite a bit because uh every
place you go you have to determine like
their like values and lines and mores
and things like this and I don't know if
anyone's ever been to Portland
um [ __ ] Portland yeah
my it's like this like this hyper hyper
hyper hyper hyper hyper liberal little
enclave and so profoundly conservative
in its own way and before the first time
I ever got to do a show there I was told
by the person putting on the show said
you should know uh that this is a safe
space I was like yeah
like that's my assumption you know
like like as an animal you know
like I only
go into those spaces
um which I understand to be
safe and then so I so I get there
and
it's
all lesbians and
me and I had
never felt so unsafe in my
life and I told them I was like look I
this is my first time in the Pacific
Northwest and I find myself asking
myself for the first time ever what do
lesbians want
um because the fact of the matter is I
continued I said I don't give a [ __ ] um
and it's not that I give any less of a
[ __ ] about your your particular
demographic than any other it's just
like where I come from what standup
comedy is it's like the most Artful way
of telling a room full of people to go
[ __ ]
themselves and so you want to play with
like people receive Notions and
stereotypes and things like this it's
like what is it about lesbians it's that
they have no sense of humor you know
um and when you're telling of a roomful
of lesbians that they have no sense of
humor and they're not laughing
um that that is the funniest [ __ ]
thing you
know like I know there are some there
are some who people who take issue you
know like with the word [ __ ] um but me I
I've only ever had problems with the
personality type you know um
here's the
album stuff in there here anyway so this
is an album and uh recorded in Montreal
what's it called it was okay okay the
full name the full name is it was okay
an album of comedy by David Hy why'd you
pick that title why why why is that the
title it encapsulates so much I think I
don't think there's one there's one to
say it's it's this or this alone I think
would spoil what it what what it is so
just to document it friend of mine David
gston said you know he's a
cinematographer he said he can shoot it
and it never occurred to me so on New
Year's Day Grumpy's Bar was shut down
for two hours and we just filled it with
like you know people who enjoy comedy
and just did the recording and that's it
and it was a you know nice way to start
off the year a lot of hungover friends
taking it a comedy show what's the sign
of a good show for you sign of a good
show
uh people will say that they were
laughing at things that they didn't know
they could laugh at perhaps or they're
laughing at things they didn't want to
laugh at or or or uh it made them
think are you offended by the hobo
comparison that's being made no I don't
I'm not offended by this I think that
it's there's a there's a truth to it I
think that not that it's easy not that
it's easy but if it's said over and over
it's kind you know no it's fine I'm not
aan by that at all oh there's a train
over
there oh
yeah you know it's a maybe it's like
like a Grain Train maybe it's not a hobo
TR
[Music]