[Applause]
[Music]
he's in New York he's in Toronto he's in
La he's sleeping on floors every day of
the week and that's what I love about
this [ __ ] gig so please welcome to
his stage the uh slightly unstable hobo
looking David
[Applause]
Hy
all right good evening it's uh it's good
I
uh my name is David Hedy uh it's it's a
stage
name uh it's also my real name uh I just
use one or the other depending as to
which entity I'm referring to at any
moment um it doesn't work very well at
all I've uh I've lost jobs but uh this
isn't that's not on you that's not on
you um no I know this convention to be
like oh it's good to be here
uh um but the fact of the matter is that
I am here you are here uh why ask how we
feel about it let's just move on you
know but I'm going to ask you all please
to hold your uh laughter till the end um
um because yeah well yes while in one
respect like each joke does exist unto
itself in its own particularity um on
another deeper level they all comprise
like a greater hole
um and and and you're not capable of you
know appreciating what's truly hilarious
about any any particular bit until we've
gotten to the end and you've the youve
the context
um and I'm sorry I'm sorry like I know
that you come to a comedy show uh
expecting to laugh um and enjoy
yourselves U but life isn't fair
um I I feel like this is going to be one
of those shows where you leave uh
feeling like [ __ ] um but they but then
get that slight little pickme up when
you realize that no one from the show is
actually on your subway car home
um cuz it's not easy I don't know I feel
like the fact that you're out there and
I'm here like we are are unable to
relate I uh I remember before I ever did
standup whenever I was out in the
audience the only thing going through my
head the entire time was you know like I
I can do better than this [ __ ]
um no but really this is what I'm hoping
will be a very limited edition series of
my standup uh entitled jokes that I
wrote last night while awake at 400 in
the morning um on account of not being
able to sleep for fear of the way that
my life is unfolding
um is dedicated to my mother
um but she and I have a very strain
relationship um she says all she's ever
wanted is for me to to to be happy um
All I've Ever Wanted uh is to be loved
and respected um and it's a real
stalemate
um no but really uh the last time the
last time she she I went out for dinner
the bill came in and and she said
$67 was it worth
it and I said like normally I like to do
what I can to try not to put a dollar
value um on the time that we spend
together uh but if I'm forced to um the
this was a very expensive
meal no my mother's doing quite well the
last time I went home I discovered that
she recently renovated my room into a
place where a kid would have been happy
growing up
[Applause]
um it wasn't easy it wasn't easy my
father was a
little violent um I I remember I recall
as a as as a kid telling my mom one day
when I grow big enough uh he's going to
beat the [ __ ] out of only you um
[Music]
I I remember though telling um my
telling my sister I think the one thing
preventing me from killing myself uh is
the fear of what it might do to the
family um and and she said David you
can't continue to live your life with
respect to what you think will make
other people happy
um so few ever actually recognized that
as a joke
um yet yet no one ever intervenes you
know um I remember the last my my my
mother what happens after we die and she
said Daddy Goes to Jail
um but we wanted to disclose like to
reveal to my sister the fact of her
adoption um but in the way sort of least
traumatic as possible uh so we we let
her know in the midst of a sort of
collective family sexual assault
um you don't realize it right now but
that was your favorite joke of the
evening
um no years you know I mean like now now
now you may not see what's so funny um
but ye years from now you may look back
on this entire evening as a whole you
know and laugh and that's really the
essence of Comedy I feel right
there they say though a more senior
comic has told me that you have to love
your
audience but but I
think there has to be a way around that
um Love is something that develops over
time you know possibly at the end of the
at the end end of the set but uh no
really though if you're not enjoying
yourselves this evening uh you've only
yourself to blame
um this is your life uh you know and and
and whether you're at a comedy show or
you're or you're you're making love
you're on your way to work you have to
take control and responsibility for your
experience of it you know like uh like
I'm not enjoying
myself but but who would I be to blame
you you
know like I don't think
Jesus I don't think Jesus was ever like
oh I've never been to Paris know
like no probably like a very rich
internal life you
know but really though all these years I
done stand up for myself cuz I you know
for for me cuz I wanted to but now I
realize that there is no self the self
doesn't exist there's only relation um
between me and you with respect to why
we're here and what we want in
particular time and place and so for me
you are the necessary evil um which
allows me to do what I want which is to
tell
jokes but the terrible thing is is that
I can't even tell the jokes that I want
to tell because you don't understand
comedy the way that I know
it no but really thank you for being
here uh
obviously obviously without an audience
it' be impossible for me to to share
with the world uh through my standup
just how much I I dislike doing this
um because all these young Comics all
these very young Comics always make so
so angry I I I can't help but feel like
if you know if only ID started like 10
years earlier by now I could be done
with the whole [ __ ] thing
already
but I hope everyone's been having like a
nice break as of I um my friend held a
little get together to celebrate the
birth of work child and I guess it was
inappropriate but at the time looking at
that beautiful new baby all I could
think to myself was this life to shall
die and I told my friends how I felt and
they said well that's what makes its
life so valuable and I said no that's
what makes its life such a
waste
and while they all gave me looks of
understanding I don't think any of them
truly appreciated what I meant because
none of them bothered to pull the baby
from the
pool I remember though my girlfriend was
pregnant and uh she wanted to keep the
kid but I just wasn't ready to be a
father um and she said when we leave
this world don't you want there to
remain something behind that's a part of
the two of us and the symbol of the love
we have have for each other and I said
of course but I'm just not ready to be a
father and so we compromised uh we went
to this Artisans workshop and and we
crafted with our very own hands this mug
out
of out of clay
um and we and we signed it and
everything
uh and now that's uh where we keep the
aborted fetus um
sadly though you know the stresses of
the time were so great it led to our
eventual breakup um and so now I only
have access to The Mug on Mondays
Wednesdays Fridays
and every other
Saturday often times where there can be
women in the audience who've actually
had a miscarriage uh who could have
difficulty appreciating the humor um
it's almost as if uh if some
something died inside of
them I'm sorry this is the Persona with
which I'm forced to continue
um my girlfriend though absolutely
refuses to use any form of birth control
uh whatsoever and it's really sort of
changed my world to know that now each
time I have sex there's the real
possibility of me bringing about not
only a brand new life but also a single
mother no I know that there can be some
uh some women who find that joke to be
slightly misogynistic
um but then again you know your gender
really isn't known for its sense of
humor
um but I'm a good person I'm a good
person I I just have no jokes to
illustrate the fact
um I have a I have a friend though he's
in lots of bands and he says the way it
works is that all Comics want be
musicians and and all musicians want to
be
comics and it just makes me so angry I'm
like why would I want to be anyone who
wants to be a
comic by the privilege though this year
of doing my first set at a music f
festival and afterwards like we had a
car ride home back to Montreal 13 hours
straight overnight with these four
musicians and the whole way we had this
very sort of esoteric uh philosophical
conversation as to the nature of Art and
I came to think you know why comedy why
am I a comic why do I tell jokes and so
so basically like we're only here to be
happy really and so for me what's
funniest is when we're not
happy um and it just what happens to be
the case that just intuitively I I tend
to subvert for myself any happy moment
which which begins you know I see what's
terrible in it and even for the stage
now doing standup I look for what's
awful in every moment so my life is a
series of like unhappy unhappy instances
and that's why jokes that's why I'm a
comic
um and then so I asked the musician I
was like why music like why are why do
you why why music and he's like
well he's like when I'm like actively
listening to music
or like writing or playing
it it's like that's when I'm closest to
the
universal that's when I'm
one with the
universe and I was like
[Music]
oh you can go [ __ ] yourself like [ __ ]
you [ __ ] you [ __ ]
you
I don't know no one asked for this no
one asked for this
life not it takes up all lot lot most
lots of my time and my money and I think
that I I don't think I'm getting back
what I put into it but that's
uh but if I if I had to own a
slave if I had to own a slave I I think
it would be John col train
um
and if I had to own a second slave like
if I had to own a second slave I think
it would be thonus
monk um although just a small part of me
can't help it feel that perhaps what
with all the slaving away all day uh it
would affect their music just a little
bit you
know I think I
can I think that I can tell that joke
though because I'm a comic
um and I don't own I don't own anything
so
uh I was going through um I was going
through a really rough time last year
and I didn't know whether I could go on
um and so for the first time ever I
prayed uh and I asked God for the
strength and the courage to
continue and he said
uh uh
no
I'm just tired of seeing seeing blood in
my urine I think that's
yeah there's a woman that I know she's
morbidly obese and uh not a single time
throughout her entire pregnancy did she
receive a
congratulations and she thinks it's
because people were afraid to confuse
her possible being with with child for
what may in fact he have been just yet
another fold of fat um whereas in
actuality no one was happy to see her
procreating no the one thing I won't
make fun of in my stand up is the plate
of the fat and obese um you know it
really is a genetic Lottery uh the the
way that I see it um you know I was
simply fortunate enough to to have been
born with a sense of
Shame but you always hear like how this
sort of like distorted feminine ideal of
beauty creates all these like anxieties
and eating disorders and women um which
is terrible uh but no one ever talks
about how difficult it is for me to find
a girl whom I can bring myself to [ __ ]
um but I'm over my whole sort of younger
girl phase I've simply arrived at that
level of maturity where I where I
realize uh what's truly satisfying is
you know the complete domination of the
will of an equal
[Laughter]
um in 1972 though John lenon and Yoko
Ono released to sort of an you know
understandably apprehensive audience um
the song Woman is the [ __ ] of the
world uh to you know you know talk about
the second class status and um you know
leaders of African-American communities
were quite upset saying this is a slap
in the face and culture
sensitive um so John and Yoko they sort
of like they they they they went back
and they re-released the song under a
second title uh [ __ ] is the [ __ ] of
the
world but you know but ethics uh which
is what I think is the essence of Comedy
is quite ambiguous uh whereas rules of
grammar are quite clear-cut
um for instance if a transgendered
person gets gets mad at you for using
the wrong pronoun it's it's actually
permissible for you to tell him or her
to go [ __ ]
themselves I've been tutoring this kid
though is not doing very well at school
he's in grade four uh but he reads at a
grade 2 literacy level and he's got uh a
bad attitude to boot um the last
time the last time I I I went in to see
him he told me that my hair was kind of
messy and I said so what um you can't
read no but really like I was doing you
know I was in the states for a while
doing stand up there and the thing with
the states is like the word like the
word [ __ ] is so common it's it's all
over especially in uh in rap music I
find uh although I can understand it I
guess in one sense because it's a word
that like Rhymes so easily
uh and it has this particular sort of
meter to it which also is you know it's
good to it works
and I guess what I'm trying to say is
that like these people don't want to
work hard
[Laughter]
um
but but it's contextual you know it's a
word like [ __ ] like what it depends
how you're using it you know like for
some people are so reluctant to
like like my girlfriend
um it was our it was our safe word
[Music]
um that's that's how she
died
[Music]
but it's all pretense right like if I
say like uh if I say like I like [ __ ]
little
boys
but I don't love
it then you don't know where on the
Spectrum it may
lie no but really though for the first
time ever a girl asked me to to like you
know ejaculate over her face and uh
like I you know it isn't anything I've
ever had any interest in doing um but I
said like if if this is something that
you
enjoy I'm H I'm happy to oblige uh but
perhaps if while it's happening you
could please explain to me just what it
is about this that you like uh then at
least I could get something out of the
whole
experience all I'm saying is
that personal relationship can be quite
difficult um I remember this guy went
school for years he was complete wreck
after his girlfriend left him he had no
idea what had happened and I remember uh
between his sobbing he softly said to me
he said David as my only friend uh tell
me the
truth and I said
uh I'm I'm not your friend
um but they say that it's out of the
profoundest human suffering that emerges
the greatest communic achievement and I
think that's true in personally I you
know that's why I think it's so tragic
about the the death camps
um when you think of all the incredible
jokes you must have lost you
know but if there's one thing that I've
learned uh throughout all my years of
standup it's that no one likes this next
joke
um because I'm an adherent of the sort
of classically modern historical notion
of stand up comedy uh According to which
there's sort of an implicit uh
discernable directional progress uh to
the unfolding of joke telling over time
um it just so happens that we're at what
one may conceive of as sort of like the
you know like sort of like the Communist
totalitarian stage uh and I know that
it's not easy um but I promise you that
if you stick with me uh in only two
generations time uh perfect hilarity for
everyone will will history vindicate
that
joke ought it to because I I think that
if you're only asking how much you know
did you laugh then you're really missing
the bigger picture
um I was telling the one of my harder
jokes on evening about the the the rape
and murder of this woman and after my
set a man from the audience came up to
me and said you know uh I think you
ought to be aware of the fact that in
real life my wife wife was actually
raped and
murdered and he told me this and I had
one of those moments where things sort
of stand still and you start to see
things
differently and when I finally gathered
a hold of myself I apologized to the man
for being so incredibly Thoughtless and
told him that from now on uh you can be
the one to tell the
joke
but they tell me they say David there's
nothing at all funny about sexual
assault and I say I
know um that's
not why I do
it I've been thinking quite a bit though
recently about circumcision um um it was
Abraham at least according to the Bible
who's the first person to be circumcised
in fact he circumcised himself uh what
happened at least according to the Bible
is that God spoke to him and said this
shall be our covenant between me and you
respect to all of your progeny
throughout the ages and uh it's very
strange to me because like God could
have chosen anything to be the
Covenant but this is what
wanted so it's like God is vast and
infinite unknowable and complex and all
these things the one thing that we can
say for certain is that God really does
like circumcised
penises and I'm no Theologian and and I
don't know if like Angels on the head of
a pin um but apparently on a good day
God could fit like four of them in his
mouth at once
um and if NRA is to be believed that's
actually how he died
um I just like the image of God sitting
there with all these dicks in his mouth
thinking oh it's good to be God you
know I think it was anel or Augustine uh
who asked whether God could shove so
many [ __ ] into his mouth that it would
be too many [ __ ] for God uh and
obviously the answer is no um which was
decided uh during Vatican 2 um when
Church Council got together to reconcile
sort of modernity and and
Doctrine no but NRA actually has this
notion of eternal return which is that
if time and space are infinite it's not
that any Universe which can possibly
exist will come about uh a single time
but rather it will recur an infinite
number of
times and this notion sort of came to
mind once uh while in the midst of
masturbating um and the idea that there
could be an infinite number of universes
comprised solely of one person having
this thought while
masturbating that was my worst
masturbation session
ever there's this comic that I know
though who
uh he was I guess he was like you know
molested as a kid um and every single
all all he talks about on stage is how
he was sexually abused and my heart was
like oh like like perhaps like if only
you hadn't been like sexually abused as
a kid today you might understand how to
tell a [ __ ]
joke it's not that I rever
pedophiles
uh but just a little part of me just
reveres them just a little bit uh
because to my mind mind it's it's
unimaginable that they are incapable of
recognizing the incredible potential
harm that they're doing possibly ruining
a life for something that they
love cuz I know that I have never felt a
love like that
before and I don't think that I ever
will um and like I don't want to touch a
kid
um but like if I loved standup so much
that in order to do it I would go
through a
kid I think that would be a beautiful
thing I think though that everyone
should touch a kid at least a single
time
um I'm not saying it would make you look
a good person or good citizen but you
only go around once and you really don't
know what you like until you try it uh
especially in the bedroom
um and you know like social Ms evolve
and and change and and and and and and
laws 65 5 years ago there no voting
rights for black people right so like
who knows what 3 weeks from now will be
a be able to
touch oftentimes after a set some the
audence come up to me and say I really
didn't appreciate the things that you
said on stage uh but then you know other
times uh sexual predators will
approach and say you you really struck a
cord
uh so I guess it balances out you know
why why is it always though like only
the absolute sort of objectively worst
societies that don't recognize cultural
relativism that's that's normally the
big Applause break number right there
but like this friend of mine he wanted
to volunteer in Africa but not with some
sort of Western organization with its
own Imperial agenda for the continent
and uh but with like a local group so
for six months he ended up with the uh
the sudes uh government um helping to to
to to rape and murder darans
[Laughter]
um but I've but I've recently I don't
know I've recently sort of been on the
lookout for some expad Sudanese chicks
um it's not that I find their slender
faces or cool dark complexions to be
especially attractive it's just that I
think could be a lot less pressure and
work to date a girl who doesn't have a
clitoris I actually told that Joo the
evening when we were working over at the
women's shelter
um but it didn't go over very well at
all
I I I [ __ ] up the timing and
everything but if you're only sort of
like think thinking about these jokes
and laughing to yourself and not out
loud that I can't see the backs of your
mouths which is why I do this uh I feel
like [ __ ] the audience in the face is
like the final taboo of standup somehow
so a lot of a lot of people were quite
outraged when the director uh Roman
palansky pleaded guilty to what was
essentially the rape of a miner um but I
think we forgetting that he was also a
holocaust suror um because in my mind
the two things sort of even out uh the
way that I see it that 13-year-old girl
was essentially just his
Palestine as a side note um I actually
came up with that uh joke one evening
after someone challenged me to write
something that would offend Jews women
uh and fans of Chinatown um
this is a fine line that we didn't
comedy tragedy I agree personally I've
never been quite exactly sure where I
stand on the issue of
genocide um because on the one hand unly
tragic uh but on the other hand
undeniably
funny I guess it's just one of
those things where you really had to be
there
um my grandfather though was one of the
few uh lucky members of his generation
to grow up Jewish in Europe and avoid
the horrors of the Holocaust uh
thankfully uh several months before the
war broke out he was beaten to death in
a
[Laughter]
pom
no but there still is the uncomfortable
lingering question as to why if the Jews
as they did so outnumber the Nazis at
the camps why didn't they fight back um
you obviously I don't know uh but what I
can say is that we Jews do pride
ourselves on what we like to believe is
our distinctly dark self-deprecating
sense of
humor and in fact today it is nice to
have for ourselves as a source of
material um
basically the greatest human suffering
in living
memory and yeah you know like while it
would have been nice to have had a full
set of of grandparents um I simply
cannot tell you to just what an extent I
respect their commitment to the
joke when the Nazis though they did some
unconscionable things they actually
forced the Jews to work the
crematoria on Saturdays
[Laughter]
that's our that's our day of rest uh
it's it's an a front to God
um I know that people like oh like too
soon too soon and like yeah yeah okay
but like one more year you know
so there's this new field of Academia
though which asks uh what would have
happened had decisive moments in history
turned out differently and
apparently had Hitler won the war um
people wouldn't get so [ __ ] upset
when I tell a holocaust
[Music]
[Applause]
joke I think the big difference though
between the Holocaust and the Armenian
Genocide of of 19 sort of 14 to 18 is
that why there were still a few crazy
holocausts is out there The Armenian
Genocide never happened
um if I may though I'd like to read to
you my favorite passage from the Bible
um it's about menstration um it goes as
follows um when a woman has a discharge
of blood which is her regular discharge
from her body she shall be in her
impurity for seven days and whoever
touches her shall be unclean and
everything upon which she lies during
her impurity will be unclean everything
also upon which she sits shall be
unclean and whoever touches her bed
shall wash his clothes whoever touches
anything upon which she sits shall wash
his clothes whether it is a bed or
anything upon which she sits and goes on
and on and on and on and that there is
actually um from a brief period after
the destruction of the second temple um
when for a a brief while God was
thinking of just giving it all up and
instead going into the laundering
business
um
for the first time ever though I know
it's like a very sort of like cliche
premise but I actually lost a condom
inside of a girl um she's about sort of
like 55 with shoulder length brown hair
um so if
anyone happens to find it uh you can
talk to ram uh he has my contact info
and no questions asked you
know as a man though it's one of my
great Pleasures in life to pee uh
standing
up and uh over a sitting down woman
um and into the mouth of another sitting
down
woman obviously it would be so much you
know greater to pee into the mouth of a
standing up woman standing
being so Majestic um but I can no longer
achat the stream
um I think though that in order to be
penetrated I would really have to feel
like this guy is so
masterful I don't know I just feel like
it's a really like giving up of oneself
but I don't think that I'm willing to to
sort of concede that I feel that I don't
know
like like my uncle for instance um he
bought a he he bought a cottage recently
and it's beautiful it's the first one in
our family it's like two stories and
it's newly finished it's lovely and I
remember the first time I saw it just
thinking like oh like if I could have
this
life I would let you [ __ ] me however you
want whenever you
want but still I couldn't be like no
like just cuz I can't afford a cottage
at this point in my life it doesn't mean
I've made all my decisions wrong I have
my Pleasures you
know but the strangest thing was was to
to recognize that the one thing
preventing me from allowing my uncle to
[ __ ]
me was my low
self-esteem I remember I was in New York
happened to be over the the Gay Pride
weekend um or The Pride weekend and
there were all these you know at at the
parade all these all these gay guys
dancing sort of half naked in the
streets uh which is fine um but it
couldn't help but confirm for me my
suspicion that perhaps if in fact
instead of having uh gone to the gym all
the time
um they'd instead put some of those
hours into actually sort of attempting
to advance their civil rights uh then
today today we'd have no need for the
parade at all you
know like I don't know what Martin
Luther King Jr was packing under his
suit that day he made that speech um but
that's the point you
know I recently joined Montreal's Gates
trade Alliance we go in the city beating
up the B
bisexuals but I can't stand these big
Burly guys who always like come on admit
it Dave you're a
[ __ ] and I'm just like isn't it enough
that you're inside of
me this year though um these American
scientists sort of cured uh an a newborn
an infant of its of its
HIV and so now it's like uh you know for
years now for me um in order to cure my
own AIDS I've been [ __ ] the wrong
baby
um some people don't like that when I
tell that joke but I feel like Gary's
life is over anyway you know so like
what's the what's the
difference all I'm saying though is at
what point ought we to be granting to
person sort of legal autonomy to make
decisions over their own lives um like
what if one day
uh I'm just lying there
uh perfectly
still not
moving not not moving at all and a baby
uh happens to crawl
up onto my naked
body
and I don't I don't move I just lie
there perfectly
still and and and
unassuming
and it takes me into its
mouth and it starts to fate me um with
its beautiful little baby
[Applause]
[Laughter]
breath
and I'm still not
moving wouldn't that be
awesome there's no like good way to go
into my rape
material cuz there's a question as to
whether we live in a rape culture which
is one that sort of condones and
normalizes and accepts it and I don't
think that we do CU I think that if we
did I think people would enjoy these
next jokes much more
um because in Cleveland OH there in
Cleveland there was this there was a Sex
Dungeon um these women were kept in The
Sex Dungeon for years which it's like
one of those horrific things I can I can
I can I can think of um and I saw on TV
one of the women uh read her Victim
Impact statement in court
and she was saying like You know despite
the things you did to me the indignities
I suffered at your hands
and it's like I can still be the person
I want and live the life that I want I'm
going be the person I I can be on and on
and on and on it's like what are you
talking to what do you mean shut up like
shut shut the [ __ ] up
like after everything you've gone
through you still think you're capable
of doing what you want in your
life then how am I
able to blame my
parents for the basically the right
decisions they made you know how are any
how's any of us to blame our
circumstances for where we are in
life I think she have to go back on
television and and and and and and and
and and sort of recant and apologizing
I'm sorry like I made a mistake like my
life is over and it's just [ __ ] and I
can't do anything and like then it's a
service to humanity that's her place in
the cosmos I think that's a go back and
do what's right you
know I've just never been a great
advocate of life you know um which is to
say that I don't think it's good um
unconditionally like I don't know what
to say anymore when a when a when when a
friend tells me uh they're
pregnant it's okay get up just stand up
stand up and stand up stand up it's okay
it's okay okay it's all right it wasn't
going well anyway I wasn't feeling that
one so it's okay it's
good like I don't know what to say
anymore when a friend me they're
pregnant like you want a kid just like
you want anything else in life it's
something outside of you in the world
that you think will make you
happy like just because I don't I may
not want a kid doesn't mean I'm any more
selfish a person like maybe I I want a
couch you
know so I'll get that couch and when my
time comes I will leave that couch to
another couch or whatever you know but I
don't know I think the only way that I
could have a kid would be if I were to
accidentally impregnate a girl and it be
out of my hands but like to decide for
another point of self-awareness that
this is worth it to sort of Burden it to
have to kill its own time till its own
demise just cuz I can't make it on my
own
alone it's anyway ah
[Music]
anyway and I would love to be a father I
think I think be so much fun but I can't
do this to another human being you know
at least with my experience of life um
so I think what you should what we
should do when someone tells you they're
pregnant is you know we ought to wait
like seven 8 years uh and then turn to
the kid and be like how do you feel
about
this and if they're
like ah it's worth it or anything above
then we should turn to the parents and
be like oh
congratulations
one time I almost I had this like near I
I was almost hit by hit by a car and my
whole life flashed before my eyes and it
was just one long [ __ ] shot compilation
um and I was like yeah I I figured as
much like this
is I was in Greenwich London England
which is like the center no man just get
up yeah that's okay man no it's totally
yeah yeah it's okay okay yeah that's
good no I think it's fine yeah yeah okay
okay well we we'll edit that out I think
that
uh I was in Gran Lon England um and
there's this old Observatory uh and
there's an exhibit on the cosmos and so
we are like just one planet revolving
around a single star in uh a galaxy of
billions of stars which itself is within
a universe of billions of
galaxies and so so if intelligent life
came about once it's not that there's a
mere possibility that it may have come
about about a single other time but
rather there's a good reason to think
that it would have come about
innumerable other
times and I I I I stood there trying to
take take it all in and I couldn't help
but feel that there had to be a better
astronomy exhibit out
there
I think the homeless though
um I think what really bothers me with
the homeless I think they're lazy I
think that's their main problem about
like about half of them haven't even
finished you know to bother growing all
their limbs
[Laughter]
um but really what it is like stop like
what I don't understand like why why why
the why aren't why aren't the homeless
always the first in line at record store
autograph signings you know I
mean I I mean you're going to sleep on
the street anyway you
know you might as well meet Drake you
know
anyway I was working though uh we're
coming to the end though I I I I mean
maybe we'll see
so this friend of mine though last
weekend she she revealed me she has
cancer uh I however chose not to burden
her with how she'd uh ruined my
evening often times after after I said
the the MC will come back on and be like
oh like David's available for children's
parties and weddings and bids fuzz and
everyone will
laugh but the fact is I actually am
available for children's parties
and I think that the I think though the
thing that I find most intrinsically
degrading about elder
abuse is the constant having to remind
them as to why you're treating them so
badly
no
but I was reading about this kid with
mustroph who was teased so badly by this
other kid about his muscular distrophy
that uh he killed
himself and at least you know to my mind
um just to have the capacity to do such
a thing it really doesn't sound like
such severe muscular distrophy
but what I find most I can't understand
the most is these people with like these
incredible physical disabilities who
nonetheless are capable of maintaining a
deep religious
Faith CU you're like you think that like
like you know like given like what they
they're already forced to put up with in
this world God would have at least
spared their
minds I don't know I think the one thing
though the one sort of civil rights
movement I can get behind is the fight
for the for the for the right to
assisted suicide uh CU I mean not not
being able to kill
yourself you that's that's that's no way
to live
um but what I really don't get about
retards
uh is the always going around in the
velcro scrap
shoes
cuz like I can get like not having the
manual dexterity to like operate the
laces but what's wrong with a nice penny
loafer you
know maybe that's part of the maybe
that's part of the whole retardation
thing I don't
know anyway I know it's like I know it's
like convention to uh to to to want to
leave an audience wanting more
um but like if I'm going to be getting
off anyway I feel like that's like the
crest way of going about it
um there's no real
closing number to this I guess that
uh we stick around and have some ending
what you mean this
is terrible ending to a
show so happy New Year and thank you
thank you everyone for being here thank
you very
[Music]
much W
[Applause]
[Music]
woo
e
[Music]