[Music]
congratulations on your little bundle of
joy you must have worked so hard at
[ __ ] to get that adorable boy he
looks just like you and just like your
old
man a look how he fits in the palm of
your
hand right now he's super cute with spit
up on his bib but I can't wait till he's
old enough to drive me to his crib when
baby becomes legal I'll be
54 my breast and badge might sag and sag
but he'll be happy to
score I know it might seem weird to say
it now when he's in a
na but there is going to be a day when
this cougar will make him
[Music]
happy you know that I won't make make a
move for 18 years and I'll wait till
he's 21 to get him trashed on beers but
I can see it in his little we Angelic
face he's not going to have a problem
getting [ __ ] all over the place when
baby becomes legal I'll be
54 my breast and V might sag and sag but
he'll be happy to
score I know it might seem weird to say
it now when he's in a
nappy there is going to be a day when
this cgar will
make him
happy him happy
[Music]
didy