I would
go gay for you i' swing that way for you
gang way coming through I'm going to
make my Les
debut would you go gay for me it might
be fun you'll see no need to go to
Berkeley people would buy were too hot
betties honestly I've thought about you
and me in about aund ways but I'm not
saying we need to show our pride in a
weekend June parade I just want to be
covered in your kisses [ __ ] their dises
we're more than sisses I think that this
is my best idea but I don't need to be
your misses I'm gay for you let's not
delay this breakthrough a penis just
won't make do is this some kind of hu
are you gay for me it might be fun
you'll see no need to go to Berkeley
people would B for two hotties you don't
know the effort I to look into your eyes
when all I really want to do is put my
head between your thighs typically I go
for men who sweat with hairy chests they
are the best but I feel that I must
confess I'm totally obsess with your
perfect for us I'm gay for you you have
to know it's true I'm wet under this moo
moo just be flattered when a straight
girl says she's gay for you don't roll
your eyes and poo poo a penis just won't
make do this must be some kind of homo
Co
[Music]