[Music]
Vice
President
Joe born in scrantom PA
1942 without your pants on hey little
baby
you who knew that you would grow to
be the second in command of the best
country
vice president number
47 that toothy
grin is simply
Heaven I think about you all the
time want to be caught in your
age
69 Joe
bid don't you try
hiding I'm good for the
riding Hey Jo Biden
Jo B for you my legs wi in why don't you
just slide in
Mr B
teeth
What dental
work is there a rise in the
[Music]
temperature around Delaware's former
Senator I could be your baby baby girl's
daughter but when you look at me through
the TV it makes my mouth water you're
the right hand to Barack
Obama now take that right hand and spank
this good to go Mama let's go to
Lincoln's room I want you so
badly it turns me on when you ask who's
your granddaddy Joe
Biden don't you try
hiding I'm good for the
riding Hey Jo
biding
Jo for you my legs wi in why don't you
just slide in
Mr no not that
hole my
moue it don't bother you when two days
kiss or when you're impersonated about
Jason
siss I might be in love with your easy
going
style here take these Viagas so you can
go that extra mile so now we're here you
see I dress
girly but like those times you ran for
press please pull out
early Mr vep if you take me all the
way up promise when I climax I will
shout USA
USA
Bing don't try hiding I'm good for the
riding
[Music]
hey for you my legs wi why don't you
just slide in
M
Mr Mr Joe
[Music]
B you