I thought I knew what I was doing in my
life like how you define yourself is
very different than how other people
Define you if somebody said hey what's
your name you're like Bruce Bruce what
do you think of you well I think I'm
smart I'm intelligent I'm a leader and
you go hey Bruce's friend what do you
think Bruce Bruce is a [ __ ]
skull two different things how people
perceive you I thought I knew what I was
talking about this is what I thought man
I've been doing comedy a long time I
know who I am I know exactly what I'm
doing and I was walking down the street
in
Milwaukee his brother goes hey [ __ ] man
you the comedian right I was like yeah
yeah man that's me that's me goes yeah
you the real philosophical [ __ ] with
the [ __ ] up eyes that's you
right and that's very far from how I
describe myself
but God damn it he's
right God damn it he's
right how'd you get your starting com
went up on a dare was playing little
basketball in Seattle and then I was a
quiet teammate they dared me to do it
but I was scared of them and then I was
dating the girl at the same time and she
said what if you don't make it the NBA
you I'm way better at this my first time
than the first first time ever tried to
do any sport so that was it I just knew
this is it man well and some people are
kind of Born Into sport do you think
you're born into comedy I 100% 100% 100%
of I mean growing up on my family on my
mom side being just non-stop preachers
and and I mean my dad and he pimp and
his grandfather just so he's like I mean
who better better bullshitters than
preachers and pimps and for me be a
comic to be combining both of those
things is yeah just's nothing more I
could have done let me tell you what's a
very effective teaching tool for
relationships two TVs in the house try
that [ __ ] for a little
while two TVs in the house you ever
noticed how vastly different you [ __ ]
TV won
[Laughter]
is my wife likes to watch St that makes
her cry on purpose
I haven't had a good cry since Wednesday
so why don't we watch this cancer baby
documentary oh God this is so sad well
change the tanel watch a cartoon No
don't touch it I need to see
it oh man uh it took a long time in
terms of uh me feeling like I was going
to be ready for it because uh again I'm
I wanted that Marvin Gay like Marvin Gay
when he wouldn't did what's going on he
got in so much trouble from the record
label because he was over by months and
months he said I just know it's not rich
so he went and locked himself in the
Poconos and they wanted him to do the
same old Tammy Terrell pop music stuff
and so I thought if I'm going to do an
album you know I want to be something
special and so I went through the eye
surgeries that I did and I found that
piece of material which took me about 20
minutes of material and I thought okay
now this is what I'm going to wrap the
out album around so I called the blind
ambition and we turned into a special
and then standard records made of my
first album and then you know those guys
being as good as they are having
represented Lewis Black and everybody
who was good uh for it to do as well as
he did in terms of critical success was
like it was I get emotional thinking
about it man it was such a almost
biblical leap of faith to get it done oh
listen oh I got to tell you what
happened so one time I was was about to
have surgery on this the the only good
eye that I have and a New York surgeon
said we can try the procedure and it
might work but it probably won't I was
like might work but probably won't how
many years of medical school is
that everything might work but probably
won't me trying to fix it myself might
work but probably
won't who wouldn't do anything with
those kind of options you could try to
make a sudden move jaill pocket in front
of police and it might work but it
probably
[Laughter]
won't you can you can try to let Jesus
take the we feel like the song so much
that might work but it probably won't
you try to eat a bucket of Popeyes and
sit through a coffee date and it might
work but it probably won't you try to
get Jews of forgive and forget might
work but probably
won't you try to get a big black woman
celebrate quietly on the prices right
guess what's going to
happen what's next one what do you got
coming up next what I've been working on
is um I know at some point I'll have to
do another hour but I haven't really
been chasing that new hour yet uh I've
been really working on uh a television
show which you have in development
called Linux 2020 that I wrote uh on my
phone you know like holding the phone to
my eye like this is how I write no glad
like this and I wrote a whole script
like this because I got I you know I
knew that I have to change something
because I got so much success from blind
the mission I was going the road
constantly 250 260 days a year and I
thought well this is going to kill me
and I have to get to another level so I
wrote this this show based upon my life
and my experiences and my day-to- day
it's something that I've always dreamt
of doing but I'm finally in a place
where you know it's it's me it's what I
it's it's who I
am can I tell you a story this is
exactly what happen this is true story I
came and so after one show I'm in uh I
go to my hotel and then I want to uh I
order a little late night panini
sandwich and uh the dude knocks on the
door I don't have my glasses on but I
got $20 in my pocket as I open the door
20 bucks squirts out of my hand and then
and then he goes hey that's $3.50 I go
okay listen dude I apologize but my eyes
are bad uh I'm pretty sure there's a $20
bill on the floor in here somewhere you
want to just come in here and just bend
over and grab that 20 for me
and he just start
running I mean he took off like he had
fallen for that before you I mean
like so in his mind you know what he
thought he thought that I was some sort
of unauthorized love
maker and that was my go-to move like
that's how I get them is like checking
hotels and I tend to be blind and I call
random sound delivered man and just be
like oh [ __ ] is somebody in this room
because I can't see very well I don't
see nothing I think I smell chicken po
oh I got you put in your
man I got
you you thought I couldn't see but I saw
you the whole time this is all part of
my gimmick