[Music]
[Applause]
yeah and it's is it's nice to be here
you guys seem like you're in a good mood
tonight is that true are you feeling
good
tonight
yeah is it because there's no kids in
here thought that might have something
to do with it I've learned that children
are a lot like farts
you don't mind them when they're your
[Laughter]
own it's nice to be here there's a lot
of pretty girls in the room tonight
thank you yeah well not all of you but
most of you are really nice to look
[Laughter]
at I'm teasing
so I'm
single can see you guys yeah no we got
that we got that D that was yeah yeah no
you don't have to explain that math to
us that's fine no just don't you don't
have to write that on the board we're
good we've got we really need we got
that you know I'm not perfect I'm pretty
close I'm
close mean I got to hit the gym let's be
honest I'm tired of looking like the
beginning of a cartoon drawing
and I think my degree is by far the
worst you can get I had a buddy of mine
graduate with me today he works at a
haunted
house and I said to him I said well hey
man hook me up with the job he goes whoa
whoa it's not that
easy can't just hook you up you got to
audition what are they looking for can
you say
boo how bad was the guy that didn't get
that job was he
[Music]
meow
meow just moo buddy that's all we were
looking for
[Music]