[Music]
it's uh it's interesting though that
like learning all this stuff learning
how to how to live
here sometimes s you can't help that you
miss home but I can't I can't go home
every weekend like that's so you know
things are not better or worse they're
different and then I'm I'm here and I'm
having a good time and then I I get
homesick oh man damn what what what's a
got to do in that situation you're
you're away from your family they're
worried about you all the time you go
visit as often as you can here's what I
do I figured it out here's what you do
when you're away from home and you miss
home you just go to the southern Embassy
and then you can be around people who
remind you of home and everything sorry
I always mess this joke up sorry I said
the southern Embassy I meant Walmart uh
[ __ ] I do that every time I'm
sorry I don't even call it Walmart or
the southern Embassy anymore to be
honest with you guys I just call it the
place White Privilege goes to die uh and
here's why every time I walk into a
Walmart I have have the exact same
thought and that thought is how am I
doing better than every white person in
here is somebody playing a trick on me
what is
happening Walmart's in the midwest are
so crazy like I feel like you couldn't
put historical context to them like
they're that nut like if I could dig up
Dr King and bring him back to life and
just push him through the automatic
doors of the Walmart on the south side
of the
he just walk in and be like
[ __ ] this was my actual dream right
here look at all these white people
doing
terribly I couldn't say it in that
speech but this is what I
wanted also Dante is Dale Earnhart Jr
our
president I'm only asking because
everyone has on his pajama bottom
so I thought maybe it was a law
that's Dante Powell the squirrels get
fat now available from standup records