I don't know if you're all if you've
ever been to Portland which I've
mentioned I love that City a lot at one
for yeah I am yes finally my group's
been
named
yes I went to Portland uh I love that
place um I I occasionally stay with
friends when I'm out there uh and it's
wonderful and I had this idea I love to
cook so I I yelped a butcher shop in the
neighborhood because I was like while
they're gone I'm going to get some pork
chops I'm going to stuff them with chizo
and mono and some fresh herbs I'm going
to make some stuff pour I'm going to
[ __ ] blow their minds thanks for
letting me stay in your house and I I
yelped a butcher
shop and I did not go to the butcher
Shop's website because you don't need to
it's a butcher shop every butcher shop
is the same right they old French Subway
tiles and these wall like wall to- wall
cold cases lit with fluorescent lighting
and every chop and and piece of meat and
oal and snouts and Trotters you can ever
imagine sausages bacon pork bellies
everything's in these bright white
containers with plastic grass for no
reason green plastic grass cuz nothing
makes you feel like oh the meat's in its
natural
environment and old [ __ ] 60 plus year
old retired Marine and blood soaked
aprons with sharp knives they're like
what do you
want Oh that's a butcher shop right and
what I walked into was all dark
repurposed wood and naked Edison bulbs
hanging from the ceiling and a single
100b dude with a curly mustache spinning
vinyl in the corner and I was like [ __ ]
I'm in a hipster butcher shop
okay we can do this it's going to be fun
I love small batch artisanal things I
love the concept of reconstituting an
old idea for a new idea I love the idea
of being an artist I love that oh man uh
just like one Cold Case and it had like
some Terin and uh it had some uh Pates
in it and some chuder meats and some
weird cold cuts I loved it I love [ __ ]
like that what I don't like when you go
to those shops whether it's coffee or
bike parts or record or meat is the
shitty [ __ ] attitude you get from the
people who work behind the
counter these [ __ ] every day they
wake up and they put their [ __ ] and
look at my it's an ironic
skullet and I'm going to unicycle to
work and I'm going to be an [ __ ] at
to everybody that comes in cuz I'm the
biggest fan of this thing and no one
will ever be a bigger fan than me look
at me I'm so special I know everything
shut the [ __ ] up you work [ __ ] retail
all right you work a goddamn retail job
if you're an [ __ ] to people stop
doing that all right I don't give a [ __ ]
how much you curl your mustache or where
the [ __ ] beans come from you're just
being an [ __ ] because you know what I
would shop in that [ __ ] store every
goddamn week I would drive to Portland
and go buy a [ __ ] Terin of hoof fat
from this place if when I asked for pork
chops the answer was oh man I wish we
had pork chops dude look
we do something really kind of like
unique here we're trying to do something
very special where we're like we make
our own Terin and we make our own like
uh like we make a a lavender Pate with
the duck fat and duck livers and just
try to do some cool [ __ ] it's very small
batch we Source locally from different
farms and we just try to do a very small
but cool thing here God I wish we had
the thing you wanted cuz Ian I want to
sell you that but please come back and
get like a fun Pate or something or like
some churis or smoke [ __ ] snouts when
we have that it's so great here please
come back I wish I had that thing then I
would shop there all the time I would
come back and be like [ __ ] yeah I'm
going to that place I'm going to dip
crackers in [ __ ] in a heart attack in
a jar I want to do that but instead what
I got
was okay I'm just going to say this
again for the 11th time today um what we
do here is really unique and very very
special and we make a lot of
Trin and Pates out of like duck liver
and lavender we try to do something very
special here that you can't get anywhere
else like we smoke our own Char cuder
meats and we like to have snouts and H
if you want something as simple and
plebian as a pork chop you can just go
down the street where the Safeway
is [ __ ]
you [ __ ] you and your dumb ironic
[ __ ] deep V t-shirt you skinny
[ __ ] who I know is a [ __ ] vegan
and the only reason you're working in
that place cuz it's funny I work in a
butcher shop isn't that shut up okay all
you had to do is be nice to me just be
nice to my dumb face and be and I would
come back and Shop there all the time
and then all you had to do was when I
was gone just punch out of your rusty
old 1920s time
clock and get on your electric unicycle
and ride to your invite only silk pajama
party at ioni and Piper place or
whatever other dumb hipster names your
friends have given
themselves at your synth band's practice
space above a small batch absent
Distillery cuz why not right and listen
to your music on Edison cylinders unless
your friend marzipan comes over with his
ironic chin strap beard and his 8bit
micro sent and he's like who wants to
hear Atari 2600 music cuz everything we
do is special and unique I don't give a
[ __ ] if you raised a pig yourself in the
back of a butcher shop on a 1200 thread
count Egyptian cotton sheet and hand
FedEd candied walnuts while the movie
Bryan song plays in the background on an
endless loop until the pig just succumbs
to its own onwe and holds its breath
voluntarily committing suicide
painlessly and quietly in a bar and made
of thousand-year-old repurposed wood
from an ancient spice trading vessel
you're being a [ __ ] Meep Barista all
I wanted was some pork chops and by the
way nobody spells Zen with an X
[Applause]