I was so bad at it you you guys like the
the drinking got out of control and and
my thing my go-to was box wine oh I love
to box of wine oh oh pink box little box
Rosé a little white Zen oh oh I got
thrown out of a bar in Austin Texas do
you know how hard that
is by the way for those of you for those
of you who are into it was called
barflies and uh uh I got kicked out of a
bar called barflies do you know how how
much of a stinger that is like you have
to be such a bad alcoholic that even
alcoholics they named a bar after
because you just hover around it like
flies on a
carcass couldn't withstand my Acappella
rendition of land down under by the Ben
minut at
work which I delivered on a table in
Gilbert Godfrey's voice from Aladdin
and baby's got good range and uh uh and
then they uh you know in movies where
they throw someone out of a bar that's a
real thing uh but the the bouncer picked
me up off the table by my belt and then
kindly walked me down the two flights of
stairs to get to the street before
tossing me in and then his friend threw
my box of wine after me I forgot to tell
you I brought my box of wine with me uh
because I used to ter frania on my
shoulder like a boom box from
the80s
and my wife and I had a fridge in our
home that had 12 boxes of frania always
chilling in it like we were doomsday
prepping for a smooth jazz
apocalypse
and and I love that wine I love it so
much it's got a little button on it oh
my God you push the button and wi's like
y yeah it falls into a solo cup and uh
uh like if you're a bottle person I get
it okay you enjoy your wine in a bottle
cuz you're a Kardashian with nothing but
money to spend and
uh [ __ ] bottle of wine man did you
know this is a true a legitimate fact a
a single bottle of wine for you wine
drinkers a single bottle of wine
contains ready one bottle of wine that's
all you get you just get a bottle you
just get one bottle with that bottle
in this box is four bottles of
wine and if you were like me you would
strap it into the passenger seat like a
child then you drive to a 7-Eleven and
get a 72 ooun commemorative Avengers
endgame big Gul cup and you fill it an
eighth of the way with blue slush and
then the rest of the way with pink wine
then you slap the lid on and you drive
to an AMC movie theater where you use
your stubs for the points you pay for
one ticket but you stay all [ __ ] day
and you get hammered in a movie theater
and that's how we surviv Trump uh uh we
stay in a theater uh they can't get you
now
okay quick quick I'm I'm GNA I'm going
to call myself out I know that's a cheap
it's an easy cheap Trump joke I all I
had to do is say his name and we're all
on the same page and we clap and we're
like yeah [ __ ] that guy and but I want
to commit to this because I um I am not
a political comedian I'm terrible at it
I wish were I'm not a smart man and I I
wish I have friends they're so good
comedians they they're such clever uh
writers and they can examine an issue
and turn it over until they find the
unexplored corner of that issue and then
they drill down and extract a
well-written uh sharp concise succinct
joke that channels our feelings of Rage
or or Injustice and they're so good at
that I don't have that I just go from
zero to [ __ ] this that's all I have and
so I can't write a good political joke
um I've only written one in the last two
and a half years I I always ask for
consent before I do it uh so if it's
okay with you may I do my only political
joke is that
okay all
right
okay knock
knock hopefully a military coup that
drags that lying piece of [ __ ] on the
White House lawn and forces him onto his
[ __ ] knees at gunpoint while they
make him watch as they execute every one
of his adult
children orange you're glad I didn't say
bananas uh so that's all I've got that's
the only one that's the only
one he's like linking yeah I wish they
both had a love of the theater anyways
uh get him in get him some culture uh I
got to tell you but I'm back to this
wine thing very important if you're a
Wine Drinker don't let me get in your
head about that enjoy your wine enjoy it
enjoy it in a bottle have fun enjoy a
bottle of wine just don't come crying to
us when your [ __ ] bottle runs out and
you can't roll it up to get more wine
out of it
uh I used to kick that box to shreds to
get that tin bag out and folding into an
origami dragon I had a real
problem that's Derek X Macho cabero now
available from standup records
[Music]