[Music]
[Applause]
drinking with Ian we're here
at woo how's everybody doing tonight
I said how's everybody doing
tonight that's better we got a great
show for you tonight our guest tonight
is comedian extraordinaire Pete
Lee and our musical guests tonight are
Chelsea
boys and now my one my only hot tody
I hey everybody Welcome to
[Applause]
hey everybody how you
doing cheers good to see so many people
here tonight welcome to another
thought-provoking interesting episode of
dream with Ian I found I found that
outside for you um well um thanks for
coming down this is our our finale for
at least the season uh we have no idea
what we're doing after this oh I forgot
my beer yeah you forgot your beer oops
that was very stupid hey guess what I'm
drinking
um but yeah this is our finale for God
knows how long so I'd like to thank
everybody for showing up it's such a
cold crappy night
seriously coming down here to johy Dirk
zombie Den um this bar has been here for
God over 100 years it's had a number of
names and yet our roof is still here
yeah take that metrome yeah what's that
mean
uh-huh yep North Minneapolis oo it's
dangerous hey we didn't spend $10
million on this damn thing anyway
somebody else we to spend uh N9 10
however many million dollars on
everybody make some noise for
Neil and drinking with Ian would be
nothing without Neil but it would be no
good without this next man ladies and
gentlemen the bartender the Stars Mr Ali
stench how's everyone doing
tonight good to hear uh before we get
into the shot just uh real quick note
this is our last night at Donnie Dirks
it's also uh Friday this coming Friday
is Jeff's last day at Donnie Durk real
bartender yeah no no no no he's moving
on to bigger and better things he's
moving on to bigger and better things so
it's a it's a happy not so
yay but just because he's moving on to
bigger and better things doesn't mean
you don't have to tip you cheap
bastards and speaking of cheap bastards
tonight's shot shot
involves a PE stained
snowball no not really it's uh we're
we're we're mere weeks before Christmas
Christmas and if you've seen the
drinking with eating Christmas special
you know how much Christmas Means to
Me I hate it with every fiber of my
being so tonight's shot is called the
spirit of the season season and to make
a spirit of the season season you take a
shot shot of Traer Vick silver
[Applause]
rum you take two shots shots of ginger
ale you take a splash splash of lemon
lemon add a little ice ice Shake It Up
Up strain
it and and happy Quanza Hanukkah
Christmas festival Spirit of the season
shots on the house
house
yeah hey everybody it is the spirit of
the Season as made by our dear friend
and Confidant Mr Ali stench everybody
put him in the
air yeah let's do this on three one two
three
salute ah delicious it's as delicious as
the spirit is I guess I don't know
it tastes like
Grandma no it doesn't actually I've
tasted your grandma what does she taste
like oh what what what does she taste
like depends
um oh it's a classic but it still
works uh anyway um believe it or not
after that uh Montage of half-thought
out comedy Minneapolis is actually known
as being a halfway decent comedy town we
have many great new clubs here we have
many great old clubs there were a lot of
clubs in the middle that went out of
business but that's okay we won't
mention them our next our our only guest
tonight uh he's headlining at Acme uh
all this week and today's live we're
doing this live right this
happening uh he's playing at Acme he's
headlining uh and he spent a lot of time
here uh everybody put your hands
together for Pete
[Applause]
Lee how are
you wonderful yeah and put it down on
your dream with you and coaster made by
our friends at Grain Belt yeah I know
right you have your own coasters this is
wonderful yeah I know and and they're
really flimsy and cheap I keep I keep
slatting closer to you like you know you
on TV you have to like sit uncomfortably
close and be like this is this is normal
we're just having a normal conversation
dudes drinking Grain Belt Quality
Beverage yeah ask for it by name yes so
anyway you're from uh Jamesville
Wisconsin originally um and you move can
I move away from you right now no I was
kind of digging this all right
um okay now now we're on your one shot
all right very good uh so you're from
Jamesville Wisconsin
uh has anybody here actually ever been
to
Jamesville really they were they
wouldn't admit it they were actually
correct tooo okay yeah now I'm from uh
I'm from M Indiana small town in the
midwest nobody nobody Woos for my
town um so how old were you when you cuz
you moved up here right out of there
what what made you come to and and how
bad really is Jamesville Wisconsin um
all right I'll answer your first
question ver um why did I come to I I
went to the University of Minnesota of
course okay and um and basically I did
that because I didn't get accepted to
the University of Wisconsin yeah so
that's why because the Badgers won the
Rose bow the year before I went to
college was why I went to this cool
comedy City really so like if I would
have gone there I'd probably be just
some fat Wisconsin I you know like
reliving my Glory Days and working at
Menards so You' be you I mean by saying
by saying a fat you're being a bit
redundant you you just be a wisconsinite
at that point I mean there's a reason
why our state is shaped like an oven
mitt you know like they are some fat
people in Wisconsin thank you thank you
for laughing one person laughed at that
um now you came here too and then and as
I said and as you said this is a good
comedy town did you have any inkling
that you wanted to get into comedy when
you came here cuz how old were you when
you when you set foot on our Shores um I
was uh 17 when I when I came to college
and I you must you must have been a
smart kid then huh no I just uh my
parents am I am I ringing I don't know
who's ringing I don't know what's
happening but um yeah I'm I'm looking
frumpy I need to sit up no I'm out of
frame um I looked really manly there you
know when you looked more manly look at
me I have no sitting here yeah look
at sorry you totally asked me like three
questions then I'm like I'm acting like
one of those people in the Best Buy
camera Department like look at me I'm on
the
monitor look at that guy he's like no
all right no that wasn't good at all um
that's why I have a beard but anyway um
sorry guys I really this this we're
doing like the Mystery Science Theater
live you know just put the camera on
people and make fun of him for 10
minutes um sorry um uh but but no I I
came up here and um my first night on
stage was actually Nick swardson's last
night here okay we have some fans of
Nick swartson here
I yeah and um and he actually has helped
me out a lot in my career um I I met him
that first night I went up to him as a
nervous fan and then about a year later
he let me do guest sets on the show at
Acme really and um and years after that
I sent my tape to Comedy Central and you
know I I had no representation no
management and um he was in a he was in
a meeting and he took advantage of it
he's
like no none of that but um do you like
how I got all Minnesota I was like no
none of that oh that was inappropriate I
feel I feel awkward um no but he uh he
actually was in a meeting for his show
gay robot yeah and um and he saw my tape
in the conference room and he was like
hey are you guys going to watch that
video and uh they were like yeah you
know we'll we'll get around to it he's
like no I mean are you going to watch it
now and um and he made them watch the
video and that's how I got my first TV
appearance so no kidding so I mean it
all worked out me you know me meeting
him that night and and uh us clicking
comedically so so it's more about who
you know then really it's really about
who you know yeah it really is because
when you moved here you had no
aspirations for comedy and Minneapolis
made you into the comedian you are I
would not be the comedian I am without
Acme in Minneapolis yeah
now
W and let's talk about this because a
lot of people talk about how important
Minneapolis is to the comedy scene all
of those people live in
Minneapolis um now how does it how does
it rank nationally because you you moved
away right you're in New York now so you
can actually take a look look at this
from a bit of a distance how how does
Minneapolis hold up well yeah I mean not
only am I in New York with some of the
greatest comedians but I've also toured
around to all the other you know great
cities and and Minneapolis definitely um
you know we don't in like Cincinnati do
we oh we don't we barely air in
Minneapolis man oh we oh my God we pound
Cincinnati on the bottom really yeah
Cincinnati could suck it yeah I didn't
know how dirty I could go with that why
don't I say it leav it to your
imagination that's why I said on the
bottom but Cincinnati is about as bad as
it gets um no they're actually they're
actually decent we're just way better
than them um but uh thank you but you
know people recognize you know we're we
obviously don't leave very often we're
still here after the crap that's
happened in the last week yeah we have
no idea how we're perceived especially
as a comedy City but you're saying we're
actually held with it at least bit of
aam it's well I mean Louis Lee at Acme
um I call him comedy Yoda CU you know
he's like 55 and he just you know and he
looks like Yoda he's he's the manager
he's the manager he's the owner of Acme
and um and everybody here is familiar
with Acme everybody's been to Acme I
assume on a number of
OCC well he basically develops Talent
you know I mean most club Owners don't
care like they're just there to sell
liquor and he actually cares about the
quality of the content that's on stage I
mean he's a guy that will bring in
comedians that are sort of up and coming
and and uh you know and and like the
fans at Acme aren't trained on like get
her done kind of humor they're trained
to like when when you have a a funny
joke that you actually have to think
about uh those fans are going to like
that joke but if you went up there and
you're like men are different than women
they'd be like okay yeah we've heard
that you know like they they won't they
won't really get in heard that they are
yeah yeah they're very they're a very
Discerning crowd and um and you know
it's basically because of Lewis that
they' be kind you know became that way
um so yeah I mean I'm lucky to have come
up within that system and um and that's
a system that's still in place yeah yeah
he still watches all the new comics and
you know breeds them and brings them up
and I'm just super lucky and when I when
I first came up because his his last
name is Lee um you know and my last name
is Lee but like he's Chinese and I'm not
yeah you know like like I do I get junk
mail in Chinese characters it's weird
like on the one side it'll be like AT&T
on the other side it'll be
like you know sorry sorry that was
racist with but so is my sense of humor
yeah um but so am I yeah hey whatever
whatever um thank you back there all
right um getting this back on was there
did we we're going to finish that I
don't know um okay all right we're
moving on we're moving on um you
mentioned earlier uh like a get her done
sense of humor uh the Larry the Cable
Guy Lois Comm denominator country music
L and buffoons yeah all right sorry no
offense to the buffoons here I actually
no but but you got what was it you were
uh the next big comic at for who Country
Music Television
CM voted this
guy the uh the best new the next big
comic basically what what happened with
that contest was they P they had uh 12
guys it was it was hosted by rooftop
comedy and uh what they did is they they
picked 12 comics and there were a
handful of them that really were kind of
country um and then there were other
people in my whole Act is about kind of
basically um making fun of myself for
being sort of an underdog yeah and um
yeah because like for example on your
website um you you are mentioned as
wussy mama's boy and
uncool these are your own words man
you're obviously not in this for the
chicks when you're when you're selling
it for that no I'm I'm married my unit
died like six months ago so oh I'm sorry
if you're married um bring bring the
room down cuz like I'm sorry no I think
they're I think they're they're mourning
the loss of your unit yeah they really
are they're very sad about that um no
but um but basically when I entered in
the contest I um I urged people to vote
for me because like do you guys remember
like when you were in like high school
and you would um you would basically
petition for votes for like the weirdest
kid in school so that the homecoming
queen had to walk down the aisle with
him of course yeah yeah you know what
I'm talking about that's why I wanted to
be the cmt's next big comic because I
wanted some redneck dude to see me on
the screen and go well who the hell is
this
fell do they look gays on there you know
like
cuz I'm not gay but like to them I'm
totally gay yeah you know and uh how
does this change the people who show up
to your shows um it's really funny
because it almost uh well I I just
finished 125 City College Tour so I mean
those are all yeah I'm I'm rich but um
but um but the when I do a club date now
every single club that I do we actually
do a country night so it'll be like
Thursday is country night and like all
the guys come out and like it's not like
they're like who the hell is this F
they're like uh they're more like uh I
like this guy I could kill him
we can take him out real easy and he's
he's obviously in contact with the Jew
run
media um
what you didn't are you [ __ ] kidding
me you didn't know I'm sorry but this
the last person who found out about it
all right my bad speak you got a new CD
out what's it called it's called gas
money cuz that's what I use it for
okay and um you can get it on standup
records you can find it on iTunes Amazon
and it's damn good it's it's damn good
yeah um Dan schle with standup records
is
here really amaz one of our sponsor been
at the corner of the show for a very
very very very very long time yes uh
he's he's been a very good friend of
mine for a long time and uh you know um
when it's a re this is actually a
re-release of my of you know of the
original release and um he basically was
one of those people that believed in me
before I had anything or you know doing
anything so um I'm I'm gonna cry Dan
yeah well so Dan old friend of mine yeah
bringing bringing people in this is good
because um and now you're headlining all
week at Acme is that right yep all week
at Acme uh please come out uh it's every
I actually haven't been there for two
years because I've been doing so many
colleges so um this is like a huge
homecoming for me so please come out to
the clubs get off your DP and come on
down miniapolis am I
right
everybody Hometown boy good ladies and
gentlemen Pete
Lee and and another Hometown boy that
does good every time ladies and
gentlemen Haiku
Jim hey thanks everybody thanks so much
you know I was hanging out with a buddy
of mine and he said um hey what was that
Viagra Haiku that you did and um instead
of reciting it to him I said You' got to
wait until Tuesday my friend and I'm
thinking wait a second I've got two
Viagra Haiku so I thought I'd do both of
those for you this evening since it's
our last night of our yeah
season and the first one goes like this
Viagra
blindness some men willing to risk it
damn I dropped my
cane
and thanks so much and also I've got one
more it uh is in the the Christmas it's
a chestnut from our Christmas uh Haiku
that I have
and it goes like this popping
Viagra warming up a chilly
night UA the North
Pole thank you so much
people ladies
gentlemen the man of power
himself it's I I'm not saying this is
our last episode ever but it has been
great being here for six years with Mr
Haiku Jim
all right everybody we have um a little
bit of uh pre-recorded merryman a little
bit of Comedy that we made for you um
it's actually a good one the last one we
had was horrible I'm sorry I mean I was
partially responsible for it but it
really sucked um but low expectations
comes High comedy so right now let's
take a gander at it it's called Uh
perfect change
is that it yep that'll be
1565 there you
are that's just a
10 oh my
[Music]
God it's okay nobody's perfect no you
don't understand I used to be what do
you mean you used to be perfect I was
perfect up until I gave you this wrong
Bill well no it's true it all started
when my mom was in labor with me for 9
minutes I helped her out on that
when I turned 1 years old I baked a
little cake to put my face in so that
everybody could have non-face cake when
I turned five I fell and skin my
knee Perfect When in high school I made
the football team with
determination after the games in the
shower room the players would all point
and laugh at themselves if you're
perfect why are you
bald that just
happened what you came in here like that
I came in here perf perfect I've never
had to change my bong water I'm drug-
free I know nine different ways to kill
a man with my bare hands and 10 ways to
save him I've only ever had sex with two
women at once unless there were more
okay that's too much it's true they're
all still climaxing and we're all still
friends shouldn't I have heard of you if
you're perfect I've always been fairly
humble no desire for fame
no one who's perfect would refer to
themselves as humble never told a lie
I've never had to I only eat organic
foods and I've never had to wipe I've
only ever heard Music Live or on vinyl
records I have no Tan Lines my blood can
theoretically cure
AIDS you can't cure AIDS you can't cure
AIDS you're not perfect neither am I
anymore ow just got a hangnail see
everybody gets hang nails they do now
you're starting to piss me off
I'm sorry I've never upset anybody
before hold on it's my
phone
hello
yeah
okay I
see all
right who is that it's my girlfriends
they're pregnant and itchy oh my god did
you tell those women you were perfect I
didn't have to they knew it the moment
we met it was perfect no it was
fate come to think of it maybe I haven't
always been perfect did always take me
two times to remember someone's name
birthday blood type eye color hi uh
could get two packs of
M11 what's the matter man look a little
down I used to be perfect now I'm bald
that's not a big deal I'm bald look
what the hell I got
hair my my phone's
ringing
hello oh hey
what really yeah no no no no I'll be
right there yeah
bye that was my girlfriend she's not
pregnant and she's finally ready to have
that threesome
I'm sorry what what do I owe you that's
$ 855
okay see here
uh perfect change what do you
know thanks take it easy
man what an [ __ ]
yep we threw that together for
written by our friend Patrick B our
friends Patrick bar and Cory Adam uh two
members of our writing staff local
comedians extraordinaire Round of
Applause for
him
and I want you find people to keep
applauding we have down in the uh Donnie
Durk zombie Den uh Bin of fun we have
our band tonight ladies and gentlemen
put a rousing round of applause in your
hands and out your mouth I think that
sounds good for the Chelsea boys
[Applause]
thank
[Music]
you I think we're actually on schedule
too
[Music]
w
you got it I got you turn
[Music]
you got it all I got your turn it
you got
it you got it I got
[Music]
you got it I got you
y
[Music]
[Applause]
ladies and gentlemen the Chelsea
[Music]
boys all right everybody uh thanks for
watching with who am I talking to here
they're talking to each other they have
a show coming up shortly we at Honey on
honey where the hell is honey it's in
Northeast oh yeah Ginger it's underneath
Ginger hop Ginger hop yeah what uh used
to be uh whatam Mig it used to be
something else anyway I'm I'm going to
stop taking up time from him and uh if
this is the last episode of with Ian
ever thanks for watching all these years
uh it's the only show that somebody in
Long John's can actually host screw it
though everybody let's close this out
everybody hey it's the Chelsea boys
[Music]
seeing body don't care
the human body is new to
me the human body's on way
[Music]
[Applause]
you save money and time you get the best
merchandise and service when you
patronize these good
neighbors drinking with the an is proud
to be sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV
Vodka no matter if it's UV blue
raspberry UV red cherry UV green apple
UV Ivory vanilla or UV orange vodka UV
flavored vodka offer a premium product
without the high price tag please visit
UV vodka.com for additional information
and recipes no beer in the midwest has a
grander brewing tradition than Grain
Belt for over 100 years Grain Belt has
been the beer that fathers have passed
on to sons and friends have passed
amongst each other at local bars and
watering holes it is a beer with
tradition that spans Generations which
is why it has become legendary both here
and across the country next time you go
out ask for a
premium EMI Audio the twin City's
Premier resource for DJs bands and
drinking with Ian rentals sales
installation and repair of DJ gear PA
systems and effect lighting a
family-owned business for over 35 years
visit emia audio.com for all your audio
video and lighting needs
a portion of drinking with Ian is
sponsored by The Onion America's Finest
news source and the AV club bringing you
reviews and commentary on the Arts and
entertainment scene available at news
stands throughout the Twin Cities and
online at the union.com and avclub.com
[Applause]
pizza luche proudly supports drinking
with Ian free delivery until 2:30 a.m.
weekdays and 3:30 a.m. weekends download
our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with the end is
nothing without our sponsors please
support them
[Music]
m