drinking with
Ian drinking baby's
blood ritual
sacrifice
drinking
with welcome to tonight's very ghoulish
and fish episode for Halloween we will
be meeting people from the dead and from
Beyond and people that should be
dead and of course the star of the
evening
Ian welcome to a very special drinking
with Ian we decided to go on location to
a haunted mansion here in lovely
Minneapolis tonight we're going to be
talking to people who are dead people
people who are wounded people who are
sick and people who will be dead before
the night's
over I have the skull of Jack PA and the
spirit of John Ritter inside this bottle
of
beer but first I'd like a very ghoulish
welcome for our shantu
Neil and as always drinking with Ian
would not be any good without a couple
drinks over to our bartender the Stars
Mr Ali
stench hey how you guys do
tonight ready for some free
liquor all right no all right well come
back later he doesn't get any okay so
now are you guys ready for free
liquor yeah all right tonight's shot is
called a dead
hooker and what you do you take your
friendly shot
glass and you fill it up
Phill it fill it with Phillips what a
tagline Phillips UV red
cherry you take a shot of
that yay shots no shots and now remember
remember kids I'm not a bartender but I
play one on TV
yeah you take a shot of Ruby kissed
cranberry all right generic do it
generic cranberry
W that's generic for real thank you
Family Dollar take a shot of
that screw the lid back on so you don't
spill screw it no spills yeah take a
shot sour sour hey I told you I'm not a
bartender but I play one on
TV and tips are graciously accepted so
you take a shot of
sour drunk from the fine folks at jro
jro
sponsorship take some lime juice and
squirt some in there squirt
it big
squirt take some
ice put the lid
on sh some lid sh it shake
it Pour strain it because we don't want
any water we want pure
liquor water oh this I don't care about
the ice
dead hooker shots on the
house on the count of three people dead
hooker one two
three there it's our old friend scooter
how you doing
scooter I'm doing very well thank you
you might remember um a couple episodes
our dear friend here Christian Hansen
AKA scooter uh thank you please please
did some uh did some great makeup he
actually slid a girl's throat this isn't
that girl um that the injuries are more
internal this time this man does the
Lord's work um in latex dark lord the
dark lord of course you do this uh
professionally more or less in a in a
need to get paid more kind of way less I
would say so tell us how you got into
this uh well I've always been into
horror movies and uh the behind the
scenes shows and makeup effect and all
that and then uh a few years ago I just
started to get more and more into it
every Halloween I'd do some ridiculously
elaborate costume or something so this
man is your all your your One-Stop ghoul
shop right here Christian we're talking
film quality props available at monster
closet.com ping his website as he should
because he should be getting paid a lot
better for this because the Twin Cities
people say oh the Twin Cities all good
but this man makes fake skulls and he
needs to make a living at it so people
get off your Duff we have been taping
this it took him about 4 days The Mask
I'm wearing together right now and of
course we being a television show
decided what the will videotape it so
here's a montage of how this mask came
to be thanks Christian
for
welcome back to the dram with Ian
Halloween hoot nny ladies and gentlemen
this man has been living breathing and
maybe evening uh Halloween for the last
20 years ladies and gentlemen I want a
round of applause for Bill Lindsay from
Impaler you're too kind you're too kind
now he's not here to hang out with you
bastards no he has a band to promote and
very recently put out by a rud of all
evil DVD the 20 years of of Impaler but
before we get to 2004 let's go back to
83 is it 1983 so uh give me some
background on Impaler well uh we started
in the spring summer of 1983 and uh this
we're going on our 21st year now so we
have a motto it's called too stupid to
quit and I guess we've been living by
that for about 21 years and uh might
have another 21 in there I don't know
hey well you know I'm not going anywhere
nobody's going to hire me so in 21 years
we'll be sitting here talking about how
we wasted our lives and how were we ever
so young we'll look back at the tapes
and and and we'll laugh well that's why
the zombie makeup it it it works on my
favor because the older I get the less I
actually have to put on ah yeah yeah
very nice beautiful cuz we're just we're
getting one year by one year at a time
closer to being Undead so um how's the
sports how is the scene been supporting
you not the scene in the flips side
magazine kind of way but Minneapolis I
mean 21 years is a long time to have a
band together your second album was done
by Bob mold and you know his bands just
fall apart at least every four years
here you are after 21 what keeps you
going well you know it's just a a love
for what I do and love for nonsense and
comic books pro wrestling heavy metal
Punk music all the good things in life
yeah am I
wrong all right now now you're talking
about love but there are some people
that hated Impaler and not just
marginally these are people who hated
impor and were on TV shows so let's talk
about how the man was trying to keep you
down [ __ ] that the
pmrc yeah Tipper Gore and the pmrc they
were opposed to us and uh well well
actually what they did was they held up
our first album Rise of the mutants on
like Phil dony who 2020 Nightline all
these major uh you know news magazine
news shows we make our records to be
played at forward i' like to talk to you
bill there's more sex and violence on
prime time TV than there is any one of
our records that's not true I uh
basically laughed all the way to the
bank because it you know you tell a kid
don't go out and buy this evil rock and
roll record it's it's degenerate it's
gory it's it's bad for you so wait yeah
yeah and and and and to close it up yeah
we made a lot of money we made a lot of
money how many copies had you sold
before people were using you as an
example of what's wrong well it had we
were just in the right place at the
right time really the album came out as
the pmrc hearings were starting you know
as this organization was forming so we
just rode that tide and you know and
started selling a lot of damn records
cuz I mean beforehand you're you're
Regional you know people knew who you
were around town but when somebody's
springing you up on Phil donu people
were like oh my God I'm 14 years old I
like I like stuff so I run out and byy
Yeah Yeah it kicked it up to a whole new
level and then we had these Knuckleheads
in town here called the Peters brothers
who uh had uh the Mount Zion Temple out
in uh Woodberry I think it is anyway
they went around burning records and
stuff and they would always like hold
ours up before they threw it on the fire
and I said that's another $8.99 in my
pocket yeah exactly anyway so that uh
brings us up to well you know 1985 but
let's just say now uh so how's impor
doing right now what do you guys we're
doing really well we just put out the
DVD and uh that's got all of our videos
from past years and I think we're going
to throw it to a video now is that
correct that is correct uh which one
would you like to see Bill uh we're
going to do a number called meat wagon
which was a video off of our uh It Won't
Die album which came out back in uh 1998
yeah way back wins so let's go check it
out
Man black a
big youash and Rock You R and sour take
you in your Darkness out not as WR your
ass is dragons C
ride
Neverland the spell Ste rotten his R to
takes you in your do now not is your ass
is Dragon
riding ride in
the H your ride in
sweep hair try to make it all too bear
get on with the semi wagon will clean it
get a ride
me get a ride in meway on your back seat
and the meway on
you
yeah
yeah to a new world of Gods and
Monsters all right that was from the
1998 album it won't die by Impaler
ladies and Gentlemen let's get some rock
meat wagon meatwagon let's put it on put
it up put it up and we don't want any
hang loose we don't want any I love you
not we don't want everyone the true
metal sign the two devil horns high in
the air come
onal it's a beautiful thing it's a
beautiful thing you're all beautiful Mr
Lindsay thank you for showing up thanks
for having me the show ain't over
there's more stuff keep watching more
drinks please the drink of with the E
crowd very easily
LED they will buy little plastic those
things you put on your finger that are
like little rubber
monsters these are drunken stupid
idiotic smelly people with a lot of
money drop us line at sponsorship at
drinking withth ian.com and make it
happen my sponsor is wandering around
the audience somewhere let's check in
with our dear friend Roy Ian I'd say
this to you you got to stop drinking all
right or just you know stick to beer
beer is okay beer beer makes you strong
and healthy well yeah it doesn't even
get you
drunk camel 16 it's a light beer they
have ice .5 uh you know a little bit a
little bit more alcohol and that what do
you got there sir um Jack and Coke Jack
and Coke Jack and Coke does it really
taste that much different from a regular
Coke yes it does really and you like
that huh yes I do how does that make you
feel pretty good pretty good H Goods to
General of a word um
swell I don't know um Keen
that does not mean that the fun is over
evidence suggests that drinking does not
make you literate what if your ass could
talk I'd interview it all night well you
know if my dog looks like you I'd shave
his ass and teach him walk backwards I
think you planned that one words mine
was spontaneous actually mine was
spontaneous too Mr guy that's rubbing up
against me I'm not rubbing up against
you I merely fell oh
man as I love big bug hey Romy hey you
like drinking you like drinking drinky
huh drink Meister Drink Master Flex you
like that you like drinking
sometimes is this a swearing
show we can curse on this s [ __ ] all
right zombies clamation what gets better
than that here's two and one Gold Digger
by Chris
corn I
I do have a couple of uh Haiku that I've
conjured up for you this evening happy
Halloween
everybody
yeah trick- or treat in
brats ungrateful kids come knocking here
have a bottle
cap and also finally I nibbled her
Mounds she marathoned my Blow Pop Here
Comes Milky
Way thanks everybody ladies and
gentlemen thanks for coming down to the
first annual drinking with Ian Halloween
hotand can I hear hell yeah
so I I called up Satan's Minneapolis
associate Ambassador and I was like hey
Steve what band should we have on the
first annual drink with the in Halloween
hooty and he's like you know what
there's two I want Impaler on but they
have they
Impaler
imp but they have GES and and things
shooting up and blood and stuff and that
probably wouldn't work in this kind of
clearance so in with them not
withstanding I go for All Flesh so
ladies and gentlemen it is my privilege
to close out the drink with the and
Halloween hoot NY with All
Flesh ladies and gentlemen enjy
I feeling need to expose myself to see
your reaction when faces
SW days and Aquatic nights L me
lubricate No
Sol only said dreams with temptation now
Fusion I
desire to believe and TR but
eternally all I
have up mind and mess up in we
drop little girls and old men young boys
and
again
we extrem
united
we come on y'all
KY
and SE
we feel me up with your
SL scar us it's br
God
took we you gave us divers not you
speak and mess up we
Dr little girls in young boys and
chicken and we Dr
Med
we don't WR joy
to but that's not my
point when you inite yourself slowly on
there who's more the
fool you and what do you dream about
when you're
not when you're
alone can you not put your hands on
something that
you who is it all
mindset and mess
up we
Dr little girls and old men young boys
and chcken in Cross
united
we in
like ladies and gentlemen All
Flesh ladies and gentlemen All Flesh
all right everybody we'll see you next
week drink up see you soon drinking with
Ian is proud to have the following as
sponsors tatters clothing where the
square get hip and the hip get famous
stop in today and check out the great
variety of clothes and accessories from
the 20s to today located in the Lin lake
neighborhood of Minneapolis The Hip
Strip City Pages how word gets around a
new issue out every Wednesday telling
you what you need to know available all
over the metro
area caff's Deli and Subs the home of
the sandwich not only do they have the
best sandwiches in town but they deliver
all over Minneapolis till 3:00 a.m. stop
in or give them a call right
now Zips Liquors located in the sew
neighborhood the official store of
drinking with
Ian Philips Union whiskey as you know it
is history Revolution smooth ask for it
by name and please enjoy in moderation
drinking with Ian is nothing without our
sponsors please support them