[Music]
oh
building riding on an eastbound freight
train speeding through the
night hobo Bill a railroad bu was fting
hey it's PA Tomkins everybody oh hi
there Ian how you doing I'm doing good
mind if I sit down it looks like you're
waiting for somebody I'm waiting for a
guy like you to come along very nice ooh
and and you even brought your own cult 4
so just in case wherever there is one
you know I will show up that's right um
Paul Tompkins Paul F Tomkins I'm sorry
uh you might recognize from a Mr show
the sketch Show featuring Kelsey Grammar
um dag sure yeah dag um and you got your
start in Philadelphia yes Philadelphia
Pennsylvania N not to be confused with
Maine exactly yeah exactly and um how
how did you start doing this wacky
comedy thing well you know it's a funny
story Ian um not really but it is a
story all right uh I always wanted to do
stand up but I was never sure how to go
about it and uh I had a friend of mine
who was a little bit older in high
school who went to uh Arizona State and
started getting into stand out there and
then came back to Philly and said you
want to get an act together and that was
it we like cobbled something together
and uh we were a team for about year and
a half then we started hating each other
which is what happens with comedy teams
uh and then I just kept doing it by
myself and despite them exactly exactly
nobody's going to tell me I'm not good
enough and do do you uh you credit that
for your your meteor eyes uh the sheer
you know the best revenge is living well
yeah if if meteors are uh super slow
then yes okay like one of those slow
moving meteors okay yeah I can't imagine
there's a booming comedy scene in
Philadelphia that's where you're right
uh yeah what was great about Phil well I
started around the time of the comedy
boom in the uh the late 80s and there
was a lot of work in the city and the
suburbs and all that stuff so you didn't
have to travel that far from home to
make a living then the bottom dropped
out and I was back to being broke so uh
I moved to Los Angeles in 1994 how long
did it take you to get on uh the the
well-known Mr show CU that started what
95 95 yeah and I started working on that
in '96 so uh I was I was pretty lucky
pretty lucky and it's pretty hateful how
quickly I managed to secure gainful
employment in Show Business and and and
well-known gainful employment and how
much of that has come come back kind of
retroactively he used to be like used to
be a rich man show cuz you had to have
to pay cable absolutely abolutely it's
for all those fat cats people watching
through their monal at home it like it
went from occasionally being recognized
from that show to uh even more
occasionally being recognized from that
show uh but it was it was a great thing
yeah it went from being like a cult hit
to uh uh a little bit less of a cult
yeah you know a very large cult like
more organized religion like Scientology
okay very nice and what was it like
working in an environment like that
because it was all I mean how many has
tape new episodes pretty much every week
yeah um and how how involved were you
with the writing how I mean talking
about you know just two two comedians
starting to hate each other I mean how
quickly did there 10 going to start
turning on each other and breaking out
knives it was a room full of hate yeah
um it was it was a we actually got along
pretty well I think despite the grueling
circumstances because it was we were all
writing and performing in every episode
and it was sketch so we were doing stuff
on location and doing stuff live so it
was a it was a lot of work and a very
small amount of time um but we I I I
still look back at that it's amazing
that it retains the quality that it does
you the circumstances you know what I
was going to hop this Freight but uh
let's hang out for a while yeah if
that's cool with you I mean there's
going to be another one and a half hour
just like
men
yeah now um as a as a byproduct of Mr
show you also became in the The Fan
Favorite a a member of the well the
Tenacious D television program so on
guys yeah my old hobo Pals stumps
whiskey Pete see you fellas see you in
the next
town ah the rails such a romantic place
to be Bey why do they have to uh yes
Tenacious D was a uh that was a really
fun thing to be a part of and I wish we
could have done more of those but uh I
just uh got to be in the movie yeah
which is in post production right now
and I repre my role of the open my Hast
um and I actually have uh a few more
scenes um and I realized recently that
uh I can't be cut out because my stuff
is married to too many important things
so uh my part is safe and secure very
good and there only like Eight Episodes
or eight 15minute vignettes or something
like that there's like six well there's
less than 10 less let's say less than 10
and somehow I mean this just really just
took off yet again due to um you know
people just trading tapes around and did
you see that pick up like walking around
town like oh my God you're the guy that
asked that that's asked to read things
oh yeah yeah that that picked up uh uh
even faster than Mr show you know it was
it was insane and then once Jack Black
kind of really took off it it became
even more insane like I used to open for
those guys um live you know they do live
dates and uh I remember when it was just
like a sort of fun kind of thing to do
to when it became this monster
experience and the first time I did it
after it become huge uh I barely got out
of there alive like if I had not been
connected with the TV show if I just
been a comic would they would have
killed me yeah yeah and so it was
basically like an inside joke to start
like everybody just kind of thought it
was funny and then next thing you know
the Frat Boys love the tenaci KE oh they
do indeed and and what's the crossover
there what do you think the appeal is
for your uh your general f app you know
people like energy and swearing yeah and
uh the D have that in abundance yeah um
and you really can't go wrong you know
especially if you're hammered no get it
yeah D The Pick of Destiny um you got
any spoilers for the uh the
hardworking would dream of spoiling this
film and I did call it a film um it's
going to be really funny like I've read
the script and uh you know I thought it
was funny and this will be fun to do and
then actually seeing the stuff executed
and I got to watch some dailies and
everything it's really going to be
hilarious it's really going to be
hilarious now after that um or maybe
during that let's just say after that uh
you went over to England to tap a little
television show very little called the
sketch show now is it featuring Kelsey
gramar is it just with Kelsey it was
Kelsey gramar presents the sketch show
yes it was even Grande Earth than you
can imagine um we like to call it Kelsey
gramar resents the sketch show since he
never showed up in England to uh do any
of the stuff we taped this is all like
okay oh yeah we taped with Mr gramar uh
the day after we got back from two
months of being in London um you know
got back to America at 9:30 at night and
then yeah so be here on the lot at 7: in
the morning and uh Mr gramar will see
you yeah Mr grammar will see you we'll
redo some of the sketches we already did
in England but with Kelsey and them as a
choice yeah you know but we were all so
thrilled to be back by that point we
didn't care you know we would have shot
all day long yeah um yeah that show
didn't didn't work out so well now did
you see this while you're were taping it
was this like one of those things just
wasn't like oh this is going to be great
I could see in the editing I can see
this all come together in a beautiful
beautiful package it became apparent
very very quickly we had a uh uh
producers who wanted us to just sort of
replicate the original uh you know
performances of the British cast yeah
because this was uh very popular unlike
in America it was very popular British
show yes for a very brief period of time
it was popular for a very brief period
of time okay um they got two seasons out
of it 12 episodes and then um which is
like 190 sketches I think exactly yeah
yeah yeah and like the idea of it wasn't
bad you know fast sketches and um sort
of you know one joking out but but it
was the jokes themselves I think that
there was a problem there I mean it's
it's puns and things like that I think
that when you're trying to sell that to
America you have to let the American
performers give American performances
and it became very clear very early that
there is a big difference between the
way we do things and the way they do
things and it's not necessarily going to
work you know here and it didn't yeah
now was it in all like British crew I me
were they basically telling you what was
funny yeah not really I mean most of the
people were pretty cool but we we did
have a producer who you know didn't feel
that comedy was subjective you know that
it's it's it's either funny or it's not
and if it's been funny once this way
then that's the way that's the only way
that it's funny and it was uh an
enormously frustrating experience you
know and I felt like I was the only one
who knew that this was going to be a
huge failure and uh I was right so I get
some comfort that I supp this isn't even
one of those things where you thought
well you know maybe a second season
we'll get we'll take care of all of that
no you know what I did I thought if we
could if we could stand if we could stay
on the air long enough that maybe we
could kind of do it right you know shoot
it in America for American audiences I
mean it's it's a tough thing to be
Americans performing for a British
studio audience and you know the
producers would say well it's it's 50%
American out there tonight well in
America it's 100% American and you don't
have to worry about you know whether or
not they're going to get little
subtleties in language and things like
that because basically we just ended up
americanizing the British sketches and
saying elevator instead of lift and
stuff like that and you know it just
didn't work now do you think you're kind
of uh cast on the show because of the
experience on Mr Show and because you're
also reunited no uh because the first
round of casting um I did not make the
second cut and then it was the network
it was Fox who said are you guys crazy
this guy is is really good we need to
have him on this show so then I got to
kind of go back in for the network uh
audition wow you were actually picked by
yeah yeah what's that like that's almost
like good news and bad news same time
enormously flattering question mark yeah
you know and do you uh consider yourself
kind of spoiled working in an
environment like Mr Show and then going
to something very regimented that that
spoiled me for the rest of my career
because it was uh you know a show where
everyone cared about what they were
doing and I just haven't had that
experience many times since then you
know uh these were guys who had an
enormous Clarity of vision they knew
exactly what they were doing what they
were all about and uh they put in a lot
of time to make sure that it was done
right you know it was the hardest thing
on that show if you remember there were
the little links between the scenes um
so everything kind of led into
everything else and that it was very
important to them and to all of us that
they be little scenes under themselves
and that it wasn't just always as easy
as coming out of a newspaper photo or
coming out of a commercial TV yeah
exactly so it was uh that was tough and
we would spend many a late night you
know working on those things but rather
than just kind of throwing up our hands
and saying that's good enough
you know it was there was always an
effort to make it good you know you're
uh changing things little by little in
La you have the paf Tomkin show now tell
me about this this isn't something
that's taped for television this is just
basically you a gaggle of friends in a
stage if if I understand it was
something that it's a variety show it's
something that I I wanted to do just
purely creatively you know without uh
trying to get you know networks down to
see it it was just there's enough of
that in my life you know trying to
maintain my career and I thought I just
want to do something that's going to be
fun and uh it ended up being more it
ended up being the most fun thing I've
ever done it's uh you know music and
comedy and I get to work with uh amazing
people like uh you know Dave Foley and
Andy RoR and uh you know Jack Black has
done the show a couple times uh and then
musicians like Amy man and F apple and
Nickel Creek and stuff like that it's
it's enormously satisfying to do and how
much longer do you see yourself doing
that is that something that could just
go on forever I'll keep doing it whether
it gets it's on television or not I'll
keep doing it because it's uh it's just
a lot of fun and I it's been like three
and a half years now so I feel like I've
really uh it's it's evolved over that
time where it's really nice and tight
and uh it's it's a fun it's a fun show
it's been sold out since the very first
performance and uh you know it seems
like people keep coming back because
even though they don't know what's going
to be on the show necessarily they trust
me enough that it's going to be
enjoyable yeah you know and it's worth
$10 yeah hey well Paul thanks for
hanging out with us I hope I hope your
friend shows up I better head back to
the studio they're probably wondering
where the hell I am Ian my friend
already did show up oh too kind mind if
I take the beer please do catch you on
the flip side man thanks all right take
care