my new girlfriend she's a cage fighter
can barely get her in
[Laughter]
one that's a role playing game G she
pretends to be a cougar I pretend to be
again well you know you can tell when
you have the crowd laughing and I like
to get the crowd on these uh rolls of
laughter where you know you call them
belly laughs or Genuine laughs you see
people take their glasses off wiping
their eyes holding their stomachs you
actually see that when you can see them
moving around the crowd that's good too
when they're laughing got my girlfriend
going down on a [ __ ] once can't
believe she stooped
[Laughter]
so I want to uh Amaze you with
misdirection and cleverness and make you
actually laugh I was a sperm donor when
I was younger glad I did that makes for
terrific people watching
[Laughter]
nowadays used to love to go to Walmart
to people watch the time I was there
noticed a couple of normal looking
people pointing to
me yeah well I just got back from the
serious motorcycle rally my seventh
year trying to bring comedy to what they
call the best party anywhere and um uh
when people ask me why I do comedy out
there well it's not CU it's easy and I'm
not a biker ComEd comic but I do want to
be a comic that bikers kind of like kind
of got that edge to my stuff and you
know it's amazing how you do comedy out
there and um I've offended bikers that
just shocks
me my girlfriend just went to the doctor
thought she was suffering from chronic
PMS turn J you just a
[Laughter]
[ __ ] it's good news right clean bill of
health she's also a major germaphobe she
is so worried about getting an STD that
even for oral sex she makes me use a
prostitute
[Laughter]
but the toughest show I ever did there
was the first one I did uh it was uh it
it turned out to be a good show but uh I
was supposed to open for a bikini
contest but before I got there there was
some people uh there was two guys on
stage that were um getting the crowd
ready for the bikini contest and are you
ready for the bikini contest are you
ready to meet the lovely ladies or yes
yeah and then the stage manager comes
out to This MC and goes um uh we got a
comedian oh wait the lovely ladies will
be out soon but first we have a
comedian and the crowd groaned and the
loudest gasp came from me my CD is
called quickies because uh my jokes are
short but
satisfying and uh one of the coolest
things about the CD is uh well I
recorded at a comedy club that I really
liked working and the with crowds that I
really liked so the CED went recording
went well I had good sets I was happy
about that but the most exciting thing
happened after whatever the production
or the engineering or whatever you know
was done to make the CD is uh the
artwork on the cover done by longtime
illustrator of Mad Magazine Mort Drucker
and uh you know I grew up reading MAD
magazine
had to be a huge influence on what I
think is funny and to have you know one
of the great caricaturists of all time
do the artwork for the cover it's just
about the coolest thing ever this book
is nothing but jokes that I've written
many of which have made it into the ACT
some of which wouldn't be in the ACT
unless of course I got a little
encouragement from the audience and it
gives me some the um permission to read
some that might be a little bit darker
and my favorite one that I close with
that are darker from the book is my
girlfriend claims the best sex we ever
had time we a ski mask pretending to be
a burglar I have no idea what she
talking
about fits in your fits in your pocket
or purse conceals easily at work and
sits perfectly in the back of a to of
tank there 500 jokes if you don't like
one keep reading there's a police
officer
are we done I think I think we got it
cool how you doing
f