now available from standup
records when I was little my mom taught
me to always finish everything on my
plate she got me in huge big trouble
first time somebody offered me
[Laughter]
cocaine just bought a new summer home
it's called the
tent I was homeless for a while didn't
want people to know so I slept in front
of a Ticket
[Laughter]
Master I had sex in the I had sex on the
beach once wasn't it all romantic we
were both homeless and it was [ __ ]
cold that
[Laughter]
night I like to get to know a woman
before we have sex just cuz know there's
little chance I'm going to get to
[Laughter]
afterwards last time I flew the airport
lost my luggage luckily they got one of
them Dope
dogs little advice for if you're trying
to smuggle in drugs from Mexico by
shoving them up your
ass don't don't drink the
[Laughter]
water speaking of the body cavity search
sorry to bring this up it's just way too
good to leave out wouldn't this be the
greatest practical joke to play and I'm
not saying that actually do it but say
you're going through customs pretty sure
you're going to get the search get one
of those magician props The Never Ending
silk scarf de if that stood up your butt
have a little note at that's at the end
of it I thought my job
[Laughter]
sucks here's my favorite practical joke
to play on someone who passes out of a
party take fake blood smear it all over
the axe you put in his
hand yeah someone did that to me
once I
hope white York belongs in a bar now
available