[Applause]
[Music]
I'm losing my
balance my interor is spinning out of
[Music]
control I'm losing my
balance heads are going to roll
[Music]
[Applause]
any
goling good to be back
oh yeah [ __ ] yeah that that's the energy
that I missed you know that [ __ ] oh
it's like a big
hug is there a gas leak in here this is
[ __ ] horrible pick up the pace
already guys are on dates I [ __ ]
David with his camera right in my face
the whole show it's a little creepy
right it's a little creepy mhm maybe I
tape you huh how's that feel yeah I'm
taping you Mr raw time yeah oh I have a
show it's on channel 13 or something
17 it's not cable lower tier cable lower
tier cable mhm well now you're on it
we're called the basement now you're on
your show that's [ __ ] weird huh I all
this is a great camera I like this what
if I he got you eating a chicken wing
ma'am it's going to be embarrassing at
3:00 a.m. in the morning when David
shows
on oh it's an onion ring wow the clarity
is great on this fck I thought it was a
chicken wing and I look at it it's a
goddamn onion
ring what is this [ __ ] Tao who makes
this H this is great why hello dick Chie
how are you
M this you know Dick Cheney has so many
problems medically this might be put in
his head someday like so he has an eye
be like his eye I'm dick
cheating how are you are you
good shut the [ __ ]
up there continue that that's a good
don't look over there keep it up
here all right
good went to the grocery store the other
day and I used to self checkout lane you
done that yet yeah what a horrible idea
that is bad enough I have to shout for
my own groceries and I got to [ __ ]
work at Albertson's
too I went to community college so I
wouldn't have to do
that it sucks CU nobody to blame for
incompetence cuz it's you now like
you're the idiot I'm like hurry up then
I'm like don't yell at me it's my first
day but then I'm like don't be training
on me [ __ ] let's
go you can't call me [ __ ] I'm going get
my manager
I bought beer at the self checkout like
you can buy beer but you can't it's like
beep wait for the
lady she has to give you permission to
buy beer she's supposed to look at your
ID but she didn't no from across a dimly
lit room she's like you're
cool that's the beginning of old isn't
it hope the beer numbs the pain old man
[Applause]
and it
dead losing my hair not evenly either L
like this shit's going on the sides I
get some clown [ __ ] going on the
sides when I die this will still be
growing this this is a protected area
here M this is a natural resource will
the pandas live I don't
know when I get my hair cut now this is
how I do it I'm like proceed
live the dream Great Clips super cut
Golden Walk whatever I go to a buffet
for my
haircuts don't when I point at people
[ __ ] keep it up
here sir that is a nice mustache
huh you're welcome to point him out
Dave's got one [ __ ] you guys really
think he still wear the mustaches huh
like it's it's okay it's okay to wear
mustaches you just had him start growing
up like he didn't want it and you're
like hey why you grow a mustache he's
like no I don't want it you're like come
on it be [ __ ] great now he's at a
comedy club there was like nice [ __ ]
mustache
jackass somebody wants to get
laid it's too hot in Texas for a
mustache [ __ ] yeah summertime I just
sometimes when I'm here in the summer I
walk around like this I'm like no
[ __ ] way this is brutal this all is
so hot and then I'll go like this like
oh not even a goatee no way am I doing
that and then I do that oh [ __ ] I have
one
eyebrow keep doing that I'm like hi
everybody I shaved my head cuz I was
just like I'm just going to get rid of
it right now why fight it just shave the
head but I can't cuz I have white
friends with shaved heads
yeah if you're a black guy I found out
you can hang out with the black ball
guys that doesn't look weird if you're a
white guy you can't hang out to the
white ball guys yeah you don't like
friends you look like you're planning
some
[ __ ] all of a sudden it's a
meeting dues are being
collected I like that show super nanny
that's like my favorite show to watch
isn't that a great show I love Super
Nanny I don't even have kids my wife is
5 foot too
so I use a lot of the things Super Nanny
teaches in our relationship now like now
we have a fight I know to get down on
her
level yeah can I talk with her not at
her and then when she realizes what she
did was wrong I stick her in the naughty
Place yeah that's right I love the
naughty
Place how about you sir it it love
it you look so pissed at that joke
ma'am that's okay it's a super nny joke
ah it's [ __ ] okay next
joke not happy with that one get a shot
of that get a shot of that all right
back up here back up here don't
[ __ ] great sir yes sir we got
documentation of that that joke f na at
that table kind of half and
half I have very sensitive lips I'll let
you know that right
now I have to use CarX I have to CarX up
a lot and uh I like to use the squishy
tube of CarX I like the CarX and the
tube I don't like it in that little
round tin where you have to we have to
that's disgusting who knows where this
finger's
been naughty
[Music]
place I uh
so I use it's probably not going to buy
the CD that's cool probably so I use the
squishy tuba car ma that's what I like
to use but it's a jelly be careful cold
climate it reacts weird I was in Denver
one time and I went to use my carax and
I was squeezing it and it wasn't coming
out and I was like what's up I just
bought this how come it's so like rock
solid and then uh a little nipple came
out and I was like yeah I was all
excited I was like Yay and I put it on
like really slow like a [ __ ] X then my
lips felt really good and then uh I put
it in my pocket and it warmed up and I
forgot about and I went to reapply the
CarX 4 hours later I just squeezed it
really hard again and [ __ ] shot all
over my
face it looked like I was in a porno
yeah and I was the
[Applause]
star my guy didn't have a mustache
what a mess that would
be 20 bucks let me shave it right now
let me shave your mustache right now
just with a shitty knife from the
kitchen I will give you 20 I'll give you
that camera that shitty
camera with the show huh that's a deal
just come over [ __ ] just rip it off
evidence oh
evidence what [ __ ] lawyer here
you don't need to be all
judicial it's a it's a big word isn't it
you don't know
me you don't know where I've been I got
I got several dictionaries at the
house I don't read them I hate reading
I'm done with reading [ __ ]
reading finish I know how fast to go on
the highway that's all I
need my friend the other day is like you
should read this book it's really good I
was like why don't you just tell tell me
about
it seems kind of dumb for us to both
read
it he like you can get it on tape a
books on tape where fun meets [ __ ]
boring
yeah hand it over I'll put that [ __ ] on
shuffle you guys don't know about
Shuffle reading do you that's some West
Coast [ __ ]
there you guys are Golf Coast
mhm Golf Coast
Coast that's
right did you guys give the K train and
relief people did you help out do it I
like how the NFL the NFL had a you could
actually donate money during a halftime
of a football game you see like a Monday
night football game you could actually
call in and talk to an actual NFL player
and donate money which I thought was a
wonderful opportunity for children to
talk to their fathers for the first
time looking like that like really oh
easy Edie
don't [ __ ] with those
millionaires I know Jim Kelly personally
he [ __ ] he hates you he doesn't not like
your he doesn't like your naughty Place
joke he
does no [ __ ] bve how can you Mo the
camera and look everywhere else you got
to watch the
reaction right here budy it's all about
the right here star
used to live in New York and I loved
living there cuz whenever wanted to feel
like a winter I would just hit the
streets of New York City and start
walking down the sidewalk at the exact
same Pace as somebody else and I would
pretend like we're
racing and after a couple of minutes of
that I would pick out a fictitious
finish line up ahead that only I knew
about and as we both crossed at the
exact same time I do one of those things
Sprinter do at the end of the race I'm
like but then I was like good race hone
he's like who the [ __ ] are
you I'm like I'm D I beat you fair and
square don't be
shitty he's like there's no way you
could beat me I'm like really cuz a
second ago you said we weren't even
racing now you're questioning if I can
beat you he's like you've been on the
you're on the roids you're juicing man
I'm like whatever that's when I have a
friend from the freshy shot Polaroid
picture of me beating him at the wire
I'm like in your face see biscuit how
you like that yeah but he's like this
has been doctored I can tell this is
touched up too late I already got roses
around me and I'm chugging milk and I
give him a second place trophy cuz he
goes back to work and is like how was
work [ __ ] did you raise
somebody you can't even say no cuz he's
got a second place trophy in his hand
and they real second place was the guy
really fast now he's pissed he's like no
he one those [ __ ] things at the
end [ __ ]
[ __ ] a lot of words for that
joke I don't take you through half your
show yeah that's funny my wife's
Catholic so we go to church every
year I'd go more often no new songs have
you notice that write some new Tunes
I'll start showing up more it's like
they finish that book and they're like
[ __ ]
done I like church cuz I like to recite
the Lord's Prayer like a hobbit it's
like my favorite thing to do the Lord's
Prayer like a hobbit I'm like our father
you are in heaven H be thy name
thy kingdom come thy will be done in
Middle Earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily
bread and forgive us our trespasses we
for those trespass against us it's great
cuz every was praying in front of you
like what the [ __ ] is behind
me and I'm like class of 88 that's who's
behind
you get some new
Tunes I also uh my wife is Irish which
is school cuz I like to talk like I'm
Irish and I'm around her family and they
hate it so I know it's racist but I
can't stop myself either it's like that
fun type of racism once it gets going
you can't stop
it no like right when I get out of bed
I'm likeo morning
everybody oh let's get down to the sh
and see what's going on they like we're
not Hobbits I'm like whatever prove it
I don't think I'd be that comfortable
doing that I was mared to like a black
lady like I don't think I could wake up
in the morning and be like where's the b
n at
[ __ ] I [ __ ] your mama going to cook
me the [ __ ] got to buy 12 [ __ ] eggs
at a time I like AR give me no [ __ ]
AR with one egg [ __ ] cracking in
half funny but I don't think I do
it cuz I'm upy
I like to you do that I like to do that
I like to do that I feel like I'm
playing like a horn or trumpet trumpet
yeah like for the
king it's [ __ ] heavy though I'd be
like sit your ass down King stop walking
in and
out how's the king doing by the way is
he doing good you have a t
on which kingdom do you uh come from do
you come from
Far tell us of your
Journey 5 whole miles five whole miles
oh what a shitty Kingdom that must
be there's a 5 mile radius where is
it it sucks yeah shitty
Kingdom you got a moat got a moat those
are
big I'm putting a mo in over at our
Castle Brinks they coming out
[Music]
digging what if you could trace Brink
security back to like the first moat
ever like they were [ __ ] on it like
way back then they're like we're digging
Moes and then they just you know they
kind of kept with the
times like I know I haven't hit my
stride yet in this show I know that I I
can feel it you know I feel it lack of
laughter I'm a [ __ ] Pro when I hear
no laughter I'm like [ __ ] buddy you're
not doing too well I don't give a [ __ ] I
got a CD for sale after the show you'll
listen to that and be like a [ __ ] okay
that's what it's
like [ __ ]
Popp it's 10 bucks see in the lobby
line
up huh for the [ __ ] CD that's for
what for [ __ ] I'll be give him
[ __ ]
for5 five bucks why why is my CD more
valuable than a
[ __ ] cuz it's goddamn good that's why
there's robot plans in that [ __ ] you
know robot plans go for $50,000 on the
outside not tonight in my CD robot plans
and comedy 10 bucks yeah see and I don't
have change either if you give me 20
you're [ __ ] getting
two that's how I move them that's how I
move them lack of
preparation you want to buy all
50 you buy all 50 I'll throw in the
bag Mar you think about it it's $500 you
sitting on 500
large you wish I wish
too I wish a millionaire would come out
to my show and be like it's a million
bucks Teddy good show and I'd be like
[ __ ]
yeah and then I create a show and
compete against you I'd be like cooked
time like your show's raw time I'd be
like cooked time our time is cooked
prepared your shit's raw you sick and
have the ships but not on my
show your show spreads bird flu not
mine not my
show you don't know about bird flu like
I do now I know bird flu I can't wait to
get bird flu
I think I might have it cuz the other
day I allowed my wife to feed me by
vomiting in my mouth which is I think no
that's how birds eat that's not sick
that's science you don't
understand I was like gu was hungry then
I ran outside and [ __ ] on a car for no
reason I was
like that was freestyle I didn't plan
that I just I'm like I can make bird flu
funny my [ __ ] jokes aren't work and
start strabbing some things Ed scraping
that's what I said not even grabbing
scrab
it that's not even a
word you guys still laughed why cuz I
forced it in your
face scrabbling scraping that's not even
on the
CD going be on the next
one manipulate I made that word up the
other day to make somebody do something
by applying pressure to their
nipple manipulate [ __ ] shave that
mustache okay easy Edie easy easy we're
the dragons please don't [ __ ] with us
like how do you know my
name cuz it's [ __ ] right there
dren oh [ __ ] what's up
Dr yeah he's like okay
beer what's that beer you need a beer
drons need a beard table two no table
103 you it's reserved for the show like
[ __ ] uh did you get your tickets on
eBay we didn't know what we were getting
you didn't know what you were getting H
oh
you pretty good pretty good I'll recover
I'll
recover it's good stuff it's good stuff
get out of his lap not
here
God I already got the mustache on for
you is it coming off later it is yeah it
is I like it it's
cute you should [ __ ] get the things
get the
things look at
me didn't get on a bus and light up a
joint everybody else is like what the
[ __ ] the Queen's like what is going on
here this Jester is
horrible is not the thing I wanted to
see I journeyed five miles past Dr of
everything to see this show it is
horrible just not to my life and I would
have him beheaded if he does not do
another [ __ ]
joke my kingdom [ __ ] jokes are all
about look at that what's up
Chandy the weight staff is like bored
she's like
hey to get some jokes
buddy this is fun you like this story my
parents I embarrassed my wife I punked
my wife the other day I like to punk and
punk people it's my thing I got a show
coming on Animal Planet called punk and
pets it's like yeah where I Punk
people's pets it's very funny like the
first episode's already shot getting
huge numbers right now too um I I uh I
Punk uh I take a a I poop you like this
I I I take a poop and kitty cats Bowl
right right then the cat comes around
the corner it's
like then
right and then I jump from behind the
counter I'm like you've been pumped Mr
Whiskers and then the cat's
like yeah that's the first episode
that's already shot something good drop
that in the
fall dropping it yeah drop a like it's
fall that's what we got going on it's a
little taste of the song that goes with
it Drop It Like It's fall you know
that's funny because leaves fall in the
fall Dro them like a
leaf [ __ ]
doesn't always work when I wing it does
it sometimes
don't but here's the story so uh so I
got my wife today got a good prank on
her [ __ ] out of the park uh my
parents came out to visit us and we
decided to play poker right so we're
playing taxes hold and my dad gets a
full house three of a kind in a pair so
just to be funny I was like a dad you
got the full queef look at
that like okay she knows what a queef is
apparently the rest of you don't so
just I have to tell you what this is I
hate to bring this up but if you don't
know what it is it's not going to be
funny but queef is
slang
slang for [ __ ]
fart yeah that's gross right that's why
it's funny to say that in front of my
parents they don't know what a queef
is my wife she knows what a queef is she
what the [ __ ] wrong with
you full queef Dad good job
so that's funny enough right gets
funnier my dad's like the full queef
look at that I got the full queef and
then my mom's like what's a queef show
me what a queef is I want to see queef
don't you think this is my wife's worst
nightmare her in-laws queef queef
queef like they couldn't stop saying it
couldn't have worked any
better now here's how beautiful a person
my wife is she's decided to explain to
my dad what a queep
is well she's afraid he'll go play poker
with other people and they' be like oh
you got the full queef way to go that
beats a dirty sanchez right
on I don't even know what that is and
apparently you two do
so so she's really nervous right very
very nervous and she goes she's looking
at my parents she goes do you guys know
what a queef is and my dad's like turns
the cards like yeah I'll just do this
right she's like okay um a que is uh a
que is it's
air it's
air comes from a part of a
woman air from a woman but you wouldn't
want to breathe
it and they're both still just staring
I'm [ __ ] dying I'm laughing so hard
like I'm crying I'm like I don't have to
work out for a week I'm like oh
[ __ ] so she goes okay um it's it's
uh it's gas it's a gasy em
Mission it's an emission of gas I'm not
sure but I think she was like when she
did
that it's a gas emission you know from
from the
vagina and they're both still just
staring and this is why I think my dad's
like the funniest guy in the world
because right before she explains it for
a third time my dad goes honey I know
what a queen f
he just thought it'd be hilarious for to
explain it twice in front of my
mom who still has no idea what a queef
is unless that's a Snapple fact she'll
never
know I love Snapple I don't even watch
the news anymore I get all my [ __ ] from
Snapple
cap if it's important Snapple will put
it on a
cap that is just for that table
you guys like the iced tea do
you I hate smoothies [ __ ] smoothies when
I see somebody eating a smoothie I go
crazy makes me insane lose my [ __ ] I
think they're making our country weak
smoothies yeah eat your fruit like a
goddamn
adult how lazy we can't even chew our
food
anymore when I see him buying I get in
the regist I get in their face I'm like
I'm a little baby and I can't eat a
banana like a big
boy o I got to have a smooy pushy Wishy
my little sippy Tippy cup cuz I'm a
little
baby then I rip off my clothes and I
have a onesie
on I have a onesie it's not sanctioned I
made it myself it's boxer briefs and a
t-shirt same color I just tuck it
in so it looks like a onesie and then I
sing to my wife baby likes to Jiggle It
for
[Music]
mother J
one point I'm going to [ __ ] hit
something you guys will be like
hilarious not a big fan of casual sex
I've always opted for formal sex I
prefer formal sex I like to wear a top
hat and a cumber
bun and say things like Miss
[Music]
Penelope might you do me the honor of
allowing me to Ram you in the can h
give your trolley a good roding
eh can I see your precious
pieces I love saying that my wife hates
that she's like don't say that that's
creepy that's the worst thing you could
tell me something's creepy I'll just
creep it up it's like a challenge I take
it to the lab and I creep ay it so now
right before she falls asleep at night I
whisper into her
ear can I see your precious
[Music]
pieces and then I protect my f
face she's Irish she'll cut
me did you guys know my wife sleeps with
a knife she doesn't know it
either but I hid one under her pillow
and then I have my friends come over and
I randomly pick up the pillow and act
surprise I'm like what the [ __ ] is
this and then my friends are like holy
[ __ ] is that bad over here and then I'm
like we're just trying to work through
some
[ __ ] that way if we ever get in a fight
public and even if I'm losing my friend
will be like why are you trying to stab
Eddie at
night and then she'll be like what the
[ __ ] are you talking about which makes
her look more
psycho now she's trying to hide
it got doing that writing some poetry
got some things going
on when we have arguments I sing my
argument now with anybody if I have an
argument I sing it because you know what
I've notied people interrupt you if
you're arguing with them which is rude
but if you sing your argument they won't
AR they don't know nobody interrupts you
if you sing so like when we fight I'm
like why do you leave all the drawers
and coverboard slightly open I feel as
if I'm living with a polter guys and
then she's like um like wait for the
[Laughter]
course and then he goes on like I really
mean it shut up all the [ __ ]
way you're like dance I love dancing I
don't even need music I need to get on
that reality show not that [ __ ] one
would to give you a partner that [ __ ]
would slow me down I need to be I need
to be on that other one where it's just
me and [ __ ]
dancing I dance I don't even need music
like my wife she's like stop for the
[ __ ] dancing she's like even in
public she goes public it's been like a
month cut it out she goes what other
wife has to tell her husband to stop
[ __ ] dancing and I was like Mrs
Patrick
swayy you don't [ __ ] with this this [ __ ]
is
crazy we went on a vacation recently
where we went snorkling and she was like
let's go scuba diving I was like let's
not she's like why not I like I don't
think I should be in charge of my own
air that's
why and then she was like oh yeah that's
a good
idea I could do it but I shouldn't
because you have to mix your air and I
wouldn't have a chance like 5 seconds in
I'd be like too
much then your eye pops out of your head
and that would suck cuz a mask would
catch your eye and your other eye be
like what the [ __ ] is that my
eye I'm like holy crap that is my eye so
you go to take your mask off you get
your eye but the water swishes in it
sucks it out then a big sea leads it
right in front of you cuz he thinks it's
like a frozen snow PE he's like [ __ ]
dibs then you got to cut open his belly
and crawl in there but there's like an
old man with a puppet hanging out right
the puppet's like I want to be a boy
someday huh
[ __ ] you guys don't read either fine
I don't
care it's a
classic I didn't read it I saw the
cartoon love cartoons you know I don't
like to what SE Turtle someone go sea
turtle what's a sea turtle it's like a
turtle that lives in the sea pretty
goddamn self explan
explanator tried to come off smart and
it [ __ ] killed me it's pretty
self-explanatory turtle is in the sea
sea
turtle you never heard of a sea
turtle they're like huge pinio was in a
whale it's what Pinocchio Pinocchio is
in a whale I know well you know what
here's the thing about my jokes
uh [ __ ]
people it's [ __ ] insane this I know
he's in a whale but I'm like I'm not
going to [ __ ] why would I why why
would a whale eat my
eye like how deep would I have to be
[ __ ] scuba diving the goddamn whale
comes up on me I'm like just make it
that's the thing about comedy all right
you just make it a sea turtle it doesn't
give a [ __ ] the sea turtle don't [ __ ]
care the world doesn't care you know who
cares lady at table 101 just like she
like why the [ __ ] why is C tur already
why why oh the other day I went on a
safari and uh and so I'm on a safari
right and I uh and I decided to put on
scuba
gear and I my eye shot out of my head
and a giraffe ate it and the giraffe was
like oh that's like a big kind of a
thing that you would eat in Africa dibs
that's what the giraffe said up his
little Pond he's like dibs and then he
went down his big neck and he ate it and
I got a cut open his belly I crawled in
there and there's like an old man with a
puppet hanging out and the puppet's like
I want to be a boy son day
yeah oh so other time I was in space I
was on a planet and uh and I was sco
diving on this plan I found water cars a
lot of [ __ ] thought out so I'm scoob
diving and then I then I took off my
mask my eye shot out of my head and a
[ __ ] galac takaka a
it yeah it's like a giraffe it's like a
giraffe not even a whale it's like a
giraffe in space and I ate it I got in
there and like a ET was in there and and
old man in a puppet and the puppet was
like I want to be a boy someday and then
eth was like I met a nice little boy on
Earth one time he helped me get home and
then I was like what the [ __ ] going
on I asked other time he's like [ __ ]
all right we got it we got it my got you
can do what you want
buddy that was great like it was a whale
it was a whale that's not on the CD that
whole rant right there the first part
with the turtle that's on the CD all
that other sh
[ __ ] yeah you did like it didn't you oh
there you
go right back to [ __ ] nothing
huh yeah well [ __ ] you guys too there
nothing just zip
Z even the Queen's like holy
[ __ ] I once bought a giraffe from a
Muslim because it
came hit the market and I bought a drop
and I I wrote it about and I killed it
with a with my husand here double handed
sword and slay the
giraffe she's been to Africa well all
right okay just so you know I don't
think she's really A
queen just I don't know how far I have
to explain this
today cuz now I'm kind of worried now
I'm a little [ __ ] worried about to
make up the the [ __ ] the
audience they're like there is royal at
the
show apparently 5 miles from here there
is a
kingdom and Brink security used to make
Moes and whales do not like sea
turtles they're like shut up sea
turtles shut
up there a guy that has a
mustache not happy about
it but at the same time he bought free
CDs which I thought was very
nice three CDs only
[Music]
$40 oh they're $10 each I know but those
you get in threes you buy them in threes
you get you give me an extra
10 no that's a that's that's [ __ ]
that's base 10 that's that's the new
that's
yeah you ever have an argument and then
that's how you end it like yeah that's
it you don't have any facts or anything
I think were talking about 16-year-old
car drivers and I was like I actually
think you're probably a better driver
when you're 16 than when you get bad
habits and you take them in and then uh
my wife was like yeah cuz that's what
insurance company say huh and she was
right but uh I was like ah I didn't even
have any facts all right you know what
[ __ ] it let's just uh get more jokes no
more no more about Eddie's day I'm sorry
to bore you with little talk I had in
the car today oh Eddie please we had the
same we had talk talks we're not telling
you our
talks we're not trying to sell you our
CDs after a show
Eddie you get some good stuff Dave this
is I don't even think your camera's on
at this point I don't want to be rude
and put it away cuz I'll hold it up [ __ ]
this I'm not waste my
table good luck with the next
joke
I love being a comic I do J I'll tell
you that she's like Edie well being a
com you I'll tell you exactly like I'll
tell you here's the deal because like I
wasn't thriving in the workplace before
like you've seen how I've stuck to
nothing like you've seen how I can't
focus on one little goddamn thing like I
used to get written up a lot that was
kind of like my thing at work that was
kind of like what I was known for have
to sign something at the end of a
meeting you ever have to do that at work
that's always fun my biggest regret is
all the bad jobs that I ever got fired
from my biggest regret is that I never
caused a scene and if you get fired
especially from a shitty job you should
go off right act like an idiot what do
you care Burger King doesn't talk to
Wendy's so I have a plan if I ever have
to get another job and I know I'm going
to get fired that day that day I'm going
to go to work with like a pocket full of
glitter and when my boss fires me I'm
going to be like oh sorry it didn't work
out
glitter I'm going to throw it right in
his
face have you guys ever tried to get
glitter off
before that's why that is funny cuz you
[ __ ] can like I might be fired you
saw us to walk around work the rest of
the day I was sparkly and
[ __ ] man what' you do with lunch eat the
ass of a unicorn look at you yeah clap
on that one pink shirt that's
right I know it's a good I didn't say
shitty pink shirt I said pink shirt he's
like it's a good looking shirt [ __ ] yeah
you should wear it with your little
mustache
don't you think you were to eat the ass
of a unicorn glitter would come out yeah
like if you had to pick something queen
and I already picked glitter what would
you pick if you were eating the ass of
unicorn what do you think would come
out what's that rainbow rainbows yeah
course like
Skittles like you got the tail up and
you're really in
there Taste the
rainbow who's saying
[ __ ] [ __ ] wouldn't come out unicorn
don't eat so they don't
[ __ ] yeah I know I [ __ ] yeah I know I
know
unicorn he's like all right I'm
out look like like he's different like
you're like it was a whale like you're
really like serious because it was a
whale but he's [ __ ] we're fighting about
a unicorn now see like you're you're
like you're textbook he's [ __ ]
Dungeons and Dragons
you guys will never hang out
again it's not like you're hanging out
now look what I bring together just Two
Worlds
Collide she's laughing from something
four hours
ago man you get like an itch right in
the middle right in the middle go for it
[ __ ] itch it I scratch that [ __ ] it
sticks around I'm not a thug but I have
lived the Thug
Lifestyle I
I used to be deep into toilet papering
tping as it's known amongst the Thugs
and I recently had the opportunity to
take my 16-year-old cousin toilet
papering and I have to tell you this
toilet papering the age of 35 is much
more fun than it ever was as a
child like go do it tonight cuz now on
the police show you have the kids run
and hide I just been tell like it's my
lawn I'm like you little
[ __ ] you little bags of [ __ ]
and it's like your one opportunity in
life you can yell at the police
department and get away with it cuz they
think you're like this pissed off irid
homeowner right they're like easy sir
calm down I'm like don't [ __ ] tell me
to be
easy paying goddamn property taxes like
a
[ __ ] you show up 20 minutes late
it's going to rain you want me com this
[ __ ] out
tomorrow you never think that's the deal
there buddy you're not paid to think
you're my [ __ ] how you oh [ __ ] write
me a ticket you see the
address give me two [ __ ] I don't give a
[ __ ] my wife works go ahead now use your
whole pan I've been drinking too to my
car see if I
care there's a meth lab in my mailbox I
like that I like that how do you like it
that way
love music big fan of music I don't like
rap I don't like when rappers put out
Thug like like thug rappers put out love
songs a lot right 50 Cent gangster
rapper he has a love song he tells a
girl how much he loves her he goes I
love you like a fat kid loves
cake that is
beautiful I could never come if I was
going to tell a girl how much I loved
her I'd be like I love you like a fat
kid loves
carrots mine's better
think about it if you're fat cuz you
love carrots you must [ __ ] really
love
carrots it's easy to attain a big ass h
of cake try getting thick on
carrots noodle it around
50 I read this the other day it's a
little gross but it is medical factual
clinical data I read this a Men's Health
Magazine are barely legal I can't
remember the publication
but it said that a man's sperm his semen
can taste like what he
eats
uh why is there
discussion that was weird I heard like
[ __ ] 12 little cell groups
are [ __ ] chatter heard the
chatter I don't know if it's true but if
it is let that be a little tip for the
fellas find out what your partner likes
and make the dietary
adjustment I'm on a steady diet of
picture frames and candles
myself yeah my [ __ ] T like the Pottery
Barn got his 12200 thread count you like
that I'm going to Craton Barrel tomorrow
so we shall see what I shall find when I
shall
go I think it's me cuz I do a good joke
with laughter and then I [ __ ] kill it
[ __ ] like that
maybe I should listen to the CD and
[ __ ] remember how I Pac
it you're going to love the CD Hey buy
all of them cuz then I'll be out and
then you guys will [ __ ] the rest of the
crowds F [ __ ] somebody
over like you can leave and see the next
group be like [ __ ] hope you didn't
want one of
these we bought all of them that's how
we roll
robot plans
buddy you know what my name for robot
hair is
illuma that's trademark you can't steal
that I wrote it down and I mailed it to
myself and I didn't open the
envelope did you see that works can you
use that in the court of law yeah think
can you think it's like a ghetto P it's
like a ghetto
patent jimny's not in the room he didn't
have to hear that cing ghetto Pat she's
like oh [ __ ] we'll buy a CD if you
[ __ ] if you don't go after
him get a picture of that get a picture
of that right there that's the ghetto
patent guy ghetto that is like the way
to say things are kind of like uh all
right we'll [ __ ] talk
later got sucking me in your world
that's how it happens then you're
shaving your head and you're marching
around a in a
robe I'm like wow this is really nice it
says Ritz Carlton on it and then they
then they [ __ ] it up
[ __ ] it
up I don't know how to get off stage
really this show could go for
hours shut up Teddy
Bear gu a dump
truck did you bring the dump truck park
it out front today good got the other
got the
hybrid where you get a dump truck and
then like a
Prius Honda you got a Honda you got a
Honda yeah oh okay she's like
yeah well you guys have been there
you've been
there remember earlier when you were
eating the the onion ring oh [ __ ] I was
like I started off
great on camera and then I make fun of
Dave's camera oh that's a good
time remember that when you're coming to
buy my CD just [ __ ] remember that
there's some crazy moments tonight yeah
and there's a lot of stuff you didn't
get to hear cuz we were [ __ ] we in
the
moment you want to [ __ ] pull the hand
away from the head sir just for the rest
of this huh you're making me want to go
to sleep [ __ ] right there why are you
guys [ __ ] on what is you got a neck
problem [ __ ]
you [ __ ] up get up buddy you're get
scoliosis sit the [ __ ] up for the last
joke God damn
it I have the queen [ __ ] take your
head off hey like
that yeah yeah there's the queen right
there
holy [ __ ] all right [ __ ] enough
enough wrap this [ __ ]
up we're going to serve it up buddy see
you in the
lobby guys for fun
yeah I believe in aliens I've never been
abducted but I don't think I'm the first
choice
either if an alien took me back to his
Planet he would get
fired they wouldn't Lear he didn't even
know halfway back he didn't pick the
right guy
he be like oh my God what did you
say like kangaroos can't walk
backwards the puppet was found inside a
whale's
belly I should have said that it doesn't
matter I said it anyways I did say it
[ __ ]
yeah he would dress it up though when he
got me back to his Planet like you
brought that gold he tried to sell it
like how why we all
gather
around that's a horrible alien
impression
huh sounds like an effeminate Cajun man
doesn't
it sure is a hot
summer
zip off comes the jump suit
huh welcome to Blue Job City
I went to that build a bear store the
other day have you been to build a bear
that's so crazy it's like you can build
a bear if you have $30 you can build a
bear so I my niece's birthday was coming
up I was like I'm Build A Bear build a
bear so I picked out all the [ __ ] like
the bear the outfit the face everything
and then I when she was like filling it
I I have my wallet I have my wallet and
I was embarrassed to tell her that so I
go uh oh [ __ ] I go uh you know I don't
want the
bear she's like what and I go uh I
changed my mind I don't I don't want the
bear she's said you got to have the bear
and I'm like but uh doesn't even look
like a bear
yet I'm like when's a bear actually
become a bear and I've always been
pro-choice but it wasn't until this
builda bear moment that I was [ __ ]
passionately
pro-choice I was like you can't [ __ ]
make me have a bear if I don't want to
have a
bear there's a lot of bears in this
world without love right
now he's got a mustache just for two
more days until the wedding's over then
he'll shave it the [ __ ] off he's got a
mustache I just made that up buddy
that's not on the CED
sorry give me your phone number I'll
call you every day and [ __ ] sing
think I'm bullshitting I will I will
call you I will [ __ ] video text phone
file wave it IOD cast your
[ __ ] you a't heard about that's a big
file that's a
big okay I'm sorry she just
apolog I like it I it's grown on me at
first I was like is he from France I
wasn't sure now but now brings it
together
he's very shy oh he's shy oh yeah I'm
shy I'm a bit
shy I am I'm a shy guy I'm a shy guy I'm
gu
shy there's really no form to the show
now is
there I did an interview for a magazine
about comedy at the end of the interview
the guy asked me this he goes one more
question goes how come black Comics are
allowed to use the nword on stage but
white Comics can and I was like probably
cuz we haven't always used it properly
in the past
we got a little bossy with
it our N word privileges have been
rebok I don't think we're getting him
back
either my grandpa thinks he's got him
already he sounds like Tupac in his
house like I don't say the N word but I
do sing it a lot cuz it's a lot of the
cool music I like like you guys should
hear me in my tourus with the windows up
play to some weird moments though one
time I had a black friend in my car and
we're singing a Dre song together and
all a sudden I realized that the N word
was coming up and I was like holy [ __ ]
yeah there's nothing in the album that
tells you how to deal with that
situation I was like man can I say it in
front of him and I could see him looking
at me too like what you going to do
player so I just changed the word hoping
he wouldn't notice I was like
Gryffindor then I threw glitter in his
face and ran out on my car you guys have
been fun thanks a lot for sticking out
say hi
[Applause]
see Eddie Goin keep it
going thank you guys very
[Music]
much I'm my
balance my interor is spinning out of
control
[Music]
I'm losing my
Bast through the atmosphere through the
stratosphere I'm out of