with him
now let's
drink oh how's everybody doing tonight
I'm pretty good too we have a really
great show lined up for you not only our
guest tonight she will also be
performing it is the very wonderful
eleny
Mandel and now the one the only the man
of the hour Mr Ian
hey
everybody I
forgot oh man how's everybody doing it's
good to see everybody here
tonight and I I hate I say this at risk
of sounding like Paul Stanley but how's
everybody doing
tonight oh my God you're doing well
that's good cuz that's I'm not getting
pelted with
spectacular another man who does not get
pelted with well the one and only
Neal the Tower of Power the man of the
hour oh wait a second I'm off Q where's
my piece of paper there's my piece of
paper oh no it's still olly Ollie stch
everybody hi
everybody how's it going
tonight double Aces all right so I was I
was hanging out on Wikipedia yesterday
and I was I was reading about rert
Holmes how many you guys remember Rupert
Holmes Rupert Holmes had a song it was
the last number one song of 1979 it was
called
escape and no one really knew about it
because they all wanted to go and hear
about the P colada
song so his record label renamed it
Escape quot the P colat
song now a lot of people confuse Rupert
Holmes with Jimmy Buffett and Jimmy
Buffett can kiss my ass cuz he
sucks but even more rert Holmes can suck
my ass because he's a bag
of so in honor of rert Holmes escape the
P colat song tonight's shot is called
Escape The Pina colostomy
W and to make it escape the Pia
colostomy you take a shot shot of
traiter
vix Bombay pineapple rum
rum you take a shot shot of orange juice
juice you take just a little splash
spash of lime juice
juice add a little ice ice
shake it
up now hold
on you strain
it
and yeah had a lime
wedge because rert Holmes can suck my
ass the Pina colostomy shots on the
house ladies and gentlemen everybody big
shots in the air right
now I want Rous the Round of Applause
for escape the Pia
colostomy Dream Within daring to be
tropical on three 1 2 3
salute that was a god T
sensation come
on don't make me come down
there all
right we got a great guest coming up in
a couple seconds
but real real quick right now here's
something we threw together for you
guys I'd like to have an
army my very own
Army I could train them myself show them
some
discipline if I had an army I'd stand on
a DS and salute them as they marched by
salute would just be for show though I'm
the real boss
here I bet chicks would dig me if I had
an
army I could get girls to sleep with me
when they see how other men carry out my
orders and if they play hard to get just
have their Village bombarded by my
Army yeah having my own Army would
rule some people think having a big army
is just compensation for something else
and I don't see it that way I like the
idea of having a long hard ship I can
take into port or a big round bulbous
bomb that I can drop into some dark hole
I don't see anything Freudian about
that my Army would be so big I mean God
it would just be so enormous H there' be
soldiers who hadn't even seen above my
waist I'd have to put my picture up in
the town square just to remind everybody
who's in charge
here best part about my Army when I'm
out on a date and some chicks like whose
Army is that and I'd be like that Army
it's my Army and they'd be like wow no
way and I'd be all oh you know it and
then they'd go you must have an enormous
penis and then she'd sleep with me and
then everybody would see that I could
satisfy a woman too
I could totally have my own Army if I
wanted that's something that's a little
something we threw together for you guys
it's called if I had my own Army I guess
big round of applause for that drink
with
in we care about you and to prove that
we actually had Espionage in this
episode our next guest is playing next
door and we said said scy in the opening
bands come over here and hang out with
us for a
while Round of Applause for
Espionage who doesn't love
espach but this girl has made this this
lovely lady has made a hell of a name
for herself she has some local ties she
has a new album out called Miracle of
five and it ising
spectacular if you haven't seen her
before get ready to be introduce her her
she's going be doing a song a little bit
later but I want to Rouse you round of
applause put two hands together for lady
Mandel
you don't have a drink sorry we screwed
up oh here you can have some of mine the
the M sorus went away I swear anyway one
more time for a lady for showing up a
lady
Mandel so um you've been you've been in
the music game for a while and you just
started as being a dentist daughter how
did you start as being a dentist
daughter and then end up go and well
screw it I you're you're from Southern
California there's going to be a
question here I swear I'm just digging
for I don't know I don't know if that's
on either where is it at oh there it is
it's not on is it on now is it on now
it's on
okay lady
Mandel we'll start
there all right so um you're from
California right yeah see see that's the
question I was going to go in the
previous take that you did not see
that's where I was going from um and
your your dad's a dentist and I can't
imagine I mean when you hear about like
a local girl from Southern California
especially in the middle of the country
doing something it generally involves
you know riddin and Rehab uh how did you
avoid all these Pratt Falls and end up
doing a hell of an Alum I'm kind of a
goody two shoes really I have a wild
side but I'm I'm a good girl so uh you
know went to school decided I want to
play music and just kept going and going
and going spending all my moneyy so how
can you be a touring musician yet be a
goody two shoes cuz I mean I've been in
crappy bands that played like two shows
and by the end of the third show oh man
I'm smacked up off my
ass yeah nobody's going to laugh at
smacked up what is it too soon for you
people what you go oh I was too I was
smacked up my ass last week I'm not
laughing at that no but I mean so is it
hard to avoid the the the pitfalls of
the road and then maintain an innocent
demeanor uh you know I have had my
moments mostly I I hang out with you
know I stand next to people who are her
getting trash so I don't have to do it
myself you have the secondhand trash
going on you know I've fallen down a
couple times I admit I don't know what
you're talking
about a bit obvious I'm
sorry um and uh some of your early
recordings were with a heart of champion
right yeah a local label how did you get
hooked up with them and they've put out
a lot of good stuff are you guys
familiar with heart of champion it
should
be how did you get hooked up with them I
I know I played I've played in
Minneapolis a bunch of times and I
started off playing here by myself which
I'm going to do in a minute it's my
band's next door and doesn't want to
drag the band's hold the way over there
they're not goody to shoes she's you're
going to be doing acoustic tonight right
or the solo thing awesome yeah uh so uh
I met Dan Cody the head of heart of a
champion at a show Dan Cody local Legend
local uh surveyor and purveyor of the
Arts he just said you know want to put
out some vinyl I said well all right
let's do it yeah and how did that work
for you you have did you spend much time
in Minneapolis on support of this and if
you didn't just lie people love to hear
Minneapolis the best crowd on
Earth I don't have to lie I always have
a great time I always go to the Brian
Lake pole Brian Lake
pole my first show ever was at the
Bryant Lake pole there nine people there
wait a second so your first show ever
yeah how the hell did that happen so I
mean my first show ever in Minneapolis
Oh in Minneapolis Oh okay and nine whole
people shut up miniapolis we love to
support new
artists but I got a free uh bowling game
oh that's nice
of and um one of the waiters bought my
record so I thought that was a good sign
he didn't you know he had to be there
and he was you know was into it so yeah
so I've been going there for breakfast
ever since that first time no and it's
great stuff they're not paying for this
but around appla
like is that the Bryant Lake bul disco
light up there what the hell was that
it's like party well I love to I love to
eat so you know if anyone has any new
recommendations okay Believe it or
you're a very spel girl I can't imagine
that you're you're you're pounding it in
I share it with the guys in the band oh
okay um so okay this uh to track off
your new album girls off Miracle of five
what out what record label Zed tone
zedone um that was recently uh featured
in Television right like some like WB
show or something did I make that up did
I dream that last night I might have I
think it was on brothers and sisters oh
okay or men and trees one of those
okay you know yeah TV I don't watch
enough TV to to really know where it
ended up but just just took the money
and yeah yeah going to Paris that's to
this um and do you have any advice for
aspiring uh you know songs I mean yet
again this has been like a pretty good
Peak for you you're on right now and
thank you for step stepping down and
hanging out with us I mean you're you're
actually too famous to be here you're
first touring musician we've ever
actually managed to get
off most of the time they're like I
screw that but no no thank you so much
for doing this but yeah do you have any
advice I mean it's like how long you
been this like been about 9 years or so
since you've been uh yeah since like the
first D I guess only do it if you really
mean it okay otherwise you know save
room for somebody else okay yeah people
who actually spare yourself the the
heartache yeah
what's kind of a Down we end this on
something do you have any funny stories
from the road or something we can we can
save this cuz everybody look there's
people who are getting down the people
are sad yeah they don't mean it that's
the problem they're just kind of they're
faking it through life
um I have more fun than is legal when
I'm on tour really the guys in my band
are amazing you know we we go sight sing
We Dance sometimes we you know drink a
little too much hey good at Two Shoes
who still drinks too much and that's why
we cam oning with i a round of applause
for lady
Mandel and I I introduced you to
Backstage
but our Haiku specialist Haiku Jim is a
huge fan of el Mandel and so much so we
have changed him a little bit for
tonight to put on a little bit of an
extra show for all of you people and
elany I I give to you haou James Brown
ladies and
gentlemen I am Haiku James
Brown can I get a witness
W you people are killing
me you know I've got some some syllables
for you syllables of Soul sweaty
syllables of
Soul hot wa let me try that again
hot all right it goes like this I got so
much
Soul the lady is faint as I pass
Get Up Get on
Up all right let's go let's go let's go
let's go come on all right
all say it loud I'm back and I'm proud
say it
loud say it loud I'm back and I'm proud
say it loud I'm back and I'm proud wow
that was surprisingly
good all right people I do have one more
uh little tidbit for you
tonight and it goes something like
this Godfather's New
gig Papa's Got a Brand New
Bag
ha good God
y'all ladies and gentlemen
i r it hiu Jim everybody SC
it hiu James
Brown all right uh here's an archival
educational film we found out in the
Deep depths of Suburbia or whatever
let's take a look at big screen and then
we're coming back with more laning
the wood spider is the most accomplished
of all Web building
species recently scientists gave these
tiny creatures a variety of psychoactive
drugs to observe their effects on Web
building when given a minute dose of LSD
the spiders web took on an unfamiliar
minimalist
structure when given caffeine the web
structure was not affected but the
spider's Behavior was
given THC the active ingredient in
marijuana the spider didn't build a web
it built a hammock where it lay all day
and watched the caffeine spider
go when given alcohol the spider built a
web found a mate and raised over a 100
young but the mate got a restraining
order and now the spider can't go within
100 cm of the
web the crack cocaine spider figured
building webs was for suckers waited
till the caffeine spider was exhausted
then came up behind it and popped a cap
in its
ass nice web Mr crack
spider when winter came the marijuana
spider had no place to live it ended up
in the crack web as the crack spider's
[ __ ] for more information on the crack
spiders [ __ ] contact the Canadian
Wildlife service in
Ottawa all right everybody we can't
bring you this much television without
having to bring you some sponsors and I
want to Rous the round of applause for
them now because they keep us on the
air we'll be back in a couple seconds
you'll save money and time you'll get
the best of merchandise and service when
you patronize these good
neighbors drinking with Ian is proud to
be sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV
Vodka no matter if it's UV blue
raspberry UV red cherry UV green apple
UV Ivory vanilla or UV orange vodka UV
flavored vodka offer a premium product
without the high price tag please visit
UV vodka.com for additional information
and recipes and please remember to
always always enjoy Philips products in
moderation there are few things in life
more fulfilling than drinking alcoholic
beverages while watching a TV show about
drinking alcoholic beverages the folks
at pizz luche would like to make your
current DWI experience even more awesome
you may ask yourself or those around you
how can I possibly have a greater time
than I am well if you order pizza luche
delivery right now we can assure you
that within about 30 minutes you will be
having the time of your life in fact our
Studies have proven that watching DWI
while eating Tasty Pizza luche Pizza
will make our already super delicious
pizza taste even better we don't know
why this show makes our pizza taste so
good but we think that Ian's crazy hair
might have something to do with
it no beer in the midwest has a grander
brewing tradition than grain Bel for
over 100 years grain Bel has been the
beer that fathers have passed on to Suns
and friends have passed amongst each
other at local bars and watering holes
it is a beer with tradition that spans
Generations which is why it has become
legendary both here and across the
country next time you go out ask for a
premium French rabbit wines are the next
French Revolution in wine premium
quality Vintage Wines and the more
convenient more ecologically friendly
Tetra pack container the chardonay P
Noir Cabernet s and Meo come from The
Vineyards in the sunny south of France
and have been named best box wine by
wine and spirits and a best value by
wine spectator and USA Today the
Innovative 1 liter package gives you two
extra glasses than the regular 750ml
bottle in a shatterproof container with
a recable screw cap French rabbit one
smart rabbit to learn more visit French
rabbit.com
if there's one thing we like better than
booze it's cheap booze and that's why we
chose Merwin Liquors as the official
drinking withian liquor store great
deals a huge selection they even have a
contest where customers can win free
drinks for a year Merwin Liquors is hard
to beat yeah it's a bit ghetto but up
your street cred and Save A Buck or two
stop in at mwin Liquors at Lindale and
West Broadway in North Minneapolis just
two blocks west of 94 or visit Merwin
liquors.com
a portion of drinking with Ian is
sponsored by The Onion America's Finest
news source and the AV club bringing you
reviews and commentary on the Arts and
entertainment scene available at news
stands throughout the Twin Cities and
online at theonion.com and avclub.com
drinking with Ian is nothing without our
sponsors please support them here are
some things you might not know about
Billy he's got small hands in the last
year he was given a Timeout on four
separate occasions he can't read during
his tenure as milk monitor the price for
chocolate milk reached alltime highs his
parents are divorced and here's the last
assignment Billy turned in does this
look like the work of a leader on this
November 7th when you receive your
ballot ignore Billy and put your gold
star next to Jimmy Jones your next
preschool President Jimmy Jones He
colors inside the
lines hi I'm Jimmy Jones and I approve
this
message hi I'm Ian of television's
drinking with Ian a lot of people know I
can be a real bastard see I have done
things and screwed over both friends and
family alike but they've come to expect
it out of me I don't think they'd like
me as much if I went all soft on them
you see I think there is a little
bastard inside all of us one that tells
us to act out of sheer self-interest
even when it harms those who love us you
had all that liquor just sitting there
in the cabinet what was I supposed to do
not drink at all your ex-boyfriend
wouldn't have slept with me if he really
wanted you back people are our friends
our family people we hang out with this
make life more interesting man damn it
they can't help themselves sorry I sold
your Dave Matthews said to buy
cigarettes but really I was doing you a
favor I sell
insurance does this sound like you or
someone you know then you're our kind of
people and we want to hear your story
sure I cheated you out of rent but think
about all the rent I did pay I thought I
was on the pill and this is why I'm
pleased to announce the biggest bastard
contest I need you to put together a
video explaining why you are someone you
know is the biggest bastard in
Minnesota best part is you even get vote
for your favorite bastard online grand
prize let's just say it's something a
little bit better than a bastard
deserves so keep watching drinking
withian and be sure to stop by drinking
within.com for full rules and to see
some of the better bastards we' found so
far cuz deep down we're all
Bast what a bunch of bastards
all right everybody thanks for tuning in
drink with Ian tonight how's everybody
doing yeah feeling pretty good too
especially cuz I know what's about to
happen you just s her she has a new
album out now on zebone records it's
called Miracle of five I want an
overwhelming I want a Stupify I want a
cacophonous round of applause for lady
Mandel
thank
you why did that train
der
2011 victims were
killed was my
twin among the
diad was my twin expected to
live I was here at
home waiting for my twin to
return all those
men women
gone rocked from the sky and a terrible
star
was my twin among the
many was my twin at peace
ready I was here at
home waiting for my twin
toti When never met but I believe my
twins out there and he's looking for
me sharp and quick he'll
compliment my
slow D
existence
hey
hey the ocean is inable
took the crew and learn the
passengers was my twin the first to
last was my twin
holding
fast I was here at
home waiting for my twin to
return whenever bad but I
believe my twins out there and he's
looking for
me sharp and quick it'll
complim my slow out all
existence for a fast so fast it
burns
swallowing everything a furious system
was
M among the
Lost
desperately breathing water from the
for I was here at
home waiting for my twin to retire
thanks ladies and gentlemen Lady
M I'd like to take her twice over she
was you know it's two for tonight figer
one more round of
applause and I'd like to thank you for
showing up and I'd like to thank you for
watching tonight hey everybody that's
Drake withan thanks a lot a