[Music]
oh something old and something new
something borrowed and something blue
life is nothing but a lock and honey
only you've got the key if you looking
for something good looking oh you're in
the right spot honey got you looking at
me yes it's a space the best looking man
comedy we're live on location at to
Tavern for the first International best
blooded married Twin Cities contest on
tonight's show we got some best of
highlights don't go no way I am the
chocolate human or so stay tuned cuz I'm
fancy R it's time
to get down with hello my name is fancy
Ray MCL I am the best looking man in
comedy talk show host i di a doen The
Only Exception is me cuz I've got the
groes of moves of looks and this
incredibly Charming personality now I
first saw s Raphael my eyes started to
Sag I said the networks are trying to
fool us that ain't nothing but down H
dress and drag now some people think
Oprah winf is the best I think Oprah
wears the crowd well she may be the
heavyweight champ honey I'm the best of
the 200
lb stay tuned I'm fancy R it's time to
get down with
it I get
[Music]
come on
bab all right we're drinking Bloody Mary
this might get scary don't worry baby
I'll still be a chocolate covered
strawberry yes it's fancy right here the
best looking Manning County here at the
first International Bloody Mary contest
tonight we've got a great show we're
featuring some of the best highlights of
the fancy rid show it's going to be a
great show don't go nowhere I want to
ask you about now what if now you just
you you lost the championship you just
won it back from Mr I was ripped off
there on February 10th you know and uh
in the contract you know I got a rematch
and so we did it and I beat the man and
that was with Nick bowinkle you paint
your mustache on
oh I'm a good looking man now you
talking you got like three hairs I ask I
want ask you
something best looking man in comedy you
can the best looking man ined I want to
ask you a question I want to ask you a
question I I want to ask you a question
please welcome from Access America
outstanding Fred Weller give a round of
applause Fred Weller all right welcome
to the show FR and Ray you are the best
looking man in col I thought it was just
a a title oh I'm the best looking thing
I've ever seen you can travel the land
you can travel the sea when you know
it's no as pretty as me they left all
over the United States they came to Twin
City to get me because I am the best
looking man in comy and he ain't do
nothing but telling the truth keep
talking you know I don't know where to
begin with you I mean well you know I
thought you want to do a little
interview and I thought to help you out
I would write out some questions you
could ask me so it's always safe to
prepare your own interview that way I
can't leave here and say GE he didn't
ask me this he didn't ask me that this
is the safest way to do it well how do
you like Minneapolis I like Minneapolis
just fine yes would you like to see more
of my fabulous Impressions I didn't put
that as a question I just stay with the
question well okay okay here we go what
makes you the favulous star that you are
well I think that's a bit much to call
me a fabulous star that's what you wrote
here all right all right never mind
we're very short on time you guest of uh
why you know the show that you're doing
that's
called what we did is look at tapes of
shows like yours all over the United
States people who are you know doing
shows like this and picked out the most
interesting and right now I'm on a tour
around the country I'm going to appear
on a few of them and yours is one of
them is this the first one you appeared
on uh the second actually but the other
I got to be number one as good look as I
am be number one but they warn me up
with the I don't want you to think that
I'm conceited cuz I talk about my looks
and I wouldn't want you out in the crowd
to think I'm conceited no I'm I'm not
conceited but I wouldn't want my crew to
think that I'm conceited I'm
convinced but I understand they did
catch you in bed with a full length
mirror now tell me
that yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
thank you m my my I am the best looking
man in comedy shut up I know I look good
please I tell you what to introduce my
first guest I wrote a little poem every
day I race through the Star Tribune like
a man having fits looking for some
gossip and some of CJ's juicy tidbits
whether it's about horse who doesn't
like fragran say that don't come to the
ground our prince who crash this car and
it mess up his Royal Crown every day she
fills me with delight I feel like JJ on
good time she's
dite now tell me something now me and
you've been talking on the phone for so
long and you I call you all the time and
I tell you how goodl look I am how goodl
looking am I and you do you think I'm
good-looking CJ now I want you I know
you're gonna be honest am I goodlooking
oh shut up
[Laughter]
uh well let me ask you like this uh are
you attracted to
me well I let me ask you like this then
um you should you should try a different
line of questioning okay how about this
why did you decide to come on the
program I've lost my
mind and you had everybody in town
calling me and encouraging me to come on
I didn't anybody call you yes you did no
I didn't yes you did I never called no
one they call CJ who who told you that I
said call you about a few people really
name one um didn't uh uh J Anthony JW
Benson call and say I should do the show
I didn't tell Anthony J Benson to tell
you to call you yeah right you didn't no
I didn't no I didn't I said but CJ I but
the thing is we've been talking on the
phone and you wrote a thing in your
column she said dear fancy Ray you might
jump up Do Your Godfather Soul rou
that's why I have the Rope here because
I want to make sure you don't jump up
[Applause]
[Laughter]
please please please please unti the
Rope I have an apple here and I know how
to use it you'll feel like a pig on a
spit oh man you must know what I
[Applause]
like now now all you got to do is call
me a couple of nasty names and I'm
ready all right that's really cool now
you know something that's really
interesting how long have you been doing
your job this is really weird well how
long have you been doing your job oh in
this show
isn't how long have you been a gossip
columnist um a year and a half that's
why has your column become so
popular I guess because I have crazy
people calling me up and saying that
they're the best looking man in commence
and then I should write about them uhhuh
I don't know it's really it's really
clicked where do you get your
information from crazy men who call me
and tell me that the best looking men in
come and that I you know I need to do
this or I need to do that and so and
after I get these phone calls from these
uh people who've been abusing drugs
then then I try to find people who have
not been abusing drugs to confirm the
information that I heard how do you
confirm now when you write a source you
get like two sources before you put a
story in depends on what the what the
item is but I try to get as close to the
actual Source uh of the information as I
can okay what happens when you get
something that's not right that you put
something misinformation in that does
haveen oh yeah I try to correct it but
that's the nature of gaset too and Liz
Smith I understand runs a correction
almost every column uhuh and I don't
have uh my uh stats aren't quite that
bad really okay okay how does that make
you feel that and in fact I ask you that
you become a celebrity by writing this
column well it's almost as absurd as you
being a
celebrity but not quite I don't know I
don't know why you so hard on me I
someone has to
be what what's the biggest Joy about
about writing a column for you oh I
don't know I think it's a lot of fun and
it's something that I'm interested in
and I don't often get to meet people
who've been growing a mustache as long
as you've been growing out
oh man oh man that's the real the
opportunity the rare opportunity to come
and humiliate myself on shows like this
that's the other look I'm sing with a ro
you talking about being I like it I like
it a lot it's you it's you it
is stay tuned I'm getting out of this
rope too I'm coming
outome back we're here with the
legendary Percy Ross give Round of
Applause y Percy
woo I ask you all sorts of different
questions I want to ask you where did
your wealth eventually come from uh
plastic trash can bags you know liners
to put your leaves in and your rubbish
in mhm was it always a lifelong ambition
yours to be a philanthropist oh no you
had to be a millionaire first and then
you
become but you always want to give away
money yes if I had more that I needed
for myself okay okay let me ask you this
what would you say to those who would
say you do this a truthful us does it
quietly and discreetly oh yeah and you
do it like through your newspaper column
and through the radio show and they say
that you're just doing it seeking
publicity what would you say is that
well little publicity never hurt
anybody I like that I like that I like
that we giving out money money more
money come on up here more money is
anybody else want some money out there
you see all the black people rolling up
here why sitting back there you know
we're fine we won't take any cash here
here we go hi Mr Ross my name is Kathy
Marshall hi I'm a single mother with two
children I live from Check to Check um I
have a son who he um he's farsighted he
wears stick lenses on his glass saw he's
taunted by children his age and older
than him because he has six lenses and I
was told that he could get the thinner
ones that would be more attractive for
him they're expensive though aren't they
they're like 80 they well they told me
about $85 $85 and up listen forget it I
mean forget the fact that you're not
going to get it cuz you are I'm going to
give you a 100 bucks h thank you all
right all right thank you all right a
wait a while hold it okay wait a minute
you're going to get new glasses right
well you better make that 100 quter
because I think they're going to cost a
little bit more but you want one
condition the old pair you give to the
Lions Club closest to you okay because
they have a bank for for all kinds of
glasses for all kinds of kids if he
won't need the old ones anymore okay you
got $125 check coming in the mail Monday
morning all right you're on the call
more money more money more money one
thing that I've noticed I went out today
I stopped by here's a product that's
killing
people have you ever wrote a letter of
complaint to these people well we we
have taken strong positions we don't
allow SM I ask you have you personally
done anything with this company a letter
theed man tobacco it's still here and
this is killing people but I don't see
you on television or in front of the
media criticizing this uh we we've
criticize that we don't think that they
should use Indian people in any way in
any fashion to promote
alcohol or anything else chip a lot
Spring Water that's right that I mean
they could they could put a picture of
you know I mean how would you feel how
would you feel if they call us instead
of call it red man they call it redneck
they had a picture of you they had a
picture of
you all right now we going to do stuff
Dr I ain't never done before but I tell
you what here go what we got for you now
we got the Michael Jackson MC Hammer di
hey
I now you want be Michael Jackson or MC
Hammer which one you want me to be you
be you be MC Hammer all right and then
we we going to give you a little puppet
show
okay all right to to all the girls in
the back row I want to say hi I don't
want inter of you but I just want to say
hi I'm going Say Too Legit to
Quit I'm having I'm having a little
trouble right now MC h can you help me
grab my wenie oh no I can't touch
this look give me that glove I help you
grab your
weenie oh man cuz I don't want to touch
you man you too crazy give
her y'all all
right I tell you what can you draw me in
a little song right now let's sing old
classic
take I don't sing I'm sing you can sing
okay Take Me Out to the Ball Game take
me out with the
crow talk about Jo frasia ch Larry
Holmes I'm still fast and pretty you
look at this suit you know I'm pretty
but I want to congratulate the greatest
of all times next to me that's fancy Ray
three times world champion in Cable
cable access three year anniversary he's
so pretty not as pretty as me but he's
still very pretty the greatest of all
times all your teeth me open your M no
no no no no let me ask you a question
let me ask you a question sir tell us
about the governor your ex h no no I'm
nothing no no no no yeah
yeah yeah now I asked you a question
last time I asked you a question let me
tell you something let me tell you how
good is the governor and
B we want to know we want to know I
couldn't Poss I you know I must I it's
very important that I be honest yeah be
honest you hear what I got from my BR no
I didn't hear what you got what did you
get from you really want to know I
really want do youall want to know want
know well you know i' I've I've joked
around about always wanting to have had
a black lover it was my secret desire
it's and I've never had one and so I did
get a black dildo for
my really to replace the governor oh is
that right is that right is that right
he was gone no he's a nice guy listen I
can't what can I say who did the
governor sent it to you
no no no he would have sent me something
else you just got me so hot right now I
throw you on the floor right now and
make love let's do it I tell you what
comeing next we got PSA I'm slip no no
no no no just lie down I'll show you all
right I'm get a bit more F I stay get
[Applause]
down come
on
I'm I said get down
[Music]
come on
baby and of course on today's show we're
talking about prostitution today is part
one of our two-part series and I don't
know if you guys know about this I'm
going ask you guys a question do you
know what happens in the City of
Minneapolis as they find you picking up
a prostitute in your car no they take
your car away from you that's right how
much you have to pay for Cal Fair
[Applause]
today I got a friend that's got an
ingenious idea when he goes to pick a
prostitute the city Minneapolis he rides
the city
bus he sure does he just yells out the
window hey Mama jump on big red let's
get it
on I got exact things I ring the bell
and I'm
[Laughter]
done now we heading across the street to
the famous Cosmopolitan Club now this is
a club a special kind of Club woo when I
say special I mean really special that
has all kinds of different types of
activities going on in here and we about
to go inside and see what's happening
right here 965 cosmopol street that what
makes it historic it's closing down
tomorrow so we're going in right before
the official closing day inside the
coiling club right here's the entry way
we ring the doorbell and inside we'll
see the treats the feets hello Rebecca
Rand how you doing oh my my my how you
doing welcome glad you're back am I the
best looking thing in here today you are
the best looking
thing shut up I already know that we
going to take a look little look around
and see what's going down here at the
cosmetolog clubs right here here should
we go this way let's go this way all
right right here we got some young
ladies right here how you ladies doing
hello what's your name Kelly Casey Casey
Angela what's your name Angela you shy
aren't you Angela yes I am have you seen
someone as pretty as me in here today no
I haven't I don't think she ever has
let's take a look oh I'm beautiful we
gotta hiire these ladies right here art
in a different kind of way shut up let's
take a look around we're GNA take a
little walk through the back here now
right here this looks like a little
we're going to explore this right here
looks like a little preparation area
here at cosmetolog Club I don't know if
we can go in the back here can we come
back here I think we can we going to
anyways come on let's go all right we
going to check it on out now this right
here now you see this facility here they
got a shower here for cleanliness
obviously and you got little different
rooms back here little washrooms and
we're gonna keep on walking back here
through the back here oh a mirror this
is my favorite PL my my my oh I feel
good not that good not yet here with
three beautiful young ladies what's your
name I'm Casey Casey Sasha Sasha I'm
Tamara and Tamara thank you guys for
coming down now Tamara may be running
out of here because I understand you
have a client tied up in another room
yes I do I mean no not he'll be there
for a while he's not going anywhere
you've got him tied up yes you tie them
up good first thing I want to ask you
young ladies why are you doing this who
wants to answer that first
money for money hell yeah more money
more money well everybody needs a job
you know do you think of this as a job
or is it a career for you it's a job I
mean um it's a good job for the time
being but um it's a good stepping stone
that you can use to get to other places
I guess what can being a prostitute what
I mean where you see this to being a
stepping tone stepping stone to what
well to getting the type of money that
you need to get yourself together and to
achieve all the other goals that you
wish to accomplish okay what about the
social stigma attached to being a
prostitute
social signal who cares what people
think anymore I mean 10 years from now
the people who look at you are going to
have no effect in your life why let
anybody can be one I mean it takes a
certain amount of talent and and Beauty
to be one and
also so like what kind of talent do you
have please elaborate on
that well it's um it's it's something
you have to experience to really
appreciate
M okay I'm not going touch that one
although I'd like to shut
up us custom Coast Guard dope dog
nickname bust him like most dope
sniffing dogs he's got to have it train
to have to have it pick up the tracks of
the traffickers and track them like a
rabbit up the coastline K9 control
substance retriever receiver of the
golden nose award for lead him to the
cash cashing in on the stash now he's in
line for his isue a booty never do he do
a line in the line of duty he's a dope
dog
undercover knock with a bark took a bite
out of crime posing as a cni ey dog he
bit the blind the man with the cane made
of
coke hi this is Lacy Rose and I'm
partying at dream girls dancing here
when I'm in the Twin Cities I only watch
the fancy Ray
Show 1,000 bloody Maries on the wall
1,000 blood marries you take one down
pass it around
999,000 wo this is fanty I hope you
enjoyed tonight's program before we go
any further I want to thank my fantastic
sponsors I want thank Insight newspaper
we can find my cable cash schedule here
by J woo with Styles my fancy haird
located on 36 and pin in North
Minneapolis and my new sponsor the
Electric Fetus if you want Blues Jazz
rock and roll whatever you need do like
fancy Ray and go find it at the fetus I
hope you enjoyed tonight program taking
us home we got a fantastic treat make
sure you tune in next week to the
fantasy R show because if I'm there you
Bloody Mar time honey get down with
it at what period do you know when you
contracted AIDS let's talk about the
AIDS now sure I think I was probably
exposed to the virus in about 1982 which
is kind of ironic because I had run for
office and lost and was personally
bummed out and frankly using too many
chemicals and just being in a down
period And I think it was at that point
that I really exposed myself and assumed
that the virus wasn't here in
Minneapolis an assumption that a lot of
other people still make you know it's in
San Francisco and New York but it's not
here and then um I had skin
manifestations things along the way that
kind of suggested to me that maybe
something was wrong plus I was learning
more as was the world about uh AIDS and
I finally went in for testing in the
very end of ' 885 and found out in the
first week of the new year of ' 86 that
I was HIV positive how did you react to
the them telling you you have AIDS
actually um the counselor at The Red
Door Clinic that I went to was uh kind
of surprised because I wasn't very
shocked um you know I kind of took it
with stoic uh Norwegian
attitude uh you know at the beginning
and I guess that I had really thought it
through and been prepared and thought
there was a 50-50 chance based on what
I've been doing years ago I've been
practicing safe sex ironically really
since 1983 but um it was too late in a
fact okay okay and right now that you
have the disease I want to talk some
more about this what are you doing to
keep yourself healthy and keep yourself
up and sure that's the most important
thing because the disease is really
treacherous and it does waste your body
you know I used to be as beautiful as
you at least at least is I tell you what
I tell you
actually talk about keeping beautiful
coming up next we got Lorraine till the
executive director of the Minnesota age
project but I got a little exercise for
us to do so that we can exercise and
keep ourselves healthy would you join me
on a performance stage sure all right
give him a round of
[Applause]
applause all right there he is right now
Brian Kyle with the best of man County
and he was as beautiful as I am let me
hear the music and this is going to keep
you really really healthy take a deep
breath ready
[Music]
[Applause]
and how many people here practice say
sex how many people practice say sex all
right I'll tell you what we got right
here I got my a jacket and I want you
all to practice stay sex and have a good
night practice stay sex
stfe and remember tune in next week and
get down with my name is f race peace
love happiness have a good night
[Applause]