all right this is fancy Ray the best
looking man in com today oh man tonight
we got a fantastic show we are featuring
The Star Trek convention also me fancy
Ray going to be live on location at toz
in Downtown Minneapolis don't go nowhere
get some information about the show and
if you're lucky you might win some free
tickets so I tell you what don't go
nowhere I the chocolate human or and
tonight baby we going to get down with
it my my
my Hello my name is fancy Ray MCL I am
the best looking man in comedy talk show
host are di dozen The Only Exception is
me cuz I've got the gro of moves of
looks and this incredibly Charming
personality now I first saw s Jessie
Raphael my eyes they started to Sag I
said the networks are trying to fool us
that ain't nothing but Don H dress and
drag
now some people think Oprah Winford is
the best they think Oprah wears the
crown well she may be the heavyweight
champ honey I'm the best under the 200
lb stay tuned I'm fancy R it's time to
get down with
it I said get
down
the on
bab all right this this is fancy Ray the
best looking man in comedy today I'm
live on location here at the Minneapolis
Convention Center we're here to see Star
Trek the old generation the Next
Generation we're going to see all King
gons ramun woo Rudolph's barbecue
whatever you want to see right here
we're going to see a little bit of
everything the chocolate human Orchid
and I don't know about you but don't go
nowhere I'm fancy R and it's a Star Trek
convention and tonight we going to get
down with it oh my my my my
[Music]
my all right this is FY we're here with
my new friend George how you doing
George oh fine how about you oh man how
do I look I don't know I'm in the future
generation not the next not the past the
future what do you like so much about
Star Trek well it's a real enjoyable
show and the uh Concepts in it are real
nice helping people helping people you
know that that's something about that
philosophy that the writer started
really has a universal pill what who was
the original writer Star Trek uh well
there were quite a few of them Jee
roddenbery is the one that actually
started the program
um his concept basically was the future
was a lot better uh people helping
people and there wasn't as many problems
as there are now but even with that he
made commentary on a lot of things that
were uh problems in the current day mhm
who's your favorite character on Star
Trek um I'd have to say data data so we
met a little data just a little earlier
yeah what what what is it about data
that you like um I like the way he looks
at the world sees things that other
people don't see mhm we look right in
that world and tell me what do you see I
see a man with a camera oh really all
right now look this way now what do you
see I'm not sure well stay tuned and
you're going to get down with it oh my
my my my thank you George sure all right
this is fancy R the best looking man in
comedy today I'm here at the Star Trek
convention and we got what are you I'm
the crow the crow yes the recently
released Brandon Lee movie oh man I'm
scared of you now Shameless plug
there how you doing I'm doing pretty
good fun you're a big tricky yeah oh
yeah treer treer I'm sorry no no explain
to me now what's the difference between
a Trekker and a treky I'm sorry well the
treky is the one that watches TV and
goes oh wow that's really neat this is
so cool you know how do they do that you
know how does rker get that thing to
work and what does a treky do treker is
sitting there saying GE I wonder where
the on button is for the lights is that
right okay okay so you're really into
the technical side well not really it's
just that we know it's a movie we know
it's a TV show we know it's it's not
real mhm and we know it uhhuh we know a
lot of behind the scenes facts too okay
now tell tell my viewers out there a
behind the scenes facts that most people
don't know the bathrooms are opposite
the door to the ready room H I'm
learning stuff here now now what's your
favorite episode of Star Trek the old
one or the new one the old one the old
one day of the dub day of the dub you
know my favorite remember when Mark got
pregnant and Mindy had the baby somebody
get him away from me thanks a lot man
stay tuned and get down with it oh my my
my my all right this is fancy right the
best looking man in County we're here at
the Minneapolis Convention Center and we
got a couple of very interesting people
are you're not people you're Klingons
right we're Klingons now what is a Kling
on I see I see the most powerful race in
the universe learn to speak our language
you may it that may be the most powerful
but definitely not the most
pretty now are you a Star Trek yeah yeah
hell yeah the old Star Trek though you
know Captain Kirk was my man you know
cuz he got all the babes you know so
that's why I'm be I want to be kind of
you put Captain Curt Spock together and
put a little Li barach in it and you got
me my my my my my do you see the guy who
looks like Captain C out right yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah I'm I'm going to talk to
him actually he Chan me to a fight you
know there was a you know he was after
you and I wanted you and you know got a
little car you know but it was cool it
was cool it was cool these things happen
these things happen like I'm happening
here at the Star Trek convention in many
of at convention in a fancy ra that
chocolate human I can't believe it I'm
all the way live my my my my and that's
my camera but he don't like to be on
camera but knock him on camera and he
was smiling that's a good thing that is
a good thing stay tuned and get down
with it ow ow
ow ow my my my I'm here with my new
buddy how you doing pretty good now
you're a treky fan right I'm a Trekker
Tre I'm sorry I keep making that mistake
it's treer that's I have multiple
interests Star Trek isn't the only thing
I get into I like it a lot but not
enough to wear the ears
and like my show don't you yep you think
I'd be good in Star Trek well yeah
there'd definitely be a need for some
interesting aliens
all right this is fancy R the best
looking man in comedy we're here at with
the dealer at the Star Trek convention
how you doing very good what's your name
Bernie Murphy Bernie Murphy now Bernie
you're not from the Twin Cities no we're
from Romeo Michigan which is about 30
miles north of Detroit you travel all
over the United States doing these just
mainly in the midwest uhhuh what's the
big seller this year uh the big seller
this year so far has been the uh
postcards for us and these thermal care
pH that they use in Deep Space 9 to
serve the drinks really it'll keep your
drink hot or cold for up to 20 hours you
got the fancy Ray juice oh
yeah all right this is fancy Ray the
best looking man in commentary I ran to
old high school friend of mine introduce
yourself Joel Anderson Joel Anderson man
how you doing Joel oh not bad is that
right now you're a Trey I know you are
yeah I am now what now what do you like
about the treky uh the action footage
and the Hooters the Hooters wait wait a
minute I didn't see no Hooters oh well
you don't watch enough no okay that's
true well there's Hooters on on on Star
always really Riker Jonathan Frank he
always gets babes is that right like
like old Captain Kurt used to oh almost
almost as good now I said you're a high
school friend of mine now tell these
people out here something about me that
no one out there knows something about
you that no one else knows that no one
knows okay next
show stay tuned tell him to get
down stay down and get down and get down
oh my my my all right Joe good to go oh
thank
[Music]
you all right now you see what I got in
my hand right now they call these
trebles now they're making millions of
dollars off this and you know what I'm
going to tell you something now if you
take a look at this fancy Ray is going
to go into the future this is fany r on
a bad hair
day you know that's impossible stay
tuned and get down with it my little
fuzzy
buddy hi this is emo Phillips and you're
get hang down with my favorite homeboy
fancy Ray so don't touch that dial
because I spat on
it let the Thunder Roll let the
lightning strike the best looking man is
going to be at toobz and on the mic so
men grab your women women grab your men
and if you ain't got one grab your next
to Ken cuz what's yours is yours and
what's his is his women got the power
guys give it up cuz who there it
is I ain't doing nothing but telling the
truth and I'm going to tell you the
truth about something else fancy R the
best looking man in comedy is going to
be live at toes Friday and Saturday June
17th and 18th 900 p.m. shows do not miss
this show it's going to be fabulous Me
featuring my fantastic comedy plus James
Brown screaming Jay Hawkins MC Jager lip
syns also poetry by the master himself
me fancy Ray mcloney featuring the all
new poem fancy ray goes to hell it's
going to be a fantastic show Friday June
17th and 18th at toes with me fancy Ray
toes is located on 6th Avenue right
across the street from Glicks you know
this should be the old building was
known as cheers do not miss the show
it's going to be good to go O my soul
stay tuned we're going right back to the
Star Trek convention I am the best
looking man in comedy and I want to see
you June 17th and 18th at to's
I all right this is fancy I'm drawing
the crowd no matter where I go my soul
cuz I got one hell of a show how you
doing very good how are you oh man I'm
doing fantastic now you guys are dealers
here from Sun Coast yes we are what's
the big seller right now ooh the micro
machines going like crazy now what mic
machine they specialize in doing
Miniatures of a whole bunch of different
kind of SPAC ships and space station
from lots of different shows okay okay
that's really cool and you know
something I was looking at all these
pictures how come everyone on here is
ugly man they need some pretty people on
Star Trek don't you agree well you can
never have enough of pretty people but I
think Jean radbury had strange tastes is
that right is that right so now what
kind of taste do you like
well the most beautiful man in the world
well yeah but I to him already so what
can I say hey man you're a great guy man
thanks a lot all right my my my my
my all right this is fancy R the best
looking man in comedy we're here to see
if anyone in the next generation is as
pretty as I am let's look at these
pictures our Scott now look at this ugly
ugly oh man that's a Frankenstein oh
check this out H Ross Pro is going to be
in the next Generation I love it I love
it I love it is there a Star Trek dance
is there not that I know of can we make
one up right now should we make one
let's make one up I'm scared no that's
the one where you just jump back and
forth like this show show that's the
Star Treck dance yeah see oh God it's
like we need a couple of cing on right
now all right all right this is fancy
Ray the best looking man in comedy I'm
here at the Star Trek convention and we
got I don't know what are you I'm
a Klingon you're a Klingon now now
someone explain me what is a Klingon a
Klingon is a being from the planet of
konos really we are warriors uh-huh but
at this time I'm here at Star Trek
convention to have fun really so you're
here to have fun huh yes now show me
something fun can you do show me
something fun what's a cing on Dance
what's what's a hit hit song in Kling on
line a Kling on hit song
yeah can't quite dance to that but hey
man whatever turned you on the cing on
brother right here with fancy Ray man
I'm going to show you the fancy Ray
dance ready all right can you do this
one the most beautiful man in the world
oh I can bend over like that but I'll
never get back up again all right you
Stik you on saying in my my my stay
tuned in get the with it all right this
is fancy R I'm here with my main man
from Star Trek the Next Generation Avery
Brooks now Avery I understand you want
$25,000 per show okay now now now tell
me this and you don't want to give out
autographs now is it that rough for
black men in the 21st
century did Jesse Jackson succeed will
there be a next Generation what's going
on Avery are you happy are you glad to
see
me stay tuned Avery Brooks with fancy R
O I'm in the next who's the prettiest
wait a
minute I know me my my my stay tun tell
to get down with it get down with it my
my my
ow all right this is fancy Ray MCL the
best looking man in comedy and I'm in
front of this glorious I don't know what
this is but we got the man who invented
this right here what's your name my name
is Michael padon Michael good to meet
you Michael now what exactly is this
this is the USS Enterprise original Star
Trek shows uh communication panel
Lieutenant hura um sat at this for years
really now you built this right here yes
I did now what's the purpose that you
built this for conventions um kids make
models adults make bigger things okay
man this is glorious this is absolutely
this is like totally lifelike in real
yes it's it's it's um pretty close to
the authentic setup of what the show was
like now what I want to ask you is I
like to buy this from you this could
make a nice headboard to my
bed all right this is fancy Ray the best
looking man comment today I'm here with
three captains of Starships right mm
what's your name my name is Phil Goldman
I'm with the Nomas okay my name is Dave
kumin I'm with us Arc and you are mine
from the Imperium all right you're from
North Dakota right all right man now you
look like Scotty oh I've been hearing a
little bit about that today but I'll
take it as long as it isn't for the
guts now what a captain guys you guys
have your own fan clubs here right
exactly okay now how many people do you
have in your fan club oh we got about
200 people in a fan club about 60 people
that show up about every month a lot of
them that you see around to mhm how do
you become a Captain uh beg a lot you
beg a lot huh oh yeah oh man so show me
the technique that you beg how do you
become a c please please vote for me V
please star Fleet they like me help I
think I think you're going to be on the
Next Generation you wait a minute who is
this over here now wait a minute come on
over here wait a minute wait a minute
don't go nowhere who is this now who are
you my name's Adam you're Adam like as
an Adam and Eve as an Adam Bomb Adam
Bomb Adam Bomb Adam Bomb I'm scared of
you now now I don't want to talk to you
so much man
okay and we got his friend that's going
to be coming in here all these scary
names now you guys are captains now you
guys are lots of members what would you
tell the viewers out there they said I
don't know if they like Star Trek why
would why should the view out there
watch Star Trek ah Star Trek is a good
fun show it's uh pretty to watch good
people and a good view of the future and
it's on convenient times all right there
you go man thanks you guys a lot you
guys are fantastic one two three Adam
Bomb I think
not my my my stay tuned and get down
with it I'll shake it man come on what
now I heard your mom's a big fan of the
show oh yes she is really yes definitely
she loves you she loves me oh she loves
you I know how she
feels well say hi to Mom out there hi
Mom hi Mom all right this is f the best
looking man in comedy and I'm with
Commodore Mary Commodore Mary now now
I've been walking all over the place and
I tell you what in the 21th century you
had the best legs in the 24th can we get
a look at those legs are
God are they just sexy in the 21st
century
excuse me will it be the sex in the 21st
century is this what we got to look
forward to oh I hope there's more than
that oo really I'll tell you what stay
tuned and we're going to get down with
it bye my my
my let me tell you a little story about
a guy named fency Ray mclone this guy
was something else well you might know
him as some kind of singer dance a comic
some crazy forck the thing like that but
this
guy P for pound was the best
middleweight there ever was the
middleweight champ of the world
FY mclone I never forget that night in
the
garden he takes on Larry Holmes 1978
March like it was
yesterday the heavyweight champ it's 158
lb soaking wet he goes in there he's
stick and he's moving he's ahead on
points what does he do he sticks his
chin out round 10 and goes hit me hit me
you big piece and I can't even
say fancy
Ray never got
up they don't what happened poor old
fancy Ray they say he moves but never
like he used
to I know my my my my I remember a
different
time back when he could hit now he's got
to eat soup with a
straw sad story fan
sad
story I am the best looking man in
comedy my my my my my my my fancy you
look good oo that's the look a
r fancy you feel good that's the body
array M fancy you smell good um that's
the uh essence of
R yes this is fancy R mlar the best
looking man in comedy I'm live on
location here at Dream Girls with Angela
Summers stay tuned because tonight we're
going to get down with it say
I my my my my
my all right this is fancy Ray mclone
the chocolate human Arch and I'm here in
fromont the Toby's Tavern Toby's Tavern
this is where fancy Ray is going to have
his comedy show June 17th and 18th come
and see the best looking man at comedy
now you wonder now where is Toby's
Tavern at it's right on six in henpen
right down from 1 Avenue in fact there
was a Target center right down there the
Target Center across the street of
course we got Butler square and you
cannot miss it Toby's Tavern here June
17th and 18th fantasy R will be live on
location you don't want to miss this
show it's going to be one hell of a show
it's good to go O my soul stay tuned
ladies and gentlemen I am the chocolate
human orch the 17th 18th here at Toby's
T come see the best looking man in
comedy fancy Ray Oh My My My all right
this is fancy R and I got my new buddy
what's your name my name is Harold
Harold how you doing Harold good how are
you man I'm doing as beautiful as I look
how do I look you look fine not fine
super fine fantastic fashion fragrant
and ooh fertile you look okay look okay
no man okay is not a big enough word for
me you know I got a comedy show coming
at toes in Downtown Minneapolis youever
been to toes yeah you have been to toies
where's it at it's on it's downtown in
about 3rd Avenue South or something no
no 6th in hin right off sixth in hin
right across from glutes where all the
college kids hang out well I've been
there you've been there but I didn't
remember exactly well check it out it's
June 17th and 18th in Minneapolis now
what are you going to do you going to be
there I'll be doing stand up comedy
really yeah oh terrific you like jokes
oh I love jokes I do joke for you man I
saw a woman today she had some big boobs
man her boobs were so big her $18 bra
was getting paid time and a
half my my my there's more that where
that came from thanks a lot Haro a guy
oh man what a goodl looking guy good
luck thank you my my my
Harrow all right this is fancy R the
best looking man in County I'm live on
all location here at Uptown in
Minneapolis what's your name Buddy
Douglas lman Anderson Douglas how you
doing dougy just fine man you've been
out fishing today huh yeah really what'
you catch well I didn't catch anything
it was little no you did catch something
you caught me out here baby and I got a
hot tip for you June 17th and 18th I'm
going to be at Toby in Downtown
Minneapolis with the hottest comedy show
in the nation hot comedy show well
that's great oh man I'mma Be There will
you be there I'll be there the 17th and
18th 17th and 18th come see fancy Ray
I'll see fancy R the best looking man in
comedy today the best looking man in
comedy my my my my my my my my my my oh
my so dougy got it going on oh my my my
f is going to be live in our location
June 17th 18th at toes in Downtown
Minneapolis do you want to get free
tickets do you want to get free tickets
do yall want to get free tickets in here
yeah yeah free tickets give us a call
49120 68 come see fancy ra the chocolate
human orch live on location at to is my
my my how you doing I have seen you live
before you you see me live okay now we
got live witness do I know do I know you
no
okay now give me your honest opinion
what was a fancy race show like live it
was great it was great I tell you what
now you heard the ticket line 491268 we
going to give away some tickets if you
don't get tickets com and see the show
anyway it's going to be me fancy R the
best looking man in comedy you've never
seen nothing like it I'm a chocolate
human Arch I'm the crest Above the Rest
I Rise and a test I can do no less cuz I
am the best looking man in comedy I can
you have my autograph yes you're fancy R
the best Oh My My My I I don't believe
it EI wait a minute wait a minute is it
me is it me oh it is oh it is it is me
baby I'm going to give you an autograph
I'll tell you I'm going to give you
something even better than that what a
job the 17th and 18th I'm going to be
live on location at Toby in Downtown
Minneapolis but I need a job you need a
job what kind of work can you do
publicity you can do publicity yes well
I tell you what go so start yelling
fancy Ray fancy Ray fancy Ray and how
much do I get paid well you got see how
good you do first fancy
Ray Oho my my my I think we going to
hire this lady here oh my my I'm a
magnet I'm a a magnet I'm a magnet I'm a
magnet I'm a MAG oh come on in here oh
man it takes two to make it right now
you guys like the fancy R show yeah I
have never heard of it before my life
you never heard of it before in your
life nope I'm sitting over there talking
with some people they go hey there's
fancy Ray and I'm like here we are baby
you guys are looking at a this is a
classic but you guys are looking at a
true classic right here baby you think
you for Spin and put two of us together
then huh the 2 + 2 equal 4 4 plus 4 is
eight and five will get you 10 if you
know how to work it right how you guys
doing oh wow man you guys got the
classic automobile and I want to tell
you about a classic comedy show it's
going to be at toes in Downtown
Minneapolis toes you toes is well yeah
it's down there in the main part yeah
six and h r street from glutes you come
and see fan the 17th and 18th the best
looking man in comedy the most flam Bo
the 17th and 18th it's going to be
pretty wild huh it's going to be wild
all right have style I'm going be the
pretty
child you guys come on check me out okay
okay all right my my my my my good
evening what you're about to witness is
a crime a crime of nature a human
metamorphosis a singer songwriter
liberachi wakes up one morning as a
black
man only in the what if
Zone ah Sean thank you hi this is
liberachi oh sure you can't touch this
you can't touch
that I know what you're thinking you
can't touch that
either how do you feel like a little rap
right now yeah okay okay my my my music
plays so hard makes me say oh my Lord
thank you for blessing me with myaw and
most of all my brother
George oh sure you can't touch this you
can't touch that oh do you like my coat
oh shk come on in go right ahead oh
George can't wait to get his hands up
it's a virgin f
oh you can tell it takes F to no
one how about we get funky now all the
girls say goalie goalie go goalie goie
go all the guys say goalie goalie goalie
go goie goie goalie go we forget anybody
stop liberachi
[Music]
time oh I get so horny when I do
that oh you do
too I feel just like Lauren
12 oh don't laugh he cries all the way
to the bank
too oh sure George slow it down I'm
working up a
sweat that's more like it if that would
have kep I would have probably started
streaking oh I was just kidding about
the streaking you know s had it say sort
of petered
out and besides Bert R to be so jealous
I've got the diamond he has his
J oh you're slow but you're worth
waiting
for oh do you like my rank sure get it
close with the Rings you like them let's
let's make it you bought
them is it just wonderful oh why am I in
Minnesota I'm here to see the Vikings oh
sure I love football I go anywhere to
see a couple good tight
ends oh sure your butt is mine Michael
eat your heart
out how about we get funky
again got to get horny
a hello everybody this is George Wallace
that's right comedian George Wallace in
the Twin Cities the beautiful cities of
St Paul and Minneapolis Minnesota when
I'm in Minneapolis it's got to be fancy
Ray that's right and I want to wish him
a happy fourth anniversary because he's
the best looking man in Show Business
that's what he
says all right this is fancy Ray the
best looking man comedy before we go any
further I thank my fantastic sponsors I
thank Insight newspaper you can find my
cablecast schedule hair by J which
Styles my hair do and I want to thank
you for tuning in our Scott for all the
Fantastic camera work make sure you tune
in next week to the fancy R show cuz if
I'm there we going to get down with
it my my my Star Trek the Next
Generation ow ow
ow all right this is fancy Ray money I
walked through the California earthquake
I didn't get a scratch made love the 10
different women they all quit smoking
didn't need a cigarette patch I'm the
reason the West Was one I know you're
thinking they should bronze me but you
can see oh the Lord saw to it cuz it's
already been
done my my my my my I'm here at Toby's
Tavern with the owner here Toby how you
doing Toby good Ray how are you doing oh
man I feel fantastic I'm enthusiastic
I'm excited we got the big show coming
up here June 17th and 18th here at Tois
that's correct June 17th and 18th oh man
it's going to be a fantastic show 900
p.m. shows now people write me from all
over the city the country they say fancy
right why are you doing a show here at
Tois why why why here at tobis and I
want you to explain to him why we
decided to do a show here well I was
looking through the uh pioner press the
other day and I saw this incredibly
good-looking man right here on the cover
and I said I just had to have this guy
here I just couldn't I couldn't wait to
have him here man I tell you I'm very
very flattered by that this is a great
article by Mike Madison at the St Paul
Pioneer Press and a great photograph but
you know I'm actually I'm very very
modest about the press and I really
don't like to bring the Press thing up
but I mean if since you want to bring up
the Press man I mean if you want to show
an article how come you didn't show when
I was at the staring Tribune on the
cover of the staring Tribune that's was
really fantastic picture and I love that
article how about when I was on the
cover of the City Pages me fancy Ray is
love why didn't you show that one Toby
see I'm really M look at I was in Los
Angeles California me on the cover of
the paper me fancy Ray the chocolate
human or if you want to show an article
yes why didn't you show this one Toby
here at the bismar paper right there on
the cover what do you see me fancy Ray
MCL I'm incredible I'm unbelievable it's
going to be comedy it's going to be lip
sytin it's going to be poetry it's going
to be unreal June 7 17 June 18th I've
been featured on Entertainment Tonight
Jenny Jones the comedy channel me fancy
Ray M the best looking man in comedy
come see me where June 17th and 18th at
Toby's Tavern 9900 p.m shows do not miss
the show it's going to be good to go go
my my my my oh he's the man come see me
I know I look good my my my I'm going to
show you the greatest short poem of all
time okay okay me
[Laughter]
all right this is fancy R the chocolate
human Orchid now you saw all those empty
seats they're not here to see Star Trek
the Next Generation they're here to see
me fancy Ray the best look man in
comedy when are you signing when are you
signing out wait a minute wait a minute
now you you you and all those people
back there are just going to have to
wait till I got more time okay I'm doing
the show right now I'm not signing
autographs till later okay later later
later later later okay all right all
right stay tuned I'm a busy man and a
good looking one oh stay tuned and get
down with it ow