[Laughter]
yes yes I see you on the Lake Area News
man I'm on the Lake Area News man so
much good stuff 1993 I'm starting off in
a big way my my my ra the best I know
that's right man I am the best man look
at the cover cover of the city page
everybody I am the love man can I get a
witness can I get a witness I know this
so much good I was on the city pag Star
Tribune I'm just smoking I'm hot and I'm
on top my my my my I'm the best here in
the Twin States and the whole press
media knows it the best the best I'm the
best the best I am the best the Twin
City reader reader says to get out of
town what
oo get out of town get out of well the
press does some things good and bad and
some things I don't understand I know
for a fact they picked on an innocent
humble and very good-look
man now the twin C said out of this town
I should pack and the first thing I
should do is go but they must have
realized something that all of you
already know that I produced the hotest
show dance excitement comedy I've done
everything I could I don't belong in
Minneapolis I'm going to Hollywood give
all right stay tuned cuz we're going to
get
out I said get
down do
the come on
baby want to watch
everybody I said come on
baby want say everybody do a jack
I said come on
baby it's been a long long
[Music]
time the St get down with it the best
looking man in comedy R
mcloney hello hello
hello my name is s mcco I am the best
looking man in com welcome to K TV's get
down with the twin's hotest
entertainment talk
show y'all have a good time this is
Black History Month I want y'all to meet
a friend of mine cookie okay all
right people say to me Cookie how come
you ain't got no
car I tell they don't understand the
game you got to go to the white man and
get a piece of paper get a car with four
black wheels driving on the black
pavement and you got stay inside the
White
Lines I'd rather
walk hitting on my joint I was over a
friend's house he was watching the
hockey game he like to watch CU of the
fights I said my brother you don't
comprehend the game I said there white
men out there playing on White Ice with
tan sticks hitting the black Puck around
[ __ ] got the biggest white boy in the go
with the mask and pads on try to stop
that black Puck from reaching its
goal told my rather
walk hitting on my
joint you know what my favorite game
is
golf yeah you on green grass with a
black
Club Hitting that white ball around
the soon as you can sink that ball in
the hole the better your score
is sometimes just for fun I don't try to
put the ball in the hole IED to be out
there hitting a ball
around I was doing it one day and the
man came up to me and said what you
doing boy I said I'm hitting Whitey
around he said you got to leave this
course is restricted I said cuz we in
America he didn't comprehend I told him
peace anyway I roll away on his golf
court hitting on my
joint my my my my my give cookie a round
of applause everybody all
right we having a great show you know
something but I'm really excited we
celebrating Black History Month
something I'm very excited about is that
we got a new president President Clinton
let's give him a big round of
applause oh man I know A change is going
to come I was really excited y'all watch
inauguration celebration stuff man they
had some great stuff they had a MC
Fleetwood there y'all see Mick on there
Fleetwood Mac Man Governor Clinton said
that he smoked marijuana but he didn't
inhale
I tell you I hung out with mck Fleetwood
you stand next to him for 10 minutes you
don't have to in hell
I'm I saw Li Richard on there Li Richard
said he Tu he shuck the president's
finger and his whole body started
tingling and I said what finger was he
sinking you
know my my my my my my and they got this
thing y'all see Michael Jackson on that
show oh Michael look terrible in fact
you know I was thinking I saw a little
clip I was going put it on the heads
let's take a look when I was on putting
on the hits y'all take a look at this
here I want y'all to see something
Michael copies me I'm going prove that
Michael copies me show this for putting
on the heads now you look at this look
at my skin color right there that's
Michael Jackson skin color right there
he ain't doing nothing copy of me that's
Michael Jackson skin color now you know
what Michael did not realize bring the
camera back to me Michael did not
realize that ain't nothing but makeup
baby that's all it was you know I came
out about five years ago saying I was
the best looking man in County right he
started doing all the surgery and all
this that and the other thing Michael
after all that surgery baby you still
don't look bit pretty as I
do wouldn't y'all
agree shut up my my my tonight we got
fantastic show you can travel the land
you can travel to sea but you never find
comedians pretty as me with the wisdom
of Einstein the finessa clay are you
ready to have a good time with fany
Ray all right my my my my my tonight
we're celebrating Black History Month
with one of the twin City's most
controversial outspoken leaders in the
black community give Spike Moss a big
round of
[Music]
applause and gospel vocalist carless
Brewer give her a round of applause
everybody
stay tuned and get down with
it ever want to be a private eye now is
the time be on the lookout for safety in
your home over 4 million are injured in
home accidents every year nearly 30,000
die make everyone in your family a
private eye for home safety stay alert
stay alive
fancy R
mclone my my my my my
my I'm mean clean and our black history
must sex
machine my feature guest tonight is an
outspoken activist here in the black
community he represents me and people
throughout the community for now over 25
years he's outspoken a little
controversial and without doubt a true
gentleman let's go meet spikee Moss
ladies and
gentlemen what's that the people doing
what they're bothering they're bothering
you I don't think much bothers you spike
man I try to get security is that right
I'll be your security the lady on the
end you stop bothering Spike here now
man it's such a pleasure and honor to
have you here on the show I appreciate
being here no I always see you in the
media I see you around town all the time
and something I don't know Spike
is who you are and what got you going
and what you got going into where you
born at little town called Paris
Missouri okay where did you come to Twin
Cities I came here as a young boy uh
went back and forth and then finally we
settled here MH yeah at what age did you
get involved with the Civil Rights
Movement I I think I was probably 15 or
16 I was probably paying attention when
I was 11 or 12 because in Missouri black
people went through the same things you
did in Alabama or Mississippi them one
side of the track most facilities uh
black people were not allowed in so I
was already being developed and I was
already telling my mother what I didn't
like as a young child and what did you
see that you didn't like as a young
child well just not being able to walk
into a show or a restaurant or go to the
Dairy Queen get an ice cream conb or go
to the carnival and get on the rides as
a matter of fact a lot of people don't
know but when we first came here to
Minnesota probably Liz would know
nicholet used to be called nicholet
Avenue instead of a mall and all the St
on nicholet Avenue was wws SS kesky
Powers WS sure all of them had a soda
fountain that faced the nicholet Avenue
side and when you walk in the opening
doors you walk into the soda fountain
all of them had at the napkin sign thing
that said uh we don't serve colors at
the time here Minneapolis oh yeah humy
was the mayor a lot of people don't know
that about Minneapolis okay so I went
through the same thing here and trying
to understand how you fit in and why we
were treated differently as a matter of
fact we went to a show where where uh
City Foods is used to be Super Value
there was one there called the brinmar
that was the black show mhm we had never
been to Broadway cuz we couldn't get up
on Plymouth if you were seen on Plymouth
the police would carry you back to your
community the projects itself where
summerfields Park is the east side was
black the west side was white a lot of
people don't know about Minneapolis
let's talk about Minneapolis when did
you start the fight you about 15 16 here
yeah I started with with a group of boys
that I grew up with okay and we used to
go downtown and run in and sit down at
the counters because we knew we couldn't
and they used to offer us water to get
us to leave so we keep drinking water
till we get bloated but we wasn't going
and uh we used to run into into
different places where we couldn't go we
used to run in the movie show take a
seat we used to do all of that here in '
66 that's when the violence broke out
not just here but throughout the nation
what was a climate like here in
Minneapolis in 60 6 that's when you came
to prominence well what it was then for
young blacks there was nothing for us
there was no jobs the most you could do
here was either shine shoes toss salads
or be a bus boy and we all knew knew
that and most of us wouldn't apply for
it and we were at the point of
hopelessness where you know what are you
do and who's trying to lead us out and
nobody was and when things hit the fan
across the country it naturally hit the
fan here at at that time Plymouth from
Queen Avenue down to humbled Avenue on
both sides of the street was all white
businesses there was nothing else there
but businesses right and came to the
black community the first time half of
it was destroyed and the second time the
rest of it was destroyed looking back in
retrospect was that a thing because we
burnt our own Community was that a good
thing to do I think that the media
projected that to make black people
think because something is in your
community is yours if you don't own it
you don't benefit from it it's not yours
but those it serves you those Merchants
were giving black people credit on food
they were serving they there there was
some good and and then after they burnt
out was years before anything came back
I think that was a conversation for some
towns I wouldn't say that was a
conversation for our town as a matter of
fact what kicked off the second Riot was
a young man who they alleged stole a
package hot dogs and when he got up to
the counter and the man told him to uh
pull out what he had in his pants he
pulled out the hot dogs he shot him with
a deer rifle so I don't see where the
connection was with the merchants in our
community you know okay the other part
is that the black community has to
realize that we have as much opportunity
and right to own businesses in our own
Community as anyone else this whole
thing of redlining is going on today
denying us equal access to having our
own businesses if you have your own
businesses you don't really have to be
concerned about discri you can hire
yourself right that's true that's true
we need that opportunity what brought
you into the spotlight what took Spike
Moss being one of the people that out
there protesting to being a leader in
the black community I think what you
know I was on a I was on a boxing team
at the time at the philis Wheatley and I
was downtown at the Aquino parade and at
the time they were trying to back
everybody up off the curb and some young
black girl about 14 years old was pushed
off the curb and uh an officer rather
than asked her to get back hit her with
a club H and he didn't know at that time
she was pregnant and um I was the
closest to it so I stepped out well
being a boxer and wellknown other
brother stepped out in the street but
from that day I made up in my mind
everything that I knew and learned I was
going to take it forward all right we're
going to talk some more about that and
stay tuned don't go nowhere we got the
man right here Spike Moss stay tuned and
get down with
[Applause]
it hi this is Jimmy Bowman Jr doing the
English translation for Mr
Brown ah this hi this is the Godfather
of Soul James
Brown I'm here tonight to speak about
absentee fathers ha there's a lot of
single mothers out there catching hail R
off cuz pop ran off you
you I'm sorry I have no idea what Mr
Brown is saying there make it doesn't
take much to make a kid but it takes a
man to be a father
single moms are writing me from all over
the
country please saying Mr Brown please
tell your husband please please tell my
boyfriend please
[Music]
pleaseeeeeee supp
[Applause]
[Music]
please support please pleas the child
support all right welcome back to get
down with our special feature guest it's
Spike Bross give another round Applause
everybody
SP man of course we're here for Black
History Month what does Black History
Month mean to you well it's a short
opportunity to explain some of our
history uhhuh I think it's extremely
important but we need to moved from the
uh Black History Month and Incorporated
in our school system so our kids are
being taught it every year I think
what's important is is that it gives
kids the motivation and determination it
gives them back a sense of Pride uh the
self-esteem that our kids uh need so
badly uh to know exactly what role they
play in America I mean we begin with
American history but it's not that way
in most school systems and our young
people need to know that all that you
see in the world is not done by just one
part of society it's done by all of the
people who live here I think it's
crucial but I also think it needs to be
incorporated period no no doubt I think
that's very true you're out there in the
community and you're with the kids and
you see what's going on you deal with
the gang members you deal with the
street people you deal with white collar
blacks what is going on with so much
crime why is crime taking off so bad
here in our Twin Cities I think you have
to look at the level of discrimination
and denial of opportunities that just
finally caught up to us when you
devastate people to the level that
blacks have been devastated in America
we are now with families that are three
and four generations without a person in
your family that had a job
where you're raising all your family on
welfare mhm uh subsidized housing you're
getting whose fault is that though is
that their fault is that we got to
empower ourselves we have decided we
have decided as a nation that uh racism
is healthy and we're projecting it we're
maintaining it and it's a strangle hold
of people of color and it's keeping them
from being whatever it is they want to
be life in this country and I think as
long as you deny it people are still
subjected to the same thing as working
people on on the end of the month you
got to pay your bills if you don't allow
me to pay it with a job I'm going to pay
another way right one way or the other
what about the disrespect for life and
property people like the boy that went
in the house he broke in the woman's
house everyone heard about this story uh
and he was burglarized in the house
normally you a burglar you go in the
house I understand that you going to
steal something you take the TV VC and
get the hell out of there but the kid
stay then he takes a nap goes to sleep
waits for the mom and the babies to come
home and then kills the mom and cutting
the kids up I don't understand that
violence well you have to you have to
recognize this one of the things that we
try to ignore is that we're preoccupied
in teaching Americans citizens how to
behave mhm if you were five or six years
old in this country the first thing
you'd watch on TV is a cartoon right
most people look at cartoon as innocent
but you have to look at what you see
there is no cartoon figure that doesn't
steal something from the other one
doesn't bust the other one in the head
with something doesn't shoot him in the
face with a gun or fire a big hole in
the middle of his body with a cannon
you're already being taught to relish
and like violence when you get into the
movies it's Supreme uh Supreme uh what
you call it extreme rather violence when
you get into the movie shows where you
get in Friday the 13th or or or
Halloween or Jason all this type of
violence we're beginning to enjoy as
entertainment and we're also acting it
out in our society the kid get the gun
and he's got some power now what we're
saying is well you're supposed to be
intelligent enough to watch it and not
acted out but if you look at most
murders there has been that murder seen
on TV or a magazine or a comic in this
country before it took place what we
need to do to our young brothers and and
not just brothers but other people of
color to stop them from doing this stuff
well number one we're not teaching
people that they're important we're not
teaching people that we love them not
that they should love themselves what
we're doing to people is wasting them
and burning them up if you have an
attitude that no one cares about me I
don't need to care about you right
that's the attitude we're giving young
people in this nation the self-esteem
that's right that they're not and the
same time uh uh case in point when I was
a young man I couldn't go to the store
and get cigarettes I couldn't even get
them from my mother unless the merchant
knew my mother's signature a kid can get
cigarettes wherever he wants I couldn't
get alcohol a kid can get alcohol I
couldn't even see drugs let know let
alone know it existed these kids can get
drugs from adults that look like you and
me with no problem right so I'm saying
that the adults of this nation are
participating in the demise of the young
people of this nation that type of
Cruelty is coming back at us and then
we're acting like we don't understand it
a lot of times we we we blame society we
blame culture we cannot deny that but
here I'm a black man out here working
hard believing pushing and I believe I'm
going to make it and I am going to make
it cuz I look good shut up um but when
do we stop blaming and take some
responsibility upon ourselves our own
community and say let's push forward and
we got to do this in ourselves I think
you're doing both but you're not in a
position to change the demise of your
people you're not in position to offer
an alternative to them when you say
something to them if I say something to
a young man who's selling drugs on a
corner what am I going to offer him to
get him off the corner it's all right to
come at him and tell him the evils of
that but in fact that's his living
that's how he eats now how am I going to
feed him we haven't moved to that level
where young people can come to us and
get the very things they need therefore
they step out in the world and start
trying to get it on their own which
usually ends up to be negative right and
it's not a thing of blaming it's the
reality of of the demise we're in I know
you must have recognized that recent
study that said the two worst states in
this country in terms of the treatment
of people of color were Mississippi and
Minnesota now you have to realize
Mississippi does not count because it's
the poorest state in the Union it has no
industry couldn't help us if it wanted
to how did Minnesota get to the bot
that's a good question I tell you what
we're going talk about some more
controversy stay tuned with Spike Moss
we get down with it don't go nowhere ow
[ __ ] [ __ ]
[Applause]
[ __ ] what do you mean people like you
what because I'm black you some kind of
racist bigot or something no no no
you're probably on welfare no I'm not on
welfare I got a job and I pay my taxes
well I pay my taxes too but I T like to
take a peek of your criminal record wait
a minute you're going a little getting a
little carried away here I've never
committed a crime I'm just in college
trying to get an education and if that's
a criminal offense then I'm guilty yeah
but what about drugs but you do drugs I
may have experienced with drugs before
but have
you well uh you know yeah yeah are you
doing drugs now no no not now me neither
I'm just trying to prepare myself
economically and mentally for the future
well that's what I'm trying to do and my
kids too well I guess we got something
in common don't we now the point of this
skit is this we all have common ground
look you're white you're
black but neither one of us is as pretty
as you shake hand stay tuned I'm f is
time
[Applause]
TR welcome back get Sprite Mark another
round of
applause all right now we going to talk
about some controversy [ __ ] we got a
little bit time here so we got hit the
stuff real quick here now when I told
people out in the community I said Spike
Moss is going to be my show this weekend
I heard a lot of positive stuff but
there was a lot of negative reaction to
you being on the show they say well
Spike ain't nothing but out for himself
and he's out for the money he does
nothing but chase down television
cameras what would you say to that stuff
there well I'm overdue to get the
money I think the work I do is going to
draw some cameras and uh I think you
said the magic word whenever people of
color speak about their demise of
freedom is controversial right I think
if I was speaking about freedom in
Russia at the time when it was Communist
I would be considered as a controversial
person how has a person controversial
who speaks about freedom in a free
country unless in fact you're trying to
tell me because I'm black I have no
right to speak on freedom good answer
man I like that I like that another
quick question for you something that
You' been getting a lot of impressed
about is that when a lot of black
suspects are suspected of crimes rather
than going and surrendering at the
police station they're coming to you
United for peace and you're escorting
them down to be arrested why is there
the need for that well I think you got
to look at the reality of people telling
those young men or their families that
we don't want you in we're going to
murder you we're going to kill you the
reality is if we didn't have as many
brutal beatings or killings in this town
maybe you could believe you could make
it in M but I mean this is a town with a
tall history of black males shot in the
back of the head and shot in the back
and to this day not one person has been
uh found guilty for any of those
killings of black people by law
enforcement as a matter of fact I said
at the courthouse press conference
yesterday this is the only town or city
or state in its history of having a
police department where no matter what
case has been brought against our police
department they have been found not
guilty they are 100% right every time
there is no police St station nowhere
that is 100% right on every case right
and and since I'm speaking on that let
me say this about the reason I was down
there quickly please the sister that is
down there pressing charges against that
officer that officer also has some seven
to eight rape cases against black women
he he is still in uniform he does most
of it with his uniform on his badge on
he hasn't been suspended fired arrested
he has no bail you see what I'm saying
and I'm saying it's you're saying to us
that some people are above the law H
some people are above the law we got
wrap here real quick is there anything
like to say to the twin s before we go
here Spike oh it's just
hot all right man I tell you what I
can't think enough please give my friend
Spike marks a big round of applause
fight
Mar all right stay right there
buddy yes coming up next week on get
down with it we're featuring an
interview with Rock and Roll legend B
dley we're g to take a little peek at
that we'll come back with ticket
information stay tuned and get down with
it I Bly next week fight Mar all right
man good stuff man thank you started
Rocking R Bill and
chuckberry see and that's the truth you
know and I feel give credit where credit
is due Elvis was a hell of an
Entertainer and I love him for what he
did but they hung some things on him
that he didn't deserve he did not start
rock and roll and I want my title you
want the title I want my title what's
the title that you want I don't want to
be no King but I'm
good if you would like to be part of the
studio audience for get down with it
we'd love to have you so call now for
ticket information
491268 that's
[Music]
491268 and now once again here's fancy
Ray
[Music]
mcloney my my my my my my thank you I am
the best looking man in comedy if Beauty
was a crime I get life in jail but if
good looks was money I get out the next
day on
bail you think that's funny well being
ugly was a crime you get life if you was
mared so with your
wife my my my I want to take this
opportunity to thank my fantastic
sponsors I want to thank Insight
newspaper we find our cablecast schedule
hair by J which Styles my head
dude shut up now also I want to thank
all the people here in the audience the
people in the back everybody give
yourselves a round of
applause taking us home and our black
Black History Month celebration we got
Carlos Brewer singing the black national
anthem lift every voice and sing my name
is fancy Ray mclone tune in next week
and get down with
it good night happy History Month
[Applause]
byebye LIF every
voice sing until Earth and
[Music]
Heaven ring ring with the
hearton
ofy let it
Rejoice
right as the
Ling Skies let it
reside loud as the
roll L SE
sing a
song full of the faith that the dark
pass has
taught us and
sing us
song full of the hope that the present
has bought
facing the
Rising
Sun of our new
day beun so let us march
on till
Victory
[Music]
is is