hello this is fancy Ray the best looking
man in comedy today my special special
guest tonight is comedian Dana good you
may recognize Dana from his numerous TV
appearances he's known universally
throughout the standup world as Mr
Sunshine how you doing Dana pretty good
what you aing buy oh man you got it baby
now being Mr Sunshine how do you feel I
feel great you know the way I see Life
Ray we're all born the same when we come
out we're naked we're covered in blood
and we're screaming in Terror and it
doesn't have to stop there if you know
how to live right um but but but but
being known for your positiveness and
touching so many people's lives with
your optimism and your joy and your
happiness how does that make you feel it
makes me feel terrific just spreading
what I have and giving it to other
people the way I see Life Ray the
luckiest people in the world next to you
and I are the best friends of Sideshow
freaks because they get to look at them
all day long for free Dana Dana um what
do you say to yourself when you look in
the mirror every morning good morning
chump Dana this doesn't sound very happy
I mean uh what makes you happy Dana oh
there's one thing that makes me Happy's
that watching fancy Ray and getting down
with
it my my my don't go nowhere stay tuned
coming up we got Dana good my my my my
my ow
hello my name is fancy Ray MCL I am the
best looking man in comedy talk show
host are di a doen The Only Exception is
me cuz I've got the gro of moves of
looks and this incredibly Charming
personality now I first saw s Jesse
Raphael my eyes they started to Sag I
said the networks are trying to fool us
that ain't nothing but down H dress and
drag now some people think Oprah Winford
is the best they think Oprah wears the
crown well she may be the heavyweight
champ honey I'm the best under 200 lb
stay tuned I'm fancy R it's time to get
down with
it I said and get
down
the come on
bab hello this is fancy Ray MCL the best
looking man in comedy woo some people
think I'm a fruit others say I'm a berry
and those who know me well they say I'm
a chocolate covered
Cherry woo my my my feature guest
tonight is an outstanding comedian he
has been an Areno Showtime HBO he is
universally recognized for being uncanny
and unconventional he's also known as
being outstanding ladies and gentlemen
it's my pleasure to introduce comedian
Dana good are you how do I look Dana you
look incredible man I know incredible
say that again incredible I thought I
looked good and I left the house and
then I saw you uh well that happens to a
lot of people out there watching the
show you know that first thing people
say to themselves when they see you I
got to go back to work
W and they go to pay dirt oh man they
put on a new shirt they got to buckle
down oh man no doubt about it Dana your
comedy Act is very unique in fact
something that you don't know is that my
very first paid comedy gig here in minap
was I was Ming a show for you at the old
comedy Gallery at River Place oh wow I
remember that yes yes and you had this
the I remember exactly way you were you
had these great shark skin suits MH cuz
I Tred to dress up nice but it just
doesn't work mhm I get in a nice sharp
skin suit and look like why is Dana in
that stolen
suit no no they don't say that about you
Dana cuz you're making the big bucks out
in Hollywood now that's right but I
ain't I ain't spend it in un clo as you
can tell who spent more time in the
wardrobe no no no but you know something
Dana is that your comedy act you touch
issues and go places that most comedians
wouldn't go yeah I just do what I think
is funny you know as as you do you know
uh I just try to think of what kind of
show would I like to see what would make
me laugh and and those are the places I
like to go I've always been sort of
laughing at the things that not
everybody else laughs at you know but I
mean you're talking about like
alienation humiliation uh misery despair
that's not a place where most comedians
go well when I experience other emotions
I'll talk about them the question I have
to ask ask of you is how much of that is
from your personal experience and how
much of it is just an act right well
it's it's all from my personal
experience but it's not exclusively you
know I mean I I'm in a great happy mood
as much as everybody else but everybody
goes through that really awkward stage
when you're in your mid 20s or or
whenever as a kid and that's really from
where I draw most of my humor that's the
stuff that I think is really funny is
the stuff that also hurts a little bit
too you know that's that's where I find
I'm best suited I can write jokes about
politics or whatever but the stuff that
I really do best is go to that sort of
feeling of uncomfortable you know when
you're uncomfortable or you've blown it
with a woman or you know it's just when
it's really wrong that's what I find the
humor in but there's so much pain I mean
most people don't go there for humor
yeah they don't that's why I'm sort of
unique it works I mean that's but that's
you I mean that whates make Dana G so
special yeah right exactly I mean it's
it's a limited it's a a limited thing
but it it works for me you know uhhuh I
can't imagine you ever feeling any of
those feelings oh no no no no the last
time I felt misery was one day I was got
up in the morning I looked in the mirror
and it was dirty oh no no
see now you tell me that story I'll put
it into my hat okay true true it's so
true in your act you make fun of
comedians who do the like you know
punchlines set up punch line set up
punch line set up punch line I I love a
good comedian and it doesn't have to be
standard what I sort of like to poke fun
at is people that do it in an uncreative
way and there's just that cookie cutter
you know sort of thing I mean cuz you
know you created a vehicle for yourself
that's it's Unique and you're your own
person you know how to do it you know
what you're doing and we know other
people that have done the same thing and
then there were people that they there's
no creativity to it they just sort of
come out blurt out the jokes get their
check and leave and those are the people
I have little patience with who inspired
the type of Comedy that you do it um boy
it's really hard to say I remember when
I was young like who was your favorite
comic when you're starting out man
unquestionably Richard Pryor yeah
Richard prior the first Richard PRI
movie live in concert where he had the
heart attack that one bit where he had
the heart attack is really what stuck
with me as like because it was about
something really horribly painful but it
was so hilarious and he did it in such a
theatrical way I just thought that was
amazing I was also a huge fan of George
Carlin although I don't think that I
really do anything like him and uh
Albert Brooks the the actor Albert
Brooks when he did stand up for a while
and that just put me right out really
yeah okay just killed me let me wrun a
couple of names about you speaking of
comedians how about uh Andy Kaufman Andy
Kaufman brilliant I could never even
approach what he did he he Andy Coffman
did comedy about comedy people don't
understand that it's half the time when
Andy coff was working he was making fun
of Comedy it was yeah you he's one of
those people that you look at like I can
never even get close to that really
really he inspires you that much yeah
he's just so incredible yeah how about
let's say uh we got local comedian Joel
Hudson Joel Hudson big fan good friend
of mine actually uh he's the reason I
have my manager really yeah I was in
Minneapolis a couple of years ago Joel
and I met became friends he had his
manager come in from New York and uh
that's how I got my manager really okay
okay you you're hooked up now and you're
cooking now yeah yeah and Joel's still a
really good friend oh man he's a
beautiful cat man he's a great guy how
about Eddie Murphy Eddie Murphy
hilarious Delirious tour funniest live
comedy show ever now I'm surprised that
you like his style of Comedy no see I
like I like all that sort of stuff I
mean I mean I I love Don Rickles okay I
think Don you know anybody that's that's
telling the truth about who they are M
makes me laugh I didn't I never saw raw
okay and I I'm not a big fan of Martin
Lawrence because I don't think Martin
Lawrence put as much creativity into it
as Eddie Murphy did I mean Eddie has an
incredible mind and Martin I think is an
amazing performer but he doesn't the
material it just doesn't have the the
spark to me that Eddie Murphy had stepen
Wright another just being who he is
brilliant brilliant absolutely brilliant
who don't you like that's big who don't
I well I I'd hate to name any names on
camera but but you know the people that
come out and do the same BL okay let me
let me let me think hard let me okay I
tell you what we're going to do we're
going to take a commercial break right
now and we're going to come back we're
going to find out who Dana doesn't like
right here on the fancy R show tell him
to stay tuned tell him to get down with
it I'm here and we're gonna get down
with it Oh My My My Dana good we'll be
right back
oh in Break On Through with
JFK come
on all right yeah
meet the president come on I'm the
president let's have
fun the image I don't know about the
pans things they don't go with the time
the man you may be the president of the
United States but you are still the
president
of Jackie pure Oliver St right yeah oh
roses are red vies are blue you know I
look good and I know it
too this is fancy R the best looking man
in with comedian Dana good brother how
you doing Dana Shing now they're coming
back now we're sitting on the edge of
our seats we're going to find out who
Dana doesn't like who who sucks Dana who
sucks who bites the big one Jay Leno I
can't stand it can't watch him anymore
why not us used to be the best Jay in
his day was nobody could touch him was
so great and you can see him hold back
and you can see him try to please
everybody instead of making people laugh
he's not being himself have no time for
it like what do you mean he's not being
himself what he's it's like if I went on
and pretended to be really and pretended
to do just Bland material when I when
you know there's somebody there's
something behind it mhm you know if if
uh if Prince how how would I look at you
and think of Prince If Prince If Prince
went on and sang you know Michael Bolt
and stuff to try to sell more records
he's not being himself Jerry Seinfeld
same thing clever bright boring nothing
there excites me there's nothing
dangerous about either one of those
performers you know what I mean that's
but is it still funny though they're
still funny but to me I don't I'm not
interested because there's no danger
there you know what I'm saying you know
there's going to be a sense of danger
Eddie Murphy brilliant Richard Pryor you
don't know what's going to happen next
what's going to happen it might be scary
it might be wild it might be something
I've never heard before you know that's
what keeps you on your seat that's
what's vital that's what's theater
that's why you watch Jay Leno Jerry
Seinfeld boring Sandra burnhard has
never made me laugh I don't get it uhuh
how about Sam Kennison Sam Kennon was
great and when Sam Kennison started um
towards the end of his life uh he sort
of became this parody of a heavy metal
guy but before Sam Kennison was even on
TV when he was just working the door at
The Comedy Store no one could touch it
Sam Sam kenneson was the most you laugh
so hard you like beg him to stop really
yeah another guy who was just real being
himself Bill Hicks greatest being
himself talking about What mattered to
Bill Hicks the best the best yeah Paula
Poundstone very funny talks about what's
important to her gets it out M you
mentioned Leno now you've done Areno
have you done have you done Leno yet
haven't yeah know and I know the guy
I've been to his house you know but he
just I think he looks at people like me
it's probably why I don't like him is he
looks at me and sees somebody that's
that's a little on the edge and
dangerous instead of framing that and
putting it on television and presenting
it it here something different and
unique they go no no we can only have
Bland people on but is because the style
that you do the comedy that you do is
such it's so dangerous does that hurt
your TV appearance to say like Letterman
yes it does but I can't compromise who I
am you just got to do what you do and
eventually they'll catch up that's what
you wait for I mean same with you you
you wouldn't change ticket on TV you
just do what you do let everybody else
catch up could you see me in blue jeans
no could you see me in anything
but my my my my my my there's room for
all different types that's you is a wide
spectrum right now ouren is going off
the off the air going off the air he is
let me put in a plug he is the nicest
guy you know I did the Dennis Miller
show Orin show I've been to the Tonight
Show when Johnny Carson was there I've
you know been to the Leno show I've been
to all the shows Areno Hall the they're
all nice all those guys are nice people
they're all great people but uh Areno
Hall was the nicest most down toe person
I've met of all the hosts really when I
did the show came backstage thanks for
being here handshake totally normal guy
went did the show during the commercial
talks to you cool great guy I wish him
luck with whatever he does and he's a
very C he's not hurting right now yeah
he's you know you ain't going to be
seeing him at the end of the grocery
aisle asking you for paper or plastic
either and if you see fancy R then I'll
uh get silk okay that's get silk he'll
be at
Frederick's no out in Hollywood there's
so much stuff going on there's a Tom and
Roseanne thing do you know Tom and
rosean I've met them yeah very nice
people what do you think about the whole
threesome marriage divorce back together
off again it's who cares I don't care
you don't care no I mean there's other
stuff to watch I'm I'm like an old fogy
I watch
Nightline yeah I mean okay what I mean
people people aren't familiar with you
they're watching like okay now who is
fancy who now who is Dana G tell them
who Dana G is well I'm uh your average
IR rate white boy who thinks way too
much for his own good I'm always willing
to snatch defeat from the jaws of
Victory and I'm never short and I'm
never caught short of a headach MH MH
mhm you know let's put it this way if
you if you in the in the realm of music
M if you were the George Clinton and the
Parliament funell oh man flashlight I
would be Elvis Costello with a sneer and
a thick pair of
glasses room for plenty room for plenty
that's right oh and there is many oo I'm
an angry white boy that didn't get as
many women as you wanted and everybody's
going to pay now that's something you
talk about in your acting fact is your
relationships with women uhuh not a
whack
thereof tell me about women what's the
problem with you and women you're a
good-looking guy you're very talented
you got the what's going on with you and
women I just screw it up every time man
I don't know what it is I just I blow it
every time why to talk to me it's like I
I buy all these Porsches and one's
wrapped around a tree one I drove into a
lake one I drove into a ditch I don't
mean to do it they're great cars really
oh I could have get me a Porsche with no
wheels but now what's going no I no I
had one really long relationship that
really kicked me in the gut and uh and
now I'm doing fine I enjoy life really
now who you dating now Dana
several people women I know is that
right I'm sharing the wealth all right
well stay tuned not the only beautiful
person on
show and I'm a v no no I'm not we'll
talk about that after the show salt and
pepper salt and my my my my my I tell
you we're going to take another break
right now we're gonna come back and
we're gonna find out about women we're
going to talk about his act we're GNA
talk about a lot of things don't go
nowhere this is Dana good I'm the
chocolate human I know I look good don't
go nowhere it's time to get down with it
my my my oh
us custom Coast Guard dope dog nickname
bust him like most dope sniffing dogs
he's got a habit train to have to Hab it
pick up the tracks of the traffickers
and track them like a rabbit up the
coastline K9 control substance retriever
receiver of the golden nose award for
lead him to the cash cashing in on the
stash now he's in line for his isue a
booty never do he do a line in the line
of duty he's a dope dog undercover knock
with a bar took a bite out of crime
posing as a c and ey dog he bit the
blind the man with the cane made of
coat hello this is fancy Ray the best
looking man in comedy I can be your
husband I can be your wife I'm all
utility o like a Swiss army
knife I like that one we're here with
comedian Dana good welcome back Dana how
are you brother how do I look you look
fabulous you get better every day know
you can't wait for tomorrow I know I
know keep talking you're telling the
truth you're telling the truth you know
you asked me before how do I how do I s
himself can we get a shot of our shoes
this is the perfect this is Ray and this
is
me woo fan loafers sturdy old wing
tips oh parts of me is sturdy though
that's I'm not doubting that I'm not
going to go there may be wing tips on it
too whatever
works no we talking about different
women and your different experien with
women you talk about your family
background yeah how much how much is the
Dana good that we sing on stage is
really Dana lies not a word of truth I
made it all up lies no it's it's you
know you talk about a part of it you
know it's one part of my life I going to
talk about the stuff that's happy no
it's boring who
cares so that these are things that have
but I have great relations with my
family you always say you know am I
happy are you happy oh yeah no very much
very yeah I'm doing what I want to do
getting paid making bugs I've got good
shoes hair grew in I ain't bald yet yeah
much to complain about you work through
all that crap and you just talk about it
and make fun of it I mean you had so
much success early in your career I mean
like you just boom took off really right
I did I was right out of the gate right
yeah and then it sort of levels off and
you know that's the beautiful thing is
you can be a has been at 25 then you
going to reinvent yourself which is sort
of what I do what I'm doing now what so
where are you going now where's where's
Dana good going well now I'm trying not
to be so strictly talking about myself
and sort of opening it up more which is
why of I'm doing at the comedy Gallery
talking more about just the way I see
the world instead of just the way I see
myself in it how do you see the world I
mean you're part of this generation x I
mean you are that's I mean that's your
audience yeah it's true y y y Generation
X uh well I'm just talking you know you
get out in the world and there just so
many things that don't work that should
and it's just so frustrating and it's
and it goes all the way back to it goes
all the way back to Jesus they always
nail the good
guy why you know I'll be next no yeah
I'm right behind you talking about the
Generation X of course we just lost Kurt
coang with the terrible suicide thoughts
about that uh oh that was that was sad I
mean I mean people joke about suicide a
lot but I think the thing that people
don't really understand is that when you
for a lot of people that commit suicide
they don't have a choice it's a chemical
imbalance in their brain like my dad
would Kur Coan some drug addict junkie
where's my beer you know but they you
know you you put yourself in your
situation go well if I was a big rock
star and had all the money in the world
I wouldn't kill myself of course not
because your chemicals are all in the
right balance right you know that was
sad I mean again why can't Michael
Bolton get depressed and go into the
garage why does it got to be Kurt
copain come
on how come one guy I hate can't die one
time it's always Robert Kennedy it's
always John Kennedy you're from
Massachusetts that's right yeah I know
all those guys know those we party all
the time really seriously Ted gets down
really you should get Ted on this show
oh man that would be cool that' be cool
man we go swim under the bridge together
[Laughter]
no we're talking about suicide have you
I mean you talk about so much pain in
your act have you ever been close no no
no no not seriously no no no no you just
get uh you know when you're 13 and
you're Catholic you always have that Mom
I took a bottle of aspirin you don't
feel hot but no never really that much
no it just it's it's just to talk about
you know like when you say you know you
know what I would say it's like you know
when you're sitting around with your
buddies now I know you can't relate to
this let's try I'm going try I'm going
try I'm you're always sitting around
with your buddies and you're all talking
about
how you got dumped the hardest okay yeah
see I know you can't relate to this
dumped what does that mean see there you
go dumping is when a woman decides not
to go out with you oh I thought talking
about using the bathroom no no no well
that's a different story in time that's
my best I don't know about that either
I'm sure you don't I read in Hustler
magazine ice
cream but you know when you're sitting
around with your buddies and you're
talking about how you got dumped the
hardest and the guy who got the most
brutal story that's what you laugh a
hardest at that's where I come from
really yeah so tell us come on now we're
talking now tell us about the the
hardest dumping that you had the hardest
dumping I ever had moved from Boston to
San Francisco to live with this woman
wow when I got there that's love at the
airport no not at the airport like
within a week really within a week so
what did you do stayed turned out to be
the best thing that ever happened to me
uhhuh yeah but didn't go down
well you know it's like medicine tastes
really bad but in the end you're glad
you did it right right right right so
you still still friends with her now uh
it wasn't for a long time but now that
I'm successful they all come crawling
back really oh yeah so now what do you
do now now your heart broken as she
crawls back and do you say I still love
you and I care about you and and hey I'm
glad you finally woke up and hey yeah no
it's like the get smart cone of silence
how you doing keep your distance this
could be
trouble got to got to look out for
number one it's done right now wait a
minute now your act is so much full of
pain but here positiveness we're here
optimism that's the new me really that
glass ain't half empty it's half full
really that's the new me what's the give
me a new you joke oh man new you joke
this is the new the new the new Dana go
I don't have any jokes I just have these
weird stories okay give us a new Dana
good story okay let me all right hang on
I just need give me a minute we got a
minute we got a minute I'll talk about
how good look I oh I look so good give
me a give me a topic and I'll go off oh
a topic uh masturbation masturbation see
masturbation the best kind of
masturbation you can possibly have is
when you've been in your house for a
long long time couple of days and you
haven't been out of your bathrobe just
sitting around drinking coffee watching
TV nothing to do because it's pure
frustration just Joy just get it out
just sitting there in a dark room
hammering away like a chimp in the
rainforest when he sees another
bulldozer oh enjoy enjoy I tell you what
Dana me you are fantastic my pleasure
man I you know I say this so often
people don't take it seriously but I
tell you Dana Good's doing his interview
he's leaving town tomorrow that's right
now tell you what kind of guy this he is
he knows this is going to promote a show
but he's still here because he wants to
talk to you people out there my viewers
and he's a great guy when Dana good
comes back you'll see in the papers go
check this man out he's fantastic he'll
make you think he'll put you in some
places that may be a little
uncomfortable but still you'll have a
good time he's a one of a kind guy and I
really wish you the best of luck and
we'll see you you got Bob Hope coming up
this month right hey I tell you no
kidding yeah this this month but no no
there's no one like him in the world one
one of a kind Dana good stay tuned tell
to get down with
it my my my my my we'll be right back
Dana
good hi this is Bridget from Dream Girls
and when I watch TV I like watching Ray
Ray's gorgeous Ray's strong Ray's
handsome and I don't mean just any Ray
she means fancy Ray oh my my my stay
tuned it's time to get down it my my my
my
my I said get
[Music]
down
bab all right this is fancy R the best
look manic comedy today what goes up
must come down we all know this is true
I know something that goes up never
comes out I guess I'm the exception to
every
[Music]
rule my my my my my before I go any
further I want thank my fantastic
sponsors I want thank Insight news where
you can find my cablecast schedule here
by J with Styles my hair do and my main
man are Scott there on the camera the
comedy gallery and Dana G for the great
interview I hope you enjoyed tonight's
show make sure you tune in next week to
the fancy R show cuz if I'm there wo i
honey we going to get down with
it my my my I know I look
good get down with it
ow and now the world premiere of The
fany Ray
round
[Music]
right Mama I'm fancy R and I'm on the
mic I want to tell you fly girl just
what I like I like sweeten and face
sping the was and the Big M but all over
the place I'm the king of poets never R
before but here I am not knocking next
door if you open the door I'm a slide on
it and your m going to treat me like her
next K I'm fany and I'm doing my rhy and
I'm here to have myself a funky good
time 5' 11 and I'm built for Speed if
your man ain't got it I got everything
need I like sweeten the face in the
waste and the big bubble butt all over
the place let me tell you the story of
fancy R the most beautiful man in comedy
today when I was born the moon didn't
rise only the stars came out and lit of
the Skies by the time I reached the age
of five my mama said i' be prettiest man
in life I knew i' been success I didn't
knock on wood I just looked at Mir and
said o child you look good and I did
look good honey I am the best looking
man in ComEd I have always been the best
looking man in ComEd wait a minute you
ain't claing baby you ain't never seen
this before you ain't never touched it
you ain't never heard it but let me tell
you something baby tonight you going to
feel it I my my my my my I to get time
yeah I'm 5' 11 and I'm built for Speed
and if your man ain't got I got
everything you need I like sweet the
face and send the wa and the big bubble
butt all over the place are you having a
good time do you love fancy
R I know how you feel baby
my say
m say my my
my say go f say go f say go go Fancy Go
Fancy Go I'mma do my fancy dance
y I'm doing the fancy dance
y'all stay tuned and get down with it
I'm doing the fancy
dance twinkle twinkle little star how I
wonder where you are up up up the world
so high looking at me going my
Mama twinkle twinkle little star how I
wonder where you are thanks for watching
have a good night