[Applause]
well now now people keep saying now Ross
what are you going to do about the
farmer how you going to help the farmer
all right now I think about the farmer I
think about rain you get a gentle rain
is good for the crops you get a hard
driving rain wash away the seed you
can't get a crop if you can't get a crop
you can't get a priz if you can't get a
price you can't get price supports from
the government all right now I think
about the crops I think about the soil
think about soil I think about mud think
about mud I think about pigs when I
think about pigs think about Ned batty
from Deliverance
all right now when I think about I think
about Ned Betty from Deliverance think
now that boy sure had a pretty
mouth all right now now speaking of a
pretty mouth I got a fell coming up on
stage here he got pretty hair pretty
teeth pretty eyes he he's just all
around pretty I'm GNA bring him up on
stage my running mate for 1996 Francy
Ray mclone the human chocolate orch all
right thank
you thank
you that's right now you asking yourself
who am I and why am I here well it's cuz
I look good damn it he looks good shut
up now some always want to ask you what
does the h stand for well you know son
it's always stood for just H but when I
look at you I tell you it's got to stand
for
handsome no looking at me I think it's
stands for
hopeless my name is fancy Ray M the best
looking man in comedy and I'm H Ros Pro
and it's time to get down with it oh my
my my my
and get down and
wi do the
J come on
baby want to watch
everybody I said come on
baby want everybody do the
J I said come on
baby get been a long long
[Music]
time baby ladies and Gentlemen please
welcome to host and star of get with it
the best looking man in comedy Bey
[Applause]
[Music]
R hello hello hello my name is fancy Ray
mcco I am the best looking man in
comedy my my my my does this feel like
deju my my my how you guys feel about
Clinton went in the white
house now what I'm about to say you may
think it's ludicrous ludicrous and full
of dunion but the first thing he should
do when he gets to the White House is
make my face the 51st state of the
union my my my my my I am the best
looking man in cedy you know it's a wild
and crazy things happen out there you
know the city is strapped with fear
right now cuz all this crime going on
and I tell you what the most scary thing
out there in the Twin Cities the black
male cuz you black and the male you
guilty right that ain't no lie man I was
downtown the other day this old lady saw
me coming she grabbed the purse I said
baby I don't want your money well I
going to take that makeup kit you
know crazy things out there how about
you guys think about Dave durber what's
going on with him you guys hear about
that yeah woman claims that he raped her
some years ago and now she has an adult
child wait a minute explain something to
me now someone rapes you I think you
should notify somebody right if you get
pregnant and have a baby I think at that
point you should notify somebody to wait
29 years and say this is your child I
think Dave durenberger knows the true
meaning behind achy breaky heart
now if I was Dave durber i' come up my
own novelty song it'd be like to the Mel
of achy breaky heart it be called beanie
biny bone yeah be like beanie biny bone
why you leave my butt alone why you
bother me after all these years you can
to have a rash if you thinking get some
cash you better think again cuz you can
kiss my beanie B bone crazy things out
there my my my my my my my I mean that
could happen to me I mean could you
imagine somay some woman comes to me
like 5 years from now R this is your kid
he ain't my kid prove it Robert come in
the room hi this is beautiful Bobby I'm
the Prett SC playground do I look good
do I look good do I look
good my my my my my crazy things out
there I honestly I don't have kids I
don't but if I did have children believe
one thing they' be right here in
Minnesota with me that's right
benefiting from the best welfare system
entire nation crazy world out there I
got to tell y'all about a very
embarrassing situation I got caught in
this morning I was inside a bathroom the
man's waiting outside the bathroom stand
standing by the door and as he stood
there he heard all this moaning and
groaning heavy breathing and sighing he
opened the door and found me standing
looking in the
mirror you heard of Manaj twah I have
Minaj Mah it was good I work hard on my
show some I'm trying to get on my show
is Jim Baker you guys like Jim you know
he's in jail here in the Minnesota in
fact I could have had Tammy F Baker on
my show but I W know on my show who
wears more makeup than I
do crazy that thing out there oh man I
was watching the Oprah Winfrey show the
other day so you know this is true
right Oprah said that 75% of the most
beautiful women in America sit home
alone on Saturday nights and y'all know
what they
doing why yeah thinking about
me my woman brace my Tender Touch you
know the way I I better be careful I'm
turning myself on up
here people ask me all the time how I
got the name fancy R well I want y'all
to know the truth I just love fword
don't y'all like fword yeah cuz I'm not
just Fancy no I'm so flamboyant I'm
fantastic I'm fun I'm funny I'm
fashioned I'm fragrant I'm
fertile I'm fabulous I'm famous well
y'all can see how blessed I am but let's
be honest y'all the lucky ones cuz y'all
get to look at
me I guess that makes everybody in this
room fortunate my my my my my my my my I
am the best looking man in
County we got a fantastic show we got
record producer David Z in the house
tonight y'all all
right all right and from the American
superstars of dance we got tnie and
lucenda here tonight y'all all
right ever want to be a private eye now
is the time be on the lookout for safety
in your home over 4 million are injured
in home accidents every year nearly
$30,000
by once again
here fency Ray
mcloney my my my my thank you lordy M
clud people say I'm Ludy toy and fruity
I tell to shut up cuz the beaut is on
duty please now my my my my my featured
guest tonight is a fantastic producer he
helped Prince get his first record deal
he produced a great song funky town back
in 1980 and just a few years ago he
produced She Drives Me crazy with the
Fine Young Cannibals we're going to take
a look at David Z and action we'll be
right back with producer David Z y'all
all right as as we were taking a
different direction we thought we'd try
and use a different producer we were
talking to the we said who do you want
to work we said well the only person
we'd like to work with his Prince and we
found out you know that was pretty
impossible but they said there's this
guy David Z who has work with him a lot
he did like kiss and he did of purple
rain
[Music]
like she
D all right get it going for David Z
y'all David Z oh man how do I look great
great not just great I'm gorgeous God
get you and you look at me now you say
he good for
you man my my my my I got to tell you
one thing though what's got to stay out
of my closet and wearing my clothes I'm
sick of
L is that right okay I'll stay out of
your closet man if you stay out of mine
I ain't going to say shut up please now
you've been producer man some great
great success what something I never
understood what exactly does a producer
do uh producer is different with
everybody I think I mean there's some
producers that are writers and there's
some producers that are puers and
they're you know players and uh some
people just hold people's hands and some
people just say that's the good one uh
it's kind of different with everybody
really yeah so it's a unique sort of
just like get guitar players not you
know it's all different every person's a
different personality how dides someone
become a producer how did you get into
the producing game uh it was an accident
with me I uh I didn't want to do it I uh
it was a mistake I was a shoe salesman
and my wife said want you to do
something interesting so I started to be
record producer really yeah that's all
happened that's all happened huh that's
same thing with me something like that
happened to me I was working at the
fantasy house oh shut up now am
man please now but so you got on to now
you first the old Prince get his record
deal back in 7877 well yeah I mean uh uh
we did a demo tape and on the basis of
that Warren brothers signed him they I
remember they took him out to LA and we
went out there and they didn't believe
that he played everything I guess they
wanted to see it for themselves so he
kind of did an audition and they had all
these five or six producers there from
Warner Brothers ass sciti you know which
one which one's going to do it and they
like man he can do it himself we don't
need that so he's a great talent of
course you see him grow over the years
oh yeah I ask you a quick question we're
going to get on to but when you think
about the remember you saw the article
on the City Pages about how he's changed
since the great success has happened
he's CH no he hasn't changed at all you
don't you don't agree with that argument
that he's he's living in this Castle or
this isolation Elvis thing I don't think
he's changed since I've since the
beginning you know I don't know about
living in isolation if he is then he
always has okay but I don't think he's
changed okay the same person now you
work with so people we saw the Fine
Young Cannibals uh Jesse Johnson yeah
all these different artists who did you
enjoy working with the most oh there's a
there's a few that I really like Prince
Of course I love the he was he's fun all
the time find young cannibals are fun I
mean most most people I work with I do
it cuz I I know I'm going to have fun
with them that's the reason I do it to
have fun when you having fun like when
you produce a record you look at it's on
tape do you know it's going to be hit no
you know it's good you do it for what's
what you love and you hope it's going to
be a hit but you never know it's all
kind of in the air sometimes really like
like when you did funky town which was
how I mean we're talking millions of an
international smash that was really
illogical because there was no hit out
of Minneapolis ever before that except
for maybe you know a different era but
you know we we always hoped that we
could make hit records in Minneapolis
and um when that one that one was the
first one really that was such a big hit
and it just shocked me I had no idea I
didn't even know it was a hit until a
year later because we never even heard
it on the radio here right because mini
off isn't Progressive well yeah it was
kind of stifled and I think that's kind
of probably the reason that uh the music
scene flourished here is because one of
the reasons is that we didn't get to
hear all this stuff on the radio so we
got frustrated and started making our
own music it's kind of what happened now
that you have influence how come we're
not getting low even now it's still
tough for new artists get stuff on the
radio here in the Twin Cities H I don't
know I it's programmers you know mhm
it's it's what they think the people
will like and and they look at the
demographics and say well there's only
2% of these kind of people so we don't
need to play that kind of music and that
you know might they're discounting the
fact that maybe everybody likes a little
everything MH you know in Europe it's
different cuz they they just play good
music they'll play a good country song
they'll play a good R&D song they'll
play a good rap song you know just back
to back just because it's good not
because it's a certain style so I think
that's kind of healthy mhm the L more
diversity yeah and here things like like
you know it's an R&B station or it's a
pop station it's a country station
everybody's in a slot right yeah that's
not very fair yeah that's true that's
true we now talk about the uh the Fine
Young Cannibals that was a tremendous
hit she drives me crazy I heard it had a
different title initially yeah it was uh
she's my baby she's my baby mhm who
changed it you changed it no they
changed it they changed yeah they did
they wanted something a little catchier
uhhuh some somebody could identify with
and I think we all have people that
drive us
crazy so uh you know and female people
too so uh that applied everybody
understood so I think it worked so when
you made that song you had like no
inclination this is this this really has
that touch well actually they were they
threw it away they didn't want to do it
really when they sent me all the songs
um I said well I'll do that song but I
don't to do the other ones because they
weren't ready and they went well that
one we didn't want to do that one I went
oh man that's the only one I like right
now but you know all the other ones
developed as we you know did the record
but I kind of pull that one over the
trash can which is kind of interesting
mhm I don't think artists know what
sometimes what songs they write they
write so many songs that they don't know
which ones are the good ones sometimes
they're too close to it mhm so I think
that's one thing a producer should do is
be able to pick the the hit so if I'm an
artist not coming to you I got to trust
your judgment on what's good and what's
not good you you decide yep and you're
the boss huh how in fact you've worked
with something I want to ask you about
is do you ever see artists like from the
old days say like James Brown and say or
Al Green or something if I could take
him out and put some Modern beats on it
and and uh and do something with him you
yeah I do that's that would be really
fun to do sometimes um uh I'd like to
experiment with that but it's hard to
get to people once they' been
established for so long and you know
they don't want to change I I've done a
couple experiments kind of like a mad
scientist where I took uh some
established artists and they wanted
something new but yet when it came down
to it they they have a hard time going
well that's not the way we always did it
so you know we can't do it that way so
it's a little harder I like new artists
because they'll Bend you know they'll do
anything I say if I say put the guitars
underwater and play a solo and they
won't go watch they'll they'll go won't
I be electrocuted I say no don't trust
me so it'll work and that kind of stuff
you know they'll believe me and and I
like that cuz it works sometimes what's
your proudest moment as a producer what
out of all the stuff you work on what
are you most proud of oh I don't know
there's a lot of them I name a couple of
them couple of them Purple Rain I'm
proud of Kiss I'm proud of find
cannibals hit I'm proud of all of them I
know I I guess I'm proba I'm proud
actually of a lot of the things that
didn't sell because I do it because I
believe in it and there's some groups
and artist that you know maybe didn't
get so big as far as sales but I still
think they're great musicians great
songwriters I was thought there's so
many people maybe in their basement that
have as much talent as the people on top
but they might never get a chance to see
it you we got to wrap up here real quick
speaking to people in the basement what
advice would you give someone who wants
to go on and be successful producing
that's it really punch what if someone
want that says uh I'm I'm bad and I want
to get a tape to Bobby Z cuz I think
Bobby Z can do some stuff with good send
it to
him
David Bobby Bobby your your brother
who's been on the show is a dear dear
friend what if someone wants to get you
though would you say what would I say
yeah if they want to get a tap to you
I'd say uh make sure it's the best thing
you can do before you get it to somebody
really okay okay that's great that's
great but man we really appreciate
taking the time to come on down man and
give a round of applause y'all
[Applause]
DAV stay
get hello my name is Charles fer and I'm
your guest here in the Twin Cities and
guess what I'm happening now with the
man who can say his name is fancy Ray
the man who makes the night turn to day
the man who can make the dead dogs play
I'm talking about fancy a fancy fancy R
the man that makes Little Richard look
like a priest the man that makes yogurt
taste like yeast the man who can take
the moon from the sky and put it into
Hercules and make the monkey cry
[Applause]
fany oh all right thank you all right
tonight we got a fantastic show I'm
having a good time youall having a good
time all right my next guest tonight is
going to be a fantastic treat we going
to hit it off again excuse me are you
fancy Ray yes I am the best looking man
in Comon today fancy Ray you're under
arrest excuse me you're going to have to
go downtown with me you're underr for
some lud and crude behavior I'm going to
have to have you turn around at this
time put your hands up okay sir do you
have any concealed weapons at this time
depends on what you mean okay your right
hand behind your back are you sure right
hand behind your back there you go we're
just going to be downtown what's the
problem and uh luding crude behavior on
your show I heard really have I did
anything rude or crude today you got a
little bit of it y'all got to help me
out
now hand big guy I'm innocent no no no
no no no not this time big guy we're
going to we're going to sit you down
here right here if we can right here
okay and I have to ask you a couple
question questions uh first of all have
you been drinking uh no you haven't been
drinking um how do you planned on uh
driving home today uh it depends on what
you mean by drive though please now I
smell SM alcohol in this
breath okay uh first of all I need to no
no no what you smell is the essence of
R I heard it's your birthday is this
true maybe seeing how it's your birthday
and all I'm going to have to let you go
with this time
woo happy birthday to
you happy
birth Happy
Birthday baby
baby happy birthday to you
[Applause]
oh no not again you get out the car sir
what did I do officer nothing but I'm
going to have to rough you up a little
okay but just a minute just a
minute is there a problem officer well
I've be getting my behind kick this
evening what's so funny no court in
Atlant convict me with
that you get a move on it's time to get
down with it okay
all right please welcome once again from
American Superstar the dance Taylor and
lucenda give a round of applause y'all
oh my my my
my that was an incredibly hot dance
thank you that now you guys Tour all
around the Twin Cities doing this kind
of thing I'm yeah pretty much yeah I've
been in the metrome and places like that
what kind of reaction do people get I
think the cop te is like the most
popular yeah the cop and the nurse
routines oh man most popular we do also
have um Duo routines that we do like
male and female that type of thing go
down to bathing suit like where what I
normally do really you guys incredible
shape it doesn't are you inhibited about
your body at all I think you know most
people anybody is usually yeah right
yeah so how'd you get over the
inhibitation I always I usually worry
about it I mean you know everybody does
so it's it's so well it's just life mhm
you guys are you guys both can I ask how
old you are 23 23 yeah oh you guys so
guys a littleit older in the age there
no you're not like little kittens have
you ever had bad reactions going out
during the strip ofrs yeah really tell
tell us tell us something bad at that um
well I guess I should say like Bachelor
parties is is I would think that would
be very scary all these men sit around
and
go I'd rather have them do that than
just sit there and go has oh believe me
if your bodies anything like this you
wouldn't sit there go or maybe you might
go they sit there they don't say
anything just look at it you're like I'm
like I'm taking my clothes off here you
know applaud something do something here
and you get really nervous and that's
what's hard okay okay so i' rather have
them scream and holler and practicly
attack me then just sit there and yes
all right yeah you guys like stripping
the clubs too have you had some
nightclub work too um I've done a little
bit I danced in California I haven't
danced with this company for a long time
couple months but uh I enjoy it I really
do I I enjoy making people happy that's
my thing is going out there it's a job
and and it's it's it pays good you know
it doesn't pay the best but it pays
really good and it's a one-on-one thing
and you're making someone's birthday
that's special you know that's really
special man you made my birthday didn't
even
he I'll make sure to get you next time
oh man please do please do it's a lot a
lot of fun with you do the American
Superstar is a dance that's great stuff
you guys are wonderful and I tell you
what coming up we going to have a treat
we're going to pick someone out of the
studio audience and we're going to have
naughty nurse Nancy do a nice little
dance for him how's that sound all right
give a round of applause y'all'll right
back information stay tuned and get with
it s
[Applause]
Taylor for shs and vioria they're
jogging in La they're exercising
everything in lots of crazy ways what
take it from the chopper hey the chopper
yeah that's me if you want to have great
Choppers exercise your teeth exercise
those Choppers
really exercise those choppers on some
good gr your
canil bite rightow excise those Cho
on Mano
o I had a great great time I want thank
my fantastic guest I thank David Z and
these wonderful girls from the American
dance and the viewers out more
information where can they look you guys
up and the new 1992 Yellow Pages under
entertainment all right give a round of
applause
y'all superstars of dance I want to
thank my fantastic sponsor I want thank
Insight newspaper find our cablecast
schedule here by J with Styles my hair
do how you like my haird also want to
thank variety Beauty Supply home of
luster silk three locations of to serve
you and taking us home you know I want
to know is anyone out there not feeling
too well yeah
yeah I think I think we got a guy right
here Co come on up here I think we got
nurse Goodbody gonna take care of you
tune in next week and get down with
it good
night oh no
well start out here by taking you y
s you bet
h w I'm feeling better
already well it's okay but we will uh
check your heart right now check all you
want okay let me see this might be just
a little bit cold for you
I found
[Music]
it got faster and faster by the
minute I think I do have something that
just might make you feel a little bit
[Applause]
[Music]
you say I'm feeling ly I feel a Kind of
Blue you say you want to love a bunch
you don't know me get on back get on
back don't worry Jack just get on back
take me by the hand take me by the hand
learn how to rock and roll while you can
get it out yeah yeah get it out oh no
get it out come on get it out it out
yeah yeah come on now
baby get up your feet get