I am the best looking man in County oh I
can look at my mirror if I want to as
gorgeous as I am you know you jealous of
me I'm the fanciest one out there the
prettiest thing I've ever seen oo look
at my hair do baby oh I know it looks
good I'm the prettiest thing out here in
comedy you used to be the best looking
man in comedy stand aside
homeboy no sorry no I am the best
looking man in comedy I am no I'm the
best looking man in comedy I'm the best
looking man in comedy I'm the best poet
in comedy well okay let's hear your poem
let me tell you the story of fancy Ray
the most beautiful man in comedy today
when I was born the moon didn't rise
only the stars came out in L of the
skies and by the time I reached the age
of five my mom i' be the prettiest man
alive I knew I'd be a success and I did
knock on W
I just looked in the mirror oh honey you
look
good my my my my my top that one
emo my name is
emo I like to break open Oreo cookies
and suck out all the
Creo emo you check your mirror and I'm
fancy right and it's time to get down
with it
I said and get down
wi do the
J come on
baby want to watch everybody
work I said come on
baby want us everybody do the
jck I said come on
baby it's been a long long
time
W baby
oh hello this is fancy Ray MCL the best
looking man in County I'm live on
location by the beautiful Mississippi
River why is fancy Ray dressed like this
by the Mississippi tonight well to tell
you the truth I've been very concerned
about the flood victims throughout this
entire nation as we all heard on the
news there's been so many problems with
it and a lot of local stations have
helped out to pitch in to help the flood
victims I heard of one station sending
water down and some milk and even one
station sent down people to help sandbag
to help with the flood victims now I
thought about sandbagging but I I'm not
the kind of person to go do hard labor I
do other things hard anyways what I
decided I would do is come out to the
beautiful Mississippi River and I can't
sandbag what I'm going to do ladies and
gentlemen is teabag for the flood
victims yes I'm taking tea we're going
to squeeze it out right here and I'll be
selling fancy Ray tea you can't believe
it well you're not going to believe this
show we got a great show stay tuned cuz
I'm fancy Ray and baby it's time to get
down with it oh teabagging honey oh shut
up stay tuned
[Music]
I I am Everyday People yeah yeah no I'm
not an everyday person you know better
than that this is fancy Ray M the best
looking man in comedy we are live on
location at Ceda Fest 1993 you and me
and R and woo Kelli we going to have a
fantastic time tonight look at all the
beautiful people out there today see I'm
going to jump over the and see what's
happening down here cuz I'm Everyday
People yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah so don't go nowhere I'm fancy R
tonight baby Everyday People we going to
get down with
it all right this is fancy right live on
location at CEST what's your name kadra
kadra Oho man that's sound like Kalam
Mahari Calabar yeah something sweet that
you eat something sweet that I eat yeah
it's a treat what is that it knocks you
your feet it is oh yeah I would like
that where is that then where is it at
it's right here call mahara you
w you like that one huh I can't believe
he say that to me though no what how
would a gentleman approach you where you
from Somalia Somalia how do they talk in
Somalia just they talk just like you no
I mean if a man was attracted to a
beautiful woman what do he say in
Somalia a beautiful woman yeah what do
he
say that's it yes yes yes we're live on
location here at Ceda Fest you look good
but aren't you a little hot am I a
little hot yeah I am hot yeah and I got
a lot all right I like to be on top put
up the collar man you oh help me out you
put up the collar man my Valley ain't
here right now putot up to collar what's
going on hanging you know I'm everyday
people are you everyday people you bet
all right party up all all right here we
go oh now we got a good cool guy over
here what's going on buddy how you doing
buddy good pretty good what are you
doing out here I don't know you stole
pee Herman's bicycle the best looking
man how you doing over there darling
this the best
looking best looking comedian best
looking person in comedy oh keep talking
what's your name Joan you know me I do I
know you of course you know me hold on
let me put on my sunglasses Veronica
Joanne uhoh I'm in trouble okay my child
appartment payment hasn't been paid this
month yeah you how long has it been sh
your hips huh huh don't you need some
oil on them headphones
come on out here and dance
man this is the drum
circle women's
session any woman that wants to play the
drums please come
up and play the drums the Dr and play
the drums play Dr I got my man here all
right if you ever watch TV you see this
man he's famous more famous than I am
look at I don't know about that I think
I the most handsome guy I
know right pick up his show on
TV this is the women's gr
[Music]
Circle I'll father yellow Bri Road you
know where it Le the fancy R oh fancy me
I'm out here at C Fest I'm directing
traffic hold hold on you got permit to
be out here hi want to go permit looking
for somewhere to sit down you looking
for somewhere to sit down is this your
lady I'm not hitting on permits baby
let's see your permit let's see your
permit are my
permit Victoria just freshly married
yesterday no yes sir congratulations you
really give me a kiss you're freshly
married then give me a kiss nah kiss
nobody oh my my my my my my all right
this is fancy rain what's your name data
data woo and we're going to do some
Celtic Blues right CL we going to do
some Celtic Blues all right you going to
help me
out I got the Celtic Blues
baby Celtic
[Music]
blue I got the seltic blues baby is that
the seltic blues I don't sing I just
play
ah stay tuned oh thank you guys L all
right let me tell you a little story
about a guy named fancy Ray mclone this
guy was some else well you might know
him as some kind of singer dancer comic
some crazy faka thing like that but this
guy pound for pound was the best
middleweight there ever was the
middleweight champ of the world fence
sir mloy I never forget that night in
the
garden he takes on Larry Holmes 1978
March like it was
yesterday the heavyweight champ it's
158b soaking wet he goes in there he's
stick and he's moving he's ahead on
points what does he do he sticks his
chin out round 10 and goes hit me hit me
you big piece and I can't even say
fancy
Ray never got
up they don't what happened poor old
fancy Ray they say he moves but never
like he used
to I know my my my my I remember a
different
time back when he could hit now he's got
to eat soup with a
straw sad story fancy
R sad story
M searching for
adventure here goes fancy R where up
here by the blues clubs look at all
these bikes out here man you know what
I've always had a fantasy of kicking
over a
bicycle you think I'd get my kicked I
don't think so I'm going shove this bike
over can I do it what we gonna do that
let's go talk to a couple people over
here we got a couple of bikers over here
biking triking all right what's
happening well not not much we're just
down here watching uh people and
enjoying the music is that right no what
is this is an old Harley right here is
it old Harley it's old classic I'm a
classic are you but a no one ever roll
me before well last night someone did
we're we're kind of old classics oursel
here you yeah yeah but we what year is
this bik 67 can I sit in the seat you
certainly can let me sit in here okay
woo hop right in in front of you looking
for
adventure I like this man it feels good
oh man built the ride you guys are great
man enjoy you to stay out here well
where are you guys from Minneapolis
Minneapolis yeah where you guys from oh
Minneapolis all right yeah we're just
down here enjoying it all right yeah
Ceda Fest is the best wouldn't you agree
oh yeah do you know slide Stones
everyday people I know I don't know who
I am every day oh you
are thanks a lot you guys all
right you having a good time what's your
name Jackie Jackie and Pearl and pearl
can y'all Shake Your Groove Thing you
know I've been trying to find some to
sing Everyday People you know the song
Everyday People by slide Stone I I am
everyday people that's it that's it
thank y'all so much can y'all shake it
let's dance with me a little bit
here yeah what's going on what's going
on how you doing every buddy fine thanks
you playing some air guitar yeah yeah
let me play some air guitar with you
let's do
[Music]
it all right he's got the light hey hey
my my lighter my lighter you got my
[Music]
lighter oh my God no that's not my
lighter that's not that's my lighter
that's this is the lighter the fancy
lighter oh what is that is that your
stick or you just happen to see me no
shut up wait a minute
now all right come on baby they said
Light My Fire they wasn't playing was it
check this out this is unreal we're live
here at Ceda
Fest come
on
Y come over here this is the
woman's all right yes we're live on
location here at CEST and I ran to a
couple of buddies of mine hey how's it
going Ray I said a couple of buddies
what's your name oh my name is Cory
what's your name Mark I don't care what
you do oh okay what do you do uh I we
don't care we work for the city P
exactly I'm doing my advertising right
now what 7 days a week really got to
promote the show what we doing out here
uh just uh hanging out enjoying we're
just going to go get a bite to eat you
know I've been trying to get someone out
there to sing Everyday people with me
you sing Everyday People do you guys
know the song
No am Everyday People yeah he
got stay tuned all right thank you
guys I am the best I Rise the test I can
do no l all the beautiful people
Everyday People black white Puerto Rican
every just having a good time no one's
freaking I just love the atmosphere The
Joy the beauty the excitement and the
beauty is out here fancy R the chocolate
human Arch look at all the beautiful
beautiful beautiful people my my my my
my my my my my everyday people do you
see the excitement the love the joy the
beauty well I'm the beauty and I'm on
[Music]
duty all right we got a backp player
here
[Music]
does he ever take a
breath all right this is fan with my
buddy Larry hey how how are you doing
how do I look happy Cedar Fest uh great
happy Cedar beautiful beautiful he looks
beautiful really keep talking keep
talking keep talking I'm uh oh I'm
getting uh excited here I'm glad I have
my guitar in front of me watch yourself
now we going to do a little song
together right oh yeah yeah uh Me and
Bobby McGee all right Me and Bobby McGee
every sing along everybody everybody
sing along we all sing along with us Me
and Bobby McGee all right all right here
we go here we go now you ain't never
seen this fancy RAC s of Me and Bobby
McGee ow it's going to be something
busted flat and bat rou Waiting for a
Train I was feeling nearly faded as my
jeans uhhuh oh Bobby thumb the diesel
down just before it rain R Us all the
way into new
on i p my out of my dirty Red
Band s b
s with those wi wiper slapping time and
Bobby clapping hands bnie sing up every
song that
driver oh Freedom just another word for
Nothing Left to Lose and nothing ain't
worth wor nothing but it's free free
free free free and freedom good was easy
Lord when Bobby sang the
blues feeling good was good enough for
me good enough for
me lar thank you no have luck have luck
long uh I'm not that long but I'm
satisfying Larry be cool we'll be right
back m
i' been teabagging on the
Mississippi and I'm singing this old
song yes this is fancy R down by the
Mississippi I'm still teabagging I'm
about halfway filled up here right now
we are teabagging for the flug victims
as you know fancy Ray can't go do the
hard labor so I can't go down and sad
bag but as you can see I'm teabagging
for the flood victims and if you like to
get some fancy R tea give me a call here
at the station 49 92068 and you can get
some fancy R tea I might start up my own
shop fancy race cappuccino tea shop you
can come down we have Mississippi tea
we'd have Ohio River Tea we might even
have some Lake Superior tea you can't
believe it neither can I well let me get
back to tea bag and we'll get back to
the show stay tuned and get down with it
I've been teabagging on the
river all day
long hello my name is Charles fler and
I'm your guest here in the Twin Cities
and guess what I'm happening now it's
the man who can say his name is fancy
Ray the man who makes the night turn to
day the man who can make the dead dogs
play I'm talking about Fancy Fancy Fancy
R the man that makes Little Richard look
like a priest the man that makes yogurt
taste like yeast the man who can take
the moon from the sky and put it into
Hercules and make the monkey cry
F
sailing Takes Me Away we're here by the
Beautiful Lake Calhoun on a beautiful
summer day here in Minneapolis Minnesota
having a good good time we're going to
talk to some people out here and just
kind of hang out and see what's
happening hope you're enjoying the show
a little later on we got emo Phillips
live on stage at the comedy Gallery it's
going to be a fantastic show good to go
and I'm the um so stay tuned we're going
to get down with
it all right this is fancy R here at
Lake Calhoun and we got a special treat
we got the world's youngest fisherman
this guy's been catching Walley
bullheads sunnies and everything how you
doing little
fisherman how you
doing how's the fishing going out here
today I know it's been really really
rough but what you okay now you're such
a expert everyone recognize you
throughout the world as one of the best
what's your
secret I know how it feels to be out
here well tell me when you pulling the
big fish and you're reeling in it's
fighting you how does that feel
all right this is fany live on location
at Lake Calhoun in the beautiful
Minneapolis Minnesota we got people
coming up for you guys going fishing
right now we you what are you fishing
for walleye Walle Walley Lake coun y
right over there I didn't know they
catch Walley in here oh yeah you got
about you got about a 23 25 ft drop
right here uhhuh just set it down there
about 3 ft off the bottom and catch them
you're giving your secrets away right
now well I ain't telling what I'm using
uh oh don't what's your dad using over
here no don't tell them nothing well you
guys have some good luck out there okay
all right and and and you know hold on I
got some socks over here man you might
try one of my socks they've been known
to well you guys ain't fishing for carp
are
you all right we're out here power
walking oh oh now you with the what's he
using what's he using what's the babies
using over there minnows minnows okay WS
too of course worms too of course thanks
a lot there darling all right how you
doing there buddy hey hey all right
that's Dave Moore right there walking
all right have a beer on me
buddy fancy ra Wilding crazy guy stay
tuned we having a good time get down
with
it hi this is emo Phillips and you're
getting down with my favorite homeboy
fancy Ray so don't touch that dial
because I spat on
it you know the problem with this
country is people like you what do you
mean people like you what because I'm
black you some kind of racist bigot or
something no no no you're probably on
welfare no I'm not on welfare I got a
job and I pay my taxes well I pay my
taxes too but I like to take a peak of
your criminal record wait a man you're
going a little getting a little carried
away here I've never committed a crime
I'm just in college trying to get an
education and if that's a criminal
offense then I'm guilty yeah but what
about drugs but you do drugs I may have
experienced with drugs before but have
you
well uh you know yeah yeah are you doing
drugs now no no not now me neither I'm
just trying to prepare myself
economically and mentally for the future
well that's what I'm trying to do and my
kids too well I guess we got something
in common don't we now the point of this
skit is this we all have common ground
look you're white you're
black but neither one of us is as pretty
as you shake hands stay tuned I'm F it's
time to get down
give it up for my man fancy
Ray all right my my my my my my my how
you doing emo I am fancy R M the best
looking man in comedy and it's my
pleasure to be live on stage here at the
comedy Gallery with the Innovative
comedy emo Phillips give him a big round
of applause everybody emo Phillips
my my my my my my this reminds me I
forgot to go to church
today we're not going to say no prayers
emo my pleasure allow me to welcome you
to Minneapolis oh thank you I I love it
here Minneapolis is the best place in
the area you know the whole Twi cities
what a combination you got you got
Minneapolis with this exciting theater
and shopping and dining and and
restaurants and and you and you got St
Paul with its close proximity to
Minneapolis it's wonderful you travel
all over the country tell me something
em have you seen someone out in standup
comedy as pretty as fancy R you mean you
not outside of professional wrestling
I'm but you are a goodlook guy right you
know how to dress we do twe both dress
for the ladies I have my own microphone
yeah
but that's
you thought I was just excited to see
you
didn't this happened more than once I
not with me it hasn't
no you you must be good with the ladies
what's your secret my secret with the
ladies well you know what emo I walk up
to people and I say I'm emo
Phillips it doesn't even work for
me you know what I do right what do you
do with the ladies I used to I I have my
own mic I used to
be I TR to STI that in my
mouth not the
[Laughter]
[Applause]
job
yes I used to be petrified of the ladies
you know not you emo yes
bro and then this woman let me in on a
little secret what was that she said emo
the average woman would be even more
terrified of
you then you are of
her once you have that knowledge in your
you tra you travel all over the country
how do you handle all the throngs of
groupies and women that must surround
you oh boy I get wall toall groupies you
know well they're not all that large
but pretty big you know yeah lot I'm
quite handy with you're quite handy and
you're an innovator in comedy like I
said
1976 you burst on the scene and you had
an original style because stand up
comedy at that time was like Bill Cosby
Mort Saul Lenny Bruce you are total
original yeah was it tough for you it
was very hard for me you know I mean if
you know R if someone would have told me
in 76 that I'd be on TV with you I I
just would have starred at him cuz I was
on medication at that
time but it's a wonderful life isn't it
is a beautiful life boy said if you
could make just one person laugh you
wouldn't have to do this
[Applause]
show but you'd still be a good looking
guide thank you very much thank you very
much you Your Big Break came in the
early ' 80s on the David Letterman show
what was that like well Ray was very
exciting I've been on the Letterman show
six times and they told me I'll be on
again and again whenever those show are
[Music]
repeated unfortunately it's going off
the but I've been in our Sano and all
the other shows who do you like the best
now who's going to win the talk show
Wars you thank you very much yeah do you
all agree with him thank you very
much you're going to win in the same way
that the Cockroaches will eventually
inherit the
world when you're not doing standup
comedy what are some of your interest
and hobbies that you get into emo well I
campaigned very actively against wearing
fur did you know that a single fur coat
takes 14 trees just for the protest
signs no I didn't know that I didn't
know that I didn't know that I didn't
know
that well that's fantastic emo I can't
thank you enough we're live on location
at the comedy gallery on stage Sunday
night give yourselves a big round of
applause for being such a good audience
for us and give my main man emo Phillips
all right thank you my my my my my emo
emo emo
emo
right hi this is Danny Boni you might
remember me from the par family listen
whenever I'm in the Twin Cities I was in
the fancy R and get down with
it all right that's all the teabag for
fancy R today I fill up the jug I'm
going to get me a hug
now I'm looking the camera and I'm a
mug I've had a fantastic show I've hope
you had a good time I would thank my
fantastic sponsors I want to thank
Insight newspaper where you can find my
cable cast schedule hair Vis J May with
Styles this hair I know it looks good
and also straight stuff great stuff
those fancy Ray t-shirts and also my new
sponsor mink magic they got these new
hair product mink magic you can catch
them at all the beauty supply stores
throughout the entire Twin Cities I hope
you had a good night I know I have tea
bagging for the Mississippi River have a
good night big cool ah ooh
oh
[Music]
do