welcome to the first church of beauty
now tell me who has the hottest talk
show in the Twin settings you and if I
was the best looking man in comedy you
are the best I am the best looking man
in comedy you are the best looking man
in comedy tall and fine like a Georgia
Pine so goodl looking at all of be
crime shut up I am the best looking man
in comedy and on the show we have fun in
order to do that you got to party and
all the party you don't go over it well
you don't go under it well you don't go
round it well you don't get up under it
well to have a party you got to do one
thing get up get up get up because it's
time to get
down yes yes yes get
down do the
J come on
baby want to watch everybody
way I said come on
baby want to everybody do the
J I said come on
baby it's been a
bab welcome to get down with it now to
bring up your host the man who travels
the country spreading Beauty all around
fancy Ray
M yes yes yes yes yes yes
hello hello my name is fcy Ray MCL I'm
the best looking man in County woo my my
my my my are you ready to have a good
time yeah all right we got a fantastic
show for you tonight fantastic show you
know I've been reading a lot in the news
lately did you guys see the new Star
Magazine this is
unreal Cosby amazing sex
confessions no I don't know about you
but there's some things I don't want to
know about Bill Cosby here goes with
Bill said article my wife Camille was
kissing my
foot and you put a little jell pudding
on my big
toe I don't know about you but I don't
want to know that about Bill Cosby do
not want to know that about Bill Cosby
also talks about Naro he uses Ste he
been married like 27 years he still uses
condoms it's amazing amazing thing have
you noticed as the sexual diseases get
worse and worse and worse the names get
more pleasant and friendly have you
noticed this I remember years ago
doctors used to get the disease of scary
names like the
clap and syphilis
and
garia but that stuff you got Shadow
ointment or something was gone right
then came the sexual disease that never
goes away well it goes away and it comes
back and goes away and goes back what
they call that one herpes don't say like
it's a testimonial over there herpes
herpes
herpes herpes herpes couldn't that be a
song
like I got
herpes on a cloudy day they're not
visible right now but they'll be back
next May herpes my my my my I am the
best looking man in County are you ready
to have a good time are you ready to
have a good time all right we got a
fantastic show for you tonight oh I got
to answer a question I got a a letter
from a young viewer out there and I want
to read this it really was a beautiful
letter and I want to tell you what she
said she said dear fancy Ray my dad and
I think you're the greatest and she's
got good taste my dad says you remind
him a lot of James Brown did James Brown
ever record a record with the Chipmunks
sincerely Amy what if James Brown
recorded a letter with the Chipmunks
what if James Brown would have recorded
a letter with the
Chipmunks
[Music]
H when you kiss
me and you miss me
you hold
it make everything all right I wake
up in a c
[Music]
s get
it I don't
care I'm about to
F I just
want I love the last
[Music]
I don't
care about
[Music]
your I just
want to satisfy your
[Music]
phone when you kiss
me when you kiss
[Music]
me why you kiss me keep around there
no a
[Music]
what a
baby yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
oh my my my my my what if James Brown
would have recorded with the Chipmunks
my my all right we got a fantastic show
for you tonight my guest tonight include
from Northstar Judo thth degree black
belt Tom Crone yes ah
yes and male exotic dancer
extraordinaire Dallas is here tonight
yes yes yes yes so stay tuned cuz I'm
fancy Ray mclone and it's time
to oh my my my party yes yes
yes surely the birds appreciate all
we've done for
them don't you beautiful cage fresh
water n the birds to bother you none of
that blinding
sunlight oh now why would he do
that
most what don't know
they're coming they're
[Music]
[Applause]
coming all right thank you very much my
first guest started studying Judo in
1961 he's gone on to become a champion a
coach for the Junior Olympics and he
owns one of Minnesota's Premier martial
arts school north star Judo please
welcome Tom Crone give Round of Applause
Tom oh man fantastic how you doing doing
fine how are you all right oh beautiful
can't you tell I know I know I know too
and I just want to make sure that you
know that I know and they know that I
know that you know I knew that you knew
that
fantastic now Judo what's the difference
between karate and Judo well mainly the
biggest difference is that judo's in the
wrestling uh category of of sport okay
uh and karate and Taekwondo uh in the
more in the boxing or the hitting and
kicking the Striking aspect so in Judo
we don't do any hitting or kicking it's
a grappling Sport and it evolved out of
jiujitsu which was a martial art or a
fighting style so it it was originally
designed to be a sport in a form of
physical education okay and jiujitsu is
is the mother and father of and Judo
more or less yes you're right exactly
that's the sort of thing the old Samurai
Warriors the guys with the big swords
and everything used to do uh Jiu-Jitsu
was hand toand combat for them when they
dropped their sword or or whatever
weapon they were using or did close in
fighting and they didn't do a lot of
hitting and kicking back then because
everybody wore armor you know so hurt a
lot to hit them right right what's the
difference between that and say like the
Kung Fu that came out of China well
basically that's it the the Chinese uh
uh boxing styles are things like Kung Fu
and so it's just a different adaptation
it's another striking art from another
national origin okay okay typically now
you have this great school Northstar
Judo what uh who's your typical student
that comes in to study the martial art
we have a wide range uh we have uh kids
we have adults uh men women children uh
there is no typical student we have an
Olympic champion who trains there an 88
Olympic uh competitor from the US we
have Olympic team members we have
national team members and also we have
just ordinary people who want to have a
good time with a with a sport an
individual thing that they can do so we
have just people off the street who say
hey this looks like it might be fun mhm
now like I said it is a sport how how
real is this for like a self-defense
purposes the Judo is it is it an
effective self-defense method it's
excellent for that uh remembering first
of all it comes from Jiu-Jitsu and that
the prime purpose of Jiu-Jitsu was
personal defense in fact it was more
than that it was saving your life
Staying Alive in combat uh it also makes
a lot of sense because of the grappling
aspect most of the confrontations people
get into whether it's on a playground or
recess or whether it's in some other
altercation that could be far more
serious normally really uh aside from
what you see in the movies goes into a
Hands-On grappling Close Quarters sort
of Confrontation and often times ends up
on the ground so the hitting and kicking
that you see in the movies sometimes is
a little bit farther out of field than
the reality of the thing absolutely I
know I was in the I was in looking in
the mirror one day and uh and it was
incredible we started the guy started he
didn't think I looked as good as I think
I looked and I know that I look good and
he kept looking at me all funny and he
started kicking grappling and it wasn't
a real deal people watch those martial
arts movies and think that's real
martial arts but that's not that's
Entertainment That's Entertainment
that's exactly what it is okay in fact
let's take a look at some real Judo we
give us a demonstration you bet be glad
to do that okay let's take a look at it
right now come on join me on the stage
all right give him a round of
applause all right okay come on up
joining us here is Bill bil Bill bil
step on up Bill and Bill you are a
champion too in your own right um I'm
sorry
I compete nationally and I'm I'm on the
US Judo team now Junior Judo team oh
that's fantastic so what you going to
demonstrate for us first well we'll
demonstrate a little bit maybe just real
quickly about what makes Judo work okay
let's take a look let's do yeah let's do
this units a strength thing uh let's
just imagine that Bill's bigger than I
am and hold on wait wait how about how
about how about bigger and better
looking only with your
help and uh so if bill has 10 units of
strength and let's say and I have only
five let's say I'm half as strong so
Bill pushes me and I push him it's sort
of like a semi-trailer in a Volkswagen
right okay so Bill's going to push me
and I'm going to push back but that
won't do me much good right okay so what
I have to do is I have to yield when he
pushes me and I have to use his strength
all 10 units and maybe one of mine to
get him off balance okay now I appla
some of the laws of physics here put a
little leverage down in the corner use
another unit of strength over he goes
and I still got two units left to laugh
at him
wow so this is an effective form of so
use his own strength against them that's
exactly the idea okay give us another
give us another demonstration well just
real quickly uh let's just say even
though we are mostly a sport let's just
make an answer for that self-defense
question okay and suppose that Bill's
going to strike me on top of the head
let's do it this way bill because I
don't want you to H that
table um and what I'm going to do is
Bill got even bigger uh is I'm going to
just deflect that blow and use that
momentum to throw Bill onto the matap
okay
W all right great stuff now what if you
don't know how to fall now he knows how
to fall you know if you threw someone
like that and they didn't know how to
fall that could cause some injury on the
concrete especially
yes learning how to fall is worth the
price of admission to a judo school
because everybody takes a fall sometimes
whether it's off a skateboard or walking
down the street or in the uh on the ice
you know so falling skills are very
important okay let's see him throw you
around a little bit once okay this will
cost you
okay wow that's out of sight all right
give him a round of applause all
right all right coming up next we got a
PSA and then I'm going to get in the
middle of all this and we're going to
get down with it so stay tuned yes yes
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
wow who are the people in your
neighborhood Hey look it's Saddam
Hussein get him Mr
Bunny hi I'm Vice President Dan quail
and I'm here to talk to you about the
United Negro College Fund because
of a mind is a terrible thing to waste
after all
I should
know but I really want to tell you kids
out there that you should stay in school
and work hard because if you stay in
school and work hard and have a rich
father who can buy your way through life
you can reach Great Heights just look at
me hey Dan looks like there going to be
a war in Iraq they're going to
draft War
daddy daddy
it's not any har to call your
baby right yes yes yes so so now you now
what you going to show me now here we
want to show me something all right once
again we're here with Northstar Judo Dam
Crome and Bill bilky so now what you
going to show me okay I'm going to show
you how to take care of yourself if
somebody comes up to you and wants to
choke you okay okay not anybody ever
want to do that oh no oh no okay so
we'll back up here a little bit so I can
take a good fall I'm going to be choking
you here okay now you're not going to be
able to get rid of this really e no wait
a minute so someone choking me I I got I
got this instant reflex goes ah anyway
so yeah that's the one okay okay what
you're going to do is you're going to
take your right hand and push my elbow
up a little bit like this oh like so and
you take your left hand you're going to
pull down on my left elbow like that
when you do that instead adjust a little
bit that's going to turn me off balance
now you're just going to step across
with your right foot and put your left
foot back put your hip across what we
doing the Hokey poke and turn right you
put your left foot back a little more
put your hip across in front of me way
across put it against me now
smile and turn your head and
shoulders all right how about now how
about for let's say let's say for women
um let's say let's say uh you're you're
a woman and a guy comes up behind you
and grabs you what do you do well I
would probably first of all in a real
self defense situation adding more than
just Judo I'd probably slam this into
your knee down your shin into the top of
the
of the foot then I turn over this way
and throw you over my hip okay go ahead
throw me
okay
oh okay that's great okay let me get a
demonstration from you now now you show
me something now basic now I'mma throw a
punch at you not fast and just show me
basically what you do to defend yourself
against a punch back up a little bit
okay oh he's going to kick my butt now
look at back up back up I need some room
for what I'm going to do to you okay so
guy's talking to you and he's he's going
to Sucker Punch you so
who all right that's great that's great
how about how about two men now what if
two men came at you what would you do in
that situation let's try at once both of
us come at you come on me and you me and
you nice thing nice thing with Judo is I
I wouldn't do anything until somebody
grabbed a hold of me okay so let's have
Bill grab me by the wrist I just do a
little Jiu-Jitsu thing here knock him
down we'll take you over this
way knock you back over here and down
here
inde Tom
Crome Tom Crome Bill VY thank you very
much stay tuned we'll be right back my
my my thank you very much yes yes
[Music]
yes hurt injured in an auto
accident
lonely dial 1
900 law date I specialize an auto
accidents personal injury and
more 1900 law
date first I'll take care of your case
then I'll take care of you 1 900 La
[Music]
dat all right thank you very much women
have seductively unveiled themselves for
men in Herms saloons and broos
throughout the centuries in the pop era
the tables have changed and women are
gathering by The Hundreds the thousands
in nightclubs throughout the nation to
see men undressed themselves in a
sensuous manner coming up next we got a
special treat for the ladies one of
Minnesota's hottest male erotic dancers
please welcome from the great state of
Texas welcome Dallas Round of
Applause hello you're the only girl
you're all I think about you're the only
girl for me you're all I think about
you're special I love you I love you
love me and I think that is true but
every night my girlfriend tells me
I now say I but I want you to know you
know I'm not
suck
[Music]
pinio all right baby more
more lies and I try to understand a
little exaggeration and suffering now
say I trust you but I want you to know
you to know sounds like you baby I think
it's time for me to go so now I'm leing
and you know I try to to
[Music]
time all right baby no more
lies you're the only girl for
me I think about the only girl special
[Music]
you're the only girl for
me now I'm leing you know I try you
don't appreciate the time I all right
baby no
[Music]
more now you the to Pro to be you change
but the more you try to change the more
you st the same
I TR you but you should
know you your
[Music]
last
think only girl
[Music]
you you're the only girl
me you you're the only girl
me all right yes yes yes yes my my my
Dallas all right stay tuned we'll be
right back with Dallas yes yes
[Applause]
yes right thank you welcome back thank
you very much join me once again from
body PA peace welcome Dallas once again
round of applause Dallas yes yes yes
that's fantastic that takes a lot of
energy to do all that stuff a lot lot
how long You' been a um stripper
probably about six years six years what
why did you start doing it uh originally
a lot of guys will do it to go to
college get extra money go to college it
pays real well it does yeah huh taking
your clothes off pays really well huh
that's good well yeah respectively when
when uh what how does it feel when you
get up there on stage and you got WI
screaming at you well that happens to me
all the damn time but I mean for you how
does it feel how does it feel I mean you
know it's scary every time is is it is
it yeah were you when you first did were
you uncomfortable taking your clothes
off in front of people very much so and
I still am are you yeah are you mhm what
what do you do to overcome
that uh good question um well for the
most part just visualize um being on a
beach it's no more than what you wear on
a beach right so I just feel
uncomfortable dancing in my underwear
huh huh that's cool when when uh what's
the strangest reaction you've ever got
as a stripper
you um I had one lady get up and and run
out of the building out that way she
left yes oh Lord running dead run is
that right just hold oh
no yep is that right so what did that do
for youo not a whole
lot L how about how about is anyone ever
attacked you or grabbed you or bit you
or anything like that uh it's about
every show
really yeah they get pretty crazy yeah H
what kind of money do you make doing it
um geez you can make anywhere close to
$500 a week a week a week I'm taking
something off right now then that's okay
taking something off that's great the uh
what what what do you need to be a
stripper what do you need what's the
attributes that you need well I didn't
use to be but these days uh the guys
really have to be able to dance they
have to have uh a little more than uh a
normal physique um muscular some somewh
and good looks MH um they really have to
have all three these days okay and
you're working with body Paws now here
in the Twin Cities originally from Texas
yeah how you like the Twin Cities great
fantastic where can people come see you
perform here locally uh they can see me
at uh bugs okay uh which is in uh South
St Paul okay um they can see me at Mt
Pockets which is in uh Little Canada
uhhuh and uh there's a few other shows
around town fantastic man good luck to
you thanks for coming on thank you
Dallas give a round of applause Dallas
yes yes yesman J I'll be doing the
English translation for Mr
Brown this hi this is the Godfather of
Soul James
Brown I'm here tonight to speak about
absentee
fathers there's a lot of single mothers
out there catching hell cuz pop ran off
you you
do I'm sorry I have no idea what Mr
Brown is saying there make
it doesn't take much to make a kid but
it takes a man to be a
father single moms are writing me from
all over the
country please saying Mr Brown please
tell my husband please please tell my
boyfriend please please please please
please suppe please please child supp
[Music]
pleasee
support yes yes yes yes did you have a
good
time all right my my my I want to take
this opportunity to thank my very
special guest tonight from Midwest Judo
Tom Crome yes my my my my my my Lord Mel
exotic D Dallas give him a round of
[Applause]
applause I want to thank my crew of my
studio audience give yourselves a round
of applause yes yes yes yes thank you
all thank you very much and I want to
thank a couple of very special people I
want thank Ed halls I thank my mom for
providing security Judy mlar from Dallas
oh Houston Texas thank you everybody my
my my my name is fancy Ray have a good
night thank you
[Applause]
oh