[Music]
mirror mirror in my hand now tell me now
who is the prettiest in all the land why
you are Lord FY that's just what I
thought now that's why I'm so pissed off
tonight yes I said pissed I know don't
talk that way on my program but I'm a
little upset today the Minneapolis St
Paul magazine came out the sexist twin
cians and I'm not in here I can't
believe it either that's like doing a
show about big butts and Kirby Pucket
not making it that's like doing a show
about big miles and barber Carlson not
being in there I'm the sexiest man in
all the Twin Cities and they should know
it this is a bad mistake you know who's
in here irn Jacobs Prince his name ain't
Prince no more it's something like this
now I'm tell I'm very very upset and I'm
officially announcing my lawsuit against
the Minneapolis St Paul newspaper don't
go no way we going to talk some more
about the lawsuit I'm doing something
about this also on tonight's program we
got a fantastic guest we got star of his
own show on CBS This far called tall
hopes we got comedian George Wallace so
don't go nowhere I'm fancy Ray do I look
good M well yes you do like tell them
the truth baby stay tuned I'm fancy R
it's time to get down with
it I said and get down and win
do the
J come on
baby want to watch everybody
way I said come on
baby want to everybody do
ja I said come on
baby it's been a long long
time hello Minneapolis St Paul welcome
to get down with it the twin City's
hottest entertainment talk show now I
got to warn you now watching tonight's
program you may find yourself h a little
arous we've got a great show we've got
comedian George Wallace on tonight's
program and also we're talking about my
lawsuit against the Minneapolis St Paul
magazine and we're going to ask you
viewers to do me a favor and yourselves
a favor and give them a call we're going
to put put the telephone number up it's
339-7579 they didn't put me in the dog
on magazine as a sexiest twin cians and
I can't believe it now Asha Blake made
the list Christian lner no wait wait is
Asha Blake out there watching right now
good we going to talk about
it now Asha Blake let's take a look at a
few of these people in here Asha Blake
was born in Guana and then she moved up
to Canada and now she lives in the
warehouse District because quote she
wants to be near the grit well baby if
you want to be near the grit I say you
should move to some place like 15th and
park next we got John Omen he's a hair
stylist John to me looks like Jeff gold
Blum know the fly that's a ugly sucker
woooo next we got Christian lner now
listen to what they say about Christian
I couldn't believe this listen to this
he Sports gentle eyes light hair porel
and smooth skin that's almost too pure
too pretty hell they sound like they
talking about
me my picture should be on there my
picture should be in this damn magazine
next we got Angela Roma she says she has
attitude plus sultry great look gorgeous
dark eyes pencil brows pouty lips legs I
won't quit you want to see some legs
that won't quit show now well I told you
going to get a little RS tonight now
baby I said you going to get a little RS
I wasn't lying and we got some other
people in here and I don't understand
how fancy R now look at this next guy
here Richard
dco look at now look hold on put put
this man on there that looks like Louis
from
Taxi I'm the sexiest one in the Twin SE
and my lawsuit now put the telephone
number up I want you to call these
people 339 7571 and tell them how pissed
you are that fancy is not on this I'mma
put up my demands for being the sexiest
man in the Twin C I'm the most gorgeous
thing out here baby they all know it you
know it so call the Minneapolis St Paul
magazine let them know I was at runions
the other day and here goes what they
had to say about the magazine let's roll
the runions right
now all right here's fancy ra location
at rion's nightclub we got Bill Rion
from R Steve Peterson and you just asked
me a question what was the question you
just asked me I said how come fancy Rays
not in the sexiest Minnesota of
Minneapolis St Paul man I was Wonder now
look who's in here Jacobs no no no no
that's what I said now this guy is a
multi-millionaire irn Jacobs he has a
yacht he has a rollsroyce a house on
Lake minaka anybody that rich would be
very sexy don't you think no no no not
him Paul Douglas would be sexy if he had
that kind of money yes yes yes if Sharie
Willis had that kind of money he would
be on everybody's most wanted list yes
yes yes and they got this guy Prince
that's not even a guy's name his name
now is something like
this what's his what's he doing in here
what does it say about Prince now what
does it say you read this to me it says
he's been out with Hollywood stars like
Kim Bassinger vanity appollonia I've
been out with them too why you think he
breaks up with them women cuz of me now
I'm not going to talk about who I've
been to bed with I ain't going to say
nothing like din Ross CJ I ain't G to
say nothing about that man Madonna now
wait a minute now I'm the sexist one in
Minnesota y'all agree I agree yes yes
yes will yall do me a favor now we need
you to call up the Minneapolis St Paul
magazine let them know they made a big
mistake but not including fancy Ray
we'll do it right now all right what's
the number
331 so I forgot the number we going to
put it it's on the screen though give
him a call okay yes yes yes now go my my
my I look good you look good oh they
telling the truth I will be right
back mm yes they were ticked off at
runions first AV new Glam slam the
Caboose everywhere I go they say fancy R
what's going on with you in the
Minneapolis St Paul magazine well my
lawsuit baby and you can voice your
opinion call 33975 71 call them put the
number down call them tomorrow call them
more than once just call and let them
know why was the fancy R on the list why
why I'm the best looking thing out here
baby but enough about that honey I'm
going to get upset we going to talk
about our featured interview he is a man
that's an extraordinary comedian we're
talking about George Wallace we're going
to show a little clip of him on the
tonight's show and then the interview
with George Wallace and fancy Ray the
sexiest man in comedy oh stay tuned and
get down with
it this is fancy Ray ml the best looking
man in comedy I'm live on location at
the comedy Gallery G tier Plaza and
tonight we got a special treat my
featured interview tonight has been
featured on renal Hall Show The Tonight
Show his own HBO special and in fact
this fall he'll be featured on CBS in a
new show called tall hopes ladies and
gentlemen I'm talking about the one the
only legendary George Wallace he I don't
know about that legendary stuff but I'm
happy to be here fany Ray the best
looking man in Show Business oh now you
didn't seen a lot of people in Show
Business have you seen someone out there
pretty as I
am hi
hi don't do that don't leave me hanging
like that George don't leave me hanging
like that man the best looking man is
show business that's what he said that's
what he said hey and let me sing a song
to you right now oh please sing a song
to me you are so
beautiful to me yeah now you know I tag
that with to me yeah and don't go
embarrass yourself asking other people
cuz I said to me ugly people think
you're ugly as hell but to
me yo I thought you was an honest man
George now you I'm telling the truth Ray
I'm telling you how it is you are the
best looking man in Minnesota to you to
me George you've had so much success as
a comedian a lot of people don't know
that you started your career as
advertising executive yes sir I started
that back about 14 years ago as vice
president of the world's largest outdoor
advertising agency all the buses in New
York City the 5,000 buses all the
spectacular at Time Square all the buses
in the top 10 Market in the country
Chicago Boston Cleveland Detroit Los
Angeles San Francisco
and Philadelphia and I think that's 10
if it's not throw Cleveland in there so
I'm assuming at the time you were making
some big bank then well I was 24 years
old and uh I don't know $50,000 a year
on my way to make a lot is that a lot of
money I don't know but it was good I
know it was good why did you decide to
pursue a career in standup comedy oh I
wanted to be a comedian since I was 6
years old I'm in the business because of
Red Skelton okay Milton Barrow uh and
also uh some other names too some Comics
don't know moms mayy oh yes judge P me
Richard PR you know I know they all know
Richard PR but that's why I'm in the
business yes Danny K even was funny to
me when I was a kid yeah so uh that's
why I'm in the business so even when
you're doing other stuff your goal was
always to be a stand up comedian always
since I was 6 years old I wanted to get
a financial cion because I heard these
other older comedians saying that how
tough it was and I think it was tough in
their day and now it's gotten tough
again right now for some young Comics
starting but I wanted to get a few
degrees I got three degrees and I wanted
to make a lot of money get myself a
financial cushion and I saved up what
$300 or $400 I said that's
enough then I moved to Los Angeles and
immediately I started uh when I quit
advertising I wrote the red fox show for
a year and then I started doing my own
standup and I've been working since day
one wow I mean just consistently working
I'm the most blessed person in America I
love what I do I enjoy my life and I
will tell everybody out there that's are
watching fancy Ray and George Wallace
make sure you enjoy your life you got to
enjoy your life just because you have a
degree in marketing doesn't mean you got
to do statistical analysis the rest of
your life you might enjoy arranging
flowers painting cars are fixing
refrigerators you gotta enjoy your life
and Live Your Dream as my good friend
Les Brown would say Live Your Dreams
there's no reason for you not to be
happy if there's anything you enjoy
doing you should be doing it for work
and they should pay you for it so if you
have a job you don't like quit your job
tomorrow stand up right now and walk out
on that job really I'm going to get a
lot of people in
trouble and come work for George
Wallace you are
so I tell you what let's take a quick
PSA we'll come right back with the man
himself George Wallace okay and fancy R
tell him to be cool be cool y'all then
go I we'll be right back I'm my my my my
my all right your PSA tonight is me the
sexiest man in the Twin C fancy R the
Minneapolis St Paul magazine that name
me the sexiest person and we want you to
call 339-7579 call him again and again
and again say why wasn't fany on the
list because I'm known throughout the
entire world as the sexiest man and in
fact we had a guy from Japan who saw me
he said fancy Ray you're the sexiest man
in all the land we're going to show you
a clip of that we're going to come back
with George Wallace stay tuned and get
down with it now call him up 339
7571 hello this is fancy R M the best Tu
man in County what's your name Buddy my
name is T from Japan T from Japan
yesima yeah yeah haima yes oh man that's
cool you know what I'm the sexiest man
in the Twin Seas did you know that
yes I know I'm the sexiest man fancy R I
don't know no no you do know yeah no I
don't know no you do know oh I know I
know I know fancy R now who's the
sexiest man in Twin
Cities who's the sexiest man in Twin
Cities I'm going help you fancy who's
the sexist man in Twin
Cities on that's Japanese for yeah he's
the sexist man in Twin Cities stay tuned
tell to get down with it hey get down
with it yeah we'll be right back oh
thanks a lot
okay all right here we are back on
location with the man that Scots news
show coming up on CBS called tall hopes
I'm talking about the legendary George
Wallace Ray once again we having a good
time in the city the twin CI St Paul
Minneapolis Minnesota it's so nice to be
here with all these crazy people here
yeah you got crazy people in Minneapolis
here in Minneapolis yeah I went to a
church last time I was here uh uh church
had six Commandments and four do the
best you can it was crazy right and you
know I'm kind of sick too they pass pass
out the wine I pass out the
cheese we had a good time it's always a
pleasure coming to this city you notice
I have my Atlanta Braves jacket on I was
here when we we lost the World Series
here you know but we had a good time
doing it and I hope Minnesota comes back
and bounce back I hope Atlanta makes it
this year maybe we can do it again and
pay y'all
back right now I know you people saying
we hope we get there too whe so you can
pay us back right that's true that's
true man you were talking there for a
second you sound like a motivational
speaker have you ever thought about
doing that line of work too listen to me
I really do think I'm going to move into
this a little bit because I really do
enjoy that uh my good friend Les Brown
has the book live your dreams and uh uh
he's a good friend of mine I like what
he does and I do enjoy um saying good
things to good people because I think I
owe this back to the people of the world
because I've been blessed to do what I
want to do and enjoy living I think I
should be able to tell other people how
and not how but it can be done for you
to enjoy your life it's it's as easy to
enjoy your life as to be living and
traveling on this road it's no it's like
a journey right and you should have a
goal you set a goal what is more
important than the goal is the journey
you got to make sure you enjoying this
journey as you drive it's kind of like
when you're on the freeway sometime you
can just drive and do 70 80 M hour every
now and then there a traffic jam you
don't know why but it slows you down so
maybe you got to turn off make a det2 or
what but you're still on the road you
get back up on the road and you keep
trying so you got to enjoy that Journey
also okay well Reverend George let me
ask you this uh what if someone's going
through hardship out there and and life
is tough and and the girlfriend's left
them they can't pay the rent how did
they keep going through the traffic what
do you what inspiration could you offer
them well I'm saying all of those are
roadblocks and uh and and life nobody
told you life was going to be easy and
and these things are part of life you
know but death in the family uh loved
ones are lost divorces sicknesses
illnesses you know I have roadblocks and
I and you just got to say hey this is
part of life but there's no reason for
me not to uh continue living you know
like both my parents are decease and
they were the greatest people in the
world it hurt but they had already
taught me that I got to continue living
and I know that someday that I got to
leave this place too and you do too but
I'm while I'm here I'm only going to
Live Twice really yeah I'm going to live
here and I'm going to live in heaven and
I don't know what kind of job I'm going
to have in heaven I might be a janitor
up there a street sweeper but fancy Ray
if I get to heaven I don't mind sweeping
the streets up there you know what I
mean I don't mind cleaning for the man
because he's been so good to me you know
and if he if he does another thing never
does another thing for me the blessings
I've already had uh good enough for me
to get through life I'm a happy person
and I'm just I'm really blessed I go out
and I work for thousands of people every
night they don't know me I don't know
them and and we have a good time can you
believe that I I I see that I do believe
it you work with me actually so you know
what I'm talking about we work the same
show right and you get the same thrill
when you get out there and those people
don't know you how many people they
don't even know you and they come up
where they know you but they don't know
you you know and uh and they're happen
and having fun so that's what I say and
that's why I invite the sick and and and
people getting divorces and and you need
healings and things like that come out
to my show because you get to laugh and
laughter is the greatest medicine in the
world something I have to say is I've
been going out the street and talking to
people and people are so excited about
George Wallace man there's like a buzz
in the city that you come I mean you
every time you go to you must experience
that how does that feel well that's what
I enjoy also that's why I wake up to
come to work I wake up to come to
Minneapolis Minnesota St Paul Minnesota
because the people are nice I wake up to
go to Chicago tomorrow I wake up to go
everywhere because I'm meeting people
I'm enjoying what I'm doing and I love
traveling on this road gets a little
bumpy sometimes but you know you got to
you know you got good shock I got got
good shock absorbers in my body and uh
and I just keep driving sometimes I got
to drive off the road get a little
hungry sometime pull over you know have
something to eat you know sometime you
got to push the plate aside get back up
on the road keep driving and I I have a
goal to be a good person and enjoy life
and to uh be a great Entertainer which I
I am enjoying and um that I just enjoy
it man that's fabulous well let's take
another commercial and well it's not a
commercial it's a an announcement and I
was want can I get you to preach with me
a little bit whatever you want to do we
can do it with you while we're going out
here now can I get a witness come on
somebody and say amen amen um me and
fancy Ray right here in St Paul
Minneapolis Minnesota and we're starting
to have a real good time yes sir now I'm
not a real good preacher you got me
acting like a
fool we'll be right
back all right hello this is fancy Ray
MCL live on location at the chef's Cafe
with my main man Timothy D Cur Timmy I'm
I'm telling you I'm a little upset today
you are because your name is not in
Minneapolis St Paul can you believe that
I know it's unbelievable and the people
that they pick to be sexy it sounds like
it's their friends and the friends that
they'd like to have I know that's right
and I think everyone out there want to
be my friend yeah Brit here is a staff
writer and uh Claude is a managing
editor and it looks like it's just their
list because it says our first ever
selection so it doesn't really mean that
it's a true representative it's just
these two people that don't know anybody
that's my first demand I want an apology
for both these writers the editor and
the publisher of the magazine I think
you're right I think you're Absolut in
fact you know else I think I deserve Tim
my second demand is I want to be on the
cover of the St Minneapolis St Paul
magazine within the next 3 months with
in a in a full length article about me I
think you should do a writing campaign I
think you should call these people late
at night we should in fact we're going
to have the viewers do that put the
number up right now and the number is up
on the screen right now call up the
Minneapolis St Paul magazine now you may
notes here about who's in here sure
here's Asha Blake who is um living with
an ex- viiking and here's this John who
cuts hair looks like he look like the
fly yeah and he has a serious
relationship with a girl who he's been
living with for 4 years that's living in
sin I know and here's Lois who's uh been
married to her second husband for quite
some time here's uh Leslie she's single
that looks interesting here's Christian
ller he's single and then here's uh
Angela now she doesn't live here most of
the time she lives in Miami during the
winter so I don't know if i' consider
her a Minnesotan at all here's uh Irwin
who's been married for 30 years to his
wife Alexandra and then we have the he
she I don't know which
category guy yeah that well we don't
know yeah okay then we have Richard here
who lives with his wife
bunny then we have um Lori Peterson now
she's the sexual harassment attorney so
I'm sure that she's going to bring a
loss suit against Minneapolis St Paul
for using the word sex and joining it
with her name and then they said uh in
the beginning here I noticed that they
said that uh if you have any complaints
with this list that uh you should
contact them that people that they've
stupidly failed to recognize or
foolishly um included well I think
they've uh stupidly failed to recognize
you as the prettiest man in comedy and
also probably one of the sexiest twin
cians am sexy way they also miss the
chef Cafe on chicken wings every year
too and we do know that they have the
best chicken wings they in fact let's
show how sexy I want to show them how
sexy I can be eating a chicken wing now
you know you got to be sexy eating
chicken wing check this out watch this
watch this watch this
here you may not go back to your show
later aren't they
delicious sexy baby and you can call and
have him delivered too he's doing it ad
I tell you what we're going to get back
to George Wallace okay all right good
Timothy D Curry the chef's
Cafe all right here we go once again I'm
hanging out here with the legendary
George Wallace now you don't like the
word legendary but I got to apply it you
know me don't you I'm getting ready to
tell you don't use legendary I'm just an
ordinary everyday guy just like walking
in the streets every day like everybody
else out at that Mall of America here
you know I went out there and uh woo I
had to buy a new pair of shoes just
walking around that mall that's no lie
but it's a great mall and I I I just I
loved it I went to a store that called
Everything a dollar M I went in there I
got my basket loaded up went up to the
registry gave the lady a dollar I said
no that's that's everything I want you
know so I had a lot of fun out there
that's really great tell us about the
new show coming up on CBS tall hopes the
new show on CBS coming out in August
starring George Wallace and my wife will
be anamarie horseford she her name was
Thelma she played the character Thelma
on Amen with Sherman himley sometimes
back we have three kids a 17-year old
kid who's the number one basketball star
in America and I think this guy is going
to make my family A Millionaire that's
where the hopes are in this tall kid and
I think that he's going to be all lie a
little cheat a little to make sure this
kid play basketball uh because he's
going to be the millionaire of the
family whereas I have a 15-year-old kid
all I Spike Lee and the whole show is
seen through his video camera he think
he's going to be the millionaire of the
family and I never paying attention to
this because I'm only looking at Junior
the guy that's going to really bring in
the Bucks the wife Anna Marie Horford
she is a court stenographer courtroom
stenographer so she's pretty keen on you
get your grades you go to school or you
don't play basketball M and uh we have
our little fights we're considered
pretty much like The Honeymooners the
two of us so we go back and forth a lot
we have a six-year-old daughter just as
cute as she can be and uh her name is DD
and uh it's going to be a great show and
there's a great message in the show and
it's not a black show it's not a white
show it's just a show where we're having
fun and people can enjoy laughing man
I'm look you got me looking really
forward to seeing this man this sounds
fantastic tall hopes you should had a
pretty kid in the dog on show you know
and you could had your hopes based upon
me winning Mr America I should have a
pretty kid in the show don't you think
so yeah do you know
one you that made me knock off my head
George man you've done so many
incredible things what sticks out in
your mine as a highlight of your career
are
o oh um man you just hit me real good do
you ah that's what I'm trying to do
because I enjoy so many things that I do
each and every day I really don't know
what has been a highlight I I think
every day I get a chance to go on stage
somewhere uh to people I don't know that
is I enjoy the moment I enjoy the moment
because soon they will be over so I'm
enjoying every moment as it come as it
goes so at this moment right now I'm
enjoying this well fantastic something I
want to talk about really quickly is
that you know what the HBO's got this
new show the death Comedy Jam what's
your opinion of that kind of Comedy
that's coming out that's very popular in
the community now my opinion on De
Comedy Jam is that there's a market for
everything I'm out of the marketing
school I have a marketing degree and
there's a market for everything there
are people that enjoy this show I enjoy
it now I don't do that type humor I
don't I I just don't and I think funny
is funny if you just got to whatever you
enjoy that you know if you like it you
like it I I'll watch it but I can't do
it cuz I got everybody in my show I'm
from the south and my mama probably will
kill me in my ant they caught me cursing
and things like that you know I get away
with a few words to be honest you know I
go to the line but I can't do the FW and
the MF and all that I don't like it and
I don't do it but other people if you
like it you know it's whatever flips
your switch you know there you go man
you flip I switch George I tell you can
we do another couple of minutes we'll be
right back whatever you say then tell
them to stay tuned and get down with it
stay tuned and watch me pick up my money
in a few
minutes George Wallace will'll be right
back oh all right here we go fancy R M
the best look Comm man account with
George Wallace yes he will be seen on
CBS new show called tall hopes with the
tall kid short kid he needs a pretty kid
we're trying to help him find one if you
look very hard do you have glasses you
wear glasses I do have glasses
apparently I need to put them on from
what you keep
saying there's no doubt about that man
you know something that you're really
famous for is these mama jokes man I
don't even want to get into I see you
trying to talk about my mom on the SL
that's what you trying to do fan I say
nothing about your mom you are trying to
say something say about you stop I heard
about your mom you hear I heard that
your mom was so fat they told her H ass
she had to take two
trips I know you ain't talking about my
mama yeah I saw you not as ugly as your
mama is your Mama went to a hunted house
she came out they gave her an
application your mama so fat she used to
even as a kid she was so fat she used to
get off the Miro rounds and the the
horses would walk
limp Your mama's so fat when she walk
her booty
clap you got the ugliest mama in town
your mama so ugly she go in the woods
the trees pee on her you got one ugly
mama wait a minute wait a minute your
mama so ugly she go outside three people
go blind on purpose your mama teeth are
so yellow when cars go by your house
they slow down talking about ugly now
wait a minute I heard your mama was so
ugly the most romantic thing she ever
heard was turn over and face the wall
and don't say nothing I know you didn't
say that about my mama your mama's so
ugly she went to an ugly contest she she
won Face Down The Man said I'm sorry we
don't take
professionals okay you in you in heing
got a mama jokes bring them on cuz you
know I know your ugly mama your mama so
poor I saw the other day at White Castle
putting a milkshake on lway your mama so
crosy she walked out of the door walked
outside of the door turn around walk
right back in cuz she
cross I'm through now you want to hear
some more mama jokes y'all got to pay to
hear you got to pay to P those jokes man
there's no doubt George man I cannot
thank you enough for your time here I
can say that and and wholeheartedly that
George Wallace comes back to town check
him out it's a fabulous show to make you
feel good to make you laugh you'll think
it's a little bit of everything and
you're just fabulous man I really
appreciate your time thank you so much
thank you for having me and inviting me
to the show and thank you Twin Cities St
Paul Minneapolis Minnesota and all you
country people over in Wisconsin
too yeah I said it yeah I said it I'm
bad I'm bad to the bone yeah and I'm
good looking to the
skin well stay tuned
and tune in and get down with the George
Wallace ladies and gentlemen George
Wallace my B thank you so much once
again my my my
my hey hey hey what's up I'm Abdul Salam
El razak and when I'm in the Twin Cities
I watch Francy Ray the prettiest man in
show bus you know what I mean I mean
like you got to watch get down with it
all right
bye oh hello this is fancy Ray MCL the
best looking man in comedy I'm by the
sprinkle twinkle
twinkle I want to take this opportunity
to thank my fantastic sponsors I want to
thank Insight newspaper you can find my
cablecast schedule hair by J with Styles
my hairdo located on West Broadway in
North Minneapolis and straight stuff
great stuff for those fancy Ray t-shirts
they're located out Robinsdale and also
minks magic home of this new fantastic
hair products mink magic located at all
the beauty supply stores in the Twin
Cities do me a favor and support my
sponsors and when you stop by say fancy
Ray sent you my name is fancy Ray and I
am the best looking man in comedy
oo I am so beautiful to me to
me I hope you had a good night
be my little sprinkle Twinkle Twinkle
Little Star you know where I are shut up
have a good
night hello this is fancy Ray MCL the
best looking man in comedy I'm also the
sexiest man in the Twin Cities did you
know that oh sure you did how can you
contain yourself
my my my but you know something there's
a travesty that's taking place is that I
fancy R the sexiest man in the Twin
Cities wasn't included and the sexiest
person the Twin Cities a no way that's
what I thought too that's I said no way
and I've got a list of three demands for
the Minneapolis St Paul
magazine my first demand is I want an
apology from the two writers the editor
and the publisher of the magazine yeah
yes my second demand is that I want my
picture under the cover within the next
3 months in a full article yes yes yes
my third demand now I'm not doing this
for the money now I'm not doing this for
the money now I don't want the people
out there to think I'm doing this for
the money now but my third demands I
want $10,000 presented to me for all the
shame and embarrassment that I've
suffered because I've not been included
in this article is that enough yeah cash
money is that enough all right we making
$20,000 yeah
$20,000 now tell you tell 30,000 30 okay
now tell you sure I'm not doing this for
the money I'm going donate $100 of that
to any charity they want to give it to
all right yeah all right woo fancy ra
the sexiest man in County today