well what the heck's going on here
welcome to the Minneapolis television
network we're here live at the
pre-taping of get down with it and and
it's a great show we got Larry's abisco
the heavyweight champion of the world on
the show tonight and and and soul singer
Billy Clark and and some surprises in
fact we got three contestants here one
of these three contestants is going to
be on the show contestant number one
what's your name and what do you do well
I'll tell you mister my name is Aon
McShan I'm a standup comic and some of
my friends call me the dink I mean the
Duke well thank you very much contestant
number one contestant number two what's
your name and what what do you do my
name's Chris Patrick I'm a local standup
comic and I'm known as The Duke
John Wayne lot of people don't know this
but I'm known as so brother number one I
feel good
H well thank you very much contestant
number three what's your name and what
do you do well I'm Jerry Thomas from
Egan Minnesota I'm a Rancher I am the
Duke stay tuned Pilgrim get down with it
I said get
[Music]
down do the J
come on
baby want to watch
[Music]
everybody it's time to get down with it
and to bring up your host a man that
needs no introduction but I'm going give
you one anyways the best looking man in
comedy fancy Ray
mcloney
y
hello hello are you ready to have a good
time I said are you ready to have a good
time they saying we're going to have a
funky good time sing it come on let's go
we're going to have a funk good time
everybody wait a minute wait a minute
now wait a minute there are a lot of
white people here tonight for all the
white people how about we're going to
have our swell time our swell time boy
it's a great great world we live in in
fact I want to tell you our Q card man
Terry Thomas was recently featured in
the USA Today newsp paper he was
featured right there goes Terry Thomas
our Q card man they couldn't find the
beauty so they got him and you know they
got that billboard right there next to
him you know that was a big controversy
Mel GBF come to Minneapolis the
billboard should either leave it up or
take it down leave it up take it down
well I came up with a compromise leave
the billboard up but take that damn
birth mark off his
forehead now you guys look at me like
I'm pretty I'm pretty bold to say stuff
like that but you know I do have my
fears I have fears I my fears are like
penis siiz complex
it's a fear of mine I really it's a fear
you know it's it's like am I endowed
enough that fear comes from because I'm
the youngest of four boys I got three
older brothers and they used to trip me
out when I was a kid because what the
big fear they had when they were kids
was to get drowned by a chick wasn't
nothing worse in the world to get
drowned and what drowning meant for
those of y'all that don't understand
like I didn't drowning simply meant that
you didn't have enough meat on your Pole
to satisfy her thus she would drowned
you but me being so young I took it
literally I kept thinking I was going to
get together with my girlfriend dip into
her dip into her and they get sucked
into a sexual whirl
pool never to be seen again they call my
mom on the phone hello Miss mclone do
you know Patty Mullen well about 3:30
today she drowned your
son my friends be at school what happen
to rain man he drowned he drowned so the
first time I made love I was ready sure
was I tied a board to the back of my
butt I made her hold my hand she said
what you doing this for I said baby if
this board breaks I'm pulling you in
with
me all right yes indeed my name is fancy
Ray MCL I am the best looking man in
comedy you can travel the land you can
travel the sea but you never find a
comedian as pretty as me with the wisdom
of Einstein the Finesse the clay get
ready to party with fancy
Ray oh yes yes yes yes yes
W what a swinger what a biger with a
Humdinger shut up I am the best looking
man in comy tonight's program we got a
great show we have the wrestling world
champion here Larry
Zisco
yes John Wayne lookalike Jerry Thomas is
here tonight
yes all right so vocalist Billy Clark is
yes and a music video featuring the
Jamaica boy you guys want to shake it up
yeah you want Shake It Up well get up
off your feet let's get up off your feet
everybody get up off your feet grandma
get Grandma off the wheelchair cuz it's
time to shake it up let's shake and R
and roll let's do it all you guys ready
to shake yeah are you ready to shake
let's shake it all up shake it all up I
want to shake bacon break I can't help
it cuz I can't make it I need some music
so I can shake it so don't let me fake
it come on let me shake it give me the
music I don't want to fake
it so stay tuned cuz I'm fancy R MC Clon
and it's time to get down with
[Music]
it fragrances by Shulton the essence of
precious scents caught at that precise
moment of fulfillment distilled with
exquisite artistry for your every mood
in four fragrances here is the newest
Adventure in fragrance Escapade a
blending of subtle French genius with a
bow vivacious American touch to be
lovely is to feel lovely when your
fragrance expresses your gayest self so
choose a gay Adventure choose Escapade
toilet water immediately you feel
lovely while you are lovely in that
light and gay Escapade mood and remember
your Escapade stick cologne to renew
Adventure wherever you are enjoy all
these Shen fragrances Escapade
friendship's Garden early American Old
Spice desert flower at leading cosmetic
counters everywhere toilet Waters a125
and $150 stick colog
[Applause]
$1 all right welcome back my first guest
is the AWA heavyweight champion of the
world the living legend please welcome
Larry
Zisco yes Larry I can't believe we got
Spud heads with class
welcome to the show thank you uh Ray oh
just call me gorgeous
gorgeous go ahead now now let me ask you
something now I watch the AWA what is
larryland oh larryland larryland now is
this a place you can go is it is it like
Disneyland well see some people try to
get there what Larry land is is I guess
the heavyweight championship of the
world and all that goes with it you know
I mean I've been in this business on 15
glorious years I've retired men in front
of soldout Shay stadium in 1980 my man
named Sam Martino I retired Nick Bach
Winkle out in San Francisco you retired
him I retired him I beat him senseless
he retired he caused you know he accused
me of slipping someone something and all
this and that does he get like Social
Security Now with you or something I I
he just lims around but uh uh I just
recently got back February 10th from
Tokyo Japan Russell Sao in front of over
69,000 people $4 million our house the
largest house and gate in the history of
professional wrestling wow so I am I am
hot stuff and Larry land Larry land is
is all of that you know it's it's a
feeling of Beyond happiness it's Joy
it's like uh how can I explain it like
uh your ex-wife and a boyfriend getting
a car wreck and die I'm talking I'm
talking I'm talking
Joy kind of like I feel beautiful sort
of like high school with money
oh so that's lar that's larryland it's
everything I've worked for you know it's
why uh you know instead of taking
steroids and being a clown like Hulk
Hogan I've got cauliflower ears and
scars but you know it's what makes me
feel good you know I I love wrestling
and in fact uh you know the reason I'm
here this weekend is because Gorbachev
now has flown in now this show shows lb
but Gorbachev is flying in and you know
to have a meeting about 10-minute
meeting with the AWA and Nikita Koff and
they're pushing through all kind of you
know no disqualification ordinances
because professional wrestling along
with McDonald's and everything else that
gives you cancer has broken in has
broken in to to Russia you know their
economy collapsed any the hero they want
Nikita Koloff you know to have this belt
bad and of course I don't so uh Larry
land is going to be vers really the the
whole USSR here coming up to you know
June 23rd all right well man I'm 100%
behind you L I'm 100% behind me
too all right we got some stuff we going
to talk about the San Martino match in
Japan and we got some good stuff to talk
about we're going to be right back we
got PSA coming up so stay tuned we got
more Larry Zisco more Larry we'll be
right back Larry
[Applause]
zabis 999 992 993 how you doing this
Little Richard baby and I'm here with my
good friend Mr T my so one and we
talking about using condoms cuz whenever
you pump you always got to use a condom
right Mr T that's right little Richard
you got to keep pumping H what number
you on um oh shut up but you must use a
condom this is Mr T and you keep pumping
and we make sure you wear a condom well
no matter how you pump how come you not
down here pumping with me cuz baby I'm
the beauty and you the Beast shut
[Music]
up right welcome back we're once again
with Larry Zisco now now Mr T was
pumping now you say you're a natural
bodybuilder you're the one of the few
bodybuilders who can look in the mirror
and say look ma no steroids well I'm
really not a bodybuilder a wrestler
sorry sorry I do I do a lot of you know
weight training two three times a week I
do a lot of stretching you know I mean
uh you know bodybuilding has nothing to
do with wrestling right you know uh well
the best I've ever done I tell you this
is what no steroids none of this junk
was 465 pounds is the most I've ever
bench pressed but now that was at a body
weight of 240 lbs you know like some of
these guys now they got you know bench
pressing 600 lb but they weigh you know
500 lb and they can't walk up a flight
of steps so that's really not strength I
mean you need you know endurance and uh
and you know your body has to be you
know built to the point where you know
it can take a lot of abuse m i was I
once pressed it was about 700 lbs who
did I did I did with your
mouth no but she weigh 750 with her
shoes
on but I want to ask you about now what
if now you you you lost a championship
and you just won it back from mrito well
I went to Japan and uh you know it was a
a world championship match and you know
Sao you know was in the state so was
locked up here for a while got some good
press so uh you know it was it was a big
deal you know for him to to wrestle me
in Tokyo you which was you know his home
you know territory and uh there was a a
referee named Peter Takashi who was an
American hating bias referee whose
father was killed in World War II like
anybody still gives a damn right and you
know they showed the tape on the AWA
where it was a one two and the referee
just stops to count well I freaked out I
shoved him and being you know Sayo was a
tough guy but I was ripped off there on
February 10th you know and uh in the
contract you I got a rematch and so we
did it and I beat the man and that was
with Nick Bach Winkle you paint your
mustache
on I'm a good looking man now you were
talking you got like three hairs wa I
want ask I want to ask you something man
in the best looking man in comedy you
can the best looking man in comedy I
want to ask you a question I want to ask
you a question I I want to ask you a
question now I want ask you call
yourself a living legend when I think of
living legend I think of Sinatra I think
of Frank Sinatra I think of Sammy Davis
J what makes you a living legend well
the thing that made me the living legend
was number one I could kick anybody's
ass out there that claims to be a
professional wrestler number two I've
retired you know the Living Legends of
the past uh generation and the last you
know what 15 glorious years 1 two three
that's probably three generations I just
figed out what your you shut up I'm the
best wait don't tell me
this a good looking man I'm the best
looking man I've ever seen I am number
one I cannot be beat wake up and see you
in the morning without your mustache and
[Laughter]
eyebrows Scar the hell out of
you oh my god oh H I tell you you want
to talk about me like that I want to to
challenge you right now to a match I
want to challenge you right now to a
match me and you I know kind of get away
a match me and you right now I'm the
greatest I've ever seen I'm the best
looking man I'm the most flamboyant you
cannot beat me I challenge you right now
right now you can beat any man living I
challeng you right now to man you got so
much stuff in your hair I bet I could
this one click poof you go up look but
you got a bald in there man hey I've
been getting my hair y for 15 I chall
you right now to a match will you
challenge me I I challenge you right now
I don't want to I'm to wrestle but I
tell you what I'll thumb wrestle you
right now hurt that face the best two
out of three right now how's that sound
how about just one fall okay one fall
let's go me and you out there on the
floor come on let's get you on the floor
okay here let's go good M
clip now you think you can beat me fool
you want to talk about the way I look
well I tell you get my face and let's do
it right now I know how you look I'm the
best looking man in comedy and I cannot
be beat I'm number one the best looking
thing I've ever seen and
you savage okay we're not going to talk
about that we're not going to talk about
that hit it can
I I don't I don't want to hit it cuz you
might fart hit
it oh now you scared the beaut the beaut
is intimida him the beaut is intimida
him no no no we're not going I don't
want to hit you I don't want to hit you
I don't want to hit you I don't want to
hit you send my lawyer home
now okay here we go best two out of
three man against one
okay look at them Nails Mike I got
pretty
nails nails cl cl my
nail you paint those at
[Laughter]
night got them Kmart shoes on talking
about me got them King Mar where'd you
get the shirt at world wars it's a gift
let's
go got we give me things them Gilligan
pans too okay stop wrestling or what
okay here we go ready okay on ready look
like it is okay ready one ready what I
never did this okay ready
yeah one no no no no you got to go one
two three now go okay what you going
you're going to stab me with that
nail he's got grease on there you go you
[Applause]
dirty
lco the world champion
be the Undisputed world champion for a
long time all right Larry St right here
buddy up next is a music video featuring
the late great comedian up next is a
video featuring the late great comedian
Robin Harris Robin starred in the movie
do the right things house party and his
own HBO special he's got a song called
Shake it up here he is with the Jamaica
boys here goes Robin William Robin
Harris excuse me we'll be right back
Larry
Zisco Robin just try to shake it up I
ain't trying nothing it's easy no Robin
you were great in house party I was
acting in house party
[Music]
too oh man I'll be home doing your damn
homework teach me something I'm grown
watch House part want to come
out all right thank you welcome back
John Wayne is an American hero his life
and career is the stuff Legends are made
of my next guest has gotten a lot of
work because of that Legend he has
appeared throughout the country has
starred in commercials movies please
welcome John Wayne lookalike Jerry
Thomas yes Jerry Thomas welcome to the
show see oh man fantastic things have
cooled down a little bit tell me what
how do people react when they see you uh
generally a little bit
surprised they start to think back now
didn't I hear he passed away I would
imagine you probably had some very
unusual stuff happen with people running
into you a lot of different kinds of
reactions all way from tears to tears of
joy to give me a big hug I haven't had
one in a long time that's really cool
when did you start when did how when did
you realize you look like John Wayne oh
that was 15 18 years ago my kids would
be watching old black and white movie on
TV and they'd come over and in holler
dad you're on TV that' be an old John
Wayne movie being played uhhuh and that
uh that's when I first started realizing
that there was a resemblance when did
you start working as a lookalike about
eight years ago mhm approximately did
you practice or study like his voice and
mannerisms I never had to our characters
are that close together that uh I never
had to work on The Voice or the uh
particular looks it just I was lucky is
that right you you're you're it's all
natural what you do here yeah and you're
a Rancher too he portrayed the American
Cowboy and that's been my life I've been
a Rancher for about 20 years wow what
does John Wayne mean to you well see as
a kid growing up he was he was my hero
and I watched his movies and imitated
them then uh in my small style but uh
now to me it's a
responsibility kids nowadays don't have
a lot of Heroes so if I can fill in and
keep alive this particular Legend that's
pretty good goal in life oh man that's
beautiful I think that's fantastic in
fact you do keep the legend alive we got
a little clip of you in a movie that you
made what's the name of this movie like
this just left the dawn just left the
dawn well let's take a look at that clip
and we'll be right back with Jerry
Thomas yes
ass I'm
bad I am
bad not bad shooting there mister
somebody who's not supposed to be
shooting in my
town I'll tell you what this one's
murdered all over the
territory and I guess we can let it go
this
time but
remember no more shooting you bet
Duke you bet Duke you met
Duke my name's Marion
[Applause]
Pilgrim that's a lot that's fun stuff
what what how do how do you like uh
doing like the movies how many movies
have you done uh I've been in eight now
just small parts uh not all speaking
roles I've uh got one coming out called
Hollywood chaos where I play John Wayne
mhm that one had Humphrey Bogart Clark
Gable and John Wayne in
it I mean that guy was quite an
imitator definitely
great how now you're with the lookalikes
of Minnesota yeah several agencies I not
exclusive with anybody but I uh
Minnesota look alikes and resemblance
and Hollywood stars of Chicago the uh
there are several and then plus the
agents around town book me how do you
like you've done a lot lots and lots of
TV
commercials yeah uh done in with good
taste this is probably one of the
biggest stipulations I make is the fact
that uh if you're going to portray John
Wayne you portray him as John Wayne
would be portrayed so don't ask me to do
a commercial if it isn't in Good Taste M
that's you carry on that Legend in a
positive manner right what uh have you
had any contact with Wayne's family
every now and then I meet a member of
the family an old girlfriend uh director
producer uh
uh the gentleman that was on this
particular uh series that was that we
saw in the clip was also the Director of
Photography on stage coach okay with
John Wayne wow so it gives you a little
tip you know cameraman always liked it
John Wayne would kind of lean back and
step into a scene he said it'd set it up
for us uhuh but it's uh it's really neat
because everywhere you travel you you
either meet somebody that knew John
Wayne or got to meet him or worked with
him or friend or family or whatever wow
that's quite Anon what uh what's coming
up next for you well next I'm uh in
negotiations right now with Universal
Studios they had a national uh lookalike
in intell and search around the country
you want it here for Minnesota yes sir
absolutely one more time for Jerry
Thomas Jerry Thomas yes yes yes oh my my
my
[Applause]
my all right did you have a good time
all right I want to take this
opportunity to thank my very special
guest tonight I like to think Larry
Zisco yes all
right Gary Thomas
yes I want to thank my crew of my studio
audience give yourselves a round of
applause yes yes yes yes yes yes all
right and I want to thank some very
special people I want to thank Ed HW
Terry Thomas I want to thank my entire
crew and I want to thank you wonderful
people for tuning us tuning in taking us
home as an outstanding Soul vocalist he
is from the soul mot toown group called
the right choice he's taking us home his
name is Billy Clark and he's going to be
singing Larry Graham smash hit one in a
million so stay tuned cuz Billy's going
to get down with it my name is fancy R
have a good night oh yes yes yes
[Music]
love has played game on me so
long I started to believe I never find
anyone now I try to convince me to give
in said you can
[Music]
win but one day the sun came shining
through the rain stopped and the skies
were
[Music]
blue and oh what a
revelation to see
someone was saying I love you to
me a
one in a
[Music]
million
CH of a Life Time