I said
[Music]
I I said
I thank you hi this is the Reverend Pat
Robinson thank you
[Applause]
I've never been asked to appear on a
comedy TV show before although I've done
many different things I had a woman she
was in Detroit she was blind and
overweight I touched her and she was
still blind and overweight but her
pocketbook was a little
lighter I i' I I've done many different
things uh people ask me why do they call
it the 700 Club with people sitting in
about $100 and and and the IQ must be
about seven so that's how we got the
name and and I I stopped here it was
really nice I saw the Reverend Jim Baker
in prison I oh I got him a a soap pick
up before the
shower oh I did I did see the other
ministers and I we chipped in and got of
it you know because do on others you
have them do on to you and well you know
he was picking up soap in the shower uh
we don't want them to do to him what
we've been doing to the American public
for the last few
years oh I've done many different things
it's my pleasure and I've been paid
quite well to come here
today yeah oh the money is not for me
it's for the ministry as you know
there's kid starving in Africa yeah they
starving of course the money won't go to
them but to my presidential campaign I
guess I'll just say my lie now stay
tuned I'm the Reverend Pat Robinson and
it's time to
get get down
wi do the
J come on
baby want to watch everybody
work I said come on
baby hello ladies and gentlemen welcome
from the host of get down with it the
human chocolate Orchid F Ray
[Applause]
mclone all right all right hello hello
yes yes yes how's everybody doing Magic
Mike yes please hello welcome to get
down with the twin City's highest
entertainment talk show my my name is
fancy Ray M I am the best looking man in
comedy if Beauty was a crime I get a
year in jail but if good looks was money
I get out the next day on
bail shut up I am the best looking man
in County woo my my my my my it's a wild
and crazy world we liveing it's wild out
there I tell you is any single guys in
the
audience for real the single guy oh man
I tell you something if you ever go out
with a woman for the first time she has
a child do not allow her to bring a
child with her do not I on the first
date recently woman brings a kid with us
right we going to restaurant we're in
the restaurant the kidss in the
restaurant he's fidgetting he wouldn't
sit still and he's fidgetting he
wouldn't sit still he gets up starts to
wander around the restaurant she makes
him sit down he's fidget he wouldn't sit
still so she starts breastfeeding
him right there at the restaurant you
know she asked me that mind you know me
of course I said no but honestly you
know it was a little embarrassing you
know it was like me her and this
17-year-old kid of
hers well you know me the next thing you
know I started fiding I couldn't sit
still oh man so wild and crazy World why
talking about boobs I've never met a
woman that liked their boobs either
they're twoo big or one's bigger than
the other or something I a woman asked
me the other day she said Ray my boob's
too big I said no too big that means we
can throw them on our shoulders bounce
him on my butt and play patty
cake but she like you know it's all
comfortable you know it pinches here and
grabs here and I said well take it off
take the bra off she said what's going
to support him I said
me we'll use the head to face you know
but she's gonna get 18 hour support
that's right
it's a wild and crazy I had a woman that
told me she said am I too small I said
no it's fine she said they're too small
I said they're fine she look at me flat
as a pancake so I said let's get some
serp and some butter and get
busy it's so wild and crazy when I am
the best looking man in County woo you
can travel the land you can travel to
seat but you never find com as pretty as
me with the wisdom of Einstein the
finessa clay get ready to party with
fancy Ray yes yes yes yes yes
yes my my my my my my what a cff what a
cff what a African
giraffe shut up now I am the best
looking man in comy tonight's program we
got a very special cable cast we got
what I consider the Minnesota queen of
Comedy comedian extraordinaire Liz
Winstead is here tonight yes my my my my
my my yes yes yes and we got a few other
surprises for you so stay tuned cuz I'm
going to slip out and get back into
something a bit more fancy do y'all want
to turn the roof off the mother sucker
yeah this say te Ro off mother Ro off
the suck off the suck stay tuned cuz
it's time
to we'll be right
[Music]
back ah how you doing this a little
Richard oh my I'm here my good friend Mr
T I call him Mr thing cuz he's got that
thing oh my we here to spread a very
important message about the use of
condoms right Mr T that's right Little
Richard oh your mou what he trying to
say is that you must practice safe sex
in order to do that especially when you
going to get some W bamboo listen fool
if you don't let me say something I'm
going to teach you the meaning of a new
word pain oh my soul get out of here
listen up sorry about that little
Richard but listen up folks condoms are
a very serious thing that can protect
you from a lot of sexual diseases such
as syphus gonorrhea AIDS hoofa mouth and
Lim's disease child you can't get hoof
from MTH and lime disease by having sex
you can't no
well uh if you could to get him from
having sex uh Conor would stop it
right right Mr T so let's all practice
safe sex and use a condom child you
ignorant where' you go to school I
didn't oh my
[Music]
[Applause]
soul once again fcy Ray m
[Music]
[Applause]
my my my My Wo a peach is a peach and a
pair is a pair if you can beat me
rocking you can have my chair shut up
now I'm the best looking man in comedy
tonight's program I take you we got a
very special guest this young lady has
been featured on VH1 MTV HBO she did a
PBS special with whoopy Goldberg last
year she was nominated for comedi an of
the Year currently she's starring in a
one woman play called don't get me
started I tell you let's take a look at
her in action on Caroline's comedy hour
stay tuned we'll be right back with Miss
Liz Winston we'll be right
back yes I mean maybe for sex
[Music]
[Applause]
and honey car please join me walking him
Liz Winston round
oh oh darling you are the best looking
man in that
chair oh I'm the best look man I've ever
SE give me high five yeah all right man
get it going wait a minute I'm
white get it going get it pumping along
we are we're happening oh man that was
necklace can I just look at this for a
minute oh man it matches my underwear
check this out here no
Oh I thought it was cuz you didn't want
to pay for cable
that's really cool tell me something
like I said you've been doing so many
different things here lately and
appearing on television all over the
cable channels how long have you been
doing stand-up comedy eight years eight
years yeah I did it on a dare how was a
dare uh somebody said do it I was in
college and they said you know why don't
you get up there and vent this anger to
somebody else besides us so I said okay
I'll try it so I went to dudly rigs on
open mic night and Jeff Cesario was the
host okay so he was just starting out in
comedy kind of and I was just sort of
starting out and uh I did it and it was
real fun and you kept it going so you
were were you like always a Class Clown
and no I was more like the class cynic
oh that okay so watch that kind of
biting Edge humor because the type of
humor that you do is a little it's
Unique and in fact that you Carri that
into your play now yeah yeah how would
you describe your comedy uh now I would
say uh it's social commentary um
definitely uh with a liberal slant to it
um I attack everybody from uh
uh George Bush to you all the way down
the food chain I guess he's the worst on
my food chain and then it just goes down
from there okay yeah okay with with the
different types of Comedy that you do
with the different topics that you talk
on when you started off what type of
Comedy you did the same type of thing um
I was always sort of had an edge but it
was more observational I talked uh more
about my experiences back then are
different than my experiences now so
they just sort of evolved it's sort of
been the same thing although when you're
in college you really don't have a real
life to live because you're so focused
in on school that it doesn't Dawn on you
that wait a minute the minute I'm out of
school after to realize what life really
is and the minute I realized what life
really was that's when I really went off
with my comedy and said I got to talk
about this stuff okay okay how many
years had you been doing it before you
went professional
um about four really okay so you've been
doing it four years full time now four
years without a job okay yeah being a
ComEd is really a tough life like it's
not all the glamour being on the road
and right material they think it is
right it isn't
right it's really a challenge to do well
yeah I mean you're in really bad Motel
sixes with you know truckers pounding on
your door trying to get in and you know
filthy towels and cockroaches and you
know you get to the gig and it's this
weird one nighter where some guy with
three teeth hands you a microphone and
says okay go ahead we got a bachelor
party full of bunch of farmers and oh
God how has the comedy scene Chang over
the
years um audience wise or as far as the
club what do you mean I mean as uh Club
wise Club wise I think it's changed a
lot it's become very corporate it used
to be that comedy was equated with jazz
um you the same sort of people would go
see it people wanted to listen they
wanted to hear alternative things now
it's become very sort of
homogenized um it's about sell it's
about selling drinks it's about U making
a lot of money instead of making a
quality show right and and now the
market has changed because there's so
many comedians out there cuz comedy is
so hot yeah it's weird too because what
happens is these comedy clubs are
opening up so fast because they know
it's a way to make a buck and they're
forcing uh they need bodies right to
work these clubs and so what's happening
is the kids that aren't really ready to
be working in the clubs yet are being
put into situations where they have to
write material that might not be up to
standards of what they were but they
want to work and they have to work so um
they don't develop uh as well as they
could if they could just keep doing the
open mics and keep their da job and
working it out uhhuh it's kind of a
shame really mhm because when you're
forced to go out on the road you're
forced to lower your standards about
what you want to talk about so things
get really dirty they get really um
unchallenging and it's like I don't want
to me if I'm an audience person I don't
want to be treated like I'm stupid by
somebody giving me really stupid jokes I
get mad at that and what happens
especially I've never heard you comment
I read the article in the Twin City
reader that you go on the road and you
do penis jokes because that seems to
work I mean that's what you have on the
road you have to like take to the penis
lowest common denominated so I just
don't want to do it anymore so that's
why I said wait a minute I can either do
my act or I can succumb to what needs to
be done on the road and I just said I
don't want to go out on the road and be
really dirty and ridiculous now I
mentioned the twin CI reader article
what do you feel about the local comedy
scene there's a lot of controversy
around that article there you know what
I'm referring to oh the Scott hen
article yeah you wanted me to say the
Scott hon Artic sure sure cover in your
ass sure sure you know that article I'm
talking about right now
I mean I think some of it was very valid
Scott Hansen um you know basically runs
the show in the Twin Cities you know and
but the one of the problem is too though
that the comics have to get out and go
out and just and go to other cities and
try to work um you know if somebody if
you can take advantage of somebody
unfortunately as human beings we just do
right and so that's what happens you
know he's got this group of people that
don't push themselves and don't go out
to to other cities and uh want to make
money right away so they go to Scott
Hansen and he gets to say what happens
cuz he's the only guy right that's very
true well I tell you what in a few
seconds we're going to talk about you
going out to other cities and also your
one act play all right so stay tuned
more less win stick and we're going to
get down with it stay tuned
[Music]
[Applause]
ladies and
gentlemen a BN here for fancy Ray
Chevrolet on cable so you need a new car
how about this one right
here
1989 Corvette
convertible sporty f last drive this
video away
today no money down
288 a month why don't you pick up the
phone give it to KY right here at fancy
Ray
Chevrolet 1
976 v t y That's 1
1976 Beauty and ask for Raymond tune in
and get down with
[Music]
it right my my fancy Ray Chevrolet we're
once again with Liz Winston we're
talking about the comedy scene uh the
the one woman play that you're in yes
what was the concept behind the play the
concept behind the play was I wanted to
get out of comedy clubs where I wouldn't
have to battle waitresses um people
would be able to sit down in chairs not
be bothered with hecklers be able to
listen and to take standup comedy um to
a a step up okay um to be able to
combine my own life with the comedy so
it's the whole show was real everything
in the show is true and it's my opinions
about how I view the life and how um
the80s have just influenced me and what
I've seen and what I think people need
to see with what's going on how have the
80s influenced you they've made me even
angrier well it's it's just like you
think things change and he thinks
there's change but there isn't you know
I feel like we're you know we're going
into the '90s but we're stepping back
into the 50s in a lot of ways that's
true with censorship it's just like
McCarthyism and with David Duke in
Louisiana it's just like this whole
bizarre KKK thing is still alive and
well in the South and it just makes you
wonder how far have we progressed right
and so many of these stories there's
articles this big in the paper about it
you know you never read about it because
people don't don't want to let the
American people know that hey this stuff
really exists you know just keep
thinking that it's really nice and we're
America so isn't it great that we just
get to go bomb you know the crap out of
a bunch of people over there who had
nothing to do with one guy that we sold
arms to you know right right right that
you did someone clap a little bit there
are are you okay okay okay okay that's
kind that's frustrating the whole War
thing really got me really what what
really got Liz Winstead's Gander about
that war just the whole fact that we
funded this psycho and then we you know
act like it's his fault the only
something that you talked about I I saw
the plate I loved it you talked about
some facts that I didn't I didn't even
know a lot of people don't know yeah
about what we did yeah about selling him
arms then he yeah I mean a lot of stuff
that we did we uh well
gosh tell me tell me this um with the uh
with the
play it's the it's in the theater but a
lot of it is standup and like it's it's
a fine line between theater and stand up
it's really a unique mixture I was
something that was really cool that was
you came out can I give this away what
you did right at first yeah she comes
out and she's like got a backpack on the
set is like an apartment right and she
comes out and she says who wants coffee
and she goes out and gets everybody
coffee yeah soever just kind of and she
I thought she was joking cuz I didn't
get a
cup well you weren't very fancy that you
were toned down that that was very toned
down very toned down we talk about
leaving the cities here you first left
here and went to San Francisco what's
the comedy scene out cuz I hear La the
comedy scene is so rough and tough and
people are stepping on each other to get
ahead was it like that yeah you find out
who your friends are uhhuh it's very
bizarre because Los Angeles is a city
that is solely based and created for the
entertainment industry right so
everybody there it's like I pump gas but
I want to direct you know it's like
nobody has a real job please you know
you die to meet a plumber who was just a
plumber I'd probably marry
him well I'll fix some pipes any day oh
I'm sure you would shut up now shut up
anyway but so the scene out there so the
scene there is like you when you're
having a conversation with somebody you
never know why they're being nice to you
you always feel like they're going to be
nice to you until they kind of find out
who you are and if you can or cannot
help their career and if you can't
you're out conversation over and they're
always kind of looking around and who
here is better to talk to and it's it's
really bizarre sort of smoing constantly
and unreality and you can't do anything
there that doesn't involve trying to get
on TV in some way okay it's impossible
okay but you did get on TV yeah how were
you able to do that it well my HBO thing
was a fluke I was living in San
Francisco at the time and I was working
at this dive and um I had to go drive an
hour to do this um showcase for
something else and Robin Williams and
this manager happened to be in the
audience at this club in San Francisco
okay so I got on stage and I just
started bitching about I had to drive
and I just worked for these Hicks and
scream I can't smoke in
here I mean it was like and so this
voice starts laughing throughout the
whole show and it sounded like Mor and
I'm like is Mor here good this is what I
need it's some Los or Mor and it was him
okay so after the show he's like you are
so funny you're so funny and his manager
is also um the P person that produced
women of the night so they said we want
to put you on women of the night and
come down and blah blah blah so that's
how that came about so I mean you just
in the right place at the right time
luck luck luck total luck that's
beautiful that's beautiful which
probably L some of the other things
currently you live in New York City yes
how's the scene out there uh great I
really like it New York is very
different it's um it's it's like the
world's largest dumpster
but I like New York because it's a very
um you have to be on the ball to exist
there you cannot like kind of wander
around because you'll be killed you'll
be hit by a car or you'll be stabbed so
you have to have your senses about you
to live there okay and so you meet so
many people who are very interesting you
can walk to museums everybody's very
well read the audiences expect more of
you and so they push you MH if you don't
push yourself the audiences will push
you and that's really good that's great
that's great from my understand I talked
to your producer who's out of sight
Anthony Benson anony Bon and he talked
about that with the planet I don't know
if I can say this for your play what
what's coming up let me ask you what's
next for the play we're taking it to San
Francisco okay we uh we're doing it
there for a month and then we're taking
it to New York in the fall that's
fantastic and what are your future goals
my future goals is to get this thing
where I want it to be it's really a work
in progress right now it's really
something that I mean I've only done it
in front of people for going this is the
third week we're into now so it's been
constantly changing every show something
new happens something else we add
subtract do all this stuff and so um we
want to get that where we want it to be
hopefully it will become uh cable
special or short film is kind of what
I'm gearing towards that I want to stay
in front of live audiences as much as I
can because I love just the response of
having people it gets them away from
their televisions at least you know
right right and you know how they feel
it doesn't matter what the critics say
it doesn't matter what anybody says
because you know what happened with
between you and the audience and that's
the nothing can top that feeling that's
fantastic and I would tell the viewers
out there that if you get chance it's a
limited run by by time this goes on the
air probably be gone but if it comes
back go check out this play it is
fantastic the beauty said it so it must
be true shut up give Liz winon a round
of applause Liz winon Oh My
My My My My Wo yes