hi this is fancy Ray for standup records
we're proud to introduce fancy Ray
mone's the best looking man in comedy LP
are y'all ready to have a good time this
is the king of the party records and
when you buy the lp you get a free
digital download I can cut your risk of
cancer by
72% FY ra the best looking man in comedy
LP comes in two flavors dark chocolate
and milk
chocolate get your copy today
well
all right rotate your V you can't go
live this way all right we're gonna go
this way well all right welcome one
welcome all today is March 27th it's
fancy raay day here in Minneapolis in St
Paul the mayors of both Cities
Minneapolis and St Paul declared today
fancy Ray day and so happy fancy Ray Day
to everyone
watching H I'm the first the last I'm
the best and the most I'm the heartbeat
of Minneapolis Minnesota wo and my
beauty is coast to coast wo Mills have
kicked me huh they didn't tan my high a
rattlesnake bit me and just crawled off
and died I can make a superstitious man
walk under a ladder and then fire your
butt like it's pancake batter now I
can't cook a turkey and I can't shake
and bake but I make love so good it'll
make a woman's stomach ache huh I know
how to mash up the potatoes and french
up the fries the truth is the truth and
I never ever lie see I can make love for
six nights huh and on the seventh day
the men go Rayo but the women go
hooray I put the L in love the m and
muscle I'm the p and the pretty and the
h in the hustle welcome one Welcome All
I'm going wait for some more folks to
come in and join me on this glorious day
March 27th is fancy Ray day declared by
the mayor of Minneapolis and St Paul but
I want you to understand something right
here now this day isn't about just me
well it is all about me but it's all
about you if you've enjoyed my work over
the years and that means on the comedy
stage on the TV stations on the radio
station if you see faner are here fany
raised voice know one thing for sure God
is winking at
you and I just love you all this day
would not be possible without this right
here my first ever standup comedy album
titled fancy rais the best looking man
in comedy LP and and I want to thank
standup records Dan and Ian for making
this possible you can get this at
standup records.com or iTunes
amazon.com make sure that you get this
album and I want to just talk to
everyone out there here today and with
my pretty self and right now we're going
through a very challenging time the plan
today was that we were going out to the
mayor's office both Minneapolis and St
Paul going to take a limousine and go to
both locations and have that Declaration
of fancy Ray day well it's a different
day and a different time with this
Corona virus going on right now so we're
all on lockdown but you know something
they can lock me down but they can't
keep me down and something that we all
have to declare to ourselves even though
we're going through our own individual
challenges we're all going through our
own different tribulations but no one
thing that through this declare to
yourself that I'm going to get better
and stronger maybe this is an
opportunity for us to go and side and
reach up and create something bigger
better and stronger in our lives what in
your life needs to be improved what do
you need to leave behind what do you
need to do to step a new into this
wonderful wonderful existence and see
that's what fancy R does I want to lift
your vibration I want you to feel the
love and the joy which is you as we
celebrate today fancy Ray day here in
Minneapolis St Paul and all over this
country we know that today is a day of
love and joy it's about you it's about
me it's about life it's about love it's
about Joy it's about eternal hope and
it's about making the most going coast
to coast and you know I don't like to
brag and I don't like to boast but I'm
like cinnamon on your hot butter
toast we're going to do today gonna play
a couple of tracks from the new
album someone is and we paused but we're
back right here once again and I just uh
I I thank you all for joining me here
today you know I've been around for a
long time you know what's amazing is
that I've been doing comedy 30 years a
lot of you you may not be too impressed
by that you should be because how many
29 year olds do you know been doing
comedy for 30
years and this dog on Corona virus is uh
you know is is is is has got people
concerned and you should be concerned do
all the things you can but I know it's
just three places that the Corona virus
hasn't shown up uh Detroit Cleveland and
Africa you know why cuz black folks
don't drink Corona if there was a a
slick SM liquor virus popey chicken will
close down tomorrow I ain't lying I am
the best looking man in comedy and I'm
so happy to be here well you know what I
want to do real quick here before I play
a cut from the album The First Cut again
I I want to thank standup records and
say that if you've enjoyed me and that's
what today is about fancy Ray day again
it's not about me it's about you and if
you've enjoyed What I've Done TV radio
then I want you to get this album share
it with your friends and family if
you're enjoying this video and you want
some uplifted in someone's life share
this video with them and just know that
the prettiest man in comedy is here
today I'm not ly how pretty is fancy Ray
other day I blew myself a kiss the Mir
the miror got
pregnant I ain't lying my my my how
about we play a cut from the new fancy R
M the best looking man in comedy LP
available on standup records.com Amazon
and also iTunes this is track number one
from my new LP and you must get it here
we go I hope you enjoy and here we go
fancy Ray the best looking man in comedy
[Music]
LP all right ladies and gentlemen I'd
like you to keep it going the human
chocolate Orchid ladies and gentlemen FY
Ray mclone Give It Up
hello one more time I hear everybody's
voice I said hello hello my name is
fancy Ray mclone and I am the best
looking man in
comedy they want you to find e wonder of
the world they searched from mcar to
Madrid there went there some places that
were sacred others that were B like the
as Tech under the Great Pyramids they
found a tablet which R Beauty BK and
they knew wonder of the world was me
fancy Ray the human chocolate
AR my my my this is my LP get your copy
today I want to say something before I
go anywhere my favorite person on this
planet
is f
[Applause]
my favorite fragrance of all times is
FY in fact my favorite celebrity Elma is
over 3
oops messed it up see that's live
broadcast hold let me get this back here
baby way don't go nowhere
oh I messed it up oh man but you know
what that's what the live broadcast does
that's the first track from the lp and
you just got to go buy it to hear the
rest of it it's
fantastic but that's this is live
television or live podcasting I scratch
it we're going to play another track
don't go nowhere if you enjoy that no
fan the best looking man in comedy LP
get it right now go order it it's on
amazon.com
standup records.com and also at iTunes
and what's really really incredible K
look at that how pretty I am today oh
Lord have Mery I am the best looking man
in comedy I look so good sometimes cops
pull me over spread the legs and make me
pat their butts down I ay my my my my my
who is fancy R you may be folks out
there know it's all over the world this
is all over the world who is fancy R I'm
a combination of like a Richard prior
meets the Harlem Globe
TR I'm everything the human chocolate
Orchid human chocolate Orchid and the
best looking man in comedy tell you a
little bit about myself I you know
started in this career as show business
in 1984 at First Avenue nightclub and we
went out there with a joy and exuberance
and something I want to take a moment
right now is to thank all of my great
great fans number one I want to thank
think my mom and my dad who have loved
me and supported me from day one Uncle
wter I got my fiance Tiny Joe woof woof
you know she brings out the dog in there
and also I got the beautiful Dan and Ian
and everyone and and even if I'm not
calling you royalty even if I'm not
calling your name you have touched my
life you've had an impact on my life and
hopefully I've had impact on your life
as we celebrate fancy raid day March 20
7th here in Minneapolis Minnesota you
know in fact a lot of people don't
realize that this is actually my
birthday month I was I was born in
Albuquerque New Mexico and New Mexico is
known as the uh Enchanted State the
enchanted State have you notic you can't
say the word New Mexico not smile go go
say say New Mexico New Mexico See You
Smile don't you you know why cuz I'm
from there and right now you're
Enchanted
and my birthday is Actually March the 3D
which means my zodiac sign is Pisces I'm
I'm a Pisces uhhuh and that's you know
the Zodiac that's the two fish you know
so so that means I'm I'm half mermaid
and half chocolate
swordfish people get mad when I say that
they ain't no such thing as a chocolate
swordfish and that always makes me laugh
because no one ever disputes the fact
that I might be half
mermaid oh man you know here we are on
March 27th fancy raid day F if you're
watching me right now tap fancy rid day
up there right now if you're watching
put your hands there right now everybody
that can hear my voice put your hands in
there and say fancy ra day say it again
fancy ra say it again fany today is
fancy ra and we're celebrating the joy
the life the love the career of fancy R
with his fantastic new standup records
release the best looking man in comedy
again this day is about me but it's
about you fancy Ray day it's about love
and fact I'm going just indulge y'all
right now and do a poem that I like to
do it's about love especially in these
challenging times right now people have
financial hardship there was thought of
you know is this the time to release the
album and I said we have to release the
album right now because right now what
this world needs is laughter we need
more laughter we need more love we need
more vibration we need something that
says you can do it no matter what you're
going through I want you to know that
you can do it remember something that
fancy Ray says a minus sign is half of a
plus sign so take this Challenge and
make it a plus do your best if you got
to get on the bust because we know
there's a power in the universe and in
that we trust I am the best looking man
in comedy and I ain't doing nothing but
spitting wisdom love and knowledge right
now I'm going to play another track in
one second but here's a poem I want to
do for the folks who are watching It's
My Love poem and um I do this at
weddings and when I've had the honor of
doing
a life celebration ceremonies I do this
poem the title of the poem is this what
does Love Got to Do with it it
says what does love got to do
[Music]
I say
everything love is our Birthright and we
are all kings and queens it's love that
c the mountains and makes the rivers
flow love makes the birds chirp and the
beautiful flowers grow it's love that
keeps families together even when
they're far far apart it's love that
will send you to a strip mall in a
snowstorm H to buy dog food from a
that's smart love makes you happy love
makes you grow it's love that makes you
thirsty for knowledge for things you
didn't know you didn't even know love
gave you life and it will take this
physical body away it's love that makes
mothers and grandmothers beautiful even
after they turned old and gray love can
be found in the depths of the oceans and
in the redwood trees that stand tall
love
makes babies and we all know children or
what H The Greatest Love of All love can
be called God life Allah Jehovah Yahweh
Mother Nature Spirit Christ Jesus light
wind or
sound love is all there is honey and
it's love that makes the world go around
y'all didn't hear what I said I said
it's love that makes the world go round
now if you feel the love Come on talk to
me like you know I do then raise your
hand everybody raise your raise your
hands and right now tell the Universe I
love you give yourselves a round all
right we going to play another track
from the fan R comedy album the best
looking man in comedy FP we're going to
play this is track number two we're
going to play right here for you um it
is uh when it's a story of when I ran
for Minnesota Governor I was on the
ballot in the 1998 Minnesota Governor
there's a lot of history at fancy rate
started lip syncing in
1984 appeared on the show putting on
hits two times then I went on to go onto
cable AIS from 89 to 99 we had many
great performers come on my TV show
ranging from whoopy Goldberg to the
wonderful Donnie Osman Kirby pocket the
list goes on everyone appear on my show
from Gloria steum to Ryan Jeremy
appeared on get down with it the fancy
Ray Show from there 1998 I was on a
ballot for the Minnesota governor's race
and we took a stance for people who are
living with challenges in this life
Jessie ventur was on fire with all the
publicity was getting but no one was
talking about the people in the streets
so I took it upon myself to deliver a
message of Hope joy and optimism for the
folks living on the street we give a
voice to the voiceless I share a story
with you that when I ran for governor I
uh after the election I ran to a
homeless man and he said he came to me
said fancy I want to thank you for what
you said during the governor's race I I
heard what you had to say and I said
what I saw show did you vote for me did
you vote for me did you vote for me he
goes no I'm I'm homeless I don't have a
permanent address I couldn't vote for
you but I heard what you had to say and
I thank you and that made my whole run
worthwhile and what I'm saying to you
I've touched many lives in many
different ways and if there's some type
of way that I brought you a spark of Joy
a smile a laugh then uh I want you to
share my joy with my first ever Comedy
release the best looking man in comedy
LP available again amazon.com you can
get the NPR iTunes and of course standup
records.com we're going to play track
number two with that Governor's race
right now let's hope this works out a
little better than the first
time all right here we go fancy Ray the
best looking man in comedy
L coasion right now y'all nickname me
white
[Applause]
Christmas I'm known as the human
chocolate Orchid the human chocolate
Orchid
baby now everybody knows what human and
chocolate is Right correct but the
Orchid Park gets folks confused cuz when
most folks think of the Orchid they
think of the flower
which I
[Applause]
am another definition of orchid is
testicle so I'm the human chocolate
[Applause]
teso in other words oh I'm a big black
nut all right we going to cut it right
there you know what that was a little
cut right there from the lp and we not
you know I'm not even going to we're
going to do the governor's race you know
we got many great tracks on here fancy
Ray is the first track Minnesota
Governor is the second track I'm so
pretty is the third track we talk about
marriage TV commercials how many y'all
seen me on TV before if you have bad
credit no credit even a bankruptcy I
could put you in the vehicle today I am
the world's greatest television pitch
man and I've sold everything
from Cars stereos music music and I've
done everything from adult bookstores to
homeopathic health food stores I can
sell everything now folks in the Twin
Cities know me but a lot of folks don't
realize I've had great appearances on
and commercials play in San Jose
California Phoenix Arizona Fort laale
Rockford Illinois all over the country
so faner they say he's a local celebrity
no no no no fancy Ray is an
international sex symbol who bir in
Minneapolis and I ain't
lying you know something you see how
pretty I am cuz I'm so pretty I make
everything
wet except for the dry
sponges all right you know what y'all
fantastic I thank you for joining me
today on my very first live podcast here
this ain't a podcast my first live on
wonderful uh beautiful Facebook and we
just thank you all for for joining us
here today and again it's fancy Ray day
fancy Ray day is your day it's my day we
are celebrating the life the love the
career of fancy Ray mclone me the human
chocolate Orchid and universally
accepted as the best looking man in
comedy I want to thank Diablo Cody who
did my liner notes who won the Oscar for
the beautiful movie Juno and she's
kicking butt out in Los Angeles and I
just love you Diablo I know you're going
to see this and my friend they king of
rock and roll the architect Lil Richard
who has a quote on the album you got to
actually get the physical album to get
the quote from Li Richard this great
line of notes and I think you see that
there I think this this this album is
ideal for framing if you love fancy Ray
and you want that vibration close to you
you get the album played for the last
and then you can look at the dog gone
album for inspiration and and and that's
what I I'm going to do and also again I
want to thank Dan and Ian and um there's
a commercial that you go to fancy Ray uh
on YouTube you can see some more of the
stuff and we just want you all to know
today is fancy Ray day but understand
that today is your day today is your day
to shine today is your day to live today
is your day to express the beauty and
joy which is you there's a power in the
universe and that power is everywhere
and if you believe God's everywhere then
you know that that power is inside of
you so I want you to right now just go
and touch that thing inside of yourself
let's take a moment now and just give
great thanks for today it is a beautiful
day the sun is out they said it was
going to rain today in the Twin C it's
not raining how is it going to rain on
fancy rid
day because I bring the sunshine oh give
me the Star Tribune we got an article in
the city pages and I want to thank the
City Pages for the article Patrick
straight also the Star Tribune John
Breen did an article I should have
pulled this out first you got the
article there baby we got the Star
Tribune cover story and uh we are just
so thankful for all that we have and all
that we are and we thank the Star
Tribune Don Breen all of my friends out
there who are part of this wonderful
thing called Fancy rid day it's a love
it's a joy thank you fan no I thank you
for being here today baby here it is the
article in the star tribute I'm look
look at that there it says array of
sunshine array of sunshine John bream
starts It Off F Ray mclone debut album
the best looking man in comedy whereas
mayor Jacob fry has declared March 27th
fancy Ray day in Minneapolis whereas
mayor Melvin Carter has declared today
fancy Ray day in St Paul whereas fany
MCL is releasing his debut album the
best looking man in comedy on March 27
whereas Minnesota Governor Tim wals has
ordered a social distancing in Minnesota
due to the
covid-19 fancy Ray mcloney hereby
declares a party of
one to
celebrate all of the above it's a party
of one but you know something I am not
alone because you are here with
me and I am there with
you if not physically then in our
Spirits we are joined one power so
there's no separation from us at all as
we go through
this virus this lockdown this pmic
pandemic together
no that there's a power and just believe
that it's going to get better actually
right now we are living through history
you know they talked about the Great
Depression still right now you and I are
walking through history we had n 11 no
one forgets that no one's going to
forget this right here that you went
through it but the thing I challenge you
to do is number one become better that
which doesn't kill me only makes me
stronger so I'm declaring to myself
I'mma get
stronger and I want to laugh I want to
feel good connect with your family
connect with your friends the thing is
is to share some love I said love love
put some love and let's put a smile on
someone's face do an act of kindness
that no one even knows about just go do
something and let you and God know that
you did something beautiful
and make sure you get this album the
best looking man in comedy album LP it
is powerful it is beautiful it's
uplifting it is the manifestation of
love and that love fls through me in me
as as me I am the best looking man in
comy again I put the L in love the m and
muscle I'm the p and pretty and I'm the
H in the hustle and I ain't lying again
happy fancy R day oh you want one more P
one more P I'm going to do one more let
me close it out let me tell y'all the
legend of fancy
Ray the most beautiful beautiful man in
comedy today when I was born the moon
didn't rise only the stars came out and
they lit up the skies there was 3,000
rainbows 200 Thanksgiving floats
crocodiles was wearing sunglasses and
giving high fives of Billy
Goats they made two pots of coffee and
one kettle of tea cuz every nurse in the
city showed up and stood in line for a
chance huh to breastfeed
me Santa Claus arrived he was riding on
a steer he grabbed three broads and he
arrived twice that year Richard Pryor
was there huh with the whole cast from
Saturday Night Live they drinking Mad
Dog 2020 Chas with out to Coke 45 oh
there was lemon cake and there was
peacon pie folks in blue jeans and
others wearing suits and ties there was
countryline dancers hip hoppers doing
the scratch even the painting of Mona
Lisa was there what a and she was doing
the Cabbage Patch folks was drinking
champagne eating shrimp bigger than your
thumb in walk Playmate of the Year folks
got quiet oh FY a't going to get him so
I grabbed the microphone huh and
everybody started to cheer y'all didn't
hear what I said I I said everybody
started to
cheer cuz 5 minutes later I was butt
naked wearing nothing but a pair of
bunny ears then the queen showed up
Queen Elizabeth she looked hotter than a
wick Sheed me sir fancy and gave me my
first pimpstick
then she rang a bell and the whole crowd
started to sing he is the best looking
man in
comedy and the whole crowd said happy
fancy Ray day long live the king long
live the king long live the king I love
love you happy fancy raid day to
everybody again I'm going show the album
cover the best looking man in comedy LP
available amazon.com for the MP3 standup
records.com to get the lp and also you
can go to iTunes and just Google fancy
Ray and put some love in your life share
this video and may the love and life and
Power in the universe bless you and know
one thing for
sure I I love you I really really love
you and I appreciate all of you for the
years of support joy and mutual
admiration because when you are loving
me you're loving yourself it's game
recognizing game and you know what I got
the biggest game in
town God bless peace my my my my my I am
the best looking man in comedy