I'd like to take a moment of your time
right now to talk about two word that
folk like to you making love yeah that's
right I said making
but did you ever sit down and think
about the everything that's got life and
it likes to make love have you thought
about
that cows like to make love horses like
to make love mosquitoes like to make
love and human beings like to make
love but there one thing about them
horses cosos skill and thing when they
get ready to make love they make love
right there makes no difference where
they at right
there now we human beings are a little
bit different than that some of us got a
whole lot of money like to go way up in
an airplane somewhere and make
love then is those of us who like to
wait the Sunday afternoon we go way out
the boat water
somewhere and make love oh but my
children then is those never had nothing
ain't got nothing now and don't expect
to get a dog
on what we like to do is
get our sales about $2 wor the gas and
go way down the country road and make
love in the backseat of a
car please cuz that's what the show is
all about making love spreading the love
the joy the beauty that the world needs
to H today and it makes come from the
city and it makes no come from the
country and some in my voice maybe come
from the suburbs but it's just one thing
stay tuned cuz I'm F I'm the best look
man ComEd tonight we're going to get the
now get a witness gety
I get
[Music]
down come on
baby going to watch everybody
way I said come
onbody ladies and gentlemen off imitated
can't be duplicated fancy Ray m
[Applause]
all right hello Royal team
hello hello welcome to get down with the
twin City's hottest entertainment talk
show my name is fancy Ray MCL I am the
best looking man in comedy wo tall and
fine like a Georgia Pine so good-looking
it ought to be a
crime shut up I am the best looking man
in
well all right we got a fantastic show
for you all tonight all kinds of good
stuff I've been thinking about this
thing in the Middle East you know I was
watching a news report the other day and
a guy said women should women shouldn't
go over to the Saudi Arabia to fight
because they have a monthly
psycho you guys hear about this this guy
doesn't know about women I know about
women I tell you what during a monthly
cycle I would want to see a woman with a
gun in her
hands give her a gun there goes a bunch
of men look
out oh man
scary
stuff can you see George Bush George
Bush got his new secret weapon the 62nd
Airborne PMS
Sy my my my I got another idea I got
another idea how about we take all the
murderers out of prison and send them
over to fight in Saudi Arabia how that
sound that'd be quite the sight wouldn't
it okay iraqy bastard I'm going to kill
you but pick up this bar of soap first
[Applause]
cuz I'm in the Army and tonight you're
going to be all you can
[Applause]
be yes yes
yes my name is fancy way Mone I'm the
best looking man in comedy you can
travel the land you can travel the sea
but you never find com as pretty as me
with the wisdom of iide the Finesse the
clay get ready to party with fancy Ray
yes yes thank you my my my my my yes
what a swinger what a Binger what
AER oh shut up now I have the best
looking man in comedy we got a fantastic
show here tonight say Ray excuse me a
minute could I ask you for a little help
we're taping a show right now I know but
you know so much about women oh maybe I
can help you then maybe I can help you
yeah well you see I've been trying to
find out I read all the books that come
out I I got this book how to flirt say
the best place to meet somebody to flirt
with is the supermarket or if you're in
a big hurry the
sa and I've been practicing all the
flirting techniques and a mannequin over
at Carson
period was going pretty well for a while
then she ditched me for a
torso but I wanted to ask you now
suppose a guy like me met a very sweet
very pretty woman what would you say to
a woman with a real nice baby face
[Music]
baby
babyy you got the cutest little baby
face there's not another who could take
take your place baby
bab myor heart is up you should have
started something baby
bab I'm up in heaven when I'm me your f
inra
I didn't need a sh I just fell in love
with your pretty
[Music]
baby thank
you yeah you know that's really catchy I
think that that could work for me
suppose I got a date with this girl now
where would I take her to a French
restaurant Italian restaurant McDonald's
I mean what should we eat
[Music]
neckbone
turn
snake
[Music]
good C bread
all right
thank thank you you're welcome you're
welcome all right I hope that help you I
hope they help with your problem I think
so all right we got a fantastic show
here tonight we're going to talk about
rock and rolls earli years with a man
that's a rock historian Dell Roberts is
here
tonight all
right also comedian extraordinaire Dean
Johnson is here tonight
and also we're going to have a trivia
contest we're going to give away three
hair does by the man that Styles my hair
a bra Hair Designs by Tas so get your
pens and pencils ready and stay tuned oh
yeah I'mma slip out and I come back in
I'll be in something a bit more fancy so
stay tuned cuz I'm fancy r m i the best
look man in comedy and tonight it's time
to
get stay
[Applause]
tuned hi I'm Mr T now I know a lot of
you out there are saying hey if you Mr T
how come you so wimpy and small well
that's because I went on opal win's diet
program so if you spread some rumors
about me I'll rip your lips off put them
on my bike and use them as brake pads
but the real reason why I came down here
today is to give a very special message
to all the little boys and girls out
there that's using drugs your punks your
sissies your fools you walk around here
saying you want to be like me Mr T well
let me tell you something I've used
drugs I've used a lot of drugs in fact I
use them all at once that's right Mr T
is used cocaine novacain LSD DDT and the
worst one of them all crackle and I'm
living proof that drugs can mess up your
body just look at my hair you think I
get my haircut like this no drugs did
this to me and one more thing I've been
hearing a lot of you kids walk around
here wearing gold chains calling Mr T
starter kits that stuff makes me mad
because for a long time my mind was so
messed up on drugs I didn't know I was
wearing gold chains I thought I had on
one big neck tie so don't be a fool be
cool leave them drugs alone take it from
me Mr
T ladies and gentlemen once again fancy
Ray
[Applause]
mclone my my my my my my my some people
think I'm a prophet other think I'm a
clown I'm fany mown the best looking man
in town please keep it quiet now we got
a fantastic show we're going to talk
about rock and roll's early years with a
fantastic man in fact first of all we're
going to show a clip of a man who many
people consider to be the king of rock
and roll let's take a quick peek at
Elvis Presley we'll be right back ow
[Applause]
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
yes all right thank you welcome back
here to talk about the early years of
rock and roll rock historian Dale
Roberts give Dale a round of applause to
see you again I called you a rock
historian but you're a DJ music business
but over a quarter of a century now and
fan and fan no it actually goes back
about uh to 1955 so we're looking at
about 35 years wow that's a long time
and as a matter of fact unlike a lot of
people I remember the first day I heard
my first rock and roll record Rock
Around the Clock in the movie Blackboard
Jungle the cedar theater on Cedar Avenue
and I told a friend of mine I said
something's going on here and we stayed
to hear the music again at the end of
the show I went home bought a copy of
the record and I used to have to listen
to the radio under the pillow and
covers and one night I fell sleep and
the radio melted because I had tubes in
them back then so I could listen to this
rock and roll music cuz my parents uh
were concerned about listening to that
kind of music and what it do to me in
fact speaking of that kind of music that
brings a point was at this rock and roll
where does Rock and Roll come from well
the earliest thing I remember hearing
rock and roll in the Twin Cities was a
fellow named Augie Garcia and uh I used
to when I was 10 11 12 years old I was
almost six foot tall I mean I was a big
kid and I used to pretend I was shining
shoes to get into the clubs to hear
these great musicians and it goes back
to guys like Augie Garcia and some of
the R&B clubs in town down on nicholet
Avenue and it evolved out of country
western and of course R&B kind of all of
it came together and to get into the
Rock and Roll But rock and roll when you
ask someone what rock and roll is I also
have to think of n King Cole oh yeah n
Kingo no I knew you'd raise a question
that net King Co let us refer no no no
no bite let us refer to the KDWB survey
chart of December 15th 1962 okay uh you
look at the chart number 15 is dear
Lonely Hearts by n King Cole that's what
the rock and roll stations were playing
uh above that we have Brenda Lee on this
chart we also have some uh Johnny
Crawford from Rifleman had a hit
household word trade Martin with his hit
record also you have Hank Snow oh yeah
had a very famous Hank Snow we know Hank
Snow you're a big country fan and Mark
Valentino but this was actually what we
were listening to on rock and roll radio
we had to listen Listen to Hank Snow Al
Martino Louis Armstrong and Nat King
Cole to get to the Buddy Holly and
Everly Brothers music like that AB back
in the 50s now you said you heard at the
SE theater did you slick your hair back
and put the pador up and everything well
I used to put on my industrial strength
Old
Spice I had a barrel of it at home and
we'd get out the uh uh the gels for the
hair and the Vitalis or Brill cream
little dab won't do you because we we
put on so much that it stained the
pillowcases and our mothers go crazy
with this stuff and we could go out a 90
mph wind from behind and your hair
didn't move it was great that's cool
tell me something now we show a little
clip of Elvis now I know you would know
this D is Elvis alive or not is Elvis
alive everyone is holding their breath
he's in the audience he's in the
audience you know what I'm talking about
I know what you're he's in the audience
and it took more than two hands to hold
handle a Whopper with El was to that's
right well that that that just goes to
show the Nostalgia of this music that
are we we can't let these Rock Heroes
die we we want to hold on to this past
for some reason well the music does uh
what's interesting is with kids uh I
watch the New Kids on the Block and I
see and hear the Osman or even a young
Michael Jackson maybe that's why I don't
like them
know and when I watch prince I'm sitting
there I'm saying look there's Little
Richard there's Jackie Wilson there's uh
also uh some of the moves are even
people like Bo diddly people like
I mean Prince is not new I hope I'm not
offing anybody but I have seen all of
that yeah in fact I saw Prince downtown
one day and I said hi to him princ look
look at me and I said you ain't nothing
but Little Richard baby that's right he
stop I said oh shut up he kept walking
that's I mean we've seen it all before
all before ain't nothing new Under the
Sun I tell you what coming up next we
got a PSA stay tun we going talk about
more of these rock and roll artist with
Roberts stay tuned we'll be right backs
[Music]
hurt injured in an auto
accident
lonely d 1 900 law
date I specialize in auto accidents
personal injury cases and more dial 1
900 law date first I'll take care of
your case then I'll take care of you one
900 law
date all right thank you thank you
welcome back we're once again here with
mic music DJ historian Dale Roberts now
Dale somebody you just told me about it
know is that you're you're a a jockey at
Canterbury Downs well that was my last
job I
get and uh before that I was taking
lessons for break dancing and the
student loan ran
out so that was into that you know we
haven't had this much fun since
we haven't had this much fun since you
and I went to that twins convention
remember were twins you and I went there
we had them all confused that was that
was fun I tell you man people can't do
people come up to you all time say you
look like fancy Ray mclone I I know they
I tell them you know we were we actually
shut up they don't tell you
that we're talking about rock and roll U
talk about some early rock and roll
figures you know a man that I absolutely
love and I met a few times is Bo deadly
tell me about Bo I only met the guy once
uh and he's bitter that's the best way
to put it about the way he was treated
by the rock and roll industry right and
one thing about Bo dley he is just truly
one of the great pioneers he's going to
be in town uh this coming week I'm going
to see him and he puts on a great show
and I remember watching a video tape
that he was on down in Louisiana he had
70,000 people in the streets during an
event down there rocking from the front
row all the way to the back the man is
just a dynamite Entertainer but never
got his does that's true that's very
true and it's so funny that B's been
Rock and rolling for so many years and
it's not until he did his commercial
with Bo Jackson they got more
recognition that's really a shame real
quick we got to wrap up here and I I
wish we had more time who's the king of
rock and
roll well I've got to say Little Richard
and I don't say that because some
obvious reasons but
uh the first time I saw Little Richard
was down at the lon on nicholet Avenue
in Lake Street and Jimmy Hendricks was
his guitar player uh really goes back a
long way and one thing about Little
Richard uh he just captivates uh the
audience and every time I hear a rock
and roll song you here here or see
Little Richard that's that's very true
everything's just spin-off how about
Chuck Bay what's his influence Chuck is
I think even more as a writer but as
guitar also I mean in Guitar it's
everything and uh by the way Chuck
Barry's doing fine living down in
winville Missouri and he's doing just
great and the man is 65 years old hard
to believe these Rockers are really
getting on in yours and Still rocking I
have no doubt about I tell you what man
I want to see you keep on rocking I
really thank you for coming down under
such short notice thank you lot give D
Round of Applause
bra out of sight thank
you all
right coming up next is another PSA stay
tuned because we got a very funny
comedian coming up so stay tuned cuz
we're going to get down with it stay
tuned all
[Music]
right who are the people in your
neighborhood Hey look it's Saddam
Hussein
get him Mr bunny rabbit get
him hi I'm Vice President Dan quail and
I'm here to talk to you about the United
Negro College Fund because of
mind is it a terrible thing to waste I
think and and I want to tell you kids
out there to to stay in school and and
work hard cuz cuz if you stay in school
and work hard and have a rich father who
can buy your way through life you can
reach Great Heights just look at
me hey D there's going to be a
war right yes indeed welcome back coming
up next to one of the twin City's
Premier comedians he's used to host a TV
show TV personals he tours all over the
Midwest a twin City's favorite please
welcome Dean Johnson
yesan well thank you very much it sure
is nice to be here I love to do comedy
especially right here in Minneapolis
because I think Minneapolis is a big
city that has a lot of the virtues of a
small town just yesterday I was driving
up Lake Street found a place where you
can still see movies for 25
[Applause]
cents that's a nice group here I'm glad
you're laughing cuz we're living in a
crazy world it's a dangerous World they
tell you to leave a light on when you go
out of your house at night burglars
could stumble over the
furniture
suya I ate lunch in a restaurant the
other day they're so security minded all
the coat hangers are attached to a metal
pipe for security doesn't do any good
somebody took my jacket left the
hangers it's a dangerous world I opened
up a new package of razor blades inside
there was a Hershey bar
everywhere I go I see crazy things I was
up in North Dakota where the state motto
is always a place to
park stopped in a Roadside restaurant up
there true story two signs on the wall
the two signs are side by side one says
restrooms right next to it please seat
yourself this is a crazy everywhere I go
I see crazy things Minnesota State Fair
there two buildings across the street
for me other one say Firehouse beans
right across the street natural gas is
your best energy
valy oh this is f how much time have I
got left here two minutes I wanted to
explain something to you I was talking
to Dell Roberts earlier and he knows so
much about music I never knew this
before there any fans of Blues out there
Blues I've always loved the blues and I
didn't know this about it it surprised
me Dell explained to me that the blues
actually originated in ancient
Scandinavia
it was actually early
Vikings who first invented the blues and
and they they went on one of their crazy
Viking raids uh to
Chicago they taught it to people there
and then returned to Norway and Sweden
to develop that accordion
music so if you ever listen to the real
early Blues recordings you're going to
hear a lot of that old Viking influence
and just to demonstrate it sounds
something like
[Music]
[Applause]
this oh I sure do like your ludis
babe oh how you do it I just don't
know oh yeah and I'm crazy about your
lefta baby how you do it I don't know oh
but I'm really really crazy all about
your smus
[Applause]
[Music]
Bo
o thank you thank you thank you thank
you get down
withen all
right all right the
off all
right I didn't know the Blues from
Scandinavia man it's really a pleasure
and honor to have you here on the show
well it's nice to be here right this is
a this a nice
audience this is the dinki microphone
I've ever
seen that's really small it's nice to be
here though that's fantastic want me
give you a hand with the here okay help
me out all right here we go there you go
thank you R hope that's good yeah that's
Fant you got some great stuff well thank
you how long you been doing comedy for
about 10 years now wow man same jokes 10
years my ambition is eventually I figure
I'll get to the nursing home I figure
three four good jokes out of hold maybe
because nobody will remember from day to
day yeah that's really cool that's
really cool what like I you used to host
your own TV show at one time well that's
quite a while ago yeah I I was on a show
called TV personals I was hosting that
for a while and then it went immediately
off the air
oh now TV personels that's like men and
women getting together that was men and
women trying to get dates with each
other yeah all right man that's
fantastic did you ever make any of that
little babies while you on
doing no oh you're referring to the you
know the the thing is what is this
anyways well it's something I'm really
proud of because it's not that often
that a a comedian I think ever gets
asked to pose for a statue oh that's a
serious thing yeah and this is something
that means a lot to me I thought i' I'd
like to bring it out and let people have
a look at it this is the new Dean
Johnson's statue
[Applause]
[Laughter]
just something I'm kind of proud of oh
that's really cute that's really cute
you should see the statue I POS for is
that the place where you get those
quarter movies
at no that's really good that's really
now something that's really interesting
is that you come from a family of
comedians your girlfriend's a comedian
who's Denise dely hope that's I'm I can
say that we're going to get married oh
is that right congratulations all right
all right thank you right I'm getting
married too are you yeah have you told
anybody about it yet or well I'm going
to marry
myself for real my mom thinks I'm
perfect for myself so no but and also
your brother-in-law who's Paul Diller is
a wellknown comedian very well known
that's fantastic man so you guys just
kind of spread that the comedian all the
way and Grandma will be doing comedy
pretty soon that's right that's really
cool that's really cool what's the
biggest Joy about doing comedy the
biggest Joy of doing I think it's If
people really seem happy about it then
you you feel good about it especially if
you get paid oh man that's the truth but
yeah no it is a great thing you know if
you feel like somebody was a felt a
little better after you got through
telling your jokes it's great all right
well keep up the great stuff we got more
Dean later on the show so stay tuned CU
we're going to get down with it coming
up next cablecast schedule find your
station and your time and get down with
it thanks Dean all right thank you all
right yes yes yes
[Music]
all right all right yes yes yes yes yes
my my my my my thank you welcome back
thank you we had a fantastic show here I
want to take an opportunity now to give
away three 25 gift certificates to abraa
Hair Designs by TZ which Styles my
fantastic beautiful hair dude the
question is this what famous black
scientist was famous for inventing the
peanut back in the early 1800s if I
answer this question we going to give
away three question three pair of gifts
tis to a hair designs by Taz the number
is 377 4221 377 4221 get your hair style
and you can look almost as good as me
shut up that's
impossible all right I want to take this
opportunity to thank my my sponsors I
want to thank a braa hair designs don't
think Insight newspaper for which you
find our cablecast schedule also Pizza
Hut pizza give them a round of applause
yes my guests Dale Roberts and Dean
Johnson give them a round of applause
yes my fantastic crew Ed HS and all the
rest give them a round of applause and
give yourselves a round of applause yes
yes you all
right and a few very special people I
want thank the royalty my valet Chris
Patrick for coming down thanks my mom
for providing Security today thank you
all
right taking us home singing R whiskey
the outstanding Dean Johnson my name is
fcy tune in next week and get down with
it I be cool y ever do
I'm trying to get more country music
into comedy because there's quite a bit
of comedy and country music and so I got
a this an old
song called RI whiskey R whiskey R
whiskey R whiskey I cry if I don't get
Ry whiskey I surely will die her parents
don't like me they say I'm too poor they
told me never dark in their door if a
parents don't like me my money is my own
them I don't like he can leave me
[Music]
alone
W if the ocean was whiskey and I was a
duck I'd dive to the bottom never come
off while the ocean ain't whiskey and I
ain't no duck I play jack of diamonds
I'll Trust to my luck are
[Music]
[Applause]