do
the come on
baby watch
everybody I said come on
baby want everybody do the
J I said come on
baby it's been a long long
[Music]
time ah hello this is fancy Ray mclone
the chocolate Christmas
[Music]
tree I'm having a great time I'm all
ready for the holidays I got everything
that I need I've got the royalty mhm
I've got my poin cetta m oh of course
the eggnog
M and T where's my
mirror it does feel like the
holidays tonight we've got a fantastic
show from the Minneapolis gospel SS we
got Eddie Robinson country music record
artist Sherwin Linton the lovely Lio
sisters and from the bees we got Curtis
OA so tonight we going to have a fancy
show a happy holiday show so stay tuned
cuz I'm fancy Ray and it's time to to
get down with
it oo it does feel like the holidays it
[Laughter]
[Music]
does it's the exciting new Daredevil
trick track with the incredible dolphin
racer gear driven for longer battery
life Daredevil trick Track full of
fantastic tricks a sensational new
steering track Daredevil trick track
from
transogram where the fun comes
wow all right welcome back to get down
with a special holiday edition coming up
first te is one of my personal favorites
one of my favorites too shut up I said
that I just love this guy he is one of
the Premier gospel vocalists throughout
the entire nation he's from the
Minneapolis gospel sounds and his name
is Eddie Robinson he is a great t you
can catch him every Sunday at the F line
for Sunday brunch so without further Ado
ladies and gentlemen here goes Eddie
[Music]
Robinson is
this who
lay to
rest on
Mary's
La is sleeping
whom
Angels
greet with
an them
sweet while
sheers
[Music]
watch
this
this is
Christ the
King whom
sheepers
guard
and
Angels
Sing
[Applause]
Hast
H to
bring him
Lord the
babe the
son of men
[Music]
for
this this is
Christ the
King whom
she
watch
and
Angels
Sing
[Applause]
H
H to breing
him
Lord the
babe the
[Music]
[Applause]
son all right that was Eddie Robinson
don't go nowhere CA Eddie's gonna be
back a little later on in the show oh
yes my my fancy yes why do you have
those shades on oh cuz you know who's
coming on next to next we've got the
lovely Lio with sister oh yeah yeah and
you know what T there's three of them oh
yeah you know what that means mhm that
means one for me mhm and another one for
me mhm and uh the third one for
[Laughter]
me I don't think that's very funny oh
wait a minute it is the holiday season
I'll share you get what's left
I'll fix
you no don't play that song don't play
that song man you know what happens when
I hear that song man what you
[Music]
don't Frosty the
Snowman stop the
[Music]
music don't play that song
I ain't got no energy coming up next the
lovely Lia with
sisters
love so the two of us can get together
there's sweeter
or when it's and c I can hold my baby
closer to me and collect the kisses that
I the winter
weather love keep warm oh the WEA
outside is but myar so delightful and
there's no place to go let it let it let
it it does of and I corn foring the
lights are turn way down low let it s
let it s let it
[Music]
when we finally say good night how I
hate going out in the storm but if you
really hold me
TI all the way
I'll isow dying and still goodby but as
you
love let it sow let it sow let it sow I
love wi win WEA
[Music]
the weather outside WEA outside is cold
oh the weather outside is
my de
[Music]
isight and there's
to let us let us let us let
us us let
[Music]
us that's as sweet as lewood sisters
coming up next in our holiday special
treat we have country music recording
artist Sherin Linton Sheran was twice
nominated for Country musician of the
year he is one of my personal favorites
so let's take a little peek at Sherwin
and guess what I think we're going to
get surprise visitor so stay tuned and
get down with
[Music]
it Santa a
DWI we around in
the believe me I wouldn't
lie I got a D
s we around in
[Music]
the
everybody we around in
the me I wouldn't lie wo Santa got a
D yeah yes s got
d w s got
D
yes
d s
[Applause]
d Merry
Christmas I want you all to know one
thing I'm the best looking man on the
North
Pole shut up oh oh I came down to see
fancy race he's not here right now is
any little boys and girls out there like
any presents
oh what can I get for you young man I
like a um stereo no make that a CD and I
want the GI Joe kit and I want the GI
Joe man I want the Batman car and I want
the Batman back cave and I want well you
I tell you I tell you what you be a good
kid and get the hell out of here
who's next Who's
Next what can Santa good for you young
man what what would you like from Santa
what would you like from
Santa well I tell you what you be a good
boy and Santa will give you all your
presents
oh some liage
oh oh oh oh who's next who's next
Santa's got something he like to give
you well all your dreams will come
true well thank you I got to go it's not
SL time you mind your parents and be
very good and I'll see you December 25th
oh oh oh oh oh good night straight hello
this is fancy R MC reminding you let's
remember those who are less fortunate
than us during this holiday season
Christmas is a time of giving so let's
give from our hearts merry Christmas
happy New Year fancy R go straight to
the
ghetto Fancy Fancy Fancy wake up I have
something for you wake up wake up wait a
minute wait a minute I'm in my beauty
sleep wait wait wait fancy fancy Santa
left something for you Santa was here
Santa you left something for me
something for you well that's it's says
G that could be for me yeah cuz I'm good
no I'm not just good I'm great I'm super
great I'm gantu hey look at me saying
he's
goofy no I'm much too glamorous glorious
and Gul for that you know how did that
it was graceful gee that's me what does
it say it says get down with it to all
the fans that get down with it I guess
that means them all of them out there
watching get down with it to all the
fans of get down with it from Santa I
tell you what T let's take a look what's
inside
to all the fans of get down with it
Merry
Christmas s about Joe Frasier CH Larry
Holmes I'm still fast and pretty you
look at this suit you know I'm pretty
but I want to congratulate the greatest
of all times next to me that's fancy Ray
three times world champion in Cable
cable access 3E anniversary he's so
pretty not as pretty as me but he's
still very pretty the greatest Of All
Times all right yes indeed my name is
fancy R MCL I am the best looking man in
comedy you can travel the land you can
travel the sea but you never find a
comedian as pretty as me with the wisdom
of Einstein the Finesse to Clay get
ready to party with fancy
Ray oh yes yes yes yes yes do people
come up to you all time so you look like
fancy Ray mclone I I know they I tell
them you know we were we actually shut
up they don't tell you that
I can't even say I am the most try say
with me let's try come on let's get come
go okay I no no first just say say I
look good shut up okay I look good shut
up please please please and untied the
Rope I have an apple here and I know how
to use it you'll feel like a pig on a
spit oh man you must know what I
[Applause]
like why you ever pretty good sense of
current events oh yeah that's me you
have a lot of sympathy oh you understand
the motives of people well oh I sure do
but you're not very swaave and polite it
says you're deficient on that is that
what the hell does that mean talk about
the AIDS now sure I think I was probably
exposed to the virus and about 1982
which is kind of ironic because I had
run for office and lost and was
personally bummed out and frankly using
too many chemicals and just being in a
down period like how did you guys get
involved with prostitution I mean little
girls don't grow up and say one day want
to be a prostitute how did that happen I
met a girl and she said oh I know where
you can make tons of money and how many
people here practice safe sex how you
prfe all right I'll tell you what we got
right here I got my AE jacket and I want
you all to PR safe and have a good night
practice safe sex practice safe sex we
get to share in a lot of things and uh
it's it's a lot of fun what we do well
allow me to say man you guys are doing
great and congratulations to continued
success into the '90s I I don't do no
Dam no no just try one time one more
time Kirby why you get Herby or
something come on just try like
that come on Kirby Kirby buing y'all did
James Brown ever record a record with
the Chipmucks
what if he did record a record with the
chip I
just satisfy
[Music]
your when you get me
no what you give me no why you give me
keep it around that what is the mistake
what is going on here I am fancy Ray
mclone you're Prince you're Prince
you're
Prince oh oh you're friends so I just
love you oh Prince you're Prince oh I
don't know if you could ever like
someone like me cuz I'm not Kim
Bassinger aalon I'm not even
Appalachia I just love you I just love
you
[Applause]
stay tuned and get down with it stay
tuned and get down with it go one time
go shut
up here in the Twin Cities Academy Award
night is more than just a television
event
hello my name is f m I am the best
looking man in
comedy this is the fifth year of the
cricket theater in Minneapolis has held
an Academy Awards benefit restaurants
donate food and businesses donate
beverages all proceeds benefit four area
projects to help people living with
[Applause]
AIDS what are we doing here you slow it
[Music]
[Applause]
down all right
looking good shut up now please I'm the
best looking man in County you are see
he says the best looking man in comedy
he's no shrinking Vi at this fancy Ray
mclone whether you've run into him on
the streets of the Twin Cities or on the
television screen you're not likely to
have forgotten the experience and he's
moved from local cable to National
exposure on shows like the Jenny Jones
show my first guest says says he's got
the hottest entertainment show in
[Music]
do
that and I am the best looking man in
County I am the best I'm the most
flamboyant I am the most outrageous I am
the best my my my my my my
my shut up
now fancy check this out man what is it
it's a musical Christmas C really what
does it do watch I know that song do you
yeah check this out this is a rap
version jingle bound jingle bells jingle
all the way Batman smell we can go to
hell oh man put that away man I don't
like that at all let's put on someone
who really can sing Eddie Robinson from
the Minneapolis gospel sounds T tell him
to stay tuned and get down with it stay
tuned shut up I'd rather say it myself
stay tuned and get down with
it let me check that out man
Eddie God Rest Ye Merry
Gentlemen let nothing you
dismay remember Christ Our
Savior was born on Christmas
day to save us all from Satan's power
when we are gone
astray oh
Tidings of Comfort
and
joy comfort and
joy Tidings of Comfort and
Joy from God our heavenly
father the blessed angel
came and unto Ser 10
Shepherds brought Tidings of the same
this holy time of
Christmas each other now
Embrace oh
Tidings of Comfort and
Joy comfort and
joy Tiding love comfort and
joy oh
Tidings of comfort and
joy comfort and joy
[Music]
tiing
joy I have really enjoyed our holiday
show have you enjoyed a tea yes indeed I
know y'all enjoyed it cuz y'all looking
at
me before we go tonight I would like to
treat you all to my holiday story
presented in rhyme T may have the
book this was the Night Before Christmas
adaptation by fancy Ray this was a night
before Christmas and all through the
house not a soul was stirring not even a
mouse the chitlins and Cornbread were
prepared with care and hopes the black s
Nick would soon be there up on the the
roof I heard something kind of funny and
down the chimney came three gorgeous
Playboy bunnies then came Santa he was
moving kind of slow I said how do you
pay these women you don't make much do
he said they paid me they're my ho ho
hoes my my my my before we go any
further I want thank my fantastic
sponsors I want thank Insight newspaper
we find our cable cast schedule here by
J check out this hair D located on West
Broadway in North Minneapolis squeaky
miss an Lorenzo fantastic happy New Year
also variety Beauty Supply home of
luster silk three locations to serve you
I want to thank my fantastic crew Greg
Cassidy Royal T Keith hedgcock and all
you people out there for your support
friends family I love you and I just
keep pushing and working for you you
guys are fantastic taking us home we got
Curtis Oba from the
butan had a great show we've had a great
year I hope you've enjoyed it tune in
next week next year and get down with it
happy New Year fancy
[Music]
[Applause]
Ray man
hey Merry Christmas
baby honey you know you show it Treat Me
Nice
yeah I said
everywhere Merry Christmas
baby honey you know you show it Treat Me
Nice yeah you know you bought me a
diamond ring for
Christmas Lord now I feel like I've been
living in Paradise