the contest
is not
important it is too many Comics think
that their self-worth as a human
being is wrapped up in the
contest that's not true at all has
nothing to do with the contest the
contest is not important and it doesn't
matter however the contest is very
important and it matters quite a bit
for
[Music]
you like
comedy I've been trying to get in better
shape I've been riding my bicycle my
favorite thing about riding my bicycle
is going uphill more you ride your
bicycle up hill the more reasonable gas
pric is good I've been walking too I
remember you favorite thing about
walking is getting somewhere anywhere
it's great man I was think what would
Jesus do if he were a alive today would
he walk would he ride a bicycle I like
to think he'd be pimping in a g5j
freaking Jesus I
me have you seen that movie with the
Josh Brolin his W or whatever George
Bush or whatever and he's like George B
say he's never going to let anybody out
text his name I'm like I'm not going to
let any comic out weed me you know I'm
make sure I got that taking care of this
is uh ATX flashmob comedy #x flashmob
comedy you should do it in every town
you're in live entertainment is dying we
are losing a corporate battle to our
minds we need to get out there and reach
the people one-on-one Grassroots that's
what I think
so and what better way to do it than a
bunch of people trapped on a train my
daughter she's a baller she's out at a
bass trop high school she's beautiful if
you're a little bit older I'd tell you
her name uh she's 5' 11 she's a all def
Defensive Player of the Year her biggest
Rivals the huto lady
hippos I always thought that was a
rudest name for a girl's basketball team
I mean how dare they so I went to a game
it was very appropriate it made a lot of
sense we're trying to promote Austin
comedy we're trying to tell people about
our funny people are in town they should
that something's going on here they
should be aware of it that's all we're
trying to do I got in comedy by accident
literally um uh I never thought I'd be
in comedy I never I'm I'm 45 years old I
I never thought I'd doing this stuff uh
was if you talked to me May 20 or
Christmas in
2007 we wouldn't be talking about comedy
maybe about movies I watched and stuff
but uh I I got in this accident with my
wife and uh uh it was just she got hurt
real bad and uh and we were in this
awful situation and I had to take care
of her at home for like years and years
and I had her in my kitchen and she uh
had a tracho me and uh I would write
these stories uh uh these science
fiction type stories where I'd pretend
like I was mcgomery Wayne my given name
it's the cosmic Cowboy I go off into
space and I take a lot of drugs
and so believe it or not I used to be
happier than I am right now May 24th
2008 I was the happiest guy you ever met
and my lovely beautiful wife was driving
that road and there some stupid old lady
just ran into her [ __ ] ruined my life
left her mentally conscious man she's
here but she's not here we're
spiritually connected but we're not
physically not emotionally so hard I'm
so lonely trying to meet somebody you
know and I I don't know what to do I
don't have much to offer man man but I
do have some attributes y'all um I'm
adorable I'm honest I've had a bisectomy
I'm somewhat
domesticated you take me home I won't
pee in your house but I'll probably piss
in your front
yard best thing about me man you run out
of weed I'm going to leave
[Applause]
momy Wayne
everybody oh we're going to have a good
show guys my name is Avery Moore this is
the late slot it's my favorite thing
welcome to my favorite
thing
w we do it every Friday it's so good I
love it I'm just just dripping wet over
here I moved from San Antonio to tell
jokes I moved to aus to tell jokes um I
left a very comfortable job as a props
mistress and an actress at like a
nationally credited Children's Theater
so I had a career in children's theater
that was like done and I was fine and I
could have just done that my whole life
and I said no let's move to Austin and
be porn so I can tell jokes I'm very
very nervous
look how handsome he
is a little
Mory it's sold out and they only left 30
seats open but they're at the front of
the line so he should be able to get
in I hope they let me bring Jackson
in thank you
so so he expect other people
to Hi how are you how are you did you
survive yesterday I
did hi I'm Avery Avery Avery nice
opening as well nice to meet you nice to
meet you that's it Angela Reed she's
probably
over ladies and Gentlemen please welcome
Avery Moore to the
St howy
[Applause]
y'all how is everyone moon tower
baby all right do you guys like pop
country
[Music]
music
um I listen to it every day on the radio
it's what keeps the gun in the drawer
um I heard this new single though it's
called dirt road uh
obviously um and I just I hope you like
it so here it
goes you chilling on a dirt road you got
a beer in the
console you got your jeans painted on in
your hair in the wind you've got a
sidekick named Fred and he is a frog and
you riding down the dirt
road you got a beer in the
console and the sky opens up up and hey
it's God he says son you're the second
coming of Christ
Christ you say Okay God I'm going to
start a war I'm going to kill everyone
not deserving of Your Love cuz you
riding down a dirt
road you got a beer in the
console and you head up the hill and you
look out the window and man when I
looked out the window I saw some
commotion going on turned out I'd stumbl
upon an archaeological dig I turn to my
friend Fred my girl say hey why don't
you slide those sweet asses out those
vinyl bucket seats let's go check it out
we H out the truck turns out DAV
uncovered a Bible printed on Papyrus
that predates all other religious
text did you know that 666 the Number
commonly referred to is the mark of the
beast is actually
61 six
and you riding down the dirt
road thank you so much
[Applause]
guys I couldn't hear out
there thanks so much thank you
[Laughter]
I'm from
Detroit we don't have cute nicknames for
mental illness all
right either you is
crazy or you crazy than the [ __ ]
like we don't even need to bring WebMD
into
this my background is very different
from a lot of comics you know a lot of
these people grew up with like houses
where people didn't get shot on a
regular basis you know or they grew up
in the suburbs and that's foreign to me
you know I like to hear about them and
they dog and soccer games when they was
a kid I don't know nothing about that
being a part of the Austin comedy scene
I was very reluctant for a while I was
like I have nothing in common with these
people I would not drink with none of
these people I wouldn't even do drugs
with none of these people however I have
grown to love these people and I have a
lot of respect and I feel like I bring
something a little little different um I
bring my Detroit flavor I bring my
street knowledge to the game you know
all that stuff cuz I want to be famous
not really because I want to be rich I
just want some better food to
eat like my idea of making it is to be
able to drive down I35 with a plate of
steaks in the passenger seat just biting
the [ __ ] out of them and just tossing
Them Holes out the window like
yeah the de is nothing
it's just a Lie perpetuated by the
Illuminati no I got I got to go straight
[Applause]
8 a fun fun night it's the blue moon
show and let's get started right away
have a huge round of applause for
everyone's favorite host at MC satany
[Applause]
Austin Texas how the hell are you
huh all right hey you guys having a
great Festival so far
huh nice it's been a great week I know
it was a couple of days ago but uh who
had a nice 420
huh yeah one of my favorite holidays of
course my favorite holidays have to be
Easter only I celebrated the Friday
before you know what I'm saying
Good Friday are you kidding me that was
a great
Friday I started doing comedy when I was
36 uh it was it was right after uh 911
uh I'll never forget it was uh sorry
when I started doing comedy I already
had a bunch of [ __ ] going on in my life
I responsibilities I mean you I was
married had a full
job um you know a wife who was sitting
at home alone while I'm wanting to go
out gallivanting around getting drunk
with my friends telling jokes on stage
uh the only way to get better at standup
comedy is to do it and the only way to
do it is to go out in the evenings and
go to Rooms where they have stand up
comedy and get on that stage and and
tell jokes to people it's fine when
you're young and you can take that risk
on your own it's a little bit different
when you're asking a wife who had no
idea that you wanted to be a comedian
when she married you and all of a sudden
is trying to be supportive for this new
hobby that you found that it's costing
an increasing amount of money and taking
you away from her a whole lot um that
can be that it can be stressful so I got
one for you Norm okay okay here we go
can't wait Norm Wilkerson is a racist
neighbor living in Austin
[Laughter]
Texas Norm is like if your uncle got a
divorce did comedy despite everyone
around
him the Austin Chronicles set of Norm he
should have a better job for being a
part-time
comedian you would think he would have a
better job especially for his
age Norm looks like an environmentalist
that let himself go Norm will be
performing at this year's Festival as
long as his cancer stays in
remission wow that's so good yeah you
don't try to make these real at all dude
yeah I'm started a started a new job
what is it I work with Dustin though I
work at Quality Seafood oh
start he Big Sean you want to be on TV I
do uh I do have a day job right now and
a lot of times I go from work right to a
comedy show which is weird you know a
lot of weird nervous energy it's like
hey Danny how do you like to relax well
after a long day work I like to grab a
nice cold drink and then uh go give a
speech that's right after eight hours
and my feet hurt I like to get a
microphone stand in front of some bright
lights and then gamble with my own
confidence I just wanted to do something
I didn't realize it was stand up at the
time I was doing like a lot of writing
it just kind of LED to stand up that was
the easiest thing to do it's like you
can just get up on stage I moved to
Austin because I was very unhappy in
Pittsburgh which is the the way the
scene was and the the the quality of the
stage time was in loud bars and just you
know I felt like I did most of what I
could there which is like host somewhat
feature at the club did morning radio
that was kind of a goal and a friend of
mine John Evans also comic who spent a
lot of time in Austin said you probably
do really great here and uh came to
visit for like
like six days and then I was like oh
yeah I want to live
here it only took five of us to move it
took one
hour and it's done I mean like even the
unpacking this is the hardest part and
all I'm doing is talking and taking pots
out um this has been like the week from
this is an eventful week you caught me
in a good week like these are for my
first
wedding I bring them with me for every
divorce uh they always come with
me for Christmas my wife divorced me uh
it's okay she thought she bought a man
and then the warranty expired and now
I'm at a garage
sale wiggle wiggle wiggle and open your
mouth really
wide that's a great POS I'll go with
this are you a duck can you crack back a
duck we're little ducks no no she's too
smart for that Texas trans mom feeds
sugar to babies I was you are getting
put in jail how can you live this long
and not know this about yourself I
remember before I even came out um at
large I was kind of out to a small group
of people um I was talking to another
comic in town and he said both the
simultaneously most awful and and
coolest thing anybody had said to me
he's like this is going to be great for
your comedy career and it's true I feel
guilty but it's true like all of a
sudden I'm a something you know like
when you book me or when you put me on
stage you know okay we're going to have
a trans comic you know and I feel like I
know enough about what I'm doing that
I'm more than that like I'm also funny
maybe sometimes but at least the hook is
something that I can bring to the table
that I couldn't as just another dude
with a beard and plaid
shirt don't worry I'm
normal I've got two kids at home under
the age of three that's uh why I look
like this even though I'm
17 I'm joking the parenting is not that
hard I mean some of you parents out here
anybody parent all right we got one hi
you and me babe Tuesday
night we did it we got out of the
house this will be my fourth time doing
the contest and my first time as a woman
it feels like my rookie
year yes it does now I have a new
dilemma um how many jokes do I do about
being trans do I do five minutes or six
minutes of that do I do one opener to
break the ice and then jump into other
stuff can I even write any other stuff
anymore I'm not sure I haven't been able
to so far part of me just wants to go
for it and just talk about being trans
the whole time because let's face it
it's interesting and that gets me
halfway there to being funny the comics
that change me when I watch them On
Stage are the people that are being so
wholly the elves and human that you go
oh I've had that moment before oh I get
that I love having all the jokes and the
weird stories in between but I love
those you know even in an hour set just
two or three moments where you go well
that was really real and I get that
thank you very
much my name is Danny I grew up in
Pittsburgh Pennsylvania which that is
the appropriate
response let's all have a moment of
silence for that dying
Town Pittsburgh where pollution is a
part of our Rich
history people there aren't screwing
around and people there will litter and
make eye contact with
you what do you think about that [ __ ]
huh yeah it wasn't great I did not have
fun doing the contest last year or the
year before I think this is the year I
start having fun doing it though because
I just don't give a [ __ ] go into it with
zero expectations that's the best way to
go into it if you think you go in I
don't know any comic who goes in
thinking they're going to win it's it's
like everyone else thinks like oh it's
so- and so's year or it's so and so's
year I don't think any comic has ever
thought this is my year I had dropped
out of college to do comedy and and I
had you know made all these big life
choices and doing making the finals was
like my the my way of saying like look
I'm doing the right thing or I must have
made the right choice if I made the
finals but man we've had some stinkers
in the finals too there's been some
terrible Comics we've made the finals
and like what is happened like who's
judging this
stuff I try to explain like like
like I I use what I call the car analogy
I don't if you're familiar with this
right like like say you've got this car
you've had this car forever but you love
this car I mean it's a it's a
comfortable car it's a reliable car and
yeah it's a sexy car right you could
never
imagine not being
satisfied with just this one car that
doesn't mean you don't want to
occasionally
you know go out and [ __ ] other
[Applause]
women I think I had a better set than at
least one of the people who advance that
night the judges are bad people let's be
very clear on this people who purport to
be able to judge
comedy bad people four to five judges
every preliminary round we just start in
February just start you know rounding up
the people that we know enjoy it and
that are good good and are unbiased
that's why the prelims are so tough
because the judges don't know a lot
about comedy they
have uh they their senses of humor
aren't the kind of sense of humor that
drives the scene and they see something
they don't like even though it's funny
it's it might not Advance because they
didn't like it well that P that comic
worked a little dirty why the [ __ ] are
you judging I have worked all of them
every one every single one for the last
20 years like people are excited to come
in for the to judge the semi-finals and
the finals The Comedy Central and Talon
Agents from Los Angeles and San
Francisco it's just it's a big deal it's
uh potentially life-changing for not
just the winner but for all of the
finalists got me uh Comedy Central you
know like cuz I got in front of people
from Comedy Central they got me uh Last
Comic Standing it helped in many
ways got stuck taking my niece to the
park we weren't even there for 5 minutes
and she was already whining about being
always a duck and never a goose I told
her it's that kind of bitching that's
going to make you always a
bridesmaid so like he obviously really
deserved to win this the competition so
there are some people that I saw this
year in the three nights of prel
preliminaries that I did who I'm like
they could win it's exciting I don't
know they showcase Talent uh they bring
new people that like cap City's probably
never seen before and all sudden they're
like wow that person's phenomenal it's a
really cool thing for Cap City to have
and it's brings in people like me
getting to watch new comedians I've
never seen so yeah in no way would I say
anything negative about a competition
last year for for the contest my odds
are pretty good I got in third place out
of 200 Comics so this year you know I
would like to hopefully win I mean but
I'm not going to hold my breath it's
been 30 years and ain't nobody black won
so and it's been what 12 since a woman
won so it's been a minute you know I I
could hope but I'm I'm cautiously
optimistic but that's just how it is
like it's hard to say that that's just
how it is um and we shouldn't accept
that but I do feel that it's a high time
that a woman wins and not like it's our
time we deserve it
but a many women have deserved it you're
the last woman that's won the contest
why do you
think it's it's been almost 15 years
since another woman has won do you think
it's just chance for a long time there
weren't a lot of women Comics here I
think that it's only been the past maybe
like three or four years where there's
has have been more women Comics here who
who are also funny like it hasn't just
been an increase in numbers like it's
also those women are really funny
there's a lot of funny people in this
town to try and be the funniest person
in this town officially with the stats
and documented it's a special thing so I
I it's I'm embracing it more and more I
think the contest is a good stepping
stone because it's very rare that in
like your first year doing comedy you
get to like open at a comedy club like
you wouldn't get to do that if I had
started in I wouldn't get to do that if
I started in like LA or New York it was
the most fun show I'd ever done like I'd
never performed for that many people and
the crowds were awesome and I felt like
I got to see all the comics do great and
it made me really glad I'd move here it
was really fun
adrenaline just the the that first night
you want to make it to the next round
and then round after round you want to
keep going so it's like you want to
change your material but you don't want
to you know and no matter what you do
during the day the only thing you're
thinking about is that night all week
like oh man I can't 7:30 here it
is it's kind of the worst thing that
could possibly happen for me happened
which is that I'm on the first night
April 6th and today is April 1 so um
every other year I've done this I've
been somewhere in the middle and there
were 14 nights this year so like the
odds of drawing the first night were
really low and I was just sort of
counting on having a week or two to pull
my set together at some open mics and
now I've got five days four of which are
booked up with things that are not
working on Comedy part of me just wants
to write this year off now like um I'm
going to get up there I'm going to
perform um as a woman for the first time
and that'll be
fun
but as far as like getting somewhere in
the contest the likelihood of me getting
through to the semifinals and there's
some good people on my night too um I'm
not going to get I'm not going to name
names because that's a good way to sound
stupid later but uh yeah there's some
good people on my night
I I just think uh I I want to write it
off I don't want to be that negative but
just my expectations are definitely
lower now that I know I'm going to go
right away and I don't feel prepared so
that's where my head is
[Music]
at you ever spit a lugie in your hair
I've done that before I don't think you
want to get it cut off half remember
somebody telling me to like Pat it on
instead of rubbing it on so I just slap
the [ __ ] out of myself when I'm putting
makeup on I don't know if that's what
you're supposed to do or if I'm just
like punishing myself I have to wear
this stuff that makes my skin look green
because it's the only thing strong
enough to cover up my stubble it's
actually tattoo cover up like if you
work at Denny's but you got that face
tattoo in prison this is like how you'd
get rid of
it we're in ausome Texas by 183 in
Anderson Square not enough food trucks
y'all until some
comedy you think you wouldn't be nervous
by your fourth
[Music]
time oh I'm real happy got some jokes I
don't even know if they're going to work
try them out uh half the stuff is stuff
that I've definitely never done here as
a contest
before um we'll see excited most prelims
though there's only good three sets you
know sometimes there's a fourth good set
and it's a little bit agonizing but the
prelims are pretty obvious and then just
every once in a while someone will make
a wacky decision and everybody gets all
up in arms lucky number
13 woohoo from what I've been told you
don't want to be first or last but other
than that I don't
know do you have people coming to watch
you
supposedly uh actually have there's
people that want to see my com these
days not family and friends but the rest
of them
we
go you fired up
[Music]
here we are at the
beautiful newly
signag Still Still new to me
[Music]
anyway hey hey oh I was kind of hoping
to be very first really
yeah why would you want them I had an
opener I had an opener I was going to do
a thing where I got up first and I said
I can't believe they didn't announce
this before me but I guess since I'm
first I have to tell you guys cap so
embarrassed that only two women have won
this contest in 30 years and that it's
been 15 years that to balance the scales
all 230 of us have to dress like
this I thought that was a great open I
can't do it halfway [ __ ] through the
lineup I it would only work if I got to
go first pretty
[Music]
good evening ladies and gentlemen and
welcome to round one of the 30th annual
funniest person in Austin contest W and
now please help me welcome to the stage
your host and MC Matt
Bearden be excited gu to be
excited oh and the Applause lasted
almost till I got to the microphone
thank you the kind of enthusiasm is good
it's good for my own personal ego I
appreciate it uh we'll move forward
ladies and gentlemen this is the very
first night of the 30th annual funny as
person and Austin contest
H There are 16 contestants tonight each
of them received 10 tickets to
distribute to their friends and family
to have them all show up this evening
and
clearly a lot of these Comics have no
friends or family so really no point my
name is Matt beard and I'll be your host
for this evening show uh I won the
contest in
1927 and since then I have gone nowhere
so it has really worked out for for me
best of luck to everyone competing this
year maybe somebody will grab the crown
this year and do the same thing I did
which is to have children and give up
um if you're competing this evening
ladies and gentlemen uh do pay attention
to the back wall there's a light that
goes on at 5 minutes to let you know you
are nearing the end of your set
generally I will tell you this uh if you
haven't been hilarious in the first
minute the judges have already
discounted you and are probably in the
back smoking cigarettes whatever it is
the judges do and other thing I let you
know is we have judges here it's an
absolute formality we decided who was
actually going to win the entire contest
earlier in the week over some drink so
this is just a way to get in your
pockets and steal your money so
woo but so far the only complaint I have
is that everybody has been so goddamn
nice I am still attracted to women on
the theory that you should only change
one team at a
time I'm uh still I'm a member of the
trans lesbian Army so I guess I consider
myself a lesbian now I don't know how do
you describe it I don't know what the
word is for it I just I'm all about that
puss about that puss no
trumpet okay that leaves a
minute this is Maggie Chris ladies and
gentlemen Maggie
Chris
hello no you're not that drunk on a
Monday I am transgender it's okay
[Applause]
we're all experiencing the same thing
right
now uh but yeah it's New U my only
complaint so far since coming out is
that everybody's just been so goddamn
nice I took self-defense classes I
bought mace I came up with witty
comebacks and just like what does a lady
have to do to get some oppression up in
this [ __ ] you
know do I have to go to Oklahoma I don't
want to go to
Oklahoma I should mention I do have two
small children on the use it before you
lose it plan and
um they're great um they've made this so
much easier they're wonderful um and the
only trouble is I have to do regular mom
things uh like this and like in the
regular mom world this is a little
disconcerting so I found sneaky ways to
come out like for instance in my
neighborhood I just uh I just did
Halloween I went trick-or-treating I
didn't put on a costume I wore this and
every time we knocked on the door and
said trick-or treat the people would go
oh my god wow you really look like a
woman and I said thank you
and then I got to have a moment three
days later when I'm checking my mail and
they look out their window I'm like too
late you're already nice to the
neighborhood
[ __ ] I'm out
[Applause]
[Music]
that loves you it feeds you it hugs you
it [ __ ] you it sucks you it
Fox a good sense about hair B and some
deep sounds like heaven the news got a
nice rhythm going we'll keep it going
with Mr mcgomery Wayne coming to the
stage mcy
way thank you Mr Bearden Cap City I grew
up in Houston y'all I always want to be
an astronaut and I could have been an
astronaut if wasn't for that drug drug
testing I never had a problem with drug
testing only time everyone go to space
one's really really
high people want know what heaven on
Earth looks like to me heaven on Earth
looks like the love of a good woman
honestly I mean if you're lucky enough
to find a good woman that loves you that
feeds you that hugs you that [ __ ] you
that sucks you that fall asleep in your
arms and then has a good sense to get on
her side of the bed she can get some
deep RM sleep sounds like heaven to
me next day it's just the opposite she
wakes up in your arm she sucks you she
[ __ ] you she feeds you she hugs you she
loves you he I go to church on Sunday
for that I might even read the Bible I
had this girl she compliment my hair she
said your hair looks nice what do you do
to it it's like I don't know smoke a lot
of
dope take a lot of naps I know what to
say I just smiled and said thank
you I'll never be on Tinder that's I got
two kids that's two reasons I'll never
be on Tinder they're on
there damn it I don't get arguing with
you about whether weed should be legal
or weed shouldn't be legal let's just
pretend we're in Colorado we'll wake up
tomorrow morning the mountains do a dab
see these bald eagles in love go down to
McDonald's have a quake and bake special
it's a mspiff with a ganja muffin and a
hemple cranberry pomegranate juice
smoothie quarter pounds of whole new M
weeds legal da I'm smoking it All These
Bars got to change your signs from happy
hour to happiest hour sounds like heaven
on Earth to
me thank you Mr Bearden thank you Cap
City I love you Stephanie I love my
Outlaw angels I love you papa Ralph good
night Montgomery Wayne got to head back
to his Jug Band but we had him here for
a little while Montgomery Wayne
we were [ __ ] with him we just
like and when that happened he got
really anxious and upset about
it now here's what's happening the
judges are deliberating in the back room
I know some of you have things to do I
know some of you you came out you saw
your friend you saw you realize there's
no [ __ ] chance their name is getting
called at the end of this evening if you
need to go I understand it the parking
lot gets full when everyone rushes at
the same time it did kind of filter into
a nice crowd here this evening if you
got to go you got to go I understand
that all that's going to happen now is
they asked me to do a few minutes of
standup and I usually will finish out
but uh I'm far more interested in
talking to these lovely Texas women
about their evening and some of the
reactions I saw on your faces and I
figured we'll break that down a little
bit and for those of you playing along
at home the count on the official
utterances of Tinder this SE evening
22 play a different I do the contest way
differently than a lot of
people and we'll see what happens here
with some of these things cat ramzinski
is going to the semifinals
cat there you go girl
congratulations cat's not going alone
she's going with SAR June ladies and
gentlemen she's going with SAR
June
uh they love the ladies tonight Maggie
Chris also going to the
[Applause]
semifinals I felt more solid in my stage
presence for sure um after my prelim
night uh Matt Bearden pulled me aside
and said do you feel different and I
said well yeah you know I knew he was he
meant it right and I knew exactly what
his meaning but I couldn't resist going
well yeah feel different I wasn't happy
about my night as far as I didn't do
real good and I've been doing so well
and just funny how it just didn't always
go like you want a little distracted
comedy still hasn't met what I had with
Stephanie on a pretty much a daily basis
we laughed way harder than anybody ever
laughs at the comedy shows and and they
weren't really jokes it was just two
people being silly having fun and it was
jokes obviously but because I mean there
were words but but yeah I mean so you
know I missed that so I guess I was
looking for that energy at first and I
was looking for her laugh
oh should I wear my new glasses tonight
oh do you get new glasses look how awful
they
are I got them for
$20 oh my God you're
adorable they're not that bad I hated
them for a good minute but check this
out I look like a
[Laughter]
Nazi I will
I been to
contest I believe in nothing I believe
in nothing you can tell because of my
glasses I am about to go to the comedy
club to participate in this contest and
compete against all my close
friends I slept really late today in
preparation slept until about 2:30 uh I
took the day off from work and I've just
been laying around mching Heathers and
chopped and
uh you know trying on a million dresses
and putting 50 bobby pins in my hair and
that's it I'm ready I'm really
ready I'm like fifth or sixth to
last which is nice I'm not going to
watch anybody I don't think now remember
your
dreams remember your dreams are at the
end of this
thanks R it to win
it or just to do our
best what what what you want
okay can I have a Shiner and a
bullet thank you dear here's that and
then I'll pay for the other
one and then I'll eat food maybe
I'm going to eat fried pickles one time
before a contest in San Antonio I ate
fried pickles so fast that I vomited
before the
contest a whole basket definitely feel
better than I did last year I feel
calm and
okay please
[Laughter]
win f p a starts in
minutes thank you remain
seated thank you for coming out I'll be
your host in
MC I was the first winner of the contest
in
1986 thank
[Music]
you I am still
alive but every show could be my last so
welcome make sure my sweater is tied
tight and my bra straps are in and
there's no
boogers you're good
and we're
off hi right please go on the stage
Avery more
I'd say on average uh I whisper to
myself now's my
chance at least once or twice a
day now's my chance right now Avery it's
your chance get on the
bus the line is clear at Einstein's
Bagels now's your ch
when I go out to bars you know I'm a
woman I have breasts and a vagina so I
get hit on by men um but not the
ones that are under the age of 70 uh not
the young hot 60y
olds uh I get hit on by older men and I
don't know if it's my posture or my
glasses or all of this but old guys eat
this [ __ ]
up I think it's familiar
um I uh I have to admit that in college
I did dip my toes into the silver pool
uh I took I took a couple laps um I
learned a few things about myself um I
like
money um I love old
skin God I love old skin and you could
just stretch it as far as it can go
remember when you were sitting on your
grandmother's lap and you just push that
bin from side to side imagine that but
sexual I love
it it's over now I did it who knows
what's going to happen as I clutch my
purse like a
baby okay it's over now
[Music]
not watching Everybody helped a
lot here they
come Avery Moore sh up Avery
Moore where's
Avery here she
comes there you are congratulations
there's your name on a piece of paper
I'll see
hi she knows me from Silver
Alert
oh
I I made it feels good my most famous
friend
y when
closer till not moving on to the next
I'm Rosie I was one of the judges
tonight oh nice to meet you I we thought
you were I work at kxa he's a reporter
with me at kxa and we just died when you
walk
on all right I'm G to follow y'all all
right just text me wherever you want to
go
okay I'm glad it's that first one's
over I know dude I just want to make it
out of the gate you
know all
right am I supposed to be saying
anything funny right
now I mean can you am I I I can't is
that
possible I don't think I'm going to
advance I and I guess if I do it'll be a
pleasant surprise
but I've never made it out of the
preliminary rounds never uh uh never
gotten past the first
night
um which I think
we huge Injustice uh this year though
it's all going to be
different this year
uh I'm just
GNA first of all I I predict that I'm
going to win the whole thing don't we
why are you
laughing that is so [ __ ] up that you
would laugh at
that somewhere in the
middle that's not too bad fourth right
now my mindset is this is just another
show and uh I'mma go up there and I'mma
kill that
[ __ ] wait this is my [ __ ] okay I always
order a Rum Runner that is more rum than
runner it's a fruity exotical drink that
they make here the bartenders already
know when I come through the door have
my cherries and [ __ ] ready
so yeah I'm only on number one um I
usually do two before the set and then
unlimited after I'm done just in case I
don't advance I feel like I should be
like punching and [ __ ] punching at the
screen like yeah cuz I've been watching
boxing videos to get
[Laughter]
ready I just want this to be over by
this I mean my life
oh I got a million of them oh that was a
strong
drink I I that's my fault I was like
give me more rum and Runner do you have
like a like a soft open or anything like
how are you opening I'm doing uh my
uncle Carl's took a
selfie so one of the things that I find
kind of amusing uh is how the older
generation will sort of try to like glum
on to whatever kids today are doing you
know you know like when your
grandparents get on Twitter you know uh
for example my uncle Carl uh he took a
selfie only uh you know he he used a
[Music]
gun but I feel like that counts uh I
mean if you think about it in a way it's
kind of the ultimate selfie you know hey
everybody look at me you know
so so I was uh going down on my wife the
other night
while she was
ovulating boy did I have egg on my
face
huh huh I get in there
ladies thanks guys y'all have a good
night and that's how it's done
folks I had a good set I think
it's on film so we'll find out
later would you please help me we on the
stage LESA
Lester thank you oh man I have been
having a rough weekend I got called out
for slush shaming so I was down on Sixth
Street and the girl come by and she was
walking down the street and then she
just pulled it shirt up it's like woo
and it was just like raw ass Teddy and
uh I was like damn girl if you got your
titties out on the Tuesday what you
going to do when Friday get
here my friend was like oh my God Lea
did you just [ __ ] shame that
girl what [ __ ] I would
never what the [ __ ] is [ __ ]
shaming and then she explained to me
that it was wrong that I had talked
about that girl's raw titties like that
and I should be happy that she was
confident enough in me to pull her
titties out like that and I'm just
sitting here with the black lady ha not
talk about mhm
mhm so you saying we can't talk about
hoes no
more who said that
[ __ ] Huffington Post
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that sound like something some hoes came
up
with hell
[Laughter]
yeah that's what be so crazy after the
show people be want to talk and I'm like
oh I'm high come on I done took all my
[ __ ] off I done put my rope chain in the
bag and your semifinalist for tonight
you ready to keep your hands together
one time come on Round of Applause as
you
go Londa
Lester and Ali Amry ladies and gentlemen
your semifinalist for this year's
funniest person announcing
contest yeah going to the
semifinals time for another
[Laughter]
drink hiim van from zeper Talent oh nice
do you have an agent already I do not
honestly I'm kind of glad it's over
dude so glad this part is over me too I
know so glad it's over I don't even care
from this point on this was my last year
doing the contest
so don't have to put myself through this
anymore I don't know like I I turned 49
yesterday
so like I'm
almost 50 you know what I mean and it's
like I just got this new job um and it's
like a good job and I good benefits it's
a good company you know what I mean and
and it's
like I've been putting all this I've
been investing a lot of time and energy
into comedy for a lot of years now and
it's not getting me anywhere I'm not you
know what I mean I'm I'm not going to be
professional comic at this point in my
life it's just not going to
happen I don't know also I'm just not
digging comedy that much it's just not
as much fun as it used to
be first season I did Last Comic
Standing I left with something I'd never
had before which was stage fright I had
had nervousness real honest to God oh
this is a different show this is an
interesting uh new venue uh but I froze
up twice doing shows where I choked I've
never done that before in my life I
started having panic attacks uh last
year once on stage that
was pretty bad like I had to stop and
like you know and uh feel like I was on
a blackout there was one time oh God
this is I feel like okay um I left
because I was doing the open mik Cap
City it's probably a couple months
afterwards and County was hosting and
right before I went on stage paralyzed
couldn't do it I just happened was like
I I can't do it go to the next guy he's
like okay he's like just go take a walk
and I took a walk and like broke down
like outside Cap City cuz I was like I
feel like I can't do this
anymore yes it's the semifinals of the
1,000th round of the
contest this is very exciting uh four
people from tonight are going to advance
to the finals and whoever goes to the
finals then someone will win and if you
win the whole contest you get to run
nachos out of the kitchen for an entire
week here which is very exciting um
ah everyone in the world's going to
think I'm a chain
smoker
okay it's going to be
fine it's going to be fine fit smoking
cigarettes a year ago which is nice no
oh no no no no you don't have to keep
clapping more come on no no just a hero
that's
it I quit smoking cigarettes a year ago
it's nice I got my sense of smell back
uh also I can see ghosts
again which is nice people always ask me
how I quit smoking cigarettes cold
turkey f it in it was pretty
easy so every time I wanted a cigarette
I instead had a vicod in and then every
time I wanted a vicadin I had a vinin I
like
[Applause]
vikin yeah I was watching uh Palumbo and
I was like got to go outside I got to go
out good my friends are good
nobody's talking to nobody they're just
walking around bumping into walls just
no eye contact I mean because we're
friends throughout the year but soon as
contest comes around it's
like turns everyone into just crabs and
slobbering hateful
monkeys that's what it does that's what
the contest does it's embarrassing to
watch and I love it every year and you
riding down the dirt
road you got a beer in the console
and the sky opens up and hey it's God he
says hey hey hey I'm an artist
[Applause]
please and the sky opens up and hey it's
God he says son you're the second coming
of Christ
Christ cut print what's on this side
just a wall it's just a
wall oh what's over there
there's just a wall on the other
side this one we're posing and we're
posing and then I couldn't find the
camera oh they're all adorable man but
that's good you feel good about it yeah
I couldn't watch
anybody yeah me Nei it was really fun
everyone I know that's only thing is
like like as long as I just have fun
doing it yeah and I'm fine it's I like a
big like a big old crowd give me a big
old crowd give me a big old crowd
let's bring up the results ladies and
gentlemen more ladies and
gentlemen H
more here if you uh here come here help
me out read that name to everybody oh
Taz t
one more
lady uh very funny lady ladies and
gentlemen Danny
Palumbo Danny Palumbo
[Applause]
everybody Danny Palumbo huge boner
ladies and gentlemen Danny
Columbo sporting a lot of wood there
look at that huh special boner pants
he's wearing at night it's one of
everybody in his boner pants all right
the night wouldn't be complete without
Amber's spit on my
face so
excited I'm so happy for you thank you
you little devil you congrats thank
you I'm texting my
sweet felt pretty cool being like
getting to the finals you know you get
that sweet credit and all those
showcases finalist in
fpia
finally it's
good
[Music]
hello how are you fine how are you I'm
great you thirsty you going to hold off
you know what it
[Laughter]
is I'm drink the [ __ ] out that drink
thank
you here it is y'all you want to get a
up close shot of that [ __ ] boom look at
that right there so delicious I'm
fourth so hopefully that is
uh that goes
good oh hello I almost didn't make it
tonight I am tired cuz I've been looking
for a new
job just a mess oh man I've been I've
been trying to find a new job and so
I've been going out on a lot of
auditions recently so I go to this one
spot and there's a a guy I guess his
Kickstarter had kicked in and he got all
his little money and he was really
[ __ ] excited about that [ __ ] he was
just like okay listen so this young lady
right here is going to play your best
friend and she's got something very
important to tell you I want to get your
natural reaction do you have any
questions eh I don't really have no
questions it's more like a
comment I wouldn't really be hanging out
with this [ __ ] in real
life all right quiet on the
set sassy black lady and her mentally
ill white friend take one I'm like what
the
[ __ ] action hey girl hey hey girl I have
something important to tell you oh
what's
that I'm
[Music]
bipolar well
damn and the director was like cut what
the hell was that that was my natural
reaction I'm from Detroit and we don't
have cute nicknames some mental illness
all right
[Laughter]
either you is
crazy or you crazy than a [ __ ]
like we don't even need to bring Web MD
into none of
[Laughter]
[Applause]
this so then I ended up back here
tonight you know what I'm saying trying
to get chos for some
[ __ ] just keeping it real
I did all right they're weird crowd
really see I was trying to be nice I was
trying to be
nice I don't know I was just like
[ __ ] we'll see I don't know if they
ain't drunk enough or what I am going to
go go get me a strong ass
drink something strong and
brown I I ain't making no
predictions do you think that where you
are in the lineup ever matters or I
don't really know I I I I couldn't even
really
say were you
happy h i was all right I guess fourth
was all right it's better than first
ladies and gentlemen put your hands
together for finalist Ella
Gale don't stop don't stop give it up
for Rob
[Music]
gagman
congratulations Andrew
dism keep it going for Les
Lester those are your four finalists how
about a hand one time a little high five
from G Brown
congratulations I'm going to the
finals I'm going to the finals let me
show let me show you my
name oh [ __ ]
oh the last time I did the contest I
took second place the year before that I
took second place and the year before
that I took
third so and after that I said uh you
know what it's been fun roulette should
have won roulette should have won hands
down if you look at the first five years
of the contest it's a very diverse
contest have you looked at the first
five years I mean there's there's
there's ladies in there is is it
conspiracy is it is it rigged is it
racist do they not want a black person
to win you know what what do we got 2016
coming up 20 yeah think I'm think I'm
going to come back kids coming out of
retirement dust off the jokes
I feel like I'm coming down with the flu
to be honest um I was kind of sit coming
in and now I'm really about to
crash in a dark alley near 183 in Austin
Texas for semifinals of the funniest
person in Austin and I went up third and
I'm
done hi well the previous two Comics
clearly didn't get the memo that it's to
impress no just kidding I'm transgender
I guess to look this good every
day thank you you can start throwing
flowers it's a lot of confusion about
transgender people um people assume
because we switched one team we're going
to switch two teams but that's not true
I'm still attracted to women uh which is
a little confusing uh I've been trying
to explain it to people cuz they ask are
you gay now and I say yes and they go so
you're into men and I say no I'm into
women but you're not gay then no I am
gay it's like like it's very simple I'm
just I'm the kind of homosexual who
wants to put a penis in a vagina I don't
know why that's so
hard you know and it's just an absurd
thing to say but that night when I said
it I felt very sad and lonely to me
because I think I was having issues with
self-esteem dating was going weird I was
all up in my head about how people saw
me um from a sexual interest point
and um I didn't think it was funny that
night you know what I mean the joke
wasn't funny to
me all right I Won't Say I'm thinking
about next year yet not in a big rush to
do it again but I will that's the that's
the curse of this is that you do it
every year until you get it right or
learn you don't need it thank you so
much for coming out we super appreciate
one more time for these guys thank you
yay there you go John thank you that was
awesome oh I think it look great I mean
I honestly this would be the same face
I'd have if I made it because I'm so out
of it right now it doesn't make you any
less funny you know losing is not really
losing you can still persevere without
being one of the top choice and still be
productive and funny so yeah people are
going to be mad if they didn't make it
in and you
did who's this guy why did he make it in
well he had that funny bit about the
Flintstones
[Music]
they got me going first what they got me
going
first make the best impression I set the
tone for that [ __ ] oh they're filming
for this documentary what they're doing
a fpia documentary you want me to get
out of the shot you ain't got to get out
of the shot can Blake stay in the shot
see y'all afterwards see you afterwards
good evening ladies and gentlemen and
welcome to the finals of the funniest
person in Austin contest and now please
help me welcome to the stage 2014's
funniest person in Austin Cody hou
hey where I missing people
at yeah go ahead wink if you're with
your
captor welcome to the thrilling
conclusion of the 30th annual funniest
person in Austin
contest hard to believe that just 2
months ago 230 self-proclaimed comedians
started this whole whole
thing now the cream of the crop 12
contestants compete tonight because they
were unable to beat me last
[Applause]
year lot on the line tonight
$3,000 cape and crown that I used to
wear uh to bed every
night and most importantly legitimizing
their comedic aspirations to their
parents are you guys ready to get the
show
[Music]
going more more welcome to the stage
leanda
[Music]
Lester thank
you oh man I have just celebrated my 11
year anniversary of living in Austin
from I moved here from Detroit so that
is some big
[ __ ] remember the chronicle used to have
these little numbers you could call and
it was always next to the lady who
charged $75 an hour for a
massage uh so I put a ad out on there
looking for some new friends and it was
nothing sexual just hey how you doing my
name is Londa I'm new in town if you
think think you can show me the city
leave a message and I got a message all
right 2:30 in the morning some dude with
a snotty ass nose breathing real heavy
listen we having a threesome
night and we need two more
people don't you wish you could find out
who the crazy people was like in the
cartoons like remember in the cartoons
they used to have them dudes with the
swirls and [ __ ] You' be like oh no books
bunny don't [ __ ] with
him that nig's
crazy come on I'm going to go smoke a
cigarette we'll talk I wasn't really
scared going up first because I was like
well you know I've hosted before I feel
like I made it through I mean you know I
did my set I'm proud of my set I
practiced it um yeah so you know now
it's just the waiting game you know to
see how everybody else does and you know
I ain't making no predictions I did a
completely different set I mean that
[ __ ] is still funny
too so
yeah please welcome to the stage Danny
[Applause]
Palumbo I guess hi everybody
uh my my name is Danny I grew up in
Pittsburgh Pennsylvania which uh that's
the appropriate response
uh let's all have a moment of silence
for that dying
town I got family back home I tried
calling my mom today and uh she didn't
answer
again I realized today that I call my
mother way more than she calls me so
like I don't know what do I do start
playing it
cool Frank give it a couple days maybe
maybe go back to texting I don't know
maybe oh you know what maybe I said I
love you too soon and that's what
happened
I I just thought 29 years would be okay
to
say you can say it back if you want
to ow she hung
up she always does that
[ __ ] have no recourse for how you feel
for a little while
you're in a documentary now
Jackson like grand rabids
Michigan cuz he riding down a dirt
road you got a beer in the
console God is my d and I am a son
you're all Sinners I'm going to [ __ ]
kill
everyone cuz you riding down a dirt
road thank you so much don't tell anyone
you heard that my name is Avery
Moore Avery you [ __ ] killed it Mama I
hope you win so bad I want you to win
holy [ __ ]
[Music]
now I just got to stare at you [ __ ]
for who [ __ ] knows how
long is that your hunch oh holy [ __ ]
have
mercy all right tonight's second runner
up that means third
[Laughter]
place second runner up and winner of
$500 Ella Gale
Stay Stay Stay Stay
[Music]
Stay thanks
guys your first runner up that
means pretty good Ryan County
[Applause]
and this
year's funniest person in Austin winning
$3,000 Danny
Palumbo hey
than thank
you thank thank
you
uh uh cool I won $3,000 I'm going to go
see a doctor now
uh it's nice that after uh consecutive
years of white guys with beards winning
this contest that
uh you know a white guy with a mustache
wins
it uh another white guy with dumb facial
hair has won the contest cuz last year
people were like oh consecutive winners
with you know white white dudes with
beards so I wanted to make that joke and
I'm glad I addressed it up front because
I found out that's all anyone was
talking
about all you hear from like the worst
like white male comedians is that
comedy's tough for white males like we
don't get anything they just give the
spots away to minorities and women and
that's such horeshit I'm proof that's
horeshit so this is for diversity
everybody I don't what are you doing
back there right now what wait do for
what yeah okay sure yeah
yeah comedy is very
subjective you know what one person may
think is funny somebody may think is
offensive they have a formula of what
they're looking for and it's just like
Well yeah if y'all are looking for this
this and this why you just have why you
having a contest if you just want young
white s dudes then I will save my $15 to
go get high with it's nothing personal
on the judges if that's what you're
looking for then just tell me and I will
know to step back it's like playing it's
like playing a scratch off and you like
you could win $50,000 but they didn't
tell you the jackpot was already gone so
you still out here just scratching your
ass off like I know I'mma win I thought
it was [ __ ] um yeah I was really
excited for a woman to win I thought
that some was I was like oh we're on a
roll baby and we were just stacking them
up stacking them up and then it was I
love Danny and he really did deserve it
and he was really funny but I I was a
little
like again I don't think any of the
winners from the past 15 years from 2000
on have been undeserving I've seen all
of them do sets they are all still
active in the scene except for like one
or two people who have moved on bigger
things and other scenes you know what I
mean these are all great comics and so
there's no like well that was a fluke
year I mean you know I mean the evidence
is staring you in the face when year
after year after year uh these unbiased
judges come back with the same results I
think it's a resounding yes straight
white men have it when it come to uh to
to to Comedy uh and I say that as a
straight white man um so it's your
excuse
I do think the same judges Circle
through for finals year after year and
as much as I appreciate their industry
experience and the uh knowledge that
they bring to the table why not try a
new panel there's other people with
industry experience maybe the panel of
Judges being different or diverse might
tweak the results up a little bit over
the Long Haul Austin is a hole is is
inexcusable I mean I came from Houston
and the fact that I come there from
Houston and and it's 20 years later I'm
still hipper than in a race relation
wise and everybody in Austin's kind of
ridiculous you know so I'm the guy with
the cowboy hat I shouldn't be getting
along with everybody like that I feel
like Austin is just now becoming super
diverse in its comedy scene does that
make sense like I feel like maybe in the
mid 2000s it was like yeah it was
probably super white and it's white now
obviously that's the majority but like I
don't know there's lots of funny uh
women in the scene and you know nonwhite
dudes doing non-white [ __ ] male
comedy I have to work at H Quality
Seafood tomorrow at 4:00 and I fully
intends on wearing this
there uh if you if you want
tacos uh come there
[Music]
hey Lee how you doing I noticed you
weren't wearing a cape and Crown that's
weird hey guys just want to just want
you to know nothing changes I'm just
like everyone else I'm just wearing a
cape and Crown right now and I well you
know it's not a big deal
I just uh sure yeah I was actually
pounding the dashboard last night cuz I
was excited I don't have to do the
contest anymore that was the thing I was
most
[Music]
excited afterwards I was just really
excited for everyone and then the
following days I kind of got like a
little gloomy and Moody and then I just
told myself to snap out of it and stop
being a little [ __ ] and I
[Music]
did I don't think I'm going to do the
contest next year you could have
interviewed me at any time in the last
13 years and found a day uh at least one
day a month where I was saying [ __ ] this
I'm not doing this anymore because it's
I mean it's heartbreaking at times every
time you have a bad
set you're like why do I [ __ ] do this
we do it because we love it and then if
you are successful and you can make a
living doing it that's even better but I
mean you're doing it hopefully because
you just love doing
it this was probably easily my best
contest in terms of getting something
out of it you know I got to advance one
round I got a great tape from it I'm
getting um name recognition with this
act which actually is kind of
awkward I've um kind of accelerated my
plans to change my name because I was
starting to get too much recognition
with this fake stage
name I have a name that I want to use
and I'm having a big party to unveil it
and move on and like it'll be the third
time I've had to start over with a name
on a poster as a comedian but I think
it's worth it
this is the first year where I knew all
the finalists pretty much and I'm like
pretty close buddies with them all so
that was pretty special I mean you know
I just been doing shows been having a
lot of fun trying to get Stephanie to
Austin and uh feel like I'm getting
close to my comedy goals people say they
want to do comedy for a living and I
don't really know how you can do that I
mean seems kind of hard so I'm just
going to do comedy and try and
live I need to figure out a few other
part the
[Music]
equation that [ __ ] is very stressful
like people be trying to be like a man I
ain't I don't care about the contest you
care about the contest don't even
[ __ ] lie like we all care about it
because it could be a situation of a
make or break thing like you could meet
somebody I met an agent a legit like
talent agent wanted to sign me but you
know had I not done the contest ain't no
telling if this lady would have ever
reached out to me so it's very important
and like right now I can't really say
you know it could I could do it next
year I could come back like [ __ ]
Michael Jordan retired and come back
like
psych so we'll see we'll see we'll we
won't rule it out completely
and ladies and gentlemen this year's
funniest person in Austin everybody
leanda
ler when I see people do well in the
contest and they walk off stage and you
can tell when they feel good you can
tell when they shake your like when know
you're hosting and you walk up and I
always like to shake a hand it's the
whole reason I went that night it also
hurts when I see someone not do their
best and they know it because you see
their shoulders when they walk up and
that's tough too especially except I
think that I should always be able to
whisper the knowledge in their ear you
can go get a drink now it's over
[Music]
n
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
here's what I'd like to see to the
contest I'm coming for you how much is
it what's the grand prize what am I
working for grand three grand
thousand yeah you owe me
that getting
paid bow that