[Applause]
and I needed this week I needed a good
week guys I'm going through a tough time
back home in
Minnesota my car died it's always a
bummer I shouldn't even be surprised it
was a long time
coming thing had
287,000 miles on
it it was a
1993 Ford
Escort it's a stupid name for that
car cuz really when they're that old and
beat up you usually just call them
hookers not ask escorts are very
expensive $300 a night I wouldn't even
kick in the extra $17 for the high mile
synthetic oil change that is not an ESC
that's a Ford hooker or a a [ __ ] it was
a it was a Ford
[Laughter]
[ __ ] four-door Ford [ __ ] try saying
that three times fast
fun goddamn thing was totaled which of
course means the cost to repair of the
vehicle is greater than the total value
of the vehicle and what happened was the
front right tire was a little low low on
air I pulled in one of these gas
stations you got to pay $150 to use the
air compressor [ __ ] total man it's
just
total so I had to go looking for a new
car that reminded me I'm not cool
anymore if I ever was 40 years years old
wife two kids mortgage payment not
looking at the same kind of car you're
looking at 20 years ago are you like
I've been looking at the Ford Flex got a
new model called the Ford if you haven't
seen them what they do is they take all
the boxiness of a station
wagon and combine it with all the
sexlessness of a
minivan they combine those two things
together into one model and they send
you out on the highways and
byways and I've been seeing a lot of
these cars on the road and I got to
admit I think they look pretty
sharp and I think they look cool for the
wrong raises they're like wow what is
that seat eight look at all the Headroom
that is cool it's not cool and a Camaro
Blow by me in the left lane and I'll be
like well that's not even practical come
on where do you even keep the groceries
ridiculous it's been so long since I've
been cool I forgot if you drive a nrow
you don't even buy
groceries you eat out hot chicks on the
hood of your
Camaro what I'm telling you is no woman
has ever let herself get bent over the
hood of a Ford Star wi minivan that's
never happened maybe an Odyssey van
those are pretty baller but that's out
of my price range I don't
know marriage changes here man it's
changed my wife my wife's not the same
woman I married 15 years ago CU I love
her so much I didn't even see it
happening until it was way too
late I'll tell you what happened we we
were driving down the road goddamn Ford
Flex and she turns to me out of nowhere
and she says to me well I didn't know
there was an Applebees over
there yeah I know I was stunned into
silence
too so I asked her to repeat herself
hoping I had misheard her and she
said I didn't know there was an
Applebees over
there who the [ __ ] are you and what have
you done with my rock and roll wife this
is not the same woman I married the
woman I married doesn't say things like
I didn't know there was an Applebees
over there the woman I fell in love with
and pledged my life to says things like
I just love Bourbon and prescription
painkillers
that's the one I fell in love with but
she's
changed I put it in context for you when
I was still dating my wife before we
were married I picked her up one night
and I took her to a rock and roll show
cuz that's what you do when you're dumb
and crazy and in love and uh another
thing you do when you're dumb and crazy
and In Love sometimes is you uh eat too
many magic mushrooms before that rock
and roll
show and I knew for sure it was it was
too many mushrooms cuz while we were
waiting in line outside the club for the
show to start my wife passed out because
she thought she
saw a physical ray of light form on the
face of the Setting Sun hurdle through
space to smack her in the forehead and
it laid her out I'm not lying it was
pretty scary but when she came to the
first words out of her mouth was what
time do a [ __ ] con
start I didn't know there was an
Applebees over there do you see the
difference do you see what I'm talking
about early in our marriage we lived in
Vancouver British Columbia a beautiful
part of the planet and if you know
anything about British Columbia you know
they have the uh finest marijuana
available in North America and I
remember one particular time my wife and
I had to take our car across the US
Canadian border and what this woman did
this rock star of a life partner is she
stuffed her little
um her coin purse her Joey pouch I it's
my wife I don't want to get gross about
it she stuffed it filled to bursting
with British Columbia's finest marijuana
just so that we had enough smoke for our
road trip down the California coast
that's a
woman that's someone to build a life
around
I didn't know there was an Applebees
over there I don't know who that is I
don't know what to do with
that plus I think it was a little mean
for her to say that kind of
mean-spirited you know like it's cruel
we're already in a Ford Flex pulling out
of a Dairy Queen after our kids'
swimming lessons I didn't know there was
an Applebees over there that's just
rubbing salt in the wound as far as I'm
concerned and that wound should not be
filled with salt ladies and gentlemen
it should be filled with British
Columbia's finest marijuana
cuz that's how Papa likes to get down