being a parent changes you it just
changes you can't even talk I don't go
to the movies in the theaters anymore CU
it's like paying $12 to take a nap I
don't you I don't I don't I'm old I
can't it doesn't matter what you put up
on the screen you put me in a
comfortable chair in the dark for two
hours I'm out there's no good so I watch
movies at home with my kids which means
I watch all these goddamn cartoon movies
and and I find out even people without
kids adults watch these cartoon movies
that's weird like I I I watched Frozen
the other day because I love my
daughter and also because if you don't
know the story it's about a very
attractive but distant unavailable
emotionally frigid woman whose touch is
so cold it could freeze your heart and
kill you and I don't want to whip out a
picture of my wife but I thought I could
relate to the story
ah most you guys don't even [ __ ] know
her come on give
me anyway so I watched the movie Frozen
I was talking to this other guy who goes
oh yeah that movie Frozen I saw
it didn't really live up to my
expectations well now I imagine you know
how your parents
feel she like a 32-year-old guy being
pretty snarky and judgy about a cartoon
movie whose target audience is girls 6
to6 think maybe you want to move out of
your mom's basement and go see an
R-rated movie with some flesh and blood
boobies in it I think you owe it to the
family
name my point is as a parent my
expectations for a movie like Frozen
must be vastly different from his all I
expected for Frozen was to keep my kid's
mouth shut and out of my face for like
110 minutes and I got to tell you frozen
completely met all of my
expectations
right how was the movie kids great dad
can we watch it again five [ __ ]
stars exceeds all
expectations of course you know it's not
all W and roses being a family man
having the kids you know there are
Battlegrounds in the house like the
bathroom like we we have two bathrooms
in our house but nobody's using the
basement bathroom if they can help it
that's the scary one with the spider
webs and the kitty litter nobody wants
to
go so we're we're one family for sharing
one bathroom it's a disaster are my
wife's always nagging me about it oh you
got to lift a toilet seat right you get
that guys lift a toilet seat before you
go I told my wife are you kidding me I
piss all over that thing I'm not
touching it that's gross you're
disgusting besides she's not perfect in
the bathroom she needs to get off her
high horse she thinks I don't know about
her super secret gross trash can the one
that hides underneath the bathroom sink
the one that looks like you ladies try
to dress a deer in the bathroom you're
not fooling anybody we know it's there
and in my house it's
overflowing it's like I told my wife
geez you maybe want to empty it more
than twice a year she she said what are
you talking about that's just from my
last period oh my God sit down
how are you not lightheaded right
now do you need orange juice and a
cookie because it looks like the set of
a Sam peekin PA movie underneath our
vanity my wife says oh relax the cabinet
doors closed you can't see it look
ladies you only need to see it once to
know it's there always right well she
not even the worst one in the in the
family in the bathroom the worst one
believe it or not my my beautiful
seven-year-old daughter my angel and
she's perfect in almost every way uh but
there's something wrong with her cute
little derri
a because every time she sits down on
the toilet to make a BM that [ __ ] gets
everywhere every well not like up on the
wall she not slinging it like a monkey
but if it's made of porcelain it's fair
game to have crap all over it and in
places I didn't even think it was
possible to get it like on the underside
of the toilet
seat I'm asking could you guys do that I
can't do that it would seem to me that
gravity and Anatomy would conspire to
make that [ __ ]
impossible she doesn't like 40% of the
time on the Bowl along the
side on the
outside have any of you ever missed that
badly she does it all the time and I'm
the guy who's got to clean it up I'm
down to my he hands and knees I'm
scrubbing it I'm I'm obsessed with
trying to figure out how it happened I'm
breaking it down like it's the zder
footage of the Kennedy
assassination cuz I don't buy this magic
turd Theory she's trying to sell me the
angles are all
wrong I'm pretty sure there had to be a
second
[ __ ] yes