hello this is fancy Ray the best looking
man in comedy I'm here today with Gloria
stanum Gloria to kick off the show I
thought we' try something a little
unique I want to do a little word play
with you I'll say a word you tell me the
first thing that comes in your mind you
ready for this I'm ready for you sure
you want to hear the first thing that
comes into my mind
I think so let's try it black beautiful
oo uh dog cat
feminism a good thing
equality a really good thing Beauty
fancy Ray Oho she knows what's going on
we're going to talk about all these
issues and much more don't go nowhere
I'm fancy Ray this is Gloria stanham and
on tonight's show we're going to get
down with
it my my my Hello my name is fancy R I
am the best looking man in
talk show host are dime a dozen The Only
Exception is me cuz I've got the gro of
moves of looks and this incredibly
Charming personality now I first saw
Sally Jesse Raphael my eyes they started
to Sag I said the networks are trying to
fool us that ain't nothing but down H
dress and drag now some people think
Oprah Winford is the best they think
Oprah wears the crown well she may be
the heavyweight champ honey I'm the best
under 200
pound stay tuned I'm fancy R it's time
to get down with
it I
down hello this is fancy Ray mclin the
best looking man in kind I'm here today
with my special guest she has been a
leader in the fight for feminism for
over a quarter of a century she's a
founder of Miss magazine it's my
pleasure to introduce Miss Gloria steum
it's nice to meet you thank you for this
great show here I mean this is a whole
new event oh no the pleasure is all ours
to have you here in the Twin Cities
thank you how is a book tour that's a
very grueling thing I would think it is
very grueling but part of it is also
terrific which is meeting with people
just you know it's like sending out a
signal a kind of big populous signal and
anybody who wants to come comes to the
bookstores or wherever we're having the
signings and the and I love that you
know it turns into an organizing meeting
I get to learn a lot because the
audiences are incredibly smart mhm so
what have you learned tell us Gloria
steum has learned in our state here in
the Twin Cities well uh well I come here
a lot and I I really have a lot of
respect for the degree of involvement
here you know people citizens really
seem to be involved in making social
policy and uh it seems like you have the
best and worst of everything here you
have the ultra right-wing leadership and
you have the you know most enlightened
leadership you you have a little of both
right right but um but I think there are
a lot of social policies here that
people could benefit from learning about
in the rest of the the country I mean
you You' you've got more understanding
say of domestic violence I noticed that
from the questions that have been coming
out coming in you know to stations and
so on about the OJ Simpson case um
you've got I it feels like you've got
better programs for senior citizens
these senior highrises and so on where
people can live and just a general sense
that if you if you work at it together
you can change whatever the social
policy is right right and we are leading
the country in that aspect it's talking
about all the different things let's
start talking about what is feminism
feminism is just what it says in the
dictionary which means the belief I
would say the fact but anyway the belief
that women and men are full social
economic political equals MH how did you
get involved with the fight of feminism
I got born a
female but actually I shouldn't say it
that easily because it took me a long
time to realize that the position of
women wasn't due to Nature you know or
God or biology or somebody and it wasn't
until I was in my middle 30s when the
movement really came along as women came
out of the or from the civil rights
movement and the anti-war movement
realizing that if even in those very
idealistic and good movements there
still wasn't male female equality we
probably also needed uh an autonomous
women's movement mhm is is that a
reality is that something I mean at one
time there's such awareness for feminism
there's a lot of fight and pushing going
on has feminism become p a oh not at all
it's become much bigger deeper wider I
think the reason it seemed like you
heard about it before was that it was a
kind of novelty you know so you used to
there would be like six or 12 crazy
people in each town that the Press would
cover from time to time but now it's
part of everything it's it's part of the
discussion of welfare it's part of any
discussion of unemployment it's part of
discussions of how we raise our kids
what goes on in schools and so it's no
longer just one strange thing it's
really become more part of of the fabric
of our lives but hasn't like the issue
of AIDS and the poverty and stuff that's
going on around the world hasn't that
lesson everyone's like after money
nowadays as opposed of really being
aware of these social changes that need
to take place in our society well but
all of those things must be looked at as
if women mattered as much as men because
for instance um the in New York at least
I don't know about here but women are
the fastest growing AIDS population
because it wasn't perceived that you
know what women's problems were that
they really didn't necessarily have the
power to insist that their male Partners
use condoms for instance or that they
were not knowledgeable about the lives
of their
Partners um you not not to mention all
the the problems that come from less
good medical treatment having to take
care of kids and so on even while
they're sick I mean there are all kinds
of tragedies now that are especially
tragic because the women who have AIDS
have the major responsibility for
children so whatever the problem is we
just need to look at it as if everybody
mattered not not just as if a few people
mattered right right what was the Equal
Rights Amendment well the Equal Rights
Amendment was this strange idea that
women uh should be included in the
Constitution as much as anybody else you
know so it would have made sex as
unconstitutional a basis for
discrimination as national origin
religion and race now
are uh I I'm sure that eventually we
will have it really you still think so
well yes I think the Constitution should
eventually include
me yeah no I think so but it it was um
it was a great loss because we were
within only three states of getting it
ratified the problem is that the state
legislatures in many states don't
represent the people the um the 14th
Amendment and the anti-slavery
amendments were only ratified by some
states in the 60s you know I mean you
know some of these states are really far
be we're talking Major League far behind
and they're also controlled by Insurance
Industries and others who have an
economic stake in not uh equalizing
their Actuarial tables or whatever it is
but we'll get it eventually no doubt
about that I tell you what coming up
next we got to talk about the book
moving beyond words here new book here
that we're promoting and also we're
going to talk about the whole OJ the
abuse all kinds of good stuff don't go
nowhere we got Gloria dyam I'm fancy Ray
stay tuned and get down with it
oh here's story of a single mother Works
butt even when she's sick has a job just
to pay for dayare the youngest one on wi
here's the story of a man named Dan
Quail playing golf at his white M only
say Murphy Brown cus the LA riots made
Family Values worse till one day when
this mother met this fellow in a room
with a judge it's called a court CU this
man who's the father of her children
owes back child support back child
support no family values that's the way
we all lost our family values
all
right Mr Quail welcome to reality Twin
Cities welcome to get down with
us oh this is fancy Ray live at Dream
Girls where your fantasy begins I'm here
with Kim and Bridget oh and Bridget's
feeding me
cherries now I've got two lovely ladies
I'm in Dream Girls but I'm still missing
something oo you know what I
like stay tuned it's time to get down
with it oh my my my my my oh oh yes my
my fancy yes why do you have those
shades on oh cuz you know who's coming
on next to next we've got the lovely Lea
with sister oh yeah yeah and you know
what T there's three of them oh yeah you
know what that means mhm that means one
for me MH and another one for me m and
the third one for
me I I don't think that's very funny oh
wait a minute it is a holiday season
I'll share you get what's
left I'll fix
you no don't play that song don't play
that song man you know what happens when
I hear that song
I ain't got no energy come our next the
lovely Lia with sisters
now welcome back to the international
Talent search competition and the moment
you've been waiting for the
international vocal group winners ladies
and gentlemen from Minnesota the lovely
Lio and
sisters this is just
wonderful an H
honey honey you you you guys girls you
girls are the the lovely libowitz
sisters yes we are how much is it
job
oh ladies and gentlemen now it's time to
hear a beautiful musical number from
your talent search
winners wait a minute wait a minute who
are you who are you what are you doing
here you who are you
L we'll settle this by having the first
annual lioz sing
off the lovely Leo
sisters show them lean show them
girl the early
light we're the really so stay tuned and
get
down hi this is Gil Scott Heron whenever
I'm in the Twin Cities I watch get down
with it with fancy Ray I think you
should watch you'll get a lot out of it
all right this is fancy Ray back live on
location at the Downtown Minneapolis
with the beautiful Gloria steum how you
doing Gloria good good oh my my my my my
now we're talking about the different
issues of feminism what is what do
feminists think of
pornography well pornography the very
word means writing about female slaves
por means female slave so it's very
different from erotica because that is
Aeros love has some idea of of equal
choice and mutual pleasure so the two
it's it's like saying what's the
difference between sex and rape right
you know that's really the difference
between pornography and erotica you have
you had a relationship with Playboy
though you did some things with them I
did I worked as a bunny for I don't know
a month or so a long time ago in order
to expose the working conditions which
are lousy okay but when you turn 50
didn't you put another outfit on and
poed again with them oh no no where did
I hear that from no no definitely not
okay no so you are anti-p porn then
feminism there are some feminisms that
are saying that it's okay well I think
that I think the point is first of all
what are we talking about when we talk
about pornography but also that nobody
is talking about
censorship the the most that has ever
been proposed was here in the Minnesota
ordinance which would have uh said that
after something has already been
published if it can be demonstrated to
the satisfaction of a jury that it that
it contributed to a crime uh or
inhibited somebody's civil rights or you
know whatever which a crime then uh
civil damages could be posed but it was
never about prior restraint it's not
about censorship okay do you think an
image of Someone Like A Madonna you
think that's good for women or well I
think that she took the images or or
symbols of marn Monroe that had been
victim symbols and took control of them
and used them in a in a more powerful
way I don't think it's the goal but I
think it was a step forward you know for
because she clearly is in control of her
own life in fact you mentioned Marilyn
you wrote a book to text that Marilyn
Mar wrote book you met Marilyn I met her
once when I was in college yeah and she
was at the actor
studio um you know she sure made me like
everyone else you know want to take care
of her she was so vulnerable and so
sad sad story talking about someone at
the photo opposite as Jim Brown Jim
Brown in his book said that he had he
knew you you guys dated or something
like that yeah I wrote a story about him
that uh You' go back and find and New
York Magazine okay uh and we went out a
few times after that yeah good person
well you you know see I don't think of
Gloria Steam and Jim Brown together it
doesn't seem like well you know I we're
friends and and you know
he treated me fine and I treated him
fine and but I got worried about the way
he treated other women okay okay well
tell us about the new book the new book
is called moving beyond words uh yes and
it's it's really six books in one sort
of an odd format but just happened that
way so it's six books for the price of
one look at it that way okay okay and
there's everything in there from a very
outrageous piece called what if Freud
were Phyllis which is doing a sex change
operation on Sigman Freud and trying to
show the ways in which his theory is
crazy which you can especially show if
you reverse it you know if you say well
of course Anatomy is Destiny men are
incurably narcissistic and fragile
because they have genitals on the
outside and you know I mean I mean I
just reversed everything so you could
see how crazy it was uh to another piece
about the strongest woman in the world
this fabulous woman named Bev Francis
who's stronger than Arnold schwarzen
egger and I think really shows us that
we haven't even begun to explore uh
women's strength and muscles and so on
because unfortunately fat cultures I
mean Rich cultures value skinny women
and poor cultures Value fat women but
all male dominant cultures value
weakness in women and she's you know
really giving us a way out of that
there's there are pieces about all big
things in our lives aging the economy
the class system trying to walk around
them and look at them as if women
mattered so that we can really take them
on in our own lives in a creative way MH
and now you're approaching you're
approaching 60 now no I had my 60th
birthday March March 25th right right
well now you looking at life now as
coming into your mature years are you
going to start voicing opinions and
articles about a woman that's in her 60s
in the 1990s yeah I think so because
there's a whole part of life that nobody
prepared me
for at least everybody told me it was
sort of a decline or was downhill and
it's not it's very interesting it's
quite exciting because for one thing
what happens especially to women is that
you sort of become yourself you know I
mean because the female role is over so
you don't have to be a female
impersonator anymore which which women
are you know and and uh you can become
you can go back to that 8 n 10 yearold
you know strong little girl you used to
be only now you can reach the light
switch and you have your own
apartment and it's it's it's infinitely
interesting and I wasn't prepared for
that so I would like younger readers to
know what I didn't know you know which
is there is this whole interesting time
of life and you don't have to worry so
much about earlier years or settling
down or we never settle down it turns
out never oh man that's fabulous and
what are you doing now what are what are
you doing now well um I'm still U very
involved with M magazine The Miz
foundation for women um which is you
know I'm very proud of and does you know
lots of I mean it's the only National
multi-racial racial multi-issue women's
fund and uh and we do lots of things
like take our daughters to work was sort
of the tip of the iceberg of the a lot
of programs we have for girls uh and
economic empowerment um program that
helps low and low-income women to create
their own businesses cooperatively so I
do that I you know go dancing see my
friends uh write hopefully travel quite
a lot um listen there's more than enough
for the next hundred years all right
well we're going to keep looking forward
and keep reading and watching watching
you the name of the new book is moving
beyond words it's Gloria steum it's
available on Shimon Simon and Schuster
and we thank you very much for your time
and it on out any last words well I just
want to say something that I say in the
book but in case you don't get the book
I okay that I think that the whole
country you ought to be very grateful
for this Paradigm of coming out that the
gay and lesbian movement has given to
everyone because it is the most powerful
Paradigm of coming out as your true self
whoever that is and you know in the book
I'm talking about that about people who
lie about their ages you know which is
like passing used to be you know or um
what whatever it is the ways in which
we're made to feel
unacceptable it's it's inspirational
that Paradigm and and I think we all
need to realize what a gift it is all
right that's fabulous moving beyond
words Gloria steum thank you very much
thank you all right stay tuned and get
down with it oh my my my hi this is Dana
G and when I'm in the Twin Cities I
watch the fancy Ray Show and I watch it
in the nude you do too
my so how you doing this Li rich now
baby I tell you Bo knows this and Bo
knows that but Li Richard know Finance
I'm a CPA not the accountant but the
certified public architector rock and
roll W I'm the originator and the
Creator until this day there been no one
gred please I'm here to talk about Texas
April 15th and gone by honey and I got
to tell you about I'm getting less all
over the country sugar let me tell you
about my tax thing uh Little Richard
should I pay taxes on unearned income
now let me tell you something honey I
didn't give no money for Tutti Frutti
long talk Sally good go miss m rip it
upy The Girl Can't Help It she got it my
no don't pay no taxes on unearned income
shut up now next person writes me from
Detroit and she says are diamonds a good
investment well let me tell you what
maryn told me Marilyn said Richard
Diamonds Are a Girl's Best Friend but
you last forever woo I last and last and
oh but that was a long time ago please
someone asked me Dear Richard what do
you think about business Partnerships
well let me tell oldis R started with me
James Brown was my vocalist mck Jager
started with me the Beatles came in they
wanted to just touch my hand honey Paul
Mardi grabbed my finger and he want to
learn my little holler you know how I
said Paul said I said he
said next time I saw him he said I said
baby you got it
please shut up now and someone writes a
letter in from Minneapolis and says
Richard uh what do you think of the
stock market well I say what goes up
must come down and I like to be in the
middle going round and round please oh
my soul shut up now and someone writes
me L says Dear Richard are bonds a good
investment this time of yes now let me
tell you something about bonds bonds is
a solid investment I like my ass is
liquid so I can just pull out anytime
I'm ready oh my soul who is it oh the
IRS IRS what do you want uh we love you
Mr Richard but we heard you've been
giving out tax advice do you happen to
have a license who
IRS Goodrow and try
again all right before we go any further
I want to take this opportunity to thank
my fantastic sponsors I want to thank
Insight newspaper where you can find my
cablecast schedule hair by J which
Styles my hair do and also straight
stuff great stuff for those fancy raid
t-shirts and I want to thank all you
wonderful people for tuning in W for the
camera work Chris and Greg for the great
editing my name is fancy Ray and I am
the best looking man in comedy make sure
you tune in next week to the fancy race
show because if I'm there we're going to
get down with
it all right this is fancy Ray the best
looking man in comedy I'm back live on
location here at the Rison in Downtown
Minneapolis with Miss Gloria steum how
you doing Gloria how are you oh I'm just
feeling as beautiful as I look that's
great I'll have to remember to try to
say that yeah the positive energy that's
what it's all about the positive energy
you know something that that the OJ
Simpson case is brought to the Forefront
is the abuse and violence against women
any thoughts on that subject well the
only positive thing that I can imagine
coming from this tragedy is that the
country may get educated on how common
the sexual abuse of women is I mean more
women were battered last year than had
children last year wow uh and this case
is unusual only because it's typical do
you know what I mean I mean if if he
weren't famous it would be basically the
typical typical case um he had the
violence had escalated I mean there was
uh what eight occasions I think on which
the police had been called to the house
she said that he was going to kill her
she told you know many people that and
yet it wasn't taken seriously enough for
him to be actually jailed and act
actually get treatment uh also his
letter to the Press was typical you know
because it didn't have anything in it
about her it was all about himh it was
all about feel sorry for me MH he even
referred to himself as as battered