uh I've been trying to live healthier
lately as I age take care of myself yeah
I just don't want to end up like my dad
you know he's a diabetic he's a struggle
for years to try to keep his weight
under 300 pounds so he finally figured
out how to do it uh all he had to do was
amputate both of his
legs and he leveled out right at
297 like I don't know some of you got
tight on that don't worry he's thrilled
he finally reached he finally reached
his Target weight you know he's just 18
in short of his Target height but you
know you can't have
everything stillstone looks a horror
okay a couple of things I want you to
understand before I continue with my
closer uh number one this is not a
sudden tragedy don't feel too bad for my
dad he he literally had eight and a half
years notice to mix in a little light
cardio into the daily
routine yeah not pops he went a
different way uh he opted instead for
root beer floats and KitKat bars so I
say if the shoe
fits probably you probably still have
your feet bad bad bad stick around
[Applause]
um plus I I do want you to understand
this in all seriousness uh comedians
routinely use humor to deal with the
tragedy in our lives and I get my sense
of humor from my dad this is true uh
shortly after a second amputation the
two of us sat down and we wrote These
jokes together okay well I mean I chose
to sit he really had no other
option cuz that's how dad rolls
[Applause]
now and look it's a tough thing to joke
about I get it I understand it I see why
you're hesitant I and it's a big
adjustment for him I said hey Dad just
take it one step at a sorry I shouldn't
know
saying I do try to help him out though
go over and visit him all the time try
to keep his spirits up I uh I like to
put on a little sock puppet show for him
he's got a drawer full of things no
other goddamn
use you should have eaten your
vegetables call that character Lamb Chop
he hates that
one can't stand it
um but I do I try to get him out of the
house I say Dad come on let's get out of
the house let's go do something what do
you what do you want to do man he
thought about it for a while he couldn't
come up with anything because he was
stumped so I took matters into my own
hands I signed him up for this amput
support group and in all seriousness
guys if you have a loved one in the same
situation look into it's really cool
they get together they go and do all
kinds of activities and I signed him up
it was a speed dating thing I signed him
up for a singles ampute social
mixer no no no no no no no no that's not
right it was a double amputees singles
social mixer there's a
difference and uh you know Dad's always
been more of a tit man so he was willing
to give it a shot and uh and he went and
he had the time of his life guys you can
stop worrying about my dad he loved it
he said the place was crawling with
[ __ ]
[Applause]