[Music]
whenever I watch America's Funniest Home
Videos which is all the time because I
think it's the funniest show is ever on
TV yeah really like people are like what
about arrest of development I'm like I
try to pretend to be cool I'm like yeah
that's great but nothing beats an old
person falling down
Montage ever it doesn't [ __ ] matter
have you seen Louis have you seen the
old person falling down Montage episode
1 season 19 about 20 minutes
in just fast forward they [ __ ] they
have their purchases and they're walking
through a fountain I don't know why
they're in a fountain they got bags and
then
poof oh just thinking about
it but whenever I watch it and the date
is blurred out I'm always confused why
they have to blur the date out there's
no reason to blur the date out why was
that your grandpa just got hit in the
ball bag by a teeter totter and the date
is what you found offensive
what was the date like it has to be
something that everyone would know too
like it can't be like I called into to
work that day and they're going to know
that I was the one
filming cuz no one would know so it's
got to be a date that we would all see
and be like these people are jerks so
whenever it's blurred out I assume it
was filmed on September 11th
2001 and that's why they blurred it
right like they watch doomsday on TV and
their first thought is there's going to
be no traffic
we were going to the beach anyway might
as well still and then they get there
and [ __ ] grandma falls off a unicycle
or something they're like this is too
funny not to send
in but we should do something about that
date we're going to look like [ __ ]
right you're an older gentleman it
November 22nd 1963 same
joke right we all saw Lincoln