[Music]
now I know I'm looking out across this
audience right now and I see a lot of
people who have been hardened by the
ravages of time I've seen people whove
you know watched children and parents
slaughtered and that makes me sad
because I just look across this pasty
crew of Misfits we have here and
something needs to pick you up a little
bit and ladies and gentlemen I have that
for you right now this is a good one
this is good this is going to get us a
Emmy if anything will take a look at the
big screen again every year American
couples adopt thousands of needy
children abandoned in war torn
impoverished third world countries these
children are given a new chance at life
in the home of a loving family but even
still it doesn't always work
out basically we always just wanted a a
precious precious little baby we were we
were had charge cards set up at babies
are us and old baby Navy and babies
babies babies but we could just never
conceive I only have one
testicle yeah so we figured the most
important thing that we could do and the
best thing that we could do is adopt one
of those adorable starving children from
one of those third world countries meet
Greg and Linda a normal Suburban couple
with a common Rising problem yeah so you
know we wanted a baby we weren't going
to just settle for a toddler but we just
weren't all the expecting all those
problems that came up this is El
generalisimo commandante a ruthless and
barbaric leader of a third world country
which he ruled with an iron fist through
a mind-boggling snafu of bureaucratic
red tape instead of a needy third world
orphan Greg and Linda had inadvertently
adopted a third world dictator there's
good days and bad days days you know I
mean there's a period of adjustment I
mean when L first got here that's what
we call him L when he first got here I
mean he tried to gas Us in the
bathroom yeah but we decided after the
gassing incident that we were going to
try to love that boy no matter
what being a third world dictator you
know L has special needs I mean we can't
just go out to eat you know he's always
he's always got to have his food checked
for poison I got to check his food for
poison yeah you're very good by the way
you're very good very
patient he has a lot of hobbies you know
uh he likes to salute the traffic and uh
he he likes to fire his gun we had to
take his bullets away though he likes to
fire that thing in the air mhm and he
always helps Greg out with the yard work
he's truly our little
miracle you know he is a very big kid
bigger than most of the kids plus being
the only kid on the playground with a
mustache I think that's sort of hard for
him to deal with
sometimes but you know what we have to
be firm in our parenting just the other
day we had to give LF very serious
timeout he tried to cut the cat's paw
off because he thought the cat fluffers
tried to steal one of his shoes he put
the cat in a a re-education
camp seems
crazy I can't teach that cat a thing the
future remains uncertain for Greg and
Linda and their new bundle of joy L
generalisimo
commandante but with a little patience
and a lot of misplaced hope this Modern
Family just might
work just because he has killed and
murdered and tortured thousands of
people it doesn't mean that he is any
less
unfortunate I just some I don't
understand but I love
him he's my
son he's our son he's our son excuse me
he may never be the leader of the world
he'll always be the dictator of my heart
[Applause]
goog of love everybody