it is good to be here guys I got some
jokes coming up but really let me just
one more time reiterate how much we're
also thankful that you guys came out
please give yourselves a round of
applause for supporting this great cause
so many people to thank all the sponsors
the people of aamal you guys are
wonderful all right let's do this and
I'm looking out over the crowd and I see
a lot of male female couples in their
Autumn
[Laughter]
years so I imagine quite a few of you
are married Round of Applause if you're
a married couple
please all
right married couples love coming out to
comedy
shows because it counts as a
date but you are discouraged from
talking to one another during the
show it's perfect isn't
it I had to leave my wife to come here I
had to wake her up two days ago at 4 in
the morning and I say sorry
baby the Red Cross needs
me implied El Carman that's his lock of
the draw if they needed help topa Kansas
I'd be going but no they need they need
an imply Del Carman so I'm happy to be
here and I I wouldn't be here if it
weren't for my wife you know our wives
guys right they really I think anywhere
out there you find a man struggling to
do his best uh you're going to find a
good woman standing right by his side
whispering in his ear that he's a piece
of
[ __ ] that's been my experience the guy
doesn't even need to be struggling for
her to say that it's the way it
goes I've been married for 15 years I
wouldn't trade it for the world you know
I have single friends my age they're
running around in the bars chasing after
tail living a life of
desperation I watch these guys get shot
down by a different woman every night no
thanks and as a married guy it is so
nice to know that you have that special
someone waiting at home to reject all
your clumsy sexual
advances cuz I would think hearing the
word no come out of a new mouth every
night that would get depressing in a
hurry I think but when it's the same
woman night in and night out for 15
years kind of comforting in a sad sort
of way I think I know exactly where I
stand you know like I I don't know if
familiarity breeds
attempt but I'm pretty sure it doesn't
make her
wet I mean after all my wife she's the
person who knows me better than anyone I
could hardly blame her for not wanting
to mag me that makes sense doesn't it
you break it down why would you bang
that
person and I don't begrudge my single
friends their freedom I really don't
here's what I don't like those single
guys I don't like it when you do somehow
manage to convince a stranger to go home
and sleep with you you're a little too
proud of yourselves the next day like
you really pulled something off with a
high degree of difficulty you know like
I got friends that'll call me up the day
after it'll be like oh yeah I scored
last night
bro that's how my friends talk cuz I
hang out with a lot of [ __ ] but
that's a separate
issue but yeah they're always saying
like oh I scored you know why cuz I got
mad skills in the game I'm a player baby
you know I mean all that crap I always
just say settle down hold your horses
there rookie because you're not a player
you don't have mad you're not even in
the game let's be clear single guys
picking up girls in bars is not the
game that is a no contact in mural
junior varsity scrimmage at best okay
that's some Bush League stuff if you'll
pardon the D on
Tandra marriage
Punk marriage is the game that's the big
leagues right brother that is that is
interpersonal relations between a man
and a and a woman at its highest
competitive level that's the
show and these single guys aren't you're
not ready you're not ready for the big
leagues if you're running around in the
bars picking up girls patting your
yourself on the back for it you're
hitting the ball off the tea guys you're
taking Cuts in the batting cage okay
every time I want to get laid I'm facing
Roger Clemens in game seven of the World
Series and he's got all his stuff you
know what I mean Stakes are a little
higher for us married fellas every time
I manage get laid it's like a Triumph of
the human will story it is like the
movies hooers and miracle and Rudy all
wrapped up into one it's inspirational
is what I'm saying I bet you tear up at
the end I know I always
do cuz it's not easy when you're married
guys it's like trying to steal
home from first goddamn base are you
kidding me who am I Willie maze I don't
have those kind of
wheels and then these single guys want
me to be impressed when they trick a
stranger into going home with them using
what using lies low lighting and
alcohol Bravo Bert
Reynolds real
impressive Rudolph Valentino it doesn't
impress me much I've been married for 15
years that's 15 years and my wife
watching me get older uglier fatter
Baler by the day okay you know let's
let's just say cupid does not have a lot
of those same Quivers in his Arrow when
I'm going after some action like lies I
cannot use lies to get with my wife she
knows me too well she knows that I tell
everybody my favorite movie is Reservoir
Dogs so I seem like a cool
guy but that it's really The Neverending
[Applause]
Story right and every time the when that
rock biter says they look like big
strong hands I'm just weak I weep openly
and it does not turn my wife
on low lighting yeah nice don't talk to
me about low lighting my wife has seen
me sneeze
naked is not a candle dim enough on this
planet to make her unsee
that now alcohol I do have at my
disposal and I apply my wife with it
liberally yeah with my wife uh it's
wine two
bottles two bottles one bottle might
just make her talkative no good not
enough two
bottles one bottle I'll KN off before
she's done telling me about the freaky
dream she had last night you know what I
mean two
bottles I'm having a beer or two now
tonight I I I I I drink once a while I'm
not a big drinker though I'm not one of
these kinds of guys who needs to drink
to have a good time you know uh I need
my wife to drink so I can have a good
time just think about it why would you
why would your wife have sex with you
every time she looks at you she seems
every every screw up you've ever made
every Wrong Turn every time you forgot
something to at the grocery store every
time you forgot your anniversary how's
that going to be attractive to her you
know what I mean but still I can talk my
wife into letting me stuff do on top of
her I don't know like
quarterly that's the game
[ __ ] that's the
game I got a great marriage with my wife
I really do and I think it's because we
both look at our marriage in the same
way uh we do not look at our marriage as
a journey through life together that's a
little fruity for me and my wife frankly
now we look at it as a battle to the
death win or take all very competitive
marriage somebody is going to win this
marriage we both agree that a good
marriage is one where you love support
and care for your partner with
everything you got while also
simultaneously trying to drive them
[ __ ] insane for the rest of their
lives
right and so you got to keep score you
got to know who's winning no point and
play in the game if you don't know who's
ahead there's a bunch of ways you can do
that you know uh well here's a for
instance
guys uh if you ever find yourself out at
ballroom dancing
lessons because your wife said hey this
will be a fun thing for the two of us to
do together uh you are losing your
marriage in the scoring column she's
ahead right
now now of course
Ladies If you ever find yourself out of
ballroom dancing lessons because your
husband thought it would be a fun thing
for the two of you to do together you
are losing your marriage because you're
married a
homosexual happened to ktie Hol could
happen to any of
us thank you for the Applause I also
hear some oh like people are worried Tom
Cruz is going to walk in hear that joke
and get bummed out he's not
coming he's not coming guy he's
somewhere over on the Baja side blowing
a
dude pretty
sure I'll tell you how my wife and I
keep scoring our
marriage Cu uh well here's what I
believe I believe that one of the
primary goals in marriage for women is
to convince the man to give her
babies I think one of the primary goals
for men in most marriage is to convince
the woman into giving him
[ __ ] now uh my wife and I have two
children so our marriage is locked in a
dead tie