[Applause]
good evening ladies and
gentlemen welcome to the ory please put
your hands together go wild and crazy
for the awesome talents that it
what said you're going to talk for a
minute you said I had to [ __ ] up a bit
as well you didn't do that
either hey
everybody Welcome to the
Albany how is everyone tonight you
having
fun oh good isn't this great I just love
it I'm not feeling remotely
uncomfortable right
now can we practice clapping ready
fantastic ladies and gentlemen start
clapping start cheering and welcome to
the stage the awesome Talent is Mr Glenn
[Applause]
[Music]
Wall SE
[Applause]
absolutely seamless how are you that was
a that was a lovely Round of Applause
you've you've warmed my
cockles I didn't even know they were
cold till you came
along you in a good
mood
really world's
[ __ ] been watching the news at all
over the past year it's really bad
man Iceland's going out of business
and not the
shop he would have thought out of the
two the
country would have been okay but
no do you even know a country could do
that they
didn't I saw and get interviewed on the
news cuz it happened so quickly they're
like yeah we went to bed everything was
cool we woke up and
subsidizing for they naive little
icelanders up there in the Frozen sea
and naivity cuz I saw him on the news
get interviewed tall blonde gorgeous
Scandinavians look straight into the
camera went yeah we don't know what
we're going to do for
[Laughter]
manty really
you got no idea
huh cuz I
know we're going to change your name to
new
Thailand for the pedophile who doesn't
like to
sweat that's a little tester right off
the top see how far you guys want to
take
it cuz I don't know I don't know how you
guys feel about the way the world's
going but I had lunch with a friend he
was like honestly
Glenn tell
me are you worried about the financial
crisis I like do I look like I had
Investments
oo what's going to happen to me are they
going to take my broken Xbox away
now that's what I keep my Smurfs on top
of where am I going to move those little
blue
[ __ ] I don't like moving them around
cuz then I get high and forget I did it
looks like they're
alive what are you doing up
there get back down here cuz I got one
thing in life that keeps me grounded
and that is the fact that Smurfs are not
real cuz wouldn't it be really
disenchanting to find a dead one in a
mouse
TR sitting in your favorite chair what
the [ __ ] was
that oh hey look it's
Papa need him for the
collection get the little blonde one
then they can't breed that's the best
one
[Music]
mhm cuz really
I'm I'm not worried about a lifestyle
that I had and now will have lost I'm
more worried about a lifestyle that I
didn't take advantage of when I had the
opportunity like I don't want 30 years
from now some kid coming up to me in the
street going tell me Mr wool is it true
in the olden days you could have eaten
an orange any day of the year if you'd
wanted to
uh in
theory but I was more fascinated with
crystal
meth it was a methy time man we made a
big
meth those lisps are
funny come on give lisps or do you ever
met somebody you didn't know how had a
lisp and they're like hey how's it going
you're like better
now say more
stuff with your Funny
Mouth yeah man it's a bit [ __ ] though
the whole world I've stopped recycling
that's done you know fix the economy
then maybe I'll help out but
so that's changed a bit of people little
back uh uh
no you do not make fun of the
environment because how can we look into
the eyes of our
children and tell them that we have
ruined the
weather I'm just like well
don't tell him has always been that way
in fact tell them they did
it tell them if they don't eat their
vegetables the seasons will become
harsher and harsher and
harsher then invariably one day they
won't you be able to turn to him and go
see little Billy I told you to eat your
broccoli now your grandmother has died
in a
heatwave I don't think it's appropriate
you come to the
funeral I think you should sit there and
eat some spinach and hopefully your
uncle's beachfront property won't wash
into the sea and we'll have somewhere to
go on on vacation
Billy I hate
you drink
it drink it off your face Billy
it's all right he's
imaginary you don't have to worry about
him is just a little Invisible
Boy not not needing for that sort of
Silence that oh no uh boys don't drink
spit
uh not on our watch
I'm just like like I don't know how you
feel about the way the that the world's
gone in the past year but I'm I'm myself
am having a tough time seeing the dark
side of the financial downturn cuz I'll
be straight out honest with you my
ex-wife bought me out of our house right
before the property
[Music]
Crouch or as I like to call it God
taking my side
[Laughter]
yeah man I'm
divorced it's good it's good if it's not
working out get a divorce you know if it
is don't just cuz I said so that
be but you know for us there was no kids
involved and I'm happy for that cuz I'd
hate for there to be that sort of meat
shrapnel from our dead
love just looking at me every second
weekend while I took it
camping why do you drink so much
Daddy
you now make Daddy another drink you
know how I like it Whiskey and
vodka okay take Go Daddy's credit card
and chop up some more of his
[Laughter]
medicine
biger
bigger okay put a little one up for
yourself not that big do you remember
what happened last time do you have any
idea how much a kid on Coke can talk
about
[Laughter]
toys had a
divorce it's cool man it's cool having a
divorce you get to have single sex
again which is weird cuz when you're
married you look at every other female
on the planet you're
like I could [ __ ] her
too and then you get a divorce and
you're allowed to and it's
like
oh well that wasn't as much fun as I
thought it was going to be like
sometimes it's cool but most of the time
you're too drunk you don't know the
woman well enough it's just real robotic
like you don't feel like you're making
love to somebody you feel like you're
two vacuum cleaners falling down the
stairs
together like afterwards you only feel
like a kiss would be appropriate just a
firm
handshake you played a hell of a game
man sometimes it's cool though like I
was in my flat and a young lady who I'd
been seeing
but not
dating if you catch
[Music]
my called up and it was late at night so
I was drunk because that's the
rule can you see the son no get a
beer sometimes I have to go into the
basement to implement that rule
man late at night she's also very drunk
so really that call can only be about
one thing because in general girls don't
like to play
Xbox mine is broken and Smurf
covered well you know I held it together
I knew it was going down I was like oh
yeah I do believe you should come over
but aam she said yes I said don't forget
your
[Music]
vagina she said I
Shan then she called back 5 minutes
later she's like um yes I'll require
your post code in your address and the
taxi cab man will put it into his GPS
satellite navigation system and I will
be with you forth
with so I
complied then
waited a long 45
minutes with a hard
on you ever had a hard on for 45 minutes
it's [ __ ] horrible you don't know
what to do with it I'm pushing chest
pieces around a
board flipped a few peanuts into my
mouth you
know check the drapes without using my
hands
[Laughter]
[ __ ] is
she cuz where' she
go that's not
on that kind of
behavior
no it's wrong I mean maybe she's worried
about what we're doing isn't
romantic that could be something two
drunks bumping uglies in the
night it's not that romantic is it maybe
maybe she wants us to be like
swans mate for life have you heard that
lie it's not true they fly away as soon
as you let them
go with a look on their face that you
suggest they are not coming
back two feet is a lot of neck to shake
no width
I have the physical ability to turn
around and look at what's happening but
I don't want
to never take bread from a man with a
mustache just makes you
[Laughter]
sleepy here's the thing too man I am
romantic she just doesn't know it though
you know cuz I said I've been seeing uh
this girl but not dating her that wasn't
necessarily true I um I had been dating
her for a while but then uh I realized
that it wasn't going to work and that it
was cruel to keep her going on like that
and I did one of the most romantic
things I've ever done with a girl I
called her up and went to her house and
I broke up with
her as opposed to using the
system which is you just act like a dick
for a year and wait for her to break up
with you yeah don't look at the guys now
you do not mention the
system the system has worked very well
for
us we've got to ruin Christmas and try
to [ __ ] their sisters I
know never mention the system in front
of the ovary havs
[Laughter]
still do explain where she is
though out there somewhere in the night
I mean maybe she's just become
disillusioned with everything after the
call and then some little spark in her
brain just overloaded because
technologically we are living in a
fastpaced world do you realize we're the
first and only generation who's ever
been able to say I've lost my phone
[Laughter]
without making it sound like you were
mentally
deficient can you imagine trying to say
that in the
50s I lost my
phone
how like what are you a problem
Gambler and how could you Aid somebody
with that quandry in the ' 50s what
could you do to help like uh you want me
to go home and call
it it's all I can do
man you're
weird that's your biggest
problem you're [ __ ] weird man it's
got a cord it's hooked into the
wall you don't lose [ __ ] like that
I don't want you around my kids no
more it's a
rule still don't explain where she is
so she gone I
mean could it be because I'm too
Canadian you nodding your head there
Madam it's a possibility some some
ladies don't like the Canuck
[ __ ] here's the thing I'm actually not
that
Canadian I know I look like I'm the
champ but I'm not I'm like no I've lived
over here for 10 years Canada's changed
I don't know
it I see it in a crowd it's like a
distant
cousin who came out when I wasn't there
and now he's scared then you know you're
like oh oh you
are no they are like we've got
metrosexuals
now we didn't have those when I
left but God bless them they're Canadian
metrosexuals which means that they're
still
homophobic I couldn't believe mine eyes
I watch I watched a conversation in
Canada two metrosexuals and like full on
metrosexual is haircut like they'd been
a part of some sort of farming accident
to get it that way like they just
sticking their head in too close like is
that where the wheat
comes just gelled it up like yeah no
that's what I
wanted and they had like the two tight
of t-shirts like they'd stolen it from
their little
brother come on give me that I got to go
to the bar and [ __ ] baggy pants and
pink underwear hanging out the back
one looked at the other he goes I'm
telling you man Ronnie's a
[ __ ] the other's going I know totally
I'm like how gay was the Unseen man in
this
vignette what did they catch him doing
battling around in a swimming pool full
of jizz
man I'm not as uh I'm not as Canadian as
my dad holy [ __ ] man he is Uber Canadian
he's the he's the most Canadian man ever
man he used to be a
mounty yeah beat
that yeah like no like he used to have
to wear the red jacket and the hat and
not just at like a fancy dress party no
he had to go to work and then do [ __ ]
with other
mounties but that's the thing about that
red jacket and that hat they only wear
that once a year during the musical ride
and my dad told me this story like in
the 60s when he first started be a
mounty he was a mounty in B National
Park which like there's a city there
there's like a tourist City there's not
not just like a mounty for
Animals hey
beavers is that your log
well then put it
back yeah I know like for people and um
and they yeah like I say they only wear
that one one day of the year and that
was the day he' rushed back he was
running late to do the Musical Ride and
he changed it into the red jacket and
the hat and he was rushing out of the
Detachment and the dispatcher stopped
and went
George probably not like that probably a
little
soberer he said
George there's a bear in the pantry of
the bamp National Hotel now protocol
when that happens is you have to get a
park ranger down with the tranquilizer
dart to shoot the bear but if you're
going to discharge a firearm within City
Limits you need a police officer present
so she goes just go down and witness
this and then you can go off to the
musical ride so it goes to the bamp
National Park Hotel and it's full of
American tourists in the lobby who know
that something's up but they don't know
exactly what's up but he walks in and
they're all like same Margaret I told
you that's how they dress there's one
right there night
now and he walks down into the pantry
and the Bears there licking a jar of
honey you know not doing anything wrong
and the park Warden there with the with
tranquilizer D going George you witness
this he says yes I witness this shoots a
bear bear passes out they get four Hotel
Porters down you know them dudes with
the circular hats dressed like
monkeys Yeah man they get four of those
dudes down and each grab the leg of the
bear and now they got to walk the bear
through the
lobby as my dad follows them and the
park ranger follows my dad and there is
now a stunned
silence and everyone's looking us to say
what the [ __ ] happened and the park
ranger points at my dad and goes one
[Laughter]
[Applause]
punch m
sneaky oh let's have some
[Laughter]
water yeah man I don't mean I know if
there's any Canadians here I don't mean
to disparage our country's fine name but
um I I actually I like Canadians but I
hate doing shows for
them [ __ ] horrible sometimes you like
not all the time some of the shows are
good but sometimes they just stare at
your jokes as if they were the ramblings
of a man who'd flouted the bicycle
helmet laws and paid a very dear price
indeed like it just hurts their ears
sometimes like I had one dude come up to
me after the show and he's like younger
than me he's like
so how's it feel know you just offended
a room full of Christians I was
like honestly
good now you know how I feel when you
talk but what bothered me I was just
being flipping there what bothered me
about what that dude said is that as a
comedian I don't want to offend a room
full of
anybody but he was like
Christians I
was
what not just humans
Christians well they've never done
anything wrong have
they how dare
I cuz usually I won't I won't get in an
argument with people after a show you
either like the show or you don't I
honestly in my heart of hearts don't
give a [ __ ] if you don't like
it but I I got I got into it with him I
was like so whates you think you's got
some sort of inalienable right to never
hear anything you disagree with on a
standup comedy stage and he went because
Christians built Canada I said no they
didn't Chinese slaves
did and I know you probably don't know
what I'm talking about cuz as a country
and as a Canadian we very rarely ever
talk about it you may have seen all the
commercials come to Canada we've got
everything we got ice hockey we got the
mountains we got the oceans yeah where
did the railroad come from I don't
know it was just
there I think the Indians built
it with help from the
Beavers yeah man but that's the thing
that's the thing about religious offense
and now that I mean that's what bu them
the most too cuz I wasn't just standing
up saying God's knob no I was like
pointing out [ __ ] from their book and
that bugs them way more than just going
God's a [ __ ] because if you actually
point out stuff from the book that's
when they get their hackles up like you
may not quote that only we may and the
meanings of those change when we need
them
to but that's the thing about religious
offenses it only ever takes place
outside of the religion people who don't
believe in it say something that's when
they get their big hackles up going you
may not say that you are
wrong you know like how come it never
takes place inside the religion like
every time a Christian sporting athlete
wins something he'll generally thank
Jesus Christ and the Christians in the
crowd will generally cheer along going
yeah Jesus big win big
guy how come nobody ever stands up and
goes that's not how it works
like if Jesus Christ helped you in a
football match you should keep that
secret that's
cheating God helped
you if Jesus Christ helped you in a
football match that should be a secret
between you Jesus and the gangsters he
owed money
[Laughter]
to and Muslims do it too man uh all
Muslims but there's a certain section of
Islamic Society who's very sensitive to
anything a non-believer does be it
misname a teddy bear or use recycled
paper because it may contain old
editions of the Quran anytime that
happens it's
all I'm
paraphrasing but if we know that they're
that
sensitive over any little thing well
then tell me this how come no muslim in
the history of time has ever gotten
upset at the dude who named the city
Islamabad that's mere punctuation away
from
sacrilege how come they never shake the
swords over the sky at that one
is the question I pose to
you man I'll fix them all you give me
half a chance I'll fix all the religions
you know we help you join the next
Millennia like uh no more naming your
kids after Messiah that's done you can't
do that anymore and that's not just
Muslims Christians do it too but they do
it in Spain and they say it wrong so
that we didn't know what they were up
to remember the first time you sus that
Jesus
[ __ ] I didn't know that was Jesus I
thought it was a catchphrase for an
ancient Grecian
[Laughter]
sitcom hey
[Applause]
Zeus yeah man no maner kids after
Messiah especially those two groups of
people Spanish people and Muslims that's
a social ticking Time Bomb because those
are two groups of people who are very
good at
boxing how close are we to see in the
poster 12 rounds live from Las Vegas for
the welterweight championship of the
world Jesus versus
Mohamed I dare say that would be one of
the most contentious fights of our
lifetime
people from both sides of that coin
would show up oh mean Sama Bin Laden
would be there he'd have to come dress
like Batman and act like he was at a
stag do but he'd be
there the pope he'd come he'd have to
come in a big plastic ball like a
hamster but he would show
face chasing his hat around
[Laughter]
yeah
man no more naming your kids after
messiah's it's done and just on a
practical level like if you give birth
to what you honestly think is a little
Messiah why you let him be his own
Messiah why you got to hang him on the
hook with the behavior of all the
Messiahs that came before him cuz here's
the thing only reason we know about
those other size is cuz they were
[ __ ] attention seeking name
droppers when they came down they're
like oh yeah hey Son of God right here
yeah I know everything so just listen to
me because I know everything yeah no no
I'm a Son of
God look at
me you man there could be another
Messiah come along only thing he wants
to do is motorcycle
stunts you wouldn't even know he was a
messiah till the tricks just got better
and better and
better until one day he was in Atlantic
City and he jumped over eight hotels and
he did a loop to Loop of the Moon he
came back with evil coneval in a Mr T
wig of the basket of his motorcycle and
everyone's looking on going oh my God
that is the finest piece of Messiah
jumping I've ever seen in my life well
guess what Sunshine Trick's not done cuz
then he did [ __ ] spinning around in
the air like that and you could see your
granny winking at you from the Moon and
everything turned chocolate and then you
could taste the best soup you ever had
in your life and you look
down you look down and you saw a group
of ants performing The Stunt you were
watching in the sky and you're like oh
my God you are the finest jumper ever
known to man well guess what Acorn
tricks not
done he landed the jump doing a catwalk
and Meatloaf was playing bad out of hell
and his back was on fire and he rummaged
around in his jacket and he pulled out
the eight of clubs which was indeed your
[Applause]
card you looking at him going oh my God
you are the new
Messiah what do we call you you know
what his name is Rick yeah
big Rick and his motorcycle trick and
everyone's looking on going you are the
new Messiah Ricky tell us how to live
Ricky we couldn't possibly figure it out
for ourselves we have no guiding life
from within you're the Son of God you do
the thinking please Ricky tell us that a
little tell you what just put together a
list of very obvious things and call it
a religion please Ricky please Ricky
Ricky Ricky we want to kill [ __ ] can you
help us out Ricky Ricky just give us a
week we go right to Ricky
Ricky Ricky Ricky my sister's
promiscuous can me and my brothers beat
her to death in your name
Ricky
Ricky help us please tell you what just
say something ambiguous we'll take it
from there
[Applause]
Ricky would listen to all these
questions sort of take them
in
turn to the inquisitive
crowd with his only
answer for every question they'
shouted with fear in their
eyes needing to know the
answer and his only reply would
be that's all it could say
man because he actually was the son of
God and he
knew not say
anything because no matter what he
said anyone would just wait for him to
die and then use it to do whatever the
[ __ ] they wanted to do in the first
place so
really if someone says they're a Son of
God it's pretty good proof that they're
not
Ry please
help come on
man tell us
everything help us Ricky and if you're
not going to be Messiah like anymore if
you're not going to be appearing in
toast can you tell us one thing please
where did she
[Laughter]
go 45 minutes
Ricky that young boy's
life Tell Us Where She
Went Ricky would have Jus as
visor look at you and say
maybe she's with the c
driver hot fudge fuckly do big Rick on a
log with a
[Laughter]
frog that may be the
biscuit captain
halet no it's true there's a cap driver
in jolly London Town who hates my
guts well there is man I ruined his
life I didn't mean to but I just said
something flippantly I didn't care the
guy's a [ __ ] but I'm [ __ ] cuz he
was one of these dudes that prefaces
everything he says with I'm not a
racist
but and it's a little trick racists like
to do when they want to say something
racist but they know how inappropriate
that'll be so they say say they're not
going to say something racist then they
say something racist you're like oh my
God how did you do that you're James
bonded bigest
bow so he one of these dud he's driving
along he's like I'm not a
racist
but I know a doctor who says all these
bloody immigrants come from here from
who knows where and all they want is the
free healthcare then they get fixed up
and they [ __ ] off back to where it is
they came from in the first
place I said you're not a
racist immigrants aren't a
race broke his
heart CU he's now driving
going not racist
[Music]
so he had to get one in quick cuz he
didn't know how good of a I'm not a
racist butt player I
am so he goes I'm not racist but Hitler
was right about the
Jews I said the Jews aren't a race
they're a
religion well [ __ ] off they are they're
not a race you have to be
circumcised that's not a race black
people aren't born than painted
black no one has ever changed their race
well one guy did but he's dead
now and while I'm on the
subject why did the authorities wait
till after his death to investigate his
doctors surely when his nose fell
off he call him in for a bit of
questioning like what the [ __ ] did you
do to
him I'm not [ __ ] you man it's what
he
wanted but you know what they
investigated him
over sleeping
pills prescribing him sleeping pills is
the least weird thing a doctor's ever
done to him like honestly if you were
his doctor regardless of how you feel
about this situation if you were his
doctor and he came into your office and
went hey look doc here's the Big Skinny
on my life my face is falling
off and everyone on the planet thinks
that I'm a
pedophile subsequently I'm having a
little trouble getting to sleep at
night hot Coco's not turning out the
lights I mean certainly investigate it
investigate it and if there is some odd
strain of sleeping pill that's killing
musical genius isolate it and give one
to Iggy Pop and Johnny Rotten and be
done with
it exactly they are done they are
finished they are not allowed to say
anything anymore because I don't live in
the UK all the time I come in I come out
and you could imagine my chagrin when
the last time my plane landed I turned
my television on to find out that punk
music had been invented to sell
insurance and
butter that's [ __ ] man and I'm not
one of these people who says people
can't advertise or sponsor things that's
wrong people can't I don't have anything
against advertising my ex-wife Works in
advertising and she's a wonderful
fabulous woman she hates my guts which
is further proof of a good head on her
shoulders but I'm not one of these
people that says you can't advertise
anything you can but I'm sorry I don't
know how much Iggy Pop thinks he knows
about
insurance was he constantly taking calls
like Iggy I got another plan on my mind
no no wait wait let no let let me go
through my
books you can't there's nothing in rock
and roll that would qualify you for
insurance the only thing in rock and
roll that's close to insurance is
calling two dealers on the same
[Laughter]
night butter
John
butter is that what it was all
about Mr rotten you make my stomach
churn
[ __ ]
you [ __ ] you it's a solid
joke that's the worst one that's the
worst one just I remember the first time
I saw the ad I was like they shouldn't
be allowed to use a Johnny Rotten look
Al like oh my
God but it's not Johnny Rod's not the
only one who's done it aie Osborne's
done a butter commercial also which is
what what is it about rock and roll
genius who get to the age of 50 and go
you know what I got to tell everyone
what to put on
toast the only people connected to rock
and roll who could possibly endorse
butter would be
groupes and only as a
lubricant that's that you should never
oo a root lubrication
joke
oh that one went in a little
rough back to the
taxi there with the driver again cab
driver I got him down 2 nil he's never
been in this position before in his life
it should be an easy game all you do is
say you're not going to say something
racist then you say something racist it
should be as easy as racist
pie so he just had to go quick he was
like
I'm not
racist
but a par is right and we should have
[Music]
it pretty racist
H does anyone here know of any reason
why that would not be a racist
comment well well allow me to fire up
the mind blowing machine
[Music]
I said you're not a raises because a
paride is a Dutch word that means
separate it does not connotate black or
white
furthermore when the slaves were freed
from North America after emancipation
there was a group that was given a small
plot of land in Africa called Liberia
which they went back to and and
implemented a paride on the people that
were living there before they got there
so when you say a paride you're not
really talking about a black and white
issue you're talking about an African
culture versus Western culture
issue I'm
right you may never have heard of it but
it's been Googled and
wikipedian but it was funny it was funny
that [ __ ] thing like once I said it
you guys all just sort
of cuz no I know it's cuz I'm talking
about racism on a stand-up comedy stage
and I'm white no I know I'm
white oh it makes uncom it makes some
people uncomfortable if you know if I
was black it'd be fine if I was black
and talked about racism on a standup
comedy stage you'd all clap along just
so I wouldn't think you were
racist but it's cool no it's it's cool
what you did because you should be
sensitive about the issue of racism but
perhaps not so sensitive that you stop
listening to someone's point of view
based on the color of their
[Music]
skin caught you in a little Guardian
trap
there but that's the thing about racism
people only ever notice other people's
racism they never notice their own you
know like uh
one thing that pisses me off really a
lot is um the footballs kick racism out
of football and that's basically the
teams and uh the players and the owners
all Gathering Together pointing at the
fans going uh you're all
racist and stop
it because you're racist I mean by all
means keep coming to the park and
supporting our lavish Lifestyles but we
now also like to tell you all how to
think which is not being racist which is
is what you are being right now so stop
it and here's the thing I know some
hardcore football
holigans who when they when they say
things like that they're like we're
not we're not
racist we don't care what flavor [ __ ]
scores the goal as long as he's wearing
our
shirt we're shirst
we don't like the other shirts but we're
not racist so really if football wants
to have a social program like that maybe
they should get a little more
introspective and kick rape out of
football be a lot easier just get the
players to stop doing
[Laughter]
it don't get me wrong like I uh I like
some of the programs that FIFA has like
I I like the uh thing that they've done
to ensure that there'll be no
hooliganism at the next World Cup
they've uh put it in South
Africa you go ahead and try and be a
little hooligan in South
Africa I dare you to walk down the
street go who want some who wants some
you'll [ __ ] get
some that's a hoans have had an easy
ride what they had Japan and Europe [ __ ]
[ __ ] off I could be a hooligan there but
South Africa everybody's got a
gun you can't pull hooligan [ __ ] there I
guarantee you throw a plastic white
chair you'll be dead before it hits the
ground I'm so looking forward to South
Africa I'm going to be in my
lounge dressed like a
general it's my l
[Laughter]
big TV with the game on little TV with
the news on cuz I don't want to miss a
[ __ ]
thing watching Big sunburnt red English
football Hooligans getting off the plane
come and have a go if you
think oh
folks I'm surprised I can get back up
after that one
that's the second time I've been knocked
down
tonight so it was an early show
Too part of me
thought you don't have to go down for
them not unless they're [ __ ]
[Laughter]
awesome but there was no way I
couldn't God damn it
I now have a testicle in my
anus just hoping it's my
own
criminy still doesn't answer
the age-old
question where the [ __ ] she
is I'm rolling around on a stage here
where'd you
go it's
[ __ ]
bull I
mean could it be my finances girls
is that the kind of
thing that would get you not to come
over late at night for 5 and 1 half
inches
[Laughter]
AOW it's quick too
[Music]
have you got a cramp
no just
done don't worry I'm 35 it'll be back up
tomorrow the early
squirts that's what I like to call them
[Music]
is it whether or not somebody's rich is
that the kind of
thing did we stop you from coming over
girls your silence is
deafening all I can hear is the
inappropriate house music from
upstairs which I mean it's just a pub
and you can imagine I'm up here going
I'm trying to record a DVD who wouldn't
drink in a pub if unless he could
hear that's just some Insider
talk is it
girls would you not come over cuz I was
not a wealthy man cuz here's the thing
I'm actually not as poor as I appear to
be no I could have afford to dress a lot
better than I do but I don't for one
very simple reason and that is that I
[ __ ] hate rich
people I can't stand them I think
they're the biggest pack of [ __ ] who've
ever walked this fine Earth of ours I
don't want to be connected to them in
any
[Applause]
way cuz here's the thing I know I'm
scruffy I know that and when I meet
somebody new I usually have to say five
intelligent things in conversation
before they treat me like I'm not
mentally
[ __ ] number six I get to take the
cork off of a
fork and I'm not saying that there's no
reason to treat people like that I'm
just saying that there's now been a sea
change and the treatment of people like
me have received since the dawn of time
should now go to people who wear
business suits and drive big flashy cars
cuz look I know I [ __ ] my job up
before got a little drunk sometimes came
on stage sometimes I tell jokes that are
inappropriate for the room I'm playing
but I've never [ __ ] my job up so badly
that the government had to bail me out
with 750 billion [ __ ] dollars
next time you see a dude in a suit walk
by kick him in the
ass and when he turns goes hey man what
the hell is that for just go go get my
[ __ ]
money you don't have time for lunch
Chad you got to get the
money cuz it was just so arrogant what
happened man we were all just living Our
Lives
regular then one day bunch of dudes in
suits showed up they're like oh yeah man
something Heavy's gone
down and we're going to need like 750
billion to
start what do you need that money
for oh you wouldn't
understand why don't why don't you try
me I have to tell
you oh
okay here's what went down there was
some subprime toxic Mortgage Debt
money like that's your
excuse I've heard better excuses from a
junkie for where the money
went uh yeah
man I had
it and then I left the window open
and you know that little yellow cat who
lives in the
neighborhood he took
it but it's cool cuz it closed the
windows so he can't get in again so if
you just give me the money again I'll go
get that thing I said I was going to get
in the first
[Music]
place you know what I'd be willing to
let Rich folks have another go if I
thought the next generation was going to
be any better if their kids were running
around dressed like hippies making peace
signs and be like yeah man let's see
what
happens but their children
are their children dressed like gangster
rappers for some reason which by the way
there's nothing wrong with doing if you
are indeed a gangster
rapper but if you're some rich little
punk you can't dress like a gangster
rapper what are you trying to fool us
all into thinking like oh my look a [ __ ]
has moved into the basement of that
Mansion how odd
but you know why rich kids dress like
gangster rappers is because they want an
air of criminality about themselves they
want to be able to show up to the mall
and have everyone go oh my God it's a
gangster rapper run hide anything could
happen kid you want to dress like a real
criminal dress like your
dad dudes and Suits have done far worse
crimes than a gangster rapper could ever
dream of I guarantee you a load of
gangster rappers have never teamed up
and stolen the mineral from a developing
country that's never
[Laughter]
happened the album would be too
long I'm not afraid of gangster rappers
man you got a gangster rappers two major
crimes what are they pimping and drug
dealing they're not even
crimes it's social order if a girl's
going to work she needs a manager all
right I don't agree with
him but a drug dealer that's not a
criminal that's a farmer
helper know who your enemy is man you
see three gangster rappers on your front
lawn looking at your house they want the
contents you see three suits they want
the
house know who your enemy is and stop
sanitizing the world for the Western
businessman that's going to stop but we
do do that you look at any newspaper
nestled in the middle it's the business
section and it's all charts and graphs
and little stories you should call the
rest of the newspaper the
[Music]
consequences stop making it there world
but we do man and it starts with stop
indoctrinating your children into
implicitly trusting people who wear
suits that's got to end but we do that
you you look at any way a little boy is
treated you want to look good son you
put on a suit suit are good you're
getting married you put on a suit we
want you at your wedding in a symbol of
corporate
greed that's how we want you to start
your marriage and know if you get in
trouble you better put on a suit you're
going to court you put on a suit judges
like people who wear suits they trust
people who wear suit
why the most honest people I know wear
Iron Maiden t-shirts
every
day that's the way it should be should
be son you really [ __ ] up you got to
go see the judge now which is it aces
high or live after
death and if you don't understand that
reference you're a big part of the
problem yeah
man stoping stop making it through world
but we do do and we got to start the way
we start is by punishing the bankers
it's yours to take back but that's when
people get Wiggly
about how how can we get how can we take
it punish the
bankers punish them I know it's crazy I
know it's a crazy idea cuz people you
know you've got it you've got it
indoctrinated from a young age I what
did they do they were dressed pretty
nice when they did
it I mean what did they actually do I'll
tell you what they actually did they
took your [ __ ]
future they have it you think of your
kids it's it's just bankers and and not
for anything cool like it's no big like
social movement that's going to make the
world better it was just to fund their
[ __ ] Lifestyles which if you ever
knew one is just horrible it's all about
a big boat and a wife that they dipped
in plastic it's [ __ ] weird and that's
where our [ __ ] future is with them
[ __ ] that it's time to punish them and
you can act like you don't have to
punish them maybe they won't do it again
no that's incorrect because historically
Bankers are the only people that Jesus
ever yelled
at it's in the Bible
man it's the only time that it was like
yo yo jeez geez what are you doing [ __ ]
off I just got to say
this I'm the son of God and I every
ounce of me wants to turn the other
cheek right now but you guys are
[ __ ] don't touch me
Peter [ __ ] off Judi
no
no punish the bankers man and don't get
me wrong I understand the correlation
between fashion and crime I get it like
I already like but I would totally be on
the side of the Somali p Pirates if they
actually dress like
Pirates and it's negotiable too if we
sat him down and went look love what
you're doing with the piracy I want to
put a knife in my teeth and swing Along
with you
but who is doing your wardrobe my God
what is that a Chicago Cubs Jersey and
some
reok you are like a pirate DVD of a
pirate so here's the deal okay if you
make an
effort like a full-on effort I'm talking
like a feathery hat a billowy shirt some
high leather boots up to there I don't
care if you get them from a
stripper but if you meet that criteria
we as the Western World will promise to
only ever fight you with
swords negotiable man punish the bankers
though that's what I'm trying to tell
you that's my that's my biggest word to
you tonight punish them but people don't
know know people
like how how how can we punish him I
don't know
prison and not the golf school they go
to no no a [ __ ] Penitentiary that'll
learn them I they'll start thinking
about their lifestyle choices when they
got a 300 lb cellmate who's a wrestling
fanatic with a Brutus The Barber beef
cake tattoo on his shoulder holding the
Banker's head down into a bed going now
you can try not Kicking and Screaming
but I can't come if you
don't I need you kicky like a little
froggy it's a very distinct motion but
you got 10 years to learn how to do
it don't you dare back out on me
now you know I'm right you know I'm
right
and like it's not I'm not saying
anything crazy because we do know that
you can punish people over [ __ ] with
money we know that like if a guy Robs a
Bank that's 10 years in prison Bank Robs
a guy that's a government bonus where
the
[ __ ] how the hell did that happen man
and if you want to figure out an
appropriate punishment for these Banker
Pricks for what they've done to you I
got a little game you can play just
pretend in your
head that people who look like me had
done
it what do you think you would have
done if people who look like me had cost
the Western World a trillion
dollars you would have killed
us you would have had another Holocaust
we would have been lured on the trains
under the ospice of an ACDC
[Laughter]
concert
yeah huddled in the
showers and then found it very hard to
gas
us see I have to have a
shower never had one before ACDC concert
before in my life
quit touching me Ronnie for [ __ ] Sak
it's not prison
anymore how'd you get
out missed
you okay turn the shower on for [ __ ]
sakes I don't miss none of concert okay
turn the
shower he
yeah hey guys what's coming out of these
[Music]
things bartender don't turn it
off come on man we're having a party
turn it back on enough of this cyclon B
give us the cyclon
[Music]
a come on bartender turn it off
please but if you're not going to turn
it back on tell me one thing where the
[ __ ] did she
[Laughter]
go 45 minutes almost done man we got to
clear out there's a big disco on
upstairs that they couldn't have [ __ ]
turned down for any of
this do you realize how difficult this
will make the edit partender
how pointless it'll make doing two shows
if half of it's got [ __ ] dance music
on and the other half doz
it I dried the sweat stains out of this
shirt for City not knowing about the
[ __ ] Rave
upstairs cuz who couldn't enjoy their
Sunday bangers and mash without a bit of
Groove Armada
[Laughter]
we've all got problems
bartender I got a
problem just tell me where she went man
we can all go
home and then I got my
answer when the phone rang
again and there she
was I was like
you [ __ ] of
Babylon how dare you how dare
you I was on my
home
alone not doing nothing to no
one and then you called and you did not
arrive and now I have a ball bag like a
spacehopper
you
[ __ ] and I'm sorry to make a gender
specific because I know what could
happen between a guy and a guy or a girl
or a girl but I make it gender specific
because it is gender specific because
you and when I say you I mean
women aren't as big as us so you can't
punch
us so you have to do tricky [ __ ] to get
inside our heads
well
congratulations you're inside my head
why don't you have a root around look at
everything I don't want anybody to see
like the monkey porn yeah take a look at
the monkey porn I like their little
hands on their furry little backs I know
it's weird that's why I don't tell
anybody about
it why don't you see if you can tune out
the drunken clown who's looking for
Elliot I don't know what he means either
but oh for 10 years ever since I fell
off my bicycle
OT is he in here
no Every Time I Think of celery he
speaks German you figure it
out you know what I'm actually I'm
actually interested to hear what your
excuse could possibly be for this
indignation done to
me and that's when she said in a much
more angrier
well um
yes why don't you give me the address of
the place you live in now you
prick I don't know if anyone's ahead of
me on this
one but I was so
intoxicated I accidentally sent my booty
call to my ex wife's
house don't worry I played it real cool
I said
uh no
way you didn't ring the bell did you she
said no I did not I said how are you
dressed she said like a
slot I said ring the
bell oh [ __ ] folks you have been awesome
I was a little slow off the top and you
um stuck with it regardless um and uh I
think you'll probably get into about 70%
of the DVD so
congratulations but it was wonderful uh
to talk to you all I don't know where my
life is taking me I I know where I'm
going it's not like I'm being put into a
van and then you know gunthorp
um oh but I uh I'll I'll definitely be
back in England at uh some point to say
hello to all of you again thanks so much
for coming
[Music]
[Applause]
you I don't want to around this
house I got I
do you don't like the way I break the
rules I got better
yeah man we always got time for Kiki's
favorite joke this is a little DVD extra
that is that's the end of the show so
clap a little longer
[Applause]
this last joke is uh more prophetic than
you think it's about uh stopping
drinking uh when you don't want
to and only [ __ ] is that
hard I don't know if anyone's here has
ever tried to do that when you don't
want it like when you want it it's but
when you don't it's
like because your body has a host of
Tricks not just one like a bunch like
hey I'm going to reach for that coca
colola how' a beer get in my hands brain
what I don't
know you must have picked it
up but uh I tried to stop drinking once
and my brain uh used to have its
favorite trick to play on me and um that
would be uh I'd be sleeping in my own
bed cuz I wasn't
drinking as opposed to when you are
drinking and it's in like a rose bed
or a truck
bed some guy named Warren's
bed I don't know who you are
either if I could find my pants I would
leave they're on your
head I
know I'm the party pharaoh
[Laughter]
i' be asleep in my own
bed and uh my brain would want boo so
much he used to play this trick just to
make it so FL I'd be having a
dream and uh in my dream I'd get offered
a alcoholic liquor
drink but because I had it in my
subconscious that I didn't drink anymore
I would decline said
libation and then I'd wake up and go
[Applause]
[ __ ] I could have had the
drink there's no ramification to
behavior in dream world you can do
whatever you want I should have known
when the bartender was an
[Applause]
octopus desperately trying to get back
to sleep to find the under the sea
bar all I can find is Mickey in a
welding helmet trying to get his dick
out so you can do whatever you want in
your dreams man you can you
can be in trouble which is good cuz I'd
hate to stand trial for some of the [ __ ]
I've done in my
dreams can you imagine if you could get
in trouble for things that you done in
your dreams like you're having your
morning breakfast all the a sudden a
couple special officers from dream world
show up knock on the door it's like
[ __ ] Sherlock Holmes with wheels for
legs with a big piece of chocolate cake
with a bobby hat
[Laughter]
on Mr
wall Mr Glenn
Wall yeah man what do you want yeah
we've had some complaints from the
gigantic nuns that run the medieval
bowling
alley apparently you and some French
raccoon spent the better part of last
evening attempting to paint your father
[Laughter]
blue what do you want me to do about it
stop eating cheese before you go to
bed you have any idea what the
ramifications for teaching Down Syndrome
dogs how to be ninjas
is he will spend 22 plums in the
licorice
Penitentiary you have any questions for
him officer gateau
[Music]
why you
do
why no and no no you bad
boy bad boy
come
here couldn't have said it better myself
[Laughter]
[Applause]
folks good night
[Music]
[Applause]