[Music]
I mean I don't know why I'm even so
[ __ ] wrapped up in this idea of of an
afterlife I think part of it to do that
I'm getting older my family's getting
older and they're starting to get uh
health issues I mean the last time I was
here I'm a European tour I received one
of those circular emails from my mom you
know the kind that includes every member
of your family you know and that happens
is either going to be good news or
horrible and it definitely was the
latter long story short family member of
mine going in for emergency surgery 5050
whether or not they're going to make it
email me the next day and tell me how
when of good news is ladies and
gentlemen she made it she's going to be
with us for years and years to come but
I got a little
emotional and I hit
reply
all and I sent this message to every
member of my family I said look I know
since my divorce I've been a bit weird
there's reasons for that but I'm coming
out to Canada and I'm going to be around
the people I feel most comfortable with
P.S I love you guys and I'm 40 years old
and I don't give a [ __ ] who knows I love
my family I don't think that's unmanly
or a feminine if you H some in your
family you feel that way but
you tell them you tell them and you tell
them tonight because you may never get
another chance but if you do
it with an email take my advice and
proofread your [ __ ]
email before you send it cuz sometimes
it's not about the words you do say it's
about the words you leave out cuz maybe
you're a little hung over in a different
time
zone cuz I finished that heartwarming
email to my family with the message PS
I love
[Music]
[Applause]
guys let me walk you through that email
one more
time I know since my divorce I've been a
bit
weird there's reasons for
that I'm coming out to Canada
to be around the people I feel most
comfortable
with
P.S I love
guys you know my biggest problem with it
was no one called me on
it and not in how dare you say you're
gay way I don't give a [ __ ] if you think
I'm gay but you think one of my brothers
a little close to my age at some point
would have chimed into the email chain
with a oh for [ __ ] sakes Glenn it's
2017 no one gives a [ __ ]
anymore just change your Facebook status
stick a [ __ ] in your mouth and shut the
[ __ ]
up little drama
queen there is no reason on God's green
earth for you to drag your dick across
your anch cat Welly ma that's Glen wo
Creator I am but a
[Applause]