[Music]
hi I'm Keith fit I'm the director of
conventions tourism and public relations
for the city of St
Paul are you a comic book or fantasy
convention or maybe you're a tourist
who's run out of places to
[Music]
go or maybe you're a public access show
with nowhere else to
go if you are any of these or more you
can stop looking cuz you can have a ball
in St
Paul St Paul is a vibrant growing city
with lots of things to do and look at
just check out our bustling downtown
[Music]
[Applause]
take a trip through our Zoo we've had no
bear maulings for 3 years keep your
fingers crossed for year
[Music]
four and don't forget to stop by our
Science Museum that's right we believe
in science
[Music]
not only that but a lot of celebrities
are from St Paul like Charles Schultz
Kumo D Alberto V5 and
Grimace forget what you may or may not
know about St Paul rabid pigeon problem
under
[Music]
control here in St Paul we're on The
Cutting Edge of the 21st century
technology we have high-speed bones
[Music]
contrary to rumors we have no more bear
muggings and don't forget to stop by
Midway it's like a slice of alltown St
Paul hey buddy you looking for a
[Music]
date so from what I've told you and a
whole lot more you can already see
there's a whole lot going on in St Paul
so why risk Contracting Airborne herpes
in
Minneapolis when you can have a ball in
St Paul
[Music]