all right this is fancy R M the best
stck man in count we're live on location
here at the beautiful Minnesota
Renaissance festival today we're gonna
have a fantastic show with all kinds of
excitement unusual people and
Renaissance stuff going on don't go
nowhere stay tuned I am the chocolate
human and tonight we are going to get
down with it
ah do
the come on
baby to watch
everybody I said come on
baby want to everybody to do
the I said come on
baby get
[Music]
all right you ugly sucker you ugly oh
you ugly you ugly yes this is fany live
on location here at the Renaissance
Festival I tell you what you think this
is ugly we saw a guy that's even ugli at
the Champs in Maplewood this guy is
called Hawk he's a world champion coming
up next we got Hawk and fancy Ray stay
tuned and it's the fancy Ray Show oh my
so my my my my
my not my boy he mess up my boy oh my
Lord you see what's happening here I
can't believe this should I help him out
I'm oh he he took care of him out jump
in the ring with him I was going to jump
in the ring with him get
him get him get him get
him he take care of him stay tuned we
have fun
ah hello this is fancy Ray M the best
looking man in count I'm live on
location at champon Maplewood and this
guy right here is a familiar face to all
you Twin Cities wrestling fans he
started out years a go with the world
Warriors allegion of Doom he's gone on
to win countless World Championships
he's currently the European headweight
Champion also the Japanese Cod tag team
champion ladies and gentlemen it's Hawk
thank you mer much fancy you know the
only reason you can sit out here and say
you're so goodlooking is because you're
standing right next to me it's an easy
choice you know the guy I just got done
wrestling
Nails he don't care about family he
don't care about fight
he don't care about mom he don't care
about Uncle
Harry and you know what what since
they're his family I don't care about
him either I snack on danger i d on
death and dead men don't make money are
you a rock and roll fan oh yes I'm a
rock and roll fan dead men that make
money in rock and
roll are Elvis Presley and his
wife M now we're coming back with some
fighting work now you got me pumped up
here so your family is very important to
you
obviously what family you don't have
family who who take this for family oh
man so now you putting up I got a lot of
following a lot of beautiful fans they
love you out there Hulk brother you know
something I'm just happy to be alive and
be able to beat up people not go to jail
you know what I'm saying I know what
you're saying but I think I'd be doing
good in jail too if I was there I don't
think I I'd probably have cell block a
and cellb b b
full of curtain of cigarettes I think
you would too not that you promote
smoking not at all not at all now H how
many years have you been wrestling and
you're so popular throughout the entire
world 10 sick years why you say 10 sick
years that's a interesting it's a sick
business really yes what makes wrestling
such a sick business all you fans what
do we do that sick hit them beat them
they out they got outfits like
this one this is my little sexy thing
you think this kind of sex who dresses
you Boy
George well then who dresses me exactly
M Mike McGee man this is really funky
how you guys now you were of course the
Road Warriors yes still are animals just
out for about 16 months with a spinal
injury oh that's too bad well you know
that's what happens in this rough
business sometimes you can't get the
best of everybody sometimes they get the
best of you man that's true in all
things in life but why form a wrestling
team why did you decide to go a team as
opposed to going
individual I'm going individual in
Europe I'm going individual in Australia
in a lot of the states until animals
healed up I do have a Japanese partner
who's a sick puppy on his own right he
needs psychological evaluation so I
brought him to the states H and when I
he got done with my shrink he's seeing
one my shrink you know it's a big hairy
problem
uhhuh tell me about you what do you do
for a living I know you got this great
talk show when are you going to have me
on so I can Trash you're on right now
you're on right now you want TR trash
your set I'm going to trash your set
right here right now you ain't get trash
nothing pal you're just going to listen
okay yes sir what do you want me to do
sir get down and do me
50 that's on the next show and making
everybody happy like you do the best
that's what I'm trying to do I tell you
what talking about making people happy
something that's real important to you
talking about family as children are
very important to you children are very
important to me there's a there's a a
couple children out here tonight that
are handicapped that I'm very fine them
Kevin is one of them he comes to all the
matches I try to donate some of my money
to him and some of my love
September 8th I'm on lake minona with
all with Hulk Hogan and Joe sensor and
many other celebrities or a bass fishing
tournament for Ronald McDonald cancer
house because you know when you're out
you're fortunate doing what you're doing
I'm fortunate what I'm doing and we have
to spread that back it's not a matter of
getting a pad on the back it's just a
matter of makes us feel good right was
installed by our parents that's exactly
right man that's exactly right talking
about although they're rolling in their
grave looking at me now
I tell you what you know what we're
going to do we're going to come back
we're going to take a look at the haulk
DI something that's very important to
you almost as ugly as me say till time
to get down with
it what a
rush we'll be right
back hi this is Danny Bon you might
remember me from the parri family listen
whenever I'm in the Twin Cities I was in
the fancy R and get down with
it all right this is fancy R back live
on at Champs and Maplewood we're here
with Hawk and we're with the very what
would you say is this attractive I don't
want to be insulted now it's very it's
are you kidding me it's gorgeous okay
it's gorgeous uh tell you a little bit
about this please do you know in my 10
years of beating people up I've been
going to a lot of hospitals all over for
make a wish and all the good
organizations and I've seen a lot of
kids in my years three four five years
old who were watching wrestling their
8-year-old brother threw them off the
couch they broke their neck they're
paralyzed from the neck down from the
waist down which is a tragedy in itself
that's one of the reasons we have this
doll here
concept we have this is a six-foot
version we also I'm in a 4-foot version
the kids can throw them around and not
get hurt you stuff this with old rigs
the one sock left over plastic bags old
newspaper what youever it's
environmental it's two pluses in one and
the kids can't get hurt I don't want
kids watching what I'm doing and trying
what I'm doing I just want them to have
have fun watching what I'm doing I don't
I don't I can't stand the S of children
might a lot of people might out there to
find it hard to see me get emotional but
with kids I get real emotional kids kids
of the world you know that M man that's
exactly right man so the kids what they
do is they take their aggressions out on
this do take their aggressions out on
this doll without anybody getting hurt
no wait a minute I've been known to have
a few parents take their aggressions out
on their doll when like when some wife's
husband didn't come back you know a
little bit too late you know punch the
do a little bit Yeah throw a weight
around his neck throw him in the lake
whatever can you teach me a move on the
Dow here you don't know how to body slam
no just hold on let me let me grab this
mic right here grab that crotch grab the
crch uhuh hold that one there uhuh okay
okay here okay around the other way okay
the other way oh around his shoulder oh
right here and go for
it yes I am the champion he's got a what
about he don't get in the ring with me
what about me and you hooking being a
team man the hawk man I can't do that
but what can you do give you one of my
shirts the Hawkman shirt I have a I have
a fan club can I plug it of course I
what's he gonna do we gon say no and I
one of those yeah you can go ahead and
plug shaking and know what 1800 414 Hawk
you can pick up the dolls you can pick
up the shirts make your kids happy
that's what I try to do all right man
Hulk man we cannot thank you enough than
you very much gentl I know and good luck
me I'm not a gentleman I'm just a
fighter all right ladies and gentlemen
this is Hawk and tell me stay tuned and
tell to get down with it
goodbye thank you my
my I am the best looking man in comedy
shut up I know I look good please I tell
you what to introduce my first guest I
wrote a little poem every day I race
through the Star Tribune like a man
having fits looking for some gossip and
some of CJ's juicy tidbits whether it's
about horse who doesn't like fragrances
that don't come to the ground or prince
who crash his car in the mess up his
Royal Crown every day she fills me with
delight I feel like JJ on good time
she's
Dynamite yes
yes in fact she writes about Prince all
the time I called Prince up and I said
Prince what do you think of CJ's column
and this is what he
said oh yes yes
[Music]
yeah y'all from the Star Tribune CJ
CJ all
right now CJ I got to tell you one thing
before I say anything you are the only
woman in America that I would switch
jobs with oh really no I'm wrong I'm
wrong some days I'd give you this job
Christina Hefner the the editor of
Playboy I switch jobs with her too
that's one other person one other person
now tell me something now me and you've
been talking on the phone for so long
and you I call you all the time and I
tell you how good looking I am how good
looking am I and you do you think I'm
goodlook CJ now I want you I know you're
gonna be honest am I good-looking oh
shut
[Laughter]
up uh well let me ask you like this uh
are you attracted to me
[Applause]
[Laughter]
well I let me ask you like this then um
you should you should try a different
line of questioning okay how about this
why did you decide to come on the
program today I've lost my
mind and you had everybody in town
calling me and encouraging me to come on
I didn't have anybody call you yes you
did no I didn't yes you did I never
called no one they called CJ who who
told you that I said call you about a
few people really name one um didn't uh
uh Anthony JW Benson call and say I
should do the show I didn't tell Anthony
J Benson to tell you to call you yeah
right you didn't no I didn't no I didn't
I said see but CJ I what the thing is
we've been talking on the phone and you
wrote a thing in your column she said
dear fancy R you might jump up and do
your godfather Soul routin that's why I
have this rope here because I want to
make sure you don't jump
[Laughter]
[Applause]
up please please please please please
unti the Rope I have an apple here and I
know how to use it you'll feel like a
pig on a
spit oh man you must know what I
[Applause]
like now now all you got to do is call
me a couple of nasty names and I'm
ready all right that's really cool now
you know something that's really
interesting how long have you been doing
your job this is really weird well how
long have you been doing your job oh in
this show is
it how long have you been a gossip
columnist um a year and a half that's
why has your column become so
popular I guess because I have crazy
people calling me up and saying that
they're the best looking men in
community and then I should write about
them uhhuh I don't know it's really it's
really clicked where do you get your
information from crazy men who call me
and tell me that the best looking men in
come
and that I you know I need to do this or
I need to do that and so and after I get
these phone calls from these uh people
who've been abusing drugs
then then I try to find people who have
not been abusing drugs to confirm the
information that I heard how do you
confirm now when you write a source you
get like two sources before you put a
story in it depends on what the what the
item is but I try to get as close to the
actual Source uh of the information as I
can okay what happens when you get
something that's not right that you put
something misinformation in that does
happen oh yeah I try to correct it but
that's the nature of Gossip too and Liz
Smith I understand runs a correction
almost every column uhh and I don't have
uh my H stats aren't quite that bad
really okay okay how does that make you
feel that and in fact I ask you that
you've become a celebrity by writing
this column well it's almost as absurd
as you're being a
celebrity but not quite I don't know but
I don't know why you so hard on me I
someone has to be
what what's the biggest Joy about about
writing a column for you oh I don't know
I think it's a lot of fun and it's
something that I'm interested in and I
don't often get to meet people who've
been growing a mustache as long as
you've been growing
out oh man oh man that's the real the
opportunity to the rare opportunity to
come and humiliate myself on shows like
this that's the other you're not I'm
sing with a ro you talking about being
humili like it I like it it's you it's
you it
[Laughter]
is before the funny thing is now what
what have what go careful what questions
you ask get tighter oh Lord I ain't
going to say that either what what what
what what did you write that got the
most response jez I don't know that's
hard to uh the the people at Mount oliv
are pretty irritated with me last lately
yeah I heard that thing on your answer
machine what did you say oh I don't
think we should repeat it was it wrong
no it wasn't wrong they have a a banquet
a Sportsman's banquet where the women
serve the men and the men honor other
sports male Sports people this year they
are reportedly going to honor a woman
but generally um it's just sounds kind
of discriminatory to me and uh it just
it's outdated let me serve you you you
don't like the idea of women serving men
so you better stay up
under you don't like that idea what's
wrong with that
well um I it just seems like it seems as
though the largest uh Lutheran
congregation in North America could do
something that would be more inclusive
of everyone and this sounds a little
exclusive well that's what see now you
said there's nothing wrong with that
that's your opinion yeah I have a ton of
them all right well I tell you what
we're going to talk more a little bit
more about some more of your opinions
but coming up next no I think this we're
wrapping up with you right now will you
stick around for a little bit oh okay
six six minutes and we stick around we
stick around all right let's get her
stick around and we'll be right back at
CJ stay tuned I'm getting out of this
rope too uh I'm coming out of
this yes yes I see you on the Lake Area
News man I'm on the Lake Area News man
so much good stuff 1993 I'm starting off
in a big way my my my raed the best know
that's right I am the best man look at
the cover cover of the City Pages cover
the City Pages everybody loves I am the
love man can I get a witness can I get a
witness I know this get so much good
press I was on the City Pages Star
Tribune I'm just smoking I'm hot and I'm
on top my my my my I'm the best here in
the Twin States and the whole press of
media knows that the best the best the
the I am the best the Twin City reader
reader says to get out of town what
oo get out of town get out of town well
the press does some things good and bad
and some things I don't understand I
know for a fact they picked on an
innocent humble and very good-looking
man now the twin C say out of this T I
should pack and the first thing I should
do is go but they must have realized
something that all of you already know I
produced the hottest show dance
excitement comedy I've done everything I
could I don't belong in Minneapolis I'm
going to Hollywood
give all right stay tuned cuz we're
going to get out
all right yes yes yes yes now I
understand Sid Hartman's a good friend
of yours too close personal friend close
personal friend good he won't take me to
the Mount Oliver all Sportsman's banquet
he want to touch that one you want touch
that one how do you get along with the
other rid at the Star Tribune fine fine
now your personality you're you're kind
of like you you you got like a rough
kind of Edge on your personality and you
don't uh it's it's sweet around the
corners oh is it that's because you tell
everyone that I tell you what now you
what is that that's something I'm going
to give you soon as you stop Ying okay
okay no go ahead go ahead no I got
something I want I want to do with you I
got something I want to do with you oh
no oh yeah oh no here let me give you
this cuz I know I do this this is one of
the mugs that uh we give to people who
give give us tips okay and uh the little
cat pops out of the uh bag when the cup
is has warm uh any warm substance in it
oh man I'll make my cup run
over all right come on now join me over
here for a second CJ oh come on come on
come on come on CJ come on oh come on
come
on come on come on come
[Applause]
on CJ CJ CJ CJ come on CJ first let's
find out what it is all right here we go
I'm going just show you hold on yeah get
it come
on all right first you go I'm show you
this a a little quick little dance ready
what we can do put your hand like this
you flap your hand and then you see
start kicking do like this do like this
and then you know come on come on you're
doing the [ __ ] chicken now he all
right CJ got shy on me over here but I
want to thank CJ for coming out give CJ
a round of applause
CJ what all right this is fany R the
best looking man in County Today W we're
live on location here at the Minnesota
Renaissance special is y'all already
have a good time here come on in all
right come on in my my my my my my my my
my my today today ladies and gentlemen
we are going to have a good good time
don't go nowhere stay tuned I'm fancy R
having a good time hey hey wait a minute
wait a minute wait a minute you keep
touching me like that you going to pay
me
$2 stay tuned it's time to get down with
[Music]
it stop
all right this is fancy R M the best
looking man in County You Are I Am the
Lord mayor William Cooper this is where
I am mayor I suppose now as mayor what
are your duties as mayor I do as little
as possible as mayor after all it's
Politics as Usual I am known as the best
mayor money can buy all right well that
sounds great how could one run for May I
think I might make a good mayor well you
could run for mayor only if you can find
The Ballot Box my son Henry pulls it
along to different locations for 5
minutes only and then we move it again
it's a guessing game so you have to be
fast so you'll being power for a long
time a long time a long time who's the
lovely lady oh this is the lady I'm the
lady Morgan of Avalon wow well
said well it's nice to meeting you
lordship mayorip pleasure sir oh the
pleasure is all mine have a good time
you also all right thank you very much
oh oh
ow all right now we're going to bring
you the best in television because this
is good versus evil I am the best
looking man in comedy and this right
here is I am the Lord highest Sheriff so
and I would say to that best looking
part I would say that thou should be
pursued by the fashion police for your
violations wait a minute you talking
about fashion what is this stuff you got
on here man these sir are called party
tights they partly colored this is a
leather doublet of the finest leather
well draw your sword if you want to talk
like
that if I ah you're afraid of the beauty
the beauty will prevail that's right if
I good always goes over evil that's
right if I draw my sword it might be
longer than your sword and then we'd
have trouble pull pull your sword out
let's see all right let us see here
I can't even see my face oh I'm the
winner and I like the dinner woo next
year you better try to do something with
your
ker can you do thrust and Peres with the
thing let's
see I'm still the best oh thanks a lot
Lord I won shut
up what's going on here this is the last
chance to get the king's nuts well keep
watching you and be you can have my nuts
all night long ow
you're doing real good you're doing real
you how you guys doing I we're doing
just fine wonder what do you like
working about the the Renaissance
special what's the exciting thing about
it eating this the whole atmosphere the
whole atmosphere we've been around here
for 20 some years it's just a good place
to be we like to work here well that's
great that's great what would you
recommend the viewers out there come and
check out if they come out to Rance
Festival well I think what you got to do
is talk to CJ and then come then come
out with her oo that guy's going to get
me in trouble she kind of downgraded you
a little here didn't she oh but I put
her up on the upside and then we down
stroked Oh My My My thanks a lot party
up
oh all right yes fancy R is live on
location I got two very um interesting
people here what's your name I'm Floren
the fa the arch Duke of middlex one of
his Majesty's fashion
consultant what's your name
and what do you do well I'm a lady and
waiting what do you do ah i' been you've
been waiting for me baby I'm the
man now you're
F you are so
forward oh
anyway so how do you talk about fashion
how's my fashion look today
well let's see um Michu is wearing a
fabulous corduroy set of drapes and oh
and very Charming yellow tights and you
know what that means yellow yellow kiss
the
fellow not
today uh and what do you think of my
outfit white white shoes after Labor
Day
oh well what can I say I'm the best
thank you guys a lot okay a dreadful
miscalculation fabulous to meet you and
hi everybody out there in TV lad
M
FY all right this is fany R I'm here
with Isaac bloodx Isaac blood X and the
dancing queen of America the dancing
queen of now show me a move dancing
queen of
America that's the winner that's the
winner that's the winner now the reason
I stopped I got to ask you a question
you you're out here at the Renaissance
Festival and you're desk with the
Vikings how are the Vikings going to do
this year I'm going to do well Vikings
always do well that's all you can say
are you excited are you out there as a
mascot well no I'm not can you do the
Vikings or a yell or
something yeah I can do the horn blow oh
I want to see you blow my
[Music]
horn all right thank you guys a lot all
right oh my now show me that dance again
here one dance with
me the Renaissance Festival is the best
didn't you agree oh definitely oh Lord
have mercy uh cut camera Break Time
Break oh my my my my my I am the best
looking man in County oh I can look at
my mirror if I want to as gorgeous as I
am you know you jealous of me I'm the
fanciest one out there the prettiest
thing I've ever seen o look at my hair
to baby I know it looks good I'm the
prettiest thing out here in comedy you
used to be the best looking man in
comedy stand homeboy no sorry no I am
the best looking man in comedy I am no
I'm the best looking man in comedy I am
the best looking man in comedy I'm the
best poet in comedy well okay let's hear
your poem let me tell you the story of
FY Ray the most beautiful man in comedy
today when I was born the moon didn't
rise only the stars came out in L of the
skies and by the time I reached the age
of five my mom i' be the prettiest man
alive I knew I'd be a success and I did
knock on wood I just looked in the
mirror oh honey you look
good my my my my my top that one
emo my name is
emo I like to break open Oreo cookies
and tuck out all the
[Music]
Creo emo you check your mirror and I'm
fancy Ray and it's time to get down with
[Music]
[Laughter]
it well all right this is fancy red live
on location here at the Renaissance I'm
on the boat woo grabbing the rope and
I'll tell you one thing fancy R says no
to dope before we go any further I want
thank my fantastic sponsors I want to
thank Insight newspaper where you can
find my T cast schedule hair by J with
Styles my hair do and also my new
sponsor mink magic with all these new
hair care products mink magic I hope you
enjoyed the show I've had a good time
tune in next week and get down with
[Laughter]
it your I'm tell you I'm coming to get
you pal terrific yeah all right all
right wait a minute against the Splash
in the Royal Gan all right well I'm
ready right now now I'm telling you I'm
telling you what's your name Russ Russ
Russ you're going to get beat the death
here you know that oh you think so I
will I will be victorious I predict I
will be victorious do y'all agree that
I'll be victorious I agree all right my
my my my my I'mma hit him with my pretty
stick that's right man is a guru all
right here we go take it here oh no I've
never done battle with little let's get
the designer bags the designer bags the
design I'm getting them I'm mad design
oh o psychology this is psychology all
right here be the rules one hand behind
thy back at all times Target is below
the shoulders above the KNE two falls
out of three will declare the winner two
out of three I'm the best I ride the
test I can do no less and you're going
to go and go fetch I want to get you
back ready yeah all right are you ready
to I'm ready I'm I'm ready commence
blood wait wait wait what's
that yes yes the F SW
the Victor the Victor the Victor wait
one more fall you must win two out of
three fcy
f one one to nil my Lord you must win
this fall FY R has won I'm the
Victorious One are you ready I'm ready
ready commence commence
go yes I say the b is even one fall a
piece you would would you swap into the
L how dust thou my Lord I'm good I'm
good now I'm mad now I'm mad now this is
fighting one is even I'm ready one this
one
is for the gold I'm coming to get him
now all right say commence right now
commence oh chion has won the I won the
vout I am still the prettiest I am still
the prettiest M thank you have a
ceremony for you my lord we have a
ceremony for you my lord there's a
ceremony yes my Lord upon one knee my
Lord I know this word might not be
familiar to you if the word is humility
yes
by virtue I know some other H have
handsome by virtue of the power invested
in me by Lord King Henry and by virtue
of the dam good whacking Lord fancy Ray
here has Meed upon this opponent we
award him this proof of his courage
proof of his virtue and proof of his
veril this a piece of the log arise
fancy Ray King of the
L this Lord this log my Lord is thine
hoist it upon thy shoulder and carry it
off the lot
we'll do that next show okay thanks a
lot you
guys my my my my my