New York and you know what these two
things mean socially like how they
reflect uh you know society and
capitalism whatever um that's kind of my
[ __ ] you
know hi I am Jake Flores where you from
Jake uh I'm from Austin Texas originally
as a comedian living in New York in
Brooklyn for the last four or five years
I'm from Texas
I live in New York and some [ __ ] now
but I'm from
Texas don't [ __ ] with me like I'm not
from
Texas I don't know why I'm doing this
accent but I'm from
Texas hey I'm from Texas here I don't
know what I'm doing right but I'm from
[ __ ] Texas
okay and I'm woke as [ __ ] about
gender and those two things mean one
goddamn thing you call me by my
preferred
pronoun y'all
[Laughter]
right y'all is the best
pronoun you will never misgender someone
if you're just walking around drunk all
the time calling everyone [ __ ]
y'all and what were some of uh your
favorite comedians growing up oh man
um you know when I was really young I
would watch you know just comedy Central
and and not really know who I was
watching and I'd meet these people later
on you know when I was when I was doing
standup or whatever I remember watching
Marin when I was real young really
liking it it's I think about that a lot
and it's pretty weird you know I was
like a 10-year-old who was like I get
this cynical egotistic like Bohemian guy
but I did yeah you you've met some of
these people how disillusioning did that
end up
being oh it's it's varies from person to
person you know like they say don't meet
your Heroes and a lot not a lot but some
times people tend to you know let you
down be a little bit of a mess and then
sometimes it's like oh they're
everything you thought they were going
to be a lot a lot of comics I could say
I worked with who I was big fans of
proved me right you know they were great
um some I won't name complete [ __ ]
psychos but it goes with the territory
yeah you came from Austin now you're in
New York um I know there's a lot of
differences between LA and New York
stuff what are the differen is kind of
between doing comedy in Austin and doing
comedy in New York City somebody want
describe new York to me is a city with
like an exclamation point on it like no
matter what it is it has a exclamation
point you know it's like when something
terrible happens like worse than it
would be anywhere else but then when you
have like a great set you know you were
you were there next to some [ __ ]
famous person you used to watch on TV
you know and you you reach these high
highs or whatever uh so it's just kind
of like living in an exaggerated fast
motion I lived in Austin forever there's
always old musicians that'll just you
know work a job make a record in their
spare time you ask them how's the record
coming they go great you know they don't
go I'm going to be on America's Got
Talent tomorrow and it's going to make
my career you know it's just you love
what you do and you make a
thing uh humors the uh stand up Records
album we made a few years ago
um I uh well there's a lot going on
there it's actually kind of fitting that
we're in Minnesota right now cuz one of
the reasons I I decided to call it humor
is I was think I was a lot about The
Replacements and uh I really liked their
sort of sense of humor and their
antagonist antagonism with like the
music industry and just the concept of
selling your art and that sort of [ __ ]
you know so they made an album called
Let It Be yeah that's a very funny thing
to do you know just name your album like
after somebody else's clearly famous
thing you know so um that kind that idea
kind of collided with h just a
conversation I was having with a friend
of mine we were trying to figure out the
funniest album cover of all time and uh
I think Fleetwood Mac Rumors is just one
of the weirdest [ __ ] things ever you
know so you can see the dots connecting
then oh [ __ ] rumors I'll call it humors
it's also kind of a double on Tandra for
the way the med medieval you know people
would uh refer to your bile and your
insides which to me comedy is sort of
adjacent to you know uh I've been
accused of puking out jokes a few times
um uh I was in college and I was I was
dating this girl she's drawing a picture
of me right we're hanging out she's
drawing a picture she goes hey man I I
don't know if you know this but you have
very wide set eyes you have very exotic
features right and I was reading a
textbook and the textbook was telling me
that WID set eyes are often a byproduct
of fetal alcohol
syndrome so here's why I shouldn't have
kids though cuz I turned to her and I
said uh hey you know be really funny is
if I got you drunk or I got you pregnant
h probably both uh and then you got
drunk a lot while you were pregnant and
then you gave birth to a child that we
would name shark face right
cuz eyes would be all over the side of
head able to see in both directions
that'd be hilarious but not in the long
term of that story right you don't need
a sharkface kid living on your couch not
going to Community College playing Xbox
and [ __ ] all day smoking menthols for
some reason I don't know why
I think it's interesting because if you
look at uh humors you see a fresh fa
face clean shave and well not clean shap
but you know I me and this this is what
New York's done to you yeah yeah yeah
you know it's funny that you bring that
up because I've been seriously trying to
cut my hair for like a year straight and
I'm just so [ __ ] busy I just kind of
like it hadn't come up um I kind of have
live a life that's just wall to- wall
[ __ ] work and uh I kind of just
forgot to pay attention to what my head
looks
like this is a part of the show where I
guess I would ask if you guys like drugs
but we can just skip over
that the G the Gathering here we're at
right
now I feel like you guys like people
like drugs but you guys don't even know
about the the good ones yeah check this
out I started doing uh poppers recently
no one [ __ ] knows about this drug
poppers this guy [ __ ] knows there's
like a new woke like some some of you
guys don't know about this
[ __ ] they're fun they're like a disco
drug from the 70s that just gets you
high as you sniff it gets you high as
[ __ ] buy them in a like gas station
or some [ __ ] and no one does them but
everyone knows one thing about them
what's that your but they dilate your
butthole and that's why no one does
them that's the only thing there's an
amazing drug in this little capsule but
no one does them cuz no one wants people
to think that they dilate
your some drugs expand your mind
uh all
right are there any other unheralded
drugs that we need to bring back like
micro dot can we find somebody to make
some micro dot out there what is a micro
dot I don't know I think it's like
really strong acid yeah I think okay
before for my time too I don't know I
don't know man you can't get Quaaludes
anymore can you like they stop making
those uh no I don't I don't think you
can get them anymore but I'm I'm certain
someone's got them stockpiled so where
can people find you yo uh you can find
me on the internet my handle for
everything is at feral Jokes which is an
anagram for my name of Jake Flores it's
just the it became a brand listen to me
on my podcast pod Dam America if you're
into politics and stuff like that uh if
you're not and you're into something way
Dumber you can listen to Mr Cleo which
is a podcast I do where uh me and my
friend Danny Felts get drunk and run a
psychic hotline where I read tarot cards
for people that just call in from
Twitter and [ __ ] that's great uh check
out my Twitter I'll I'll pin my tour
dates um I'm hitting the road come see
me it's always the first tweet it's
pinned at the top spectacular cool
thanks Jake thank
you really dumb way to end
it no I like it it's dramatic