[Applause]
[Music]
ladies and gentlemen Jake Flores
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank
you thank
you you are incorrect though this is a
complete [ __ ] lie the whole thing's a
lie comedy is one giant lie show
business in general uh uh it's it's just
it's just untrue uh I am not a famous
comedian I have a job I bartend I ain't
nobody and it's fine it's fine CU it's
just over it's just over no one gets
paid in America to have a dream anymore
at all it's just
over it's not a big deal it's cool it's
but they're all lying when you watch
Comedy on TV all comedians are lying
Louis CK works at a Foot Locker
uh Janine gar manages a gap
uh Dave Chappelle's a bus boy at Fogo to
Chow Aziz anari isn't even real he's a
hologram right they just superimpose him
at a television it's all [ __ ]
lies uh Jim Carrey is Dana Carvey
they're the same person it's just
all it's all lies and it's fine it's
fine it's fine it's fine it's all right
to have a dream and a job it's fine you
know but the people will discourage you
from presenting yourself that way if
you're trying to make it in music or
comedy or something like that and uh
[ __ ] it [ __ ] the whole system uh it's
fine it's okay for you to get your
entertainment from people like me who's
like my mode of transportation is 2third
of a bicycle right
now because somebody stole one of the
wheels why that's so much more insulting
than stealing the whole
bicycle I have to [ __ ] wheelie
everywhere just to get to work so I can
do this I got arrested on that bicycle
which is a thing that can
happen I was on a bicycle uh I bought a
wheel for it don't worry I got a full
bicycle
going I'm riding it and uh and I I I
start to hear this cop honking like
quacking his car at me not full Sirens
because that would be like comedic level
Overkill
with a you know with a helicopter and
everything it would be awesome but uh
but he you know he didn't want to go
crazy with it so he's just like like
quacking his car at me and I didn't know
what to do I thought he wanted to go
around me so I turn around and he's
pointing like you I'm pointing at you
I'm going to arrest I was like holy [ __ ]
I am getting arrested on a on a bicycle
you know so I stopped I got out of the
bicycle I put my hands on the
bicycle there's no cops episode that
prepares you for this situation
right so I was like what do I do and
this cop he pulled me over and he told
me hey you ran a red light you know
which I did I was going uphill it was
hot there's no around [ __ ] you you know
I ran a red light and uh and the only
reason he pulled me over was just cuz he
was just a cop you know just having a
day just oh all right that's just what
you do I guess if you're a cop so uh you
know so I didn't think it would be a big
deal he was going to let me go but then
he went into his car he did a bunch of
cop [ __ ] and he came back out and uh and
he told me hey I'm taking you to jail
because you have outstanding warrants
right you have old traffic tickets uh
speeding tickets expired tags stuff like
that right uh so I went [ __ ] and then he
took me to jail and
uh I
spent
probably too long in jail for this
specific
charge I might have called the cops
Serpico like a
bunch like a lot
I was in a bad mood you know I threw a
couple Jack Bowers in
there dude busted the crime of the
century right so uh so so I went to jail
jail is
horrible
horrible I had to watch King of Queens
for eight hours it
was unbearable
the episodes weren't sequential nothing
made
sense I'm in jail and uh this dude turns
to me and he says the the classic jail
line to me goes hey man what are you in
for right and I was in for riding a
bicycle
overzealously so I turned to him and I
said I raped a bunch of murderers
and then I murdered a bunch of
rapists and that's why I'm here right
now in Class C misdemeanor overnight
holding I started barking at him like
DMX get in his face you
know and uh and he laughed which was
what I was going for right it was good
cuz for some reason in my mind in jail
I'm thinking like uh oh there's only one
thing that I'm even slightly good at
I'll use that to survive I'll be the
funny guy right somehow you know they
won't that'll get me by I don't know
what I thought was going to happen like
some guy was going to pull a knife on me
and I was going to be like a priest and
nun and a rabbi walk into a
bar and
then somehow not die right uh luckily it
didn't come to that but uh but Jail jail
is is is horrible everyone knows that
the thing they don't tell you about jail
is that it is horrible and
simultaneously really boring and long
right so you don't want to talk to
anybody because you're surrounded by
people with very creatively placed
tattoos and uh just
dumb hair I don't know
just just people that suck you know uh
so you don't want to talk to anybody but
you have to entertain yourself you have
to keep yourself going so here's what
happens when you go to jail you look
around at the group of people that you
are chained to and uh naturally start
coming up with uh nicknames and wacky
backstories for all of them right so uh
so first there was a Lupe the plunger
Torres I don't know
why no one knows why lots of parentheses
middle names going on here you know uh
and there was old sleepy racist face oh
yeah
then there was a an old white man I
called hambone
Butterbean hamone was a farmer who got
into trouble with the law I don't know I
was just making [ __ ] up
right uh then you when this happens to
you you naturally assume the role of
Morgan Freeman the narrator of
jail so I'm looking around the room and
I'm just narrating this whole experience
in my head I'm just like old old sleepy
racist
face he showed it like sticking that
needle into his face you I'm not good at
voices that's as close as going to
get I was in jail I had to make do with
a bad Morgan Freeman impression you
know so I'm going around the room and
I'm just looking at people and ham bone
man he bothered me cuz all right so we
went into this room eventually with a
toilet just in it all willy-nilly
there's just a toilet sitting in the
middle of this room it was not a bad
bathroom in life there are bathrooms and
there are rooms with toilets in them and
if you don't believe me go to jail
there's a room with a toilet in it
right it's
just it's just
there so they put us in this room and uh
and old old ham bone hammy hammy walks
up and he just whips his dick out and
starts pissing in this toilet right and
I'm like whoa like in my head I'm
thinking like hammy hammy no you're an
old white man you don't understand all
sorts of signals you're sending right
now you know but my brain and a much
more immature part of my mind I'm
thinking a old
hammy he shorted like whipping his dick
out cuz that's how you get through jail
right was in jail all night I had to
make do a lot of people when they go to
jail they uh they join gangs they take
up tattoo histry or however you say that
uh
me I went with the Performing Arts
like a person who should never be in
jail I walked around my cell I used the
ham sandwich as a microphone it was very
it was it was cool it was good and
that's how I wrote this bit
interestingly enough that's
a it's my kind of mind blowing right
it's like a snake eating its
[Laughter]
head its own head not its tail its head
I'm going to leave that one in the CD I
think it's
good just analogies that don't make
sense that is pretty freaky though a
snake eating its own head try to imagine
it it's like an eer painting I don't
know so uh so anyway I got out of uh I
got out of jail 24 hours later I spent
24 hours in the can in the can what am I
talking like I'm hard
uh I just hung out in jail and I got out
of jail and the whole thing to be honest
with you it soured me on Jail
uh I don't recommend
it but I I was really I was really
disillusioned by the whole situation
because uh you know I mean just seemed
like kind of a kind of a misuse of the
justice system it was just kind of a
bummer I just ran a red light you know
it's not really a big deal there's
murderers walking free in this country
you know it's just sucks just sucks
right so uh so I wrote a letter to the
police officer that arrested me which I
will read for you right now here we
go dear officer
Vegas we accept the fact that we had to
sacrifice a whole Thursday in jail for
whatever it was we did
wrong what we did was wrong but we think
you're crazy to make us write an essay
telling you who we think we
are you see us as you want to see us in
the simplest of
terms the most convenient
definitions but what we found out is
that each one of us is a
brain and an
athlete and a Basket
Case a
princess and a
criminal does that answer your question
sincerely The Breakfast
[Applause]
Club thanks I mailed that [ __ ] to the
police
I'm got a rested
again oh man I work at a bar I have a
job we've discussed I have a job I have
a job I have tattoos right when you have
tattoos people always tell you hey you
shouldn't shouldn't get more tattoos
because how are you going to be able to
get a job right uh which is kind of a
[ __ ] circular argument because the
same people that say that to you are the
same people that won't hire you if you
have tattoos right so in a few decades
all those people are dead we can all
have tattoos everything's fine you know
but the the argument they always give
you is what I have a problem with they
always say hey aren't you going to
regret what you look like when you're
older and the thing is you are going to
older but it's not because of the
tattoos it's because you're [ __ ]
old that [ __ ] doesn't look good on
anybody right no amount of pork pie hats
and sweater vests can cover up the fact
that you look like a a tongue your balls
look like a tongue that is stuck to a
frozen stop
sign that's what your life is you can't
stop stop it you're going to get old
it's not a big deal it's it's kind of
hilarious this generation of people
right now go crazy we're going to look
like a bunch of old Carneys when we're
we're 90 you know it's hilarious you're
going to look like a a like a
freeze-dried snake your kids are going
to sit on your lap and feed you flies
it'll be great you know and I like it I
the tattoos are really interesting you
know I have a friend who's a a bartender
and he told me this really really
touching story about meeting this great
aunt of his who was in uh the Holocaust
right she was in the concentration camps
and uh he met her like later on life and
they had this like really interesting
touching moment where they were like
looking at each other and he has like
all these sleeves his tattoos you know
his arms or whatever and uh and she has
like uh you know she had like like
prison camp tattoos right and they were
looking at each other and and she kind
of felt this connection like oh we have
the same thing and uh they were just
like sitting there and he was looking at
her like faded concent ation Camp
tattoos and when he told me that I
couldn't believe that she didn't get her
work touched up
right because looking good is important
how else are you going to get a
job I
uh all right let's go here I religion
never really stuck with me as a kid
never really got in my head and I think
the reason for that is that uh I was I'm
half Mexican I was raised by
old Catholic Mexican grandparent people
you know and uh and Catholicism is a
particularly sort of
graphic
weird just spin on that whole thing like
it's uh it's just a lot of weird imagery
and stuff um in particular there's one
character in Catholicism that they use
to sort of scare you uh just it's this
character that's like sort of this like
ominous
Supernatural monster named Jesus Christ
uh Jesus is the scariest character in
The Bible right Catholicism is all just
like these just weird like snuff
pictures of him just mid
murder just all over people's houses you
know multiple pictures of the same guy
being murdered it's it's
weird and he's like he's scary like they
try to kill him and he wouldn't die he
just keeps getting back up like Michael
Myers you
know walking somehow faster than people
are running doesn't make any
sense he's going over water and [ __ ]
he's all seral killery about it you know
he's just like uh I I did this for you
because I love
you holy
[ __ ] it's freaky if you think about it
it's weird it's weird it's a weird
narrative like he's all
just Eat My Flesh and drink my
blood [ __ ] slow down GG Allen nobody
wants to eat
you or drink you
or [ __ ] your corpse or whatever you're
trying to Goat us into here it's freaky
it's a freaky way to go about recruiting
people you know I I don't get it you
know it just it just didn't sell to me
as a kid right I just I don't want that
I just want all I want out of religion
or philosophy or I just want to live in
a world where people are just good to
each other and you know every we're just
not crazy and we're not dicks to each
other you know is that is that something
I can get out of religion you know I
live inside of your heart and I can hear
all your thoughts crazy [ __ ] [ __ ]
Jesus I don't want anything to do with
it uh it just yeah it just never stuck
and I it's It's Tricky doing material
about stuff like that because I don't
want to offend anyone you know these are
just jokes and if you're religious and
you're offended by that you know
uh I don't want to like I don't want to
offend anyone this is just just a comedy
show you know sometimes people come up
to you after the show hey I don't
appreciate what you said about you know
religion or whatever and I never want to
do that to anybody but you have to take
into account the context right you're in
a comedy show right now like uh it's
just people just saying crazy things for
fun like treat me the same way I would
treat you I would never come into your
church and not
[Laughter]
laugh ah all right cool we're on the
same page nobody left let's get started
start the show now
um you guys
drinking
yeah
woo woo woo woo what the [ __ ] is that
what is woo
woo woo is the battlecry of mediocrity I
don't
know why everyone does that if you go
anywhere in America and you go hey guys
drinking tonight go woo Budweiser potato
chips I don't know
[ __ ] America USA they start chanting
USA over and over again it's it's weird
thing it's like in everyone's DNA just
woo like if you just [ __ ] say you
drinking they just wake up and go woo I
don't know
why it's like we all just descended this
country was just kind of started by
these white trash pilgrims that just
showed up
they were talking to some Indians they
were like hey you guys want a slice of
this pumpkin I don't know what the [ __ ]
official story of Thanksgiving is they
ate pumpkins nobody eats a pumpkin you
know like hey you want some of this
pumpkin woo and then it just
started and now you can go anywhere in
the world and get people to woo doesn't
make any [ __ ] sense you can open a
manhole in the
street stick your head in you go hey
Subterranean sewer people you guys
drinking
you'll hear the faintest woo
like it's just a natural [ __ ]
reaction I don't know
why uh I'm drinking cuz I don't have any
reason not to it's great I have nothing
I don't give a [ __ ] I have no
responsibilities I don't need kids
probably never going to have kids you
can just not have kids now like we
reached it socially it's
cool my biology is so mad at me right
cuz like that's your whole deal as a
being is to procreate and further your
biology but I figured out a loophole
where I'm just like I don't feel like
it I want to go to the movies
instead I don't [ __ ] care I don't
have kids that's too much responsibility
having a kid man I don't even take care
of my [ __ ] toes cuz they're so far
away like a child that's just
it's horrible it's too much I shouldn't
have kids here's here's a story about
why I shouldn't have kids right uh I was
in college and I was was dating this
girl she's drawing a picture of me right
we're hanging out she's drawing a
picture she goes hey man I don't know if
you know this but you have very WID set
eyes you have very exotic features right
and I was reading a textbook and the
textbook was telling me that WID set
eyes are often a byproduct of fetal
alcohol syndrome
[Laughter]
so here's why I shouldn't have kids
though cuz I turned to her and I said uh
hey you know be really funny is if I got
you drunk or I got you pregnant H
probably both uh and then you got drunk
a lot while you were pregnant and then
you gave birth to a child that we would
name shark face right
cuz eyes would be all over the side of
head able to see in both directions
that'd be hilarious but
not in the long term of that story right
you don't need a sharkface kid living on
your couch not going to Community
College playing Xbox and [ __ ] all day
smoking menthols for some reason I don't
know
why you know so I don't have
kids I don't have kids I have vices
which are like kids except I like them
uh uh I like them
uh they're fun and they're like kids you
have to keep feeding them and just
they're they're crazy I I there's a lot
of drugs I can't do anymore though
really mostly just drink these days I
used to there stuff I can't do anymore
right cocaine cocaine is the worst drug
because cocaine is the easiest row to
get caught doing because whenever you're
doing it you've got like three or four
forms of ID out in front of
[Laughter]
you so the cops kicking the door and
you're like that is Def Al
me have to play it cool you have to be
like ah it's cool I'm with you guys I'm
working undercover I'm dusting for
fingerprints
haaha I think there are some
fingerprints all over the inside of my
head and on my gums a little bit
too and if you laughed at that part of
the joke you and I are in a very sad
club together
there it's called the 9 in the morning
club cost $80 to
join helps if you know
Spanish it's kind of a racist joke it's
okay I can make racist jokes like that
because I am half white and if you're
white you can just do whatever you want
right the way this country Works
apparently
uh I I'm half
Mexican and I uh I don't you know to
speak Spanish and I don't look a certain
way and sometimes people people give me
[ __ ] about it and they say Hey you know
why aren't you more Mexican it's just
cuz I'm just a person you just you're
free to just be whoever you want to be
you don't have to fit into like cultural
stereotypes and stuff you know and I
just grew up a certain way right so uh
so when people say that to me say Hey
Jake why don't why don't you act more
Mexican Jake Flores your last name is
Flores you're mexic your father's
Mexican didn't you learn anything from
your Mexican father I tell them uh I had
the ultimate Mexican father no
father it's not
true but it's
funny my parents are still married for
some reason I they didn't get the memo
that just love is dead and it's just
it's cute it's cute they think they
think they love each other it's awesome
acid's another one that's weird man I
was reading that acid is a acid was
concocted by the the CIA because they
were trying to come up with a truth
serum which is weird because they got it
almost right because acid will show you
the truth it's just the wrong kind of
Truth like I just pictur them like
interrogating some guy just be like did
you do it did you kill her he's like uh
they're like tell us the truth and he's
like the truth is that we're all made of
stars
cuz that's what you see when you take
acid it's a great drug you know um let's
get into this I uh I used to live in an
efficiency
apartment um the great thing about
living in an efficiency apartment is
that the ceilings are so low you can't
hang
yourself this is
cheap suicide joke it's a joke about
killing yourself it's [ __ ] up shame on
you for
laughing it's all right I'm just [ __ ]
with you I am crazy I'm a [ __ ] crazy
person I'm out of my mind I mental
disorders I'm
crazy don't [ __ ] with
me I'll put a potato in the microwave
and press popcorn I don't give a
[ __ ] about the rules of society all
right
jaywalking all day I I'm not like like
scary crazy just like a [ __ ] just
have like manic depression uh s i I
think I don't have insurance when you
don't have insurance you don't have
diseases you have like unofficial
diseases I you have like a unauthorized
director's cut diabetes you think you
know so I think I have manic depression
cuz I have really weird just weird days
of my life where I just can't get out of
bed you know I'm just like stuck glued
to a TV or something I watch a lot of
Netflix by the way I'm working on a plan
to get the entire country under one
Netflix
account I don't think they would notice
if there was just $7 coming in every
month we all just high
five meet me after the show for the
password
uh I I eat a lot of junk food when I do
this
so my favorite depression junk food is
bugles because bugles are like little
trumpets used to announce that you're
not [ __ ] going to work that
day she like d my ex-wife is a
[ __ ] it's fun it's a little horn you
know I wonder what molder and Skully
you're getting into for eight hours of
my life it's
great it's food man it's
[ __ ] it up I I had a near-death
experience recently because I ate a
large Papa John's Pizza uh I ate this
pizza and it put me down like hard like
I [ __ ] fell asleep for a day cuz I
ate this [ __ ] pizza right don't eat
at Pop That Place murders families it's
not
good I ate this pizza and it like it
tried to eat its way back out of me it
was [ __ ] up and I laid in my bed for
24 hours and like just just try to work
through this thing right and the thing
is when you lose when you lose 24 hours
of your life you lose a whole day right
you lose a a slice of bread in the loaf
that is life so like I don't know what
the [ __ ] happened on that date you know
last year or whatever I don't life
happened right all this drama happened
people went out they they went to work
they went on dates they met their future
husbands and wives a young man graduated
from an HVAC repair course turned his
life around quit the gang and [ __ ] all
this [ __ ] happened while I was just
processing a
[Music]
pizza on my father's deathbed he said to
me he said Jake every day is precious
don't eat at and then he died and I
never knew what he
meant my dad's alive
I he's alive and he's married to my mom
I just a lot of these jokes end with my
dad dying or something because it's a
clever way to end a joke uh so don't
worry rest in peace pops
um you're
crazy sometimes you have to take
anti-depressants crazy experimental
drugs they work for some people they
don't work for me they have weird side
effects you know I took this one pill uh
sometimes they they give you uh bizarre
dreams this one gave me wet nightmares
all right
right it's like I'm terrified right now
I have a boner what is
happening in my
mind you're crazy you date other crazy
people it's just the way of the
world I have this
ex-girlfriend this woman threw a cat at
me while I was in the shower you
understand
it's claws went into the curtain it went
down like that it made lines everyone
laughs you
know it's
crazy you date other crazy people you
learn important life lessons like
sometimes saying I love you is like
saying Candy Man or Bloody Mary or some
[ __ ] do it enough times and someone
tries to murder you in a
bathroom [ __ ] bees
everywhere bees
I'm single uh single what's up I'm
single being single is great being
single is uh it's great because you can
do whatever the [ __ ] you want single got
no kids I can do whatever I want all the
time uh you know it's it's the best uh
being single is a constant party that is
punctuated every once in a while by just
very very brief moments of just bone
chilling existential
loneliness but then it goes back to
being fun and it's fun 90% of the time
so you keep doing it cuz there's no
consequences so being single is just
like it's a it's just all partying and
drinking and whatever and then every
once in a while you're just in your
apartment and you're just peeling a
potato for one and you're just like [ __ ]
I'm going to die alone die alone and be
eaten by
cats reanimated as some sort of lonely
superhero I don't know what the [ __ ] is
going to happen I'm going to die and go
to hell I'm afraid I'm I'm afraid I'm
going to die and go to hell I'm afraid
of Hell which is weird because I don't
believe in hell but I also didn't
believe that bed bugs could survive on
seamen so what do I really
know about
life anything I'm open to new
explanations for the universe you know
I don't
know this guy tried to read my palm a
while back uh you know palmistry you
know you look at someone's hand and then
try to read their future uh if you want
to read someone's future don't look at
their hand look at their
teeth I was on the bus the other day I
looked at this dude I was like you're
going to die yesterday what the
[ __ ] happen to your mouth
[Laughter]
this is a weird one I
uh I don't know I brain plays tricks on
me sometimes I was hanging out at the
bus stop recently it's going in between
towns and uh I was looking at this puppy
this like person was walking this like
cute puppy or whatever and I uh I caught
my brain playing a really weird trick on
me it was like taking a mental image of
this puppy like to I guess think about
later to
better you know like life is that
depressing and everything's a nightmare
I guess and uh and I realized that's the
same mechanism you use for the spank
bank which uh if you don't know what
that is it's like a some people walk
around and then like take mental
snapshots of women basically and go home
and jerk off about it I'm not saying
it's a thing that I do I'm just saying
that it's a thing that people do that I
do a lot
and I'm spank banking this puppy and I'm
like Jesus Christ is that my life has
come to is that how bad it is you
know cuz I mean sometimes you're just
like in a bus and you're just watching
States pass by and you're just it sucks
you're just just zoning out and people
are just everyone on the bus is just
thinking like I wonder what time we're
going to get back to Texas and you're
just thinking like I wonder what happens
to your Spotify account when you kill
yourself and
then this puppy right comes back into
your brain so I realize that's what that
is that's what like a that's what that's
what that cute [ __ ] on the Internet is
all that cat [ __ ] just I can has
cheeseburger it's just [ __ ]
pornography for the heart that's all it
is you're [ __ ] perverts you're
jerking off your heart you have a heart
on it's coming [ __ ] blood everywhere
stop creeping out your [ __ ]
co-workers it's horrible it's a it's
just I don't know we're all going to die
I don't know how that that thought's
supposed to end
really I was in a bar a while back and
there's this guy a lot a lot of people
that hang out out in uh the punk rock
sort of scene have this tattoo or this
back patch the anti- swastica it's a
it's a dead Kennedy's thing it's a
swastika with a circle and a slash
through it like Ghostbusters or
whatever it's it's like a really bold
statement it's like oh I am against
Nazis all
right everybody's against Nazis it's a
default
position generally we all saw Indiana
Jones nobody really cares
that you're taking a stand to be against
Nazis like what do you feel like you
feel like you're going to go into a bar
and uh and and there's going to be a
couple of Nazis in the corner drinking a
manny shevitz to be ironic CU it's 2013
you know and they're going to be like oh
we can't to go anywhere I don't
know it's [ __ ]
happen but that's how people think
because we live in the city you know
uh so a lot of of weird social politics
going on in in this city because this is
a specific type of city right Austin is
a type of city it's a Brooklyn it's a
Portland it's like one of those [ __ ]
places like there's a thing here called
the uh called ham the Health Alliance
for Austin musicians right which is cool
I'm kind of for it uh except that it's
kind of exclusive right there's no
Health Alliance for Austin comedians it
would be cool if there was because it
would be called a hack and
[Laughter]
and that's fun right it's fun for
everyone
it's it's a good
joke but it bothers me because you know
it's it's kind of like there's different
types of cities right and this is kind
of a snobby city that is to say like uh
hey we're you know this town we would
like to just give free health insurance
to just the coolest of the poor people
right
just what about regular poor people like
if you're just some hobo dying in a
gutter somewhere of some hobo disease
like soup pants or beard mice or
Restless entire body syndrome
or or just a gypsy curse you
know so I'm pretty sure homeless people
get cursed by gypsies a lot for some
reason I've seen enough movies you know
if you're that person then no one gives
a [ __ ] about you grab a kear and start
strumming because no one
cares unless you're in like a cool Billy
Joel cover band or something unless it's
a big [ __ ] joke you know um it's
interesting though there's there's
there's different types of cities you
know and I like living here because this
is a certain type of city but when you
travel around you notice different
things you know I was in San Antonio a
while back which is the other kind of
place right San Antonio is a city the
main attraction there is just a mall
basically um you know it's it's just
there there's a mall and then there's
like a Ripley's Believe It Or Not Museum
and then there's just reasons to start
drinking that's all exists
in this place and I don't like it you
know I don't want to live there I want
to live here in a place where we can uh
you know elect a lizard mayor or
something and I
just but I get this weird feeling inside
of me when I go there because I was born
in San antoniio when you're born
somewhere you have this strange Cosmic
connection to it so when you're walking
around like I don't like this place but
there is this weird Spirit thing inside
of me that's like yeah like maybe it
would be kind of actually nice to stay
here and just sit on a bar stool karaoke
bar and do jello shots until I'm just
[ __ ] dead it's like that feeling you
get like how you start to get warm right
before you freeze to death you
know so this inner battle when I go to
San Antonio where it's just like San
Antonio's like Darth Vader it's like
Jake I'm your hometown and I'm like no
it's not
true cuts my arm off with a neon taco or
a Spurs sign or
something the next movie isn't as good
but living in that
City living in San Antonio is like
acting out Texas history in Reverse it's
a heroic struggle to get away from the
[Laughter]
Alamo just as far as possible you know
uh so I so I you know I don't live there
anymore I live here which is cool I like
I like the city but it's one of those
Portland Brooklyn kind of places where
there's just no [ __ ] rules it's
killing me it's killing me to live here
uh it's it's too much fun
there's f f first first off about the
city there's no repercussions for like
just how you dress or care of
yourself I don't like to throw the word
hipster around I think it's the worst
word of this generation it's just
meaningless and usually when you call
somebody a hipster you're guess what
you're a [ __ ] hipster right but uh
but it is kind of funny like it is kind
of funny that there are people walking
around in this city that just look like
Wizards that are trying to blend into
muggle Society you
know like they just don't know how
clothes work they're just full marching
band suit and ski boots or whatever and
still gets laid all the time it
shouldn't
happen it's not okay you know but uh but
you know but but whatever gives a [ __ ]
you know uh but the other problem this
town the main thing is it is is just
it's it's just okay to drink way too
much here like it's not frowned upon at
all it's just
uh you're not supposed to be able to
just have six beers with dinner or
whatever but we all agree on
it if you leave this town guess what
you're a disgusting alcoholic you don't
know
it you don't know it yet but you are you
know this isn't even this isn't even a
comedy show this I'm not recording album
here this is a reverse
intervention gathered you all here to
talk about our Collective
problem it's [ __ ] City Austin should
be spelled with two A's you
understand so those are the two things
that make you an austinite right being
uh being a just a disgusting drunk and
also being kind of a hipster snob about
it right I feel like the epitome of
being an austinite would be if you were
to breathe a bored sigh into a
breathalyzer
right like you get pulled over by the
cops and the cops are like uh you know
blow into this and you're just
like for real
[Applause]
cops like you blew a 1.5 blood alcohol L
right you're like 1.5 I remember back
when it was
1.3 back when it was
[Music]
cool oh man City's [ __ ] killing me
man it's killing
me I uh I was walking
around while back and uh I was thinking
about there's this uh old performance
artist actor guy named Spalding Gray you
never heard spelling gray he was like
this dude uh he lived in Brooklyn for a
while he was in some movies he would do
this [ __ ] where he would get up in in
bars and stuff in theaters and like you
know like like read this like really
interesting personal [ __ ] from this
journal and like uh you know was like it
was very fascinating and funny it was
like this but funny and [ __ ] and like
cool uh he probably didn't work at a bar
you know like it was it was interesting
and uh and he he jumped off the Brooklyn
Bridge or something like killed himself
like this really famous interesting
archetypal suicide like oh he's this
crazy genius or whatever right I was
thinking about that and I was having
kind of a weird day and I was walking
around uh downtown over that that bridge
that goes over the lake in the middle of
town and I looked over it and I uh I
realized that if you try to uh Spalding
Gray yourself off of the bridge downtown
you won't die you'll just end up in an
inner tube with a beer in your hand
[Laughter]
is this [ __ ] City won't let you stop
partying not even to
die it's
great it's a great way to live
man I was in New York there's a
stereotype about people from New York
it's that they're uh they're like rude
you
know good there's one here right now
yeah yelling [ __ ] out
uh maybe the joke's over I don't know
uh no I'm just messing with you New York
I was riding the Subways like a tourist
you know and uh I didn't know this but
there's a guy who operates the subway
car like he's he drives it I thought
they were automatic or whatever uh so I
didn't know this you know I'm kind of
groggy it's the morning and like I'm
just hanging out down there and as the
train takes off this guy sticks his head
out of the side of the train and uh and
it flies past me right and uh I wasn't
really paying attention what was going
on so all I see is this disembodied like
black dude's head just like hey what's
up man just fly past
me it was like terrifying like I was
like I thought I thought it was like a I
was like are you a goblin do you help me
this like a video game do you help me if
I get lost down here you know like it
was weird but he was very friendly right
he said what's up so Mor little story
people from uh people from New York
friendly they're monsters they're
terrifying monsters but they're friendly
monsters that want to help you
right I was I was at a a a bar that's
how lot of these jokes start I was in a
bar and uh this old homeless veteran guy
came up to me and uh he said hey man can
I can I sit here you know and he pointed
this seat next to me and I was like yeah
I don't care you know and he went uh
yeah cool thanks I'm sorry and I was
like it's fine I don't care he goes uh
okay I'm sorry and then I realized he
was crazy you know he just kept saying
I'm sorry so he's like uhhuh I'm sorry
and I was like it's okay I forgive you
whatever and he kept doing it and uh
then he told me this really sad story
about being in the Vietnam War right he
was like a like a veteran and uh I felt
really bad for him cuz he just sort of
been [ __ ] over by the whole system he
has no family anymore he lives in the
streets right and uh when I uh when I
got up to leave he said something very
sad to me he said hey hey man can I have
a hug and I was like ah like sure you
know uh so I wrapped his arms around me
and I wrapped my arms around him and
that's when I felt his boner digging
into my
leg had a boner right so this this
really weird moment where I was like
[ __ ] like what do I do you know like
because the man had nothing left right
he' been screwed over by his just whole
experience in Life or whatever so uh so
what I did was I just let him [ __ ] go
for it right uh
because life has [ __ ] you over that
hard I say [ __ ] go for it right uh
there's not really a point to this story
uh basically all I'm trying to say is
support the troops
in whatever weird way you
can I voted I voted for Obama the one
time I don't really give a [ __ ] about
politics like we're all screwed you know
but I voted for him the one time because
I believed that every person should have
access to uh health insurance and uh
then I started doing comedy I traveled
around and I
met everyone and now I believe that
nobody should have health insurance
right just [ __ ] the whole system just
[ __ ] them all uh but I did vote I voted
in uh Fiesta Mart which is a
Mexican-American Food Mart um in my
neighborhood you can either vote in a
church or a school or [ __ ] Fiesta uh
a place where you can buy bananas and
candles that will keep the police away
uh can also so vote there it's
fine voted it was fine didn't matter I
live in Texas nothing happened you know
I don't really have a lot of faith in
the whole democratic system anymore
because it's it's so obviously just not
really functioning uh there will never
be an another ugly president I think
that's a thing like it'll just never
happen last one was like Taft and then
after that they're out Ralph nater had a
lot of great ideas right Ralph nater
looked like a an rrum drawing of a drunk
zombie
lawyer like he looked like he was
underwater even when he was up here with
us so he'll never be a thing you
know what else what else is
[ __ ] I'm broke all the time so I buy
a lot of like cheap groceries like I
don't spend a lot of money I buy a lot
of the off-brand knockoff food products
I go out
to get groceries and uh the thing is
they taste just as good as the regular
name brand food the only thing you're
not getting is that weird like Pizzazz
you know just the like cartoon on the
box and the hey how you doing buddy you
know it's as if to say like like hey you
poor no one no one no one cares no one
in America
cares I uh I wanted to buy some
Hamburger Helper at one point and it
turns out the knockoff off-brand version
of Hamburger Helper is simply called
Skillet meal right
that's
it it's a meal it goes in a
skillet kill yourself no one
cares worst part about that to me is
that that's some dude's job right some
guy works at a graphic design firm
somewhere just hates his life it's just
like his job is to come up with the
offbrand versions of all the regular
things so there's just some guy working
somewhere just like oh I hate my life
what's next Hamburger Helper I don't
care Skillet meal I don't care
what's after that lerine breath drink I
don't give a
[ __ ] it's a drink for your
breath goes
home punches a wall he's like Sheila
suck my dick
and eats his Skillet meal
takes breath drink you know
just hates it just [ __ ] hates
it here's a story I was in a was at a
bar a while back a lot of these stories
start like that and uh was at a bar and
I went to uh went to take a piss in the
urinal and uh in the urinal and somebody
had written some graffiti like above the
urinal it said uh it said Love is Real
which is like whoa like really lofty
graffiti you know I was like oh a poet
took a piss here that's
weird but it was interesting it's kind
of an interesting social statement you
know to bring up because it was like
well it's interesting concept it's 2013
you know is love a real thing is it uh
you know like this real concept from
philosophy or is it you know maybe like
a sort of a like perpetuated uh concept
that came around around the Advent of
Agriculture that was constructed by the
church and state to keep families
together otherwise society would crumble
and people would go crazy and no one
would pay money to the the hierarchy or
whatever or maybe it's just this thing
it's sort of being perpetuated by the
Disney Corporation to put dollars in
hands sort of thing and I started you
know maybe it's the real thing I maybe
sometimes life actually works out like
that and I was thinking about all this
and I realized I was thinking this with
my dick in my hand right it's just going
all College on this urinal just like oh
interesting so I
finished I left I thought about it for a
while and it really stuck in my head I
thought about it
I think love love is like HIV it was
real in the
80s mostly dead now we mostly killed
it we killed it with drugs and
everything's fine we're better off
without it uh it was real back then when
all the cool music was made and uh were
past it you
know anyway I was uh was thinking about
this I was laying on the floor floor of
my apartment and I was staring at my
ceiling I was having a weird day and I
was just just yelling at my ceiling I
was just going like what the what the
[ __ ] do I do you know in between jobs
having a weird weird stretch you know I
was just like what the [ __ ] do I do and
my ceiling was yelling back at me
because uh I was on mushrooms and
uh and I was going what do I do and it
was going shut up and my SE my ceiling
was telling me to shut up because not
only was I on mushrooms I live in
apartment there's somebody above
me doesn't understand what's happening
you
know I like my ceiling wants me to shut
up I guess I should leave and I went
back to that bar uh went to the same
urinal and someone had added the word
gay onto that sentence right now if they
had put the word gay at the beginning it
would have said gay love is real right
it would have been an interesting
subversive social statement it's 2013
we're in the middle of a civil rights
you know de baate and everything and
cool but this [ __ ] did the
opposite this person wrote Love is Real
gay and I get what they were getting
at kind of because feelings give you
douche chills you know what I mean like
it's that's why we're all out drinking
to kill them right woo woo woo woo
Budweiser
woo I had a pen on me and uh I felt kind
of weird about this you know so I
changed it and now it says gay Love is
Real gay it's just a
fact just factual graffiti now
I neutralize the issue man
[Laughter]
I don't think pajamas are real hold stay
with me on this one I don't think
they're real I have a theory that
they're not real uh cuz like who the
[ __ ] Wears Like if you hook up with
somebody tonight you go home and to go
to sleep they put on a full
suit with pockets and a little hat with
a poofball on the side of it like that
is a lizard person
little candle with a a tray you
know person is in the Illuminati like
that shit's not
[Music]
real ah
man where we go with this where do we go
where do we go got a few minutes left
I'm going try to get one more thing on
this CD
I don't know what the [ __ ] to do man
tell a joke no [ __ ] that
man oh
[Music]
God did you guys uh you hear that the
joke about the skin head Professor he
grades on a curb okay that's stupid
[Music]
American History X was a sad
movie I like movies like horror movies I
used like them a lot more Weir thing
about horror movies is that uh
eventually like you they stop scaring
you like remember when you were a kid
and scary movies were actually freaky
they got in your head or whatever you
know the older you get they don't scare
you they just they just uh I don't know
they're just kind of weird and like
you're just numb I've seen everything on
the internet like I fell asleep watching
The Shining the other day cuz if unless
a horse is going to [ __ ] Jack Nicholson
to death I
don't doesn't freak me out I don't care
you know yeah and I think I figured out
why that is it's because when you get
older like you still have fears but all
your fears evolved into all these weird
abstract Concepts that wouldn't make a
good movie you know like you would ever
watch a movie where the ghost doesn't
you know haunt you it just just calls
you about student loan debt and [ __ ]
just just
boo you got a liberal arts degree now
you won't be able to get a job that's
[ __ ] scary [ __ ] that's what keeps me
up every
night that's what happened in my
life dropped out of
college I think that's why I don't
really give a [ __ ] about uh college
football like sport like that no cuz
there's a team for every college and
there's a college for every town but
there's no team that represents people
like me like if there was a team of
people that like played football that
didn't go to college or dropped out of
college and they got to play against the
college that'd be [ __ ] cool right
just a bunch of waiters and [ __ ] like
chain
smokers they're mascots like a used car
you
know they wheel this [ __ ] Toyota
tcell out onto the FI
just do donuts and drink cough syrup
during halftime
like be great that's the people I want
to see play a game you
know
um this is a story about the
police the the social
institution not the
band but [ __ ] them
too [ __ ] the police
[ __ ] sting Dune was a weird movie [ __ ]
him
I I was walking around a couple years
ago right I with my buddy Joe stats it's
comic walking around we got we got
jumped by a bunch of people downtown
just for like no reason you know we just
got attacked and uh and and we we called
the cops like we got attacked and we
didn't get like robbed and it wasn't
like a racially motivated thing it was
very bizarre uh just [ __ ] beat us up
and then left and we don't know what to
do you know so we called the police to
try to try to get like his face fixed
and stuff and uh and they never showed
up right it was really disheartening it
kind of sucked because the thing about
cops is that when whenever you need a
police officer they're never around
right those few times in your life but
if you're peacefully protesting or if
you have weed in your pocket you're just
hanging out [ __ ] cops are everywhere
they show up they kill
everybody they bring the at at Walkers
and death stars and [ __ ] and they
[ __ ] kill people right so uh you know
so bum me out and I was thinking about
it and I figured something out right if
you uh if you're walking around tonight
and God forbid anything happens to you
if you get attacked or uh you know
mugged or whatever uh here's what you do
you get on a bicycle and you ride it
through a red
light the cops will show up and murder
everyone you get to go home and have a
great night thank you very much thank
you
thank you thank you [ __ ] [ __ ] the police
the band [ __ ] Stak thank you very
much give it up for Jake Flores
everybody wasn't that great AR you proud
of him giving up a little bit more for
[Applause]
him so a sleeping
drunker up in Central Park
and a lion
hunter in a jungle
dark and a Chinese Den