I've got an argument going with my
American Bank I'm not even allowed to
mention their name on stage anymore so
to protect their anonymity we'll we'll
call them the bank of blam
America so they called me up girl
offering weird advice we see your money
is in a savings account but it should be
in a super savings
account what would you like us to do
about that well put it in the super
savings account
why are you calling me with this
question you're the bank this is why I
gave you my money you technically what
you're doing right now is calling me for
financial
advice so the B America calls me like is
this JJ Whitehead I say yes it is and
they go we want to talk to you about
your bank account I say go ahead and
then what do they do then they go before
we do can you please Pro
prove that you are who you think you
are by giving us your
password at which point we're all
thinking you called me
man maybe you need a password oh it
doesn't work that way Mr Whitehead we
need evidence that it's you before we
can proceed well did you not call the
phone number that JJ Whitehead gave you
the call should you need to talk to him
I think think we can assume this is
me well we don't make assumptions Mr
Whitehead well you just called me Mr
whitee
head there's two of us in this
conversation and we both seem to think
that I'm
me we got some sort of criminal
mastermind who has like stolen JJ White
head's phone and held on to it for
months at a time hoping and strategizing
that babbe eventually his bank is going
to
call do you know what they said to me at
this point they go please calm down Mr
whad I could feel the nervousness on the
other end of the phone his little voice
just went well you know cuz we are we're
we're on your
side what what if terrorism was involved
what you know what if terrorists were
getting a hold of your bank details Mr
way you know what what if what if that
was all
happening and I was say well they'd be
[ __ ] I don't know if you had a look at
my bank account but I can't even afford
to buy these people sandals let alone
Finance like their next terrorist
Mission like that's happening somewhere
in the world tonight there's like a
huddle of Isis gathered in an Alleyway
and like the leader stands up and looks
them all in the eyes and goes gentlemen
before we do this evil deed let's spare
a thought for JJ
Whitehead for providing us all with
tonight's Hello Kitty
backpack he's a good man