but the truly crazy people in Los
Angeles are literally the animal people
and before I go into it allow me to make
an announcement I love animals I love
them people are animals I love people I
love the tiny animals we have as pets I
love the larger ones we eat I love all
the animals I'm like Dr do little up
here I freaking love the
animals my husband has an iguana it's
like petting a purse but it's a
perfectly nice
animal very adorable lizard and uh but
get this when I was a kid of course if
you had an old dog or a very ill cat you
sadly put the dog down put the cat to
sleep it was very sad but they would go
to happy dog or cat heaven and you would
go to the pound to get a new [ __ ] dog
and it's a circle of life it was very
beautiful uh that doesn't happen in
Crazy Los Angeles land where people are
like oh no the cat's only 17 we're going
to get
dialysis are
you I have a friend of mine who has a
cat that is 21 years old and in addition
to the plethora of other issues going on
with this cat it now has diabetes and so
she has to shoot it up twice a day you
know what that is time for a new cat new
cat twice a day why do you get a cat so
you don't have to do anything that's why
you get a cat cuz it poops in a
box $33,000 for diabetic cat medicine
for this you know what that is that is
3,000 new cats cuz cats are
free and I have another friend of mine
who has a dog and the dog has to get a
new hip but it didn't work and so the
dog is still scooting around on a cart
like Captain Pike and let me tell you
something it is a dog it is not ever
going to be Steven Hawking not ever it's
not going to write the Great American
novel from the cart it's not going to
cure cancer from the cart if it can't
run new dog new
dog and people get mad at me in LA and
they come up to me after shows and
they're like you don't like animals and
I said no I don't like you uh cuz you're
a jackass about your pet you got to let
go weirdo and cuz what do you get with a
cat or a dog 15 20 years that's what you
get I didn't make that rule if you would
like more than that turtle turtle turtle
turtle turtle tiny turtle hat Tut two
carried around your creepy Paris Hilton
purse get left to Ted up adorable giant
tortoise that could walk slowly around
your backyard for 300
years and become a burden on your
descendants Turtle where I go to eat
breakfast LA right next to my breakfast
place there is an animal Eye Care
Clinic kid you not Animal Eye Care
Clinic I don't have insurance but let's
get Mitten in some
contacts better now or now
now better now or no