[Music]
all right text one two one two check one
you can hear a makeup in here
why you here why am I here cuz uh I
heard the Afghan women were
hot you know you see that little burka
thing it just gets me stiffer than the
gay sale at a Ricky Martin
concert you know the one modification I
would make on the burka you know they
have the ice slot here I would actually
move it down to
here my policy is no jokes left behind I
don't like to leave jokes that don't get
laughs I'll tell them until they get a
laugh if I have to jump into the
audience and start tickling some of
these guys that's what I'll
do it was funny because when I was nine
I used to get this big bag of green army
men from the 5 and 10 I would stand them
up and Rose and I'd stayed in front of
him and tell him jokes and pretend I was
Bob
[Music]
Hope just I'm kidding you're
not uh no I'm here for the troops really
you know uh I believe in what they're
doing and uh I really appreciate the
sacrifice and uh I thought it was the
least I could do as an American citizen
having them defend you know my way of
life you know I'm a comedian so I could
tell jokes so if I could offer my
services in some way then I felt uh that
uh compelled to do
it I live in Los Angeles
but I travel quite extensively chances
are if people speak English I've
probably worked there but one of my
favorite things I've ever done a
highlight of my career was actually to
go to Afghanistan and entertain the
troops truly one of my favorite things
I've done uh you know as a comedian you
know you know Bob Hope who was one of
our beloved Americans and also you know
one of the Pioneers he pioneered
Vaudeville he pioneered radio he
pioneered television and film as well as
these mediums developed but he was most
beloved to Americans because he would
travel to these War zones like in World
War II and Korea and Vietnam and
entertain the troops you know you don't
hear about too many entertainers doing
that as much anymore but I could see how
somebody like Bob Hope could get
addicted to it because it's it's such a
great feeling knowing that you're doing
something positive yeah for people that
are doing something very positive so
whether you agree with the war or not
you know those those men and women are
there under under the flag of our
country serving the country and you got
to respect them and appreciate them and
support them because at the end of the
day really what they're doing is
supporting you so you don't have to go
do those things
yeah it's one thing to say I support the
military and it's another thing to uh
step off the back of a ch47 alpha class
Shel helicopter and step into a war zone
to entertain these
guys more more than the guys up north
good by the way
yeah really that's uh that's sort of
more of an incentive Jesus it's 130 de
at
night
nice well we got the guitar and the OSI
agents picked us up and took us to the
lud Air Force Base we got there about
12:30 and then we went to the mesal we
got something to eat and we met Colonel
parar who would later take us around the
base and show us to our rooms which were
these giant mobile homes with air
conditioners in
them now this is where we're supposed to
go in case of a rocket
attack which is in here nice the
sandbags on the
top that's when you know you're doing a
good comedy gig when there's a bunker
where you got to where you got to run in
case the [ __ ] gets hairy these is where
we're
staying these are the
bunkers notice all the air conditioners
because what you say Dave it's uh I
would guess it's close to 100 and it's
only uh 7:30 in the morning notice I had
to wear an SPF 90 look at all the
water they say drink lots of water so we
got up early the next day and we ate and
then we went for a classified briefing
on exactly what this base does in the
theater of operations and basically they
run sorties they run search and rescue
missions I mean it was phenomenal I was
blown away how long we'll be here who
knows nobody has a crystal ball we're
going to be here long enough
she got back today
yeah then we did a meet and greet met a
lot of the soldiers we went to the
hospital we went to the firehouse on the
base we also went to the hanger where
the mechanics operate on the
c130s
skills really make the
outfit swear to God hey man the gloves
really make the outfit don't they I it
was like it was only a half outfit till
the gloves came out
now he's like all
right I swear to God you don't have to
know how it just make it looks good on
you the gloves one glove yeah like cuz
you you're shaking like you come up and
you're shaking hands with people and you
have a rubber glove on they go oh that
makes
sense they wouldn't even question it
they wouldn't go hey why that guy only
got one GL they wouldn't even ask they
go of course he does thank God it's a
good yeah that's what I was asking about
[Music]
come ond
[Applause]
it I am the most under flexible
uncoordinated white guy you'll ever meet
I have no business near this
[Music]
pole I know my outfit is really quite
ridiculous I mean which one of these
guys doesn't belong with the others one
of my cffs want to shake your hand so I
can't
oh oh oh how's it going nice to meet you
how's it going man chill chill how's the
heat taking treating you those everybody
else Jimmy
Pedro this young man is my first line of
defense as you enter in and out of the
gates on this
base flying one of those to right a
force BAS too
shabby no Mission just out
out wait somebody
ask man hey do the black t-shirts help
instead of a white T-shirt yeah really
black t-shirts are better than a white
t-shirt's not an option
oh you're from Australia yeah cly are
nice you guys are all working at it
together on these uh yeah big big Joint
Force so yeah helping each other out
only way
I think we'll be back here excellent
excellent look forward to dragging all
the guys down for a laugh appreciate
what you guys are doing than you guys
very much at the
camera sure thing my
pleasure hey man what's going great how
are you doing pretty
good staying
cool you know for everything these guys
are going through it's great that they
can maintain a sense of humor
you guys taking a break from sin yeah I
think last time sign
ago and who are those other three guys
with Drew tease me I'm very vulnerable
right
now let go
car I need to start walking
down maybe you can sign the
way sorry I can't he you I
can't this yours right here so when you
fly oh yeah I fly them I'll fly any of
these wow in in reality they're all
loners in the sense of that uh in a in a
month all these will go home and some
strike vles will show up targeting pot
targeting pot it's got essentially a uh
high high powered TV and infrared TV
either daylight or infrared and a and a
laser in there so helps guide these yeah
what'll happen is that'll roll up take a
look at the ground uh you'll you'll find
your target you'll uh designate the
Target and essentially it'll fire a
laser beam out of there drop that thing
off it comes off opens his eyes it looks
for as a particularly coated laser beam
and then it'll just follow that spot
down to the Target awesome it's a GPS
gued bomb right there
unbelievable all I do is give that that
that's just a that's just a gas tank
right there but the the small one 500
lounder I just feed that a very very
precise coordinate right it drops off
starts looking for GPS satellites goes
okay I'm right here I want to go right
there and finds the uh finds the target
up there's the gun 20 mm cannon in the
uh in the wing route there these right
here these uh those the confirmed tiits
those are yeah those are bombs that this
plane has dropped wow
[Music]
[Applause]
I can't believe they let me fly this
thing know that
[Music]
night we left on a C130 and flew to
bogam which was another 5 hours but that
is not really commercial Aviation you
know you're kind of sitting and netting
and there's you know probably like 35 to
40 other people on the plane plus there
was a Seal Team on board we coming into
B we did a combat Landing which is
pretty intense we got in late we got in
really late it was over at 12:30 and
that was officially Zulu time which is
some kind of military time when you're
in the middle of nowhere and you have to
keep military time they call it Zulu
time that's where we were for the next
uh several
days we got up at 5:30 in the morning
got some breakfast then we went up to
the helicopter Airfield and got on a
couple shinook helicopters and flew to
some of the forward operating bases
[Music]
can I get
some on got
[Music]
light up roads and stand in front of
them and tell them our first show went
off about 9:30 a.m. we performed in the
back of a truck under camouflage and it
was already about 9500 deges we did the
show signed some autographs they fed us
again and then we got back on the
chopper flew to Camp right of sad which
was like kind of a special Force's base
and we did a show in a small meth Hall
but I remember getting off the chopper
and the guy goes what are you doing here
I said we're the comedians he said yeah
I know what are you doing here he goes
you should have been here yesterday were
bombing us about this time shelling us
and I said that must suck and he goes ah
not really they're not very good shots
so we did that show which is very cool
and then we got back on the Trappers and
flew to cam chah halot and the guys were
just returning from Mission so they were
really excited about the show and uh we
were pumped to do it
[Music]
I don't care
you guys are going to love know from
Philadelphia has been on comic Central
lots of movies everybody how about it
for Jimmy
sh how you guys doing all
right right feel that [ __ ] energy all
right nice anyway it's good to be here I
uh we had breakfast at this Air Force
Base they were serving chicken omelets
which was [ __ ]
weird you know
you don't take the eggs out of the
chicken and then cook the
chicken that's too much
chicken you guys are great this is the
only comedy club with the two hostage
minimal how ready next night to the St
very funny guy you see The Last Comic
Standing at the night show with Jay and
also he's a former Marine ladies and
gentlemen
here why why are you
supporting uh I've been I've been behind
our war on terror since it started and
and uh this was my little way of doing
something I'm too old to reinlist so I
drew called and uh gave me the shot of
coming out here and I jumped at it so
that's the reason I'm here
[Music]
oh
then we went to jalaba we got there
about 3:30 in the afternoon I did a show
for those guys after we had lunch with
them and these guys had just really
returned from a mission we're really
excited that we were there and we're
going to actually do a show and
entertain them because they just gotten
back from mission and some of these
forward operating bases are really right
against the Pakistani border and these
guys said you know no one ever comes out
to entertain us this is great that you
guys are here then when we got to
Afghanistan and we were in jalad it was
literally 120° and I really felt for
these guys because they have on these 40
lb Kevlar vests they have on other gear
on top of that plus their weapons plus
their helmets plus they're in a really
rugged terrain and these guys were
spectacular I didn't hear any complaints
these guys believed in what they were
doing they were all about the mission
first and these people really understood
that you you have to watch out for your
partner's
back after one of the shows a kid came
up to me and he's like I literally just
came back from a firefight 20 minutes
ago you know we we kind of got ambushed
uh another Squad came in took out the
insurgents and now we're here I'm like
what the hell I could never be like I
just got shot at I think I'm going to go
watch some stand up I had a conversation
with we were talking with three young
kids that were like 23 24 and 25 right
in that range one kid had a bandage on
his arm and the other kid had stuff on
his chin and the third guy was just kind
of standing there smoking a cigarette
and I was talking to him said hey how's
everything going he go well we're doing
all right we know last night we had a
firefight we had 40 insurgents come
across the Pakistan border we squatted
nine guys they had his pinned down he
got hit with a Ricochet and I got hit
with some stuff from some shra from an
RGB a rocker Propel grenade and it kind
of caught me on the chin a little bit
and he goes and these were well trained
insurgents and uh they had us on the
retreat and he pointed over there to the
other guy and he said then his Squad
came over the hill and thank God saved
our asses I was just impressed with the
military I think they have a tough job
to do I I I believe in what they're
doing they certainly believe in what
they're doing and you hear stories in
the news and I really want to go over
firsthand and see what it was like and
talk to these people and meet these
people guys are really impressive human
beings
[Music]
what I what I wanted to do is going be
taking downstairs to the Operation
Center cuz the guys down there they
spend their day day in day out staring
at uh closer TV screens or computer
monitors and they don't really get to do
a lot of the fun stuff or have any
excitement in their life and As Good As
It Gets is know they almost they
probably afford to a rocket attack
things live enough for him so if you
don't mind I'll take you downstairs and
I'll show you what you know how that
works and then if there is an attack on
the base then suddenly we we are the
focal point of everything even the
generals and all this stuff uh defer to
us and it's our judgment and they've
been pretty good about never really
second guessing us or never what's going
on what's going on what's going on and
bothered us like that
[Music]
say hi
Jenny
jny Jenny from the Bas jny from the Bas
sorry we already have a Jenny from the
vly how in the hell is irritability a
sign of suicide
[ __ ] made that
brother he saw you
in but it's got better
[Music]
wow right now
they're
sparklers for the this is our uh for the
fireworks show for the show we're going
to
have 625 per minute uh put the Hellfire
racks on there right um but we can
configure the aircraft to go rock Ro ET
heavy which is 76 Rockets or the pedals
do is they control the pitch of the tail
R we're going all right awesome that's
pretty wild that's awesome that's that's
how we fly I'm you guys see
[Music]
you feel like you've been in
danger yes absolutely I've been in
danger there's this a interviewer that's
been following me around trying to get
interviews and I'm trying to hide from
her I respected the military a lot
before I came here I respect him so much
more
after this trip uh you know flying in
the c130s and the the the ch47 alpha
class the shinook helicopter and being
some of those Forward Air bases and uh
being eight clicks from the uh Pakistani
border I get a whole new respect I know
who do you got to sleep with to get laid
in this
town I can't wait to do the big show
tonight I've been doing fire bases you
know I came out to do shows you know
tonight we're actually going to be on a
stage with a PA system and you know
there's going to be like 600 people
there and uh you know I'm I'm really
looking forward to it I can't wait you
know I'm bringing a little laughter and
joy into these guys' lives you know any
other questions cuz if not I'd like to
go to chow hall and then get some RNR
all right yeah yeah any other questions
any other
questions settle down
[Laughter]
but uh any I'm glad you guys are just
ballsy just living here and putting up
with this stuff God bless you man
honestly you guys
are I'm here for 4 days I'm like [ __ ] I
can't wait to get out of
here you remember what [ __ ] used to
taste like
Pedro Hernandez everybody Pedro
Hernandez oh
oh oh I'm so happy to be here that was
late that was late
stop now what's going on guys what's
going
[Music]
on all right some of y'all are looking
at me like you tell us
Pedro we have guns [ __ ] explain
yourself
hi how about it for J everybody huh Mr J
Cary how about it for
Pedro that's
enough hi guys what's going
on where can a fella just meet some guys
in this town what's what's up where's
all the Asians here
tonight two awesome all the rest of Stu
as they should be uh our next guy coming
up really funny you might see a comedy
subject you've been out all these guys
have a lot of good TV credits please
welcome from Philadelphia Pennsylvania
chimy sht everybody JY sh chy sh true
car ladies and gentlemen true car Pedro
Steve D let them know you guys are
[ __ ] awesome man unfuckingbelievable
everybody amazing they want if I can do
everything and they never forget
anything don't forget
anything except to buy more tampons
that's the one thing they can't seem to
remember it's like they're in denial
about the fact they bleed once a month
or
something can't you girls go to Sam's
Club and a px pick up a 55 gallon drum
with those damn Tamp pod wheel upstairs
and put it behind the closet door next
to your shoe collection and leave us out
of
it we don't send you out for bald cream
and crex
[ __ ] hey honey I got a clump of grapes
hanging out of my mud
whistle they pick me up and do that
preparation a on your way back in
pumpkin I'll be face down the couch
squirt a little on my balloon KN rub it
in a little
Chase I love you too sweetie happy
Valentine's
Day we don't do it we take care of that
sounds that's all I'm saying I'm just
saying police your own area that's all
Le you on
there and trim that thing up once in a
while
we you pulled out your panties it looks
like someone hit a gorilla in the back
with a hatchet just just just triming up
a little
bit we just want to be able to see the
bubble Dum is that so much
to God bless you get home safe and uh we
[ __ ] love you man you're amazing
thank you so much thank you so much
Pedro Hernandez Pedro
Hernandez Steve bur Steve
bur David Mell David
murell Jimmy sh once
again God bless all you guys thank you
very
much thanks God bless you oh thanks man
thanks
about and I remember walking through
there with Drew and people would just
pop their head out of like cubicles or
offices and the minute they saw them
just they'd light up and they'd smile
and that was that's what it was about
you know them just smiling for at least
a few minutes even if they just got to
meet him if they couldn't go to a show
and that guy led by example too because
when you see a guy that's as big as he
is taking pictures with people while
he's eating then you you see that and
you go man this is a huge star and he's
doing that well yeah I I got you know
then subconsciously you're like I'm
going to do everything you know I can to
to accommodate these guys while I'm here
too
[Music]
so because because these people make
tremendous sacrifices you know uh
defending America and our way of life I
think it's important I really do
[Music]
[Applause]
oh when I was funny when I was in the
Marin I couldn't get away with that but
now I can cuz I'm a
millionaire this last guy is really
really funny from Philadelphia who's
from Philly are Philly people one person
awesome two people [ __ ]
greater please welcome Jimmy Schubert
everybody Jimmy Schubert
you car ladies and gentlemen let him
know your name Steve bur for let him
know how you [ __ ] doing all
right man this a first for me actually
performing on the surface of the [ __ ]
Sun I going to have to air chisel my
left test go off my thigh later on it's
a little moist out here should have
attack I SP other the pants
[Music]
day dream I've ever heard of in my life
you just cup of SP you weirdo
[Applause]
[Music]
you guys
rock you guys rock you are awesome God
bless you God bless your families get
home safe and
uh I love you for what you're doing
[Music]