it's not C you that's all I'm
saying separates from food items that's
where made cow disase comes from cuz
some idiot fed cows to the other cows no
wonder the
man oh you
Furious it's good the beer in Cleveland
I didn't know
[Music]
was that uh something I should be aware
of is this a
test this is only a test of my
ACT we just want to
see the [ __ ] did somebody tripping alarm
I don't care I'm still
going what okay everybody relax we're
getting information what's
happening ladies and gentlemen uh we
just need to clear uh the showroom at
this point um we just have a problem
upstairs so please Cal me go out the one
exit here and if the ex is it please
escort people out of the back corner to
the exit upstairs as well
[Music]
hey I got one more
joke hey was it something I said please
exra cly no pushing take your
time what's the difference between a $50
Vis gynecologist and
$75 so here's what happens 12 minutes
into my first show on a Saturday night
at this club in Cleveland Ohio uh bus
boy was moving a stack of chairs hit one
of those water sprinklers and knocked it
right out of the ceiling which then
automatically caused the fire department
the building had to be evacuated and 44
gallons of water started gushing out per
minute in this fourstar beautiful
restaurant and Club so the audience was
stuck there I was there anyway so I
figured I continued to do my show on the
sidewalk and this is what
happened all right how about it hand for
the Davis and Rock ladies and gentlemen
and we still are going to try to do the
10:15 show so maybe we'll put you in
this is a first for me ladies and
gentlemen 17 years of Comedy never had
this happen before H here for the
fireman doing a hell of a job
controlling the
water yeah
unbelievable so uh what's the difference
between a $50 visit to the gynecologist
and a $75 visit that's a $50 visit
that's a $75 visit all right I'm trying
to keep everything going it's going to
be here right now where was I I was just
in Philadelphia recently I saw my family
it's uh so my grandmother I haven't seen
her in a while I walk in her house first
thing she says to me is Jimmy last time
I saw you you were this
High I said well it's good to see you
too Gramps you know I come from an Irish
family I have an uncle that carries a
case of beer in the trunk of his car for
emergencies kind of emergency would you
have you needed a case of beer for you
know say [ __ ] we got a flat and no here
let's drink
woo anyway uh so I saw my grandmother
she's crazy than catch sh all she does
now is make cakes cake cake cake cake we
got the news crew here we're making a
news here unless he's just some wacko
with a video camera this is great I love
this uh where are you from Sir is that a
camera on your shoulder you just happy
to see me just we're still doing the
show little water problem is not going
to stop us cuz C rocks my
friend so uh anyway this is going to be
very difficult where were we inside the
showroom the chicken omelette thing we
did that yeah we did oh you know I saw
the well people do weird things with
animals I saw the story in the news not
too long ago but these people that were
licking frogs to get high anybody seen
that story in the news yeah see there's
your damn drug problem right there I'm
walking past my television set guy comes
on the news he goes next story up man
logged up for licking the front frog
went how the hell you get locked up for
licking a frog I thought the guy had its
little frog legs apart
gone I mean how the hell else would you
get locked up for licking a frog you
know I I just assume the worst when you
hear a story like
that so it turns out these frogs
actually perspire they secrete a
substance on his back is classified as
an endo hallucinogenic it's a class a
narcotic it's a very powerful toxin it's
part of the frog's defense mechanism
like if another animal tried to eat the
Frog there's frog consecrates this
hallucinogenic substance that way when
the animal grabs in its mouth and starts
tripping and drops the Frog and sees
like 14 different frogs and doesn't know
which one to go after but that's how the
Frog gets out of trouble you have to
bear with me ladies gentlemen this is my
usual environment I work
in I'm not uh you know I'm out of
context I'm all disc combated out
here some of the shit's funny some of
the shit's not
I uh what else oh you know I love to
watch I once I watch that wild Discovery
you watch that show it's like the porno
channel for Animals someone's always
getting it on that show and uh I don't
mind watching you know cuz you learn
things like you know the male rhinoceros
is the only land mammal who can have sex
for 30 minutes in the animal kingdom you
know why no known Predators he's just
out
there no one's going to eat eat his ass
you know that makes sense I mean some of
those other animals don't have that
Advantage those little prairie dogs are
out there trying to procreate you know
they got to keep an eye
out I mean they can't even get too into
it he gets too into it he's not paying
attention next thing you know big bobcat
jumps out of weeds just rips the male's
head off you know but his body still
going cuz of nerves and the feel left
feel and she's getting num from behind
by headless Prairie duck I don't need to
see that talk about losing a woody I was
uh they had they had the American Eagle
on not too long
ago can I a shot and beer out here
please I need something to help me out
the uh wow this has never [ __ ]
happened before I had a guy had a
[ __ ] seizure one time in the front
row I had a blackouts that didn't stop
me either The Show Must Go On ladies and
gentlemen it's not really a job you can
call and go I don't feel funny today you
still got to [ __ ] show
up really it's not really a job you're
not going to call in six4 it's like
being a a porno star not really a je I
don't feel too good I can't come in and
make love to those three beautiful women
all right that's not part of the regular
routine I just started improvise I'm
back into the regular stuff now sir oh
you're with the Fox News yeah okay you
need me to report do a live remote all
right if you need me I'm here I'm in the
Union by the way
H I'll tell you my favorite uh what is
people going back in now or what drinks
oh drinks oh we got one all I need one
I'll tell you
that I need
one okay couple alcoholics over here
they need one alol oh yeah hey hook that
up to the [ __ ] beard top all way up
the I better not step off the sidewalk
or they'll let me up like a [ __ ]
Christmas tree
it wasn't so funny for funny man Jimmy
shart last night the pck huh Tony huh
you like this I go home I open a
refrigerator door to L comes on I do 15
minutes that's the kind of Entertainer I
am I'm B from everything
Tony Tony's another club owner that
books a lot of clubs and he's never seen
this [ __ ] happen
either all right so where were we the
uh frog said the Frog thing yeah but
that's done and this very care okay so
I'm I'm trying to get to it uh you know
what I was a long ago I was in a seafood
restaurant that had the audacity to put
a giant fish aquarium in the middle of
the seafood restaurant yeah well why the
hell would you do that the little fish
got nothing to do except swim around all
day and watch the waiters walk by with
the different ways that they can be
prepared I mean you talk about inhume
you could see the horror on your little
fish faces just cuz they don't have
necks doesn't mean they're
stupid well I'm not going to go into a
barbecue joint that has a petting zoo in
the middle of it that's all I'm saying
I'm just trying to eat some fish and the
little [ __ ] are staring at
you oh [ __ ] there goes another one on a
better rice for the side of
asparagus just a matter of time for they
coming at us
Larry
Larry L
I'm crying for you li except nobody
knows I'm crying cuz I'm in
water don't you see the cruel irony of
it all where the animal rights people on
something like that huh you know I guess
if you don't have fur you're out of luck
cuz that's what they don't want you
wearing fur don't wear fur don't wear I
don't care when you wear leather really
just fur I'm guessing that's cuz it's
much easier to harass a woman than it is
a biker
that would be my guess otherwise why
don't you went down to the biker bar and
throw red paint on warlocks colors and
watch your teeth become an endangered
species let's see how committed you are
to your cause I mean you know the animal
rights people they you know cuz I travel
to concrete arteries into this nation's
great highways all I've ever seen are a
damn deer crossing size between the deer
crossing size there are skunks squirrels
and little furry bunny rabbits and
[ __ ]
dead where's the little guy supposed to
cross at huh what's a squirrel going to
strap with a pair of antlers he made out
of some
Twigs don't have me I'm a deer I'm a
really small deer I got a thyroid
problem I'm a [ __ ] street performer
Tony don't let anybody kid you I'm going
to juggle some rocks in a minute [ __ ]
qu my tape Camp Town L sing that song
dude holy
[ __ ] why is that shot in a
beer I was uh tell you my favorite joke
this is a an Irish guy gets up Irish
woman gets up it's the morning of her
25th wedding anniversary she gets up and
her husband's not beside her in bed so
she puts on her robe and she goes
downstairs and there's her husband
Sheamus he's making all her favorite
breakfast foods goes sweetie it's the
morning of a 25th wedding anniversary I
made you all your favorite breakfast
foods she goes oh Sheamus he goes not
only that but here's $200 and would you
go shopping for a new dress and a new
pair of shoes I don't come back till
6:00 this evening cuz Sheamus is making
dinner
she goes back at 6:00 with the new dress
and the new shoes the table set the
fresh cut flowers the candles are going
and Sheamus goes sweetie you're not
going to believe it I forgot the snails
for the es cargo I got to run down the
fish market and get a big bag of snails
he goes down Fish Market gets his snails
he's walking home past the pub there's
his buddy o goes Sheamus come in for a
pint he goes I can't I got to get the
snails home it's the wife's 25th wedding
anniversary he goes come in for one pint
so he comes in for one pint now you cut
to 3:00 in the morning morning and
Sheamus and [ __ ] hammered with his
bag of snails walking back home he trips
up the step the bag of snails smacks
against the door it rips open the snails
fall all out onto the sidewalk and out
into the street his wife hears the
Racket and goes you son of a [ __ ] he
looks at her he looks down at the stairs
he goes come on fellas we're almost home
boys come on fellas we're all most home
fellas come on all right who's my
favorite stet joke for that all right
Jesus hey it's a tough Hall it's a tough
Alleyway Tony it's a tough Alleyway Hey
so uh so I saw this uh uh oh [ __ ] I
don't know if I could do this outside if
we get the music playing if I could well
it's not really like uh yeah you can do
it okay I guess I could [ __ ] you people
are here with me what are we going to do
huh so our night's already [ __ ]
up M doesn't make the best of it [ __ ]
rock so we were in uh you know I was uh
how you doing good we find that [ __ ]
turnoff valve yet you shouldn't be
looking for that [ __ ] turnoff valve
anytime soon I'd like to get back to my
cocktail if you know before it goes flat
son of a [ __ ] he's on a city of payroll
bastard all
right [ __ ] I've never had this happen so
uh [ __ ] I wish I do some good jokes he's
kids today that's what I'm saying these
kids with the school shooting spoy I got
to watch another story on CNN about
these kids killing in a high school kids
I'm going to [ __ ] kill somebody I
would't even want to be in school today
cuz you got to be good with Max oh he
sucked at Max but if you're in school
today you better excel at math cuz your
life depends on getting the equation
right cuz if Little Johnny comes in the
cafeteria with an AK-47 to hold 17 shots
he's already squeezed off six rounds and
injured four people and I'm 15 ft from
the exit door how fast do I have to run
before Little Johnny picks me up and
pumps off a couple shots in my direction
so I can live and going a be in Geometry
tomorrow
why the fu but will you beat your
[ __ ] children please just so to know
the difference between right and wrong
okay why'd you do it Johnny why'd you do
it well the jocks picked on me Johnny
that's what jocks do they pick on you
you go learn computers that way later on
in life you can hire the jocks a fireman
discriminately and get your renge it's
called natural selection and if you pay
attention history class you [ __ ] know
that I wasn't popular yeah well if you
shoot Sally she's definitely not going
to the prom with you take it through kid
take off that helmet you little [ __ ]
what's with these kids they got it so
easy they got computers and [ __ ] I
didn't have no computer in school all I
have was a pencil and the kit next to
me and if he would have apped himself I
could have been somebody that [ __ ]
had plans I hated that prick now here's
the
thing why you know why you can't even
fire people anymore you fire somebody
they come back and fire at you what in
the hell did that start happening I've
been fired from jobs I never felt the
need to run home and come back with an
Arsenal to will make Charlton h and
jealous and shoot everybody then say hi
that one Tuesday back in
1999 girl do do the show here girls you
don't M thanks appreciate it I got
enough [ __ ] problems without without
[ __ ] people cackling behind
me they don't [ __ ] mind it's I got
enough working okay here comes the truck
can I get up that cherry picker i' feel
more at home is that what it is all
right he's leaving I'm going to go look
for that shutle up valve on the other
block I know it's somewhere around here
this the great the [ __ ] one time
there going to be a shut off B they got
to covered in [ __ ]
gravel I know it's here
somewhere let's all start looking for
the shut off Val if we want to get back
to our party we got to find this damn
thing so where were we oh yeah that's
what it was you know what is wrong with
people anymore you know you see all
these freaks these these uh you can't
even swing at this gruntled postal work
without hitting a spre killer of some
sort anymore you know
hasn't anybody just [ __ ] any lock
down here nothing I'd like to take this
[ __ ] show inside if I
could anytime you guys get the guy with
a metal detector out here let's see if
he can [ __ ] oh all right cheers oh
hey here we go I got to tell you cheers
SL hey you people are unbelievable I
never did a show like this before but
let's see he's taping it'll be on my
website jimmy.com and I tell you what
I'm never coming back here again no I'm
no it's it's my favorite comedy club in
the country I can't believe it happened
I'm a [ __ ] draw in this town I was
sold out for the second show and here I
am on the sidewalk like some [ __ ]
circus clown well you people are
unbelievable and thanks for coming out
so when you when
you when
you when you die may be Buri in the
coffin made a 100y old oak that should
be taken from a treade it's planed
tomorrow God
[Music]
bless a what the [ __ ] was that rifle
cleaner what was that the Mickey manal
starter kit holy
[ __ ] Jameson oh okay I can relax I I put
that [ __ ] on my weedies in the morning
Jameson I'm I'm Irish by the way if you
do that it's not the Breakfast of
Champions anymore it becomes a breakfast
of guys who don't mind coming in second
or
third now here's what's what what Denny
what we get the showroom can I go back
inside now no is it are they clean going
to it in about 15 minutes you said that
15 minutes
ago 15 minutes start seting all right
start seating for the second show yeah
you're doing a show you know this is a
three show night for me you know one
inside one out here one back
inside ladies and gentlemen this guy's
the best this is Nick C this the owner
of this establishment he's doing
everything he can there's nothing you
can do you know but you people are
[ __ ] gems uh so thanks for hanging
out with us where we at 15 minutes yeah
we are going to we are going to to do a
late
show we are going to do our late show
and we are going to start seating in
about 15 minutes everything's okay it is
safe we had a sprinkler just cut loose
on us and has caused this uh
catastrophe uh what we'd like to do is
invite you in uh enjoy the show enjoy
the rest of Jimmy Schubert don't I over
given him everything I got
my [ __ ] again come on inside I'll be
better that I'm not more you people
great thanks for hanging out with us you
applaud yourself we applaud you as a
matter of fact
[Applause]
okay and um I do thank you very much for
uh uh kind of uh waiting this out with
us um and I uh we have a staff that's
terrific and they're working their tails
off to get the Place shaped
up and uh I do want to make a special
thanks to the Cleveland fire
[Applause]
department everybody in this town knows
the
Heartbreak of uh what you
lose here and
here uh those guys lost uh buddies
friends relatives to a cutback and uh
they had to tighten their belt tube and
they really deserve a great deal they
have been Gallant tonight as far as I'm
concerned so thank you very much to the
Cleveland Fire
Department in the meantime if you'd like
to come in um the doors and the bar are
[Applause]
open as a matter of fact if you get into
the showroom ladies and gentlemen this
is Ron Ellington shop he will be on
stage to entertain you while we're
seating okay thank
you all right that story come with a
wakeup call for CRA six I don't know I'm
kidding but uh so you've heard Tony guys
thanks you the best and thanks for
hanging out so we're going to move
inside now gradually all right good
deal yeah
[Music]