uh I am a full-time comic I feel very uh
fortunate to do this job the main reason
for this uh is because I get to travel a
lot like travel is the main gig that's
rad for me uh but I get to go to places
like shreport Louisiana anybody been
there not yeah I like it it's a cool
town but strange don't shake your head
that it's strange because I did a show
there and afterwards I was selling merch
again and uh this woman came up you know
you can tell when someone's staring at
you hardcore it just that weird like
someone's looking at me it was a crowded
room like this and a woman in her young
20s she was wearing like a low cut
velvety gown like a black gown and she
had dark eyes Shadow on like she was in
a suie sue cover band or some [ __ ] like
that and she was locking eyes for me
from like 30 feet away I'm like whoa
this what's up with this chick and she
parted through the crowd and she came up
to me she didn't say a word she just
took my hand like what is happened I
don't know what's happening and she said
uh I really liked your set like oh oh
wow this is like one of those penous
Forum letter things like [ __ ] right
this is a sexy like right on hello
thanks thank
you he said leading closer I'm like I
don't know what's happening okay yeah
hello she said you know uh this is where
True Blood
happened I said you know that's not a
[ __ ] documentary right like what the
[ __ ] is what is happening here and I had
never been confronted with a real fake
vampire before CU she had those like I
work at Hot Topic Fang things that you
insert to whatever you own the night I
don't know how that works out and so I
didn't know what to do to thwart the she
vampirus so I just reached to my back
pocket and pulled out a greeting card
that says daddy loves his little girl
very very much and she went and ran to
an 80s night across town as half that
story is true
uh I do like True Blood though who likes
that stupid sexy show does anyone else
like that stupid don't shake your head
that's [ __ ] you know well you don't
like boobs and vampires those are two
that those are the chocolate and peanut
butter of [ __ ] cool
things it's a dumb show it's a guilty
pleasure but I have Netflix insomnia and
access to
marijuana so I binge watched the first
season of of True Blood and the problem
is I'm also very practical so I watch
the entire season in a day smoke my face
off and then it's 2: in the morning on a
Sunday and I'm looking at the ceiling
trying to apply science to True Blood
I'm like all right let's see let's see
all right so when the vampires in True
Blood when they get emotional and they
cry they cry like tears of blood right
it's like bloody tears going down their
face so by that logic whenever Bill
bangs
sukie vampires just jizz blood all the
time right there's just like a 24-hour
gu show happening on the set of True
Blood at all times and does that mean by
like by that extension is giving a girl
a facial called giving her a carry he's
like oh a oh they're all going to laugh
at you
a oh show me those dirty pillows
a just ruining prom night in a
fiction like one week out of every month
is Bill talk to suuki like just like is
that you or is that me I don't even know
what's happening now and it's both ways
because if you're a guy and you pick up
like a [ __ ] vampirus and she's a
squirter it's like the [ __ ] elevator
to The Shining are opening every what
I'm trying to get at
is they go through a lot of sheets in
sheveport
Louisiana mainly because of the clan but
also because of all the
vampires oh Dallas I know the sun's out
thank you for not being vampires and for