show and address them and they ended up
getting tossed out and at the end of the
show I had a marine combine said hey man
you handled that really well I was
willing to snap that dudes net for you
I'm JT average debt from Austin Texas
all right this is my first time I've
ever been here I got into the building
20 minutes ago and I spent 14 hours
getting here so what's up hi thank you
it was it started off great I got off
the airplane and this woman is looking
at me from across the way kind of
strange like 50-something year-old woman
and she looks at me and she goes it you
what the [ __ ] is like what yeah hi how's
it going he's like I'm not you've been
on the TV and I have like yeah hi it's
like I'm a huge fan of yours until I
[ __ ] doubt it right on look you don't
understand my husband and I watch you on
Mythbusters all so I was still happy to
be here but god damn it that was a rough
way to end a 14 hour trip that's good to
go it I got in the comedy uh Dean
basically a George Carlin fan growing up
in New York and we're out of 16 I went
on stage at state of New York City for
the first time ever I was a total
bringer show one of those like hey kid
you got you got the thing you got five
friends like I guess I friends I did
that twice as figured out it was a scam
but I was like I got a gig at age 16 I'm
a comic no and then I was doing other
things like radio and putting on punk
rock shows for a long time so 2008 I
started this thing called the
altercation Punk comedy tour and it's
all been a a steady work in progress
since then
the new album is called misanthrope it's
a my latest our this one is all me it
was filmed in dallas at a place called
three links which is one of my favorite
rock venues in the country and with
filmed last summer came out in august of
2016 and it's basically an hour of me
kind of ranting and raving about the
kids today and just kind of my old man
persona I'm slowly going from a useful
punk rocker filled with angst to kind of
a forty-year-old get off my lawn guy
filled with angst so it's a little bit
more worldly I think no it's the audio
CD in full and also it's a film special
filmed by bleeding heart productions
which is an amazing production crew out
of Texas and yes the three camera shoot
it's an hour long and there's a bonus
documentary on it as well which features
me on the road in places like
Philadelphia and Trenton New Jersey
lovely Trenton New Jersey and also
Arizona and there's guest appearances by
people like David heady he was also on
stand-up records and is brilliant mr.
Shue Bali who is one of my favorite
people to tour with ever and the lizard
man for the jimbros circus sideshow
makes an appearance as well some famous
people you might know so yeah it's it's
a CD it's a DVD that includes the full
one-hour special visit rope and an
additional our bonus road documentary
featuring material and behind-the-scenes
mania from all those people that I just
said you can't afford not to five it
it's practically giving yourself away so
every comedian of the podcast and people
have been asked me forever to start once
the last summer I finally did but I
essentially drag fee because I didn't
want it just to be comedians talking to
comedians about comedy because the world
does not need that so I I started
something called the road podcast calm
and I was amazed that the road podcast
hadn't been taking it I don't know how I
hit the jackpot on that so its a mix of
comedians there's a lot of comedians on
it but there's also a lot of musicians
folks that I you know know and love
people like Mike Watt we had Dinosaur Jr
on I'm not that long ago Rollins has
been a guest on it Swan you know just
really all underground cool
stuff and also things that have no
comedy related whatsoever that just wild
stuff you see on the road I went to the
thing in Texas called the snake farm
which is exactly what it sounds like
just a roadside zoo where they have like
a 12-foot king cobra and I just talked
to like you know the guy who feeds hold
chickens to alligators and [ __ ] like
that I live in your neighborhood and
like i said i love it also they were
like it develop at a nice development
and it's very Leave It to Beaver it's
very chill and about a month ago my wife
woke me up on a Saturday morning it was
like nine in the morning i was super
hungover weird we'll all do shots and
she said you're not gonna believe that
somebody broke into our neighbors car
like what like doesn't happen here she's
like yeah they're driving away now so
like pull on like some gym shorts and
like a wife beater he should I go
running outside and I see them driving
on street I waved them down and they
pull over and I'm like what happened
they rolled the window down to like yeah
somebody smashed in my wife's car last
night they took her makeup bag and her
iPod I'm like that's horrible I said
well there's anything i can do they said
well we got some you know glass we're
gonna go get fingerprints and check it
out and then the backseat is their son
charlie okay Charlie's like the best kid
ever he's like the one kid I like he was
like every kid from Norman Rockville
plays baseball he's awesome he's like
yeah Charlie right yeah you're you're
one of the good ones man i was like
Charlie you okay buddy you scared it's
like nah we're gonna get the bad guys I
know we're going to like I know I'm
going over kiddo not to be a jerk but
all right fine like Michael they have
any leads or like what we think somebody
may have seen something we're going to
go to the cops now and see what's up and
like Charlie you know where you get the
bad guys right I know your sense of
safety is all messed up right now but
we're gonna get the bad guys and he goes
yeah I yeah
a like you might have somebody talk to
Charlie he seems really upset I said
well let me know if there's anything I
can do and they said thank you so much
and you know I looked in the back and
Charlie has taken a beach towel and put
it completely over his head like the
plant goes just checked out and like I
would have something talked to Charlie
they're like they just find a minute ago
I don't know what happened isn't okay
well i'll keep on your place they roll
the window up they drive away i stand up
and that's what I noticed my dick is
hanging out of my gym shorts so the
entire time I'm talking to the kid he
has the dick angle you know nothing
Bad's gonna happen to you right Charlie
and this poor kids mine my constituents
smash-and-grabs is a dead of night it's
like what does he want with my mom's
makeup bag does he put lipstick on it
like Fraggle [ __ ] did he put on weird
stories what is going on with the creepy
dude who used to live in New York and
the worst part is he's got the dick
angle so when they're driving or like
why are you crying the bad man showed me
the one-eyed snake monster shut up we
were there we saw the whole thing and
that's why I don't have kids so my bones
are literally freezing so I'm going to
go I got to go to put on my way to
Chicago and the rest of this tour so by
misanthrope out now dvd-audio full
documentary on stand up records my
favorite label in the world and check
out the road podcast you get a chance
with the road podcast calm you can find
it on itunes and all those platforms and
you can see all my dates at jakey comedy
calm but thanks so much I'm freezing I'm
going to go drink a hot toddy with a lot
of bourbon bye
you