show and addressed them and they ended
up getting tossed out and uh at the end
of the show I had a marine come by and
said hey man you handled that really
well I was willing to snap that dude's
neck for
you I'm JT haversat from Austin
Texas all right this is my first time
I've ever been here I got into the
building 20 minutes ago and I spent 14
hours getting here so what's up all
right thank you it was it started off
great I got off the airplane and this
woman is looking at me from across the
way kind of strange like 50 something
year old woman and she looks at me and
she goes it's
you what the [ __ ] does that like what
yeah hi how's it going she's like I'm
you've been on the TV and I have like
yeah hi she's like I'm a huge fan of
yours I'm going I [ __ ] doubt
it but right now I'm just like you don't
understand my husband and I watch you on
MythBusters
all so I'm still happy to be here but
God damn it that was a rough way to end
a 14-hour trip how'd you get into comedy
I got into comedy uh being basically a
George Carlin fan growing up in New York
and when I was 16 I went on stage at
standup New York City for the first time
ever uh it was a total bringer show one
of those like Hey kid you got you got
the thing you got five FRS friends I'm
like I got five friends and I did that
twice and figured out it was a scam uh
but I was like I got a gig at age 16 I'm
a comic no uh and then I was doing other
things like radio and putting on punk
rock shows for a long time so 2008 I
started this thing called the
altercation Punk Comedy Tour and it's
all been a a steady uh work in progress
since
then the new album is called missing
thrope it's uh my latest hour this one
is all me um it was filmed in Dallas at
a place called Three Links which is one
of my favorite rock venues in the
country and uh was filmed last summer it
came out in August of
2016 and it's uh basically an hour of me
kind of ranting and raving about the
kids today and just kind of my old man
Persona I'm I'm slowly going from a a
youthful punk rocker filled with angst
to kind of a 40-year-old get off my lawn
guy filled with angst so it's a little
bit more worldly I think and it's not
just a CD right no it's the audio CD in
full and also it's a film special filmed
by bleeding heart Productions which is
an amazing production crew out of Texas
and uh has a three camera shoot it's an
hour long and there's a bonus
documentary on it as well which uh
features me on the road in places like
Philadelphia and Trenton New Jersey
lovely Trenton New Jersey and also
Arizona and there's guest appearances by
people like David Hedy who was also on
standup records and who's brilliant
Mishu Bali who's one of my favorite
people to tour with ever and uh the
lizard man from the gym Rose circus side
show makes an appearance as well as some
famous people you might know so yeah so
it's a CD it's a what it's a CD it's a
DVD that includes the full 1 hour
special missen thrope and an additional
hour bonus Road documentary featuring
material and behind the scenes Mania
from all those people that I just said
you can't afford not to buy this it's
it's practically giving itself
away so every comedian has a podcast and
people have been asking me forever to to
start one so last summer I finally did
uh but I intentionally dragged feet
because I didn't want it just to be
comedians talking to comedians about
comedy because the world does not need
that so I uh I started something called
the road podcast.com and uh I was amazed
that the road podcast hadn't been taken
yet I don't know how I hit the jackpot
on that so it's a mix of comedians
there's a lot of comedians on it but
there's also a lot of musician folks
that I you know know and love people
like Mike Watt we had Dinosaur Jr on it
not that long ago Rollins has been a
guest on it uh swans you know just
really alt underground cool stuff and uh
also things that have no comedy related
whatsoever that just wild stuff you see
on the road I went to the thing in Texas
called The Snake Farm which is exactly
what it sounds like just a roadside Zoo
where they have like a 12T king cobra
and I just talk to like you know the guy
who feeds whole chickens to alligators
and [ __ ] like that I live in a
neighborhood and uh like I said I live
in Austin I live in like a development a
nice development and it's very uh Leave
it to Beaver it's very chill and and uh
about a month ago my wife woke me up on
a Saturday morning it was like 9:00 in
the morning and I was super hung over
weird we'll all do shots and she said
you're not going to believe this
somebody broke into our neighbor's car
I'm like what it like doesn't happen
here she's like yeah they're driving
away now so I like pull on like some uh
gym shorts and like a wife feater
t-shirt I go running outside and I see
them driving down the street and I wave
them down and they pull over and I'm
like what happened they rolled the
window down they're like yeah somebody
smashed in my wife's car last night they
took her makeup bag and her iPod I'm
like oh that's horrible I said well
there's anything I can do they said well
we got some you know glass we're going
to go get fingerprints and check it out
and in the back seat is their son
Charlie okay Charlie's like the best kid
ever he's like the one kid I like he's
like every kid from Norman Rockwell
plays baseball he's awesome he's like
yeah Charlie yeah you're you're one of
the good ones man I was like Charlie you
okay buddy you scared he's like no we're
gonna get the bad guys I know we're
going to
uh I'm like I know I'm hung over kid you
don't have to be a jerk but all right
fine like like will they have any leads
they're like well we think somebody may
have seen something so we're going to go
to the cops now and see what's up and
I'm like Charlie you know we're going to
get the bad guys right I know your sense
of safety is all messed up right now but
we're going to get the bad guys and he
goes yeah I yeah
I like you might want to have somebody
talk to Charlie he seems really
upset I said well let me know if there's
anything I can do and they said thank
you so much and you know I looked in the
back and Charlie has taken a beach towel
and put it completely over his head like
the Plaid ghost just checked out I'm
like might want have somebody talk to
Charlie they're like yeah he was fine a
minute ago I don't know what happened
and he said okay well I'll keep eyes on
your place they roll the window up they
drive away I stand up and that's what I
noticed my dick is hanging out of my gym
shorts so the entire time I'm talking to
the kid he has the dick and go you know
nothing bad's GNA happen to you right
Charlie and this poor kid's mind my
[ __ ] doing smashing grabs in the dead
of night just like like what does he
want with my mom's makeup bag does he
put lipstick on it like fraggle [ __ ]
does he put on weird stories what is
going on with the creepy dude who used
to live in New York and the worst part
is he's got the dick angle so when
they're driving they're like why you
crying the Badman showed me the oneeyed
snake monster shut up we were there we
saw the whole thing and that's why I
don't have kids so my bones are
literally freezing so I'm going to go I
got to go to uh on my way to Chicago and
uh the rest of this tour so buy missen
Thro out now DVD audio full documentary
on standup records my favorite label in
the world and uh check out the road
podcast you get a chance the road
podcast.com you can find it on iTunes
and all those platforms and uh you can
see all my dates at JTC comedy.com so
thanks so much I'm freezing I'm going to
go drink a hot totdy with a lot of
bourbon bye