have you guys been having a good time at
the AKA Comedy Festival this is so much
so much [ __ ] fun man it is great um
I'm going to leave you with this all
right here's a weird question is anybody
else this the dumbest question to ask in
Paradise uh I'm who's in their
30s all right who's in their
20s the most tired you're
like all right people in your 30s you're
my people [ __ ] give yourselves a
round of applause that was badass cuz
I'm 38 it's hard to go out and do stuff
I appreciate it man all right here's the
other question are you still pissed off
about stuff you still get angry no cuz
it's Paradise [ __ ] I'm a maniac I lose
my mind all the time and it's weird I
know because because when you're in your
teens you're supposed to be angry all
the time right you're like I'm angry and
horny I just want to punch my own dick
and fight my f you're that guy when
you're in your 20s you're pissed off but
you have places to go you're in your
social Prime you're like that guy just
cut me off but I have 14 parties to get
to tonight I'm on my way when you're in
your 30s you get upset about the most
ridiculous [ __ ] okay case in point
there's a place I like to go in Austin
Texas called Jack in the Box has anybody
ever heard of Jack in the Box okay all
right even if they don't have it here
you know what it is right the fast food
place they have looks like an Undertaker
with a head disorder is there guy
smiling Jack they have a thing there
called a big Texas
cheeseburger try seman Big Texas
cheeseburger if if you have an
experience it weighs 19 PBS it costs
$150 and if you eat one after drinking a
lot downtown and get pulled over by the
the cops you register deliciousness
instead of DWI you're welcome all right
and I was downtown I had had a couple of
drinks and I was downtown I was in line
and Jack in the Box at two in the
morning and uh I looked to my left and I
was ready to order my burger I was
getting my food and there was a big sign
with smiling Jack and he was holding up
a big piece of cheesecake and the slogan
said it's not too late to order
cheesecake and besides you've earned
it and I went [ __ ] yeah Jack
you get me bro like I work hard I have I
mean I'm going to spend that extra $2 I
am going to get that she and then I
looked a little closer and noticed in
the center of the poster in Jack's
forehead someone had spit a
lugie and I lost my goddamn mind
38-year-old grown man in line who who
the [ __ ] would do this to my friend Jack
man who the [ __ ] will do this to my
buddy Jack like he works really hard
making fries fresh for you and somewhat
witty commercials who would do this to
[ __ ] I said no I know exactly the guy
who would do this let me know if he
sounds familiar he's the douchebag with
the truck big enough to have its own ZIP
code listening to really shitty music
like puddle of Mud or stain lifter or
dirt Satchel whatever you finger bang
your cousin to the Waco family reunion I
don't even know anymore and he's always
got the same shirt it's the ultimate
fighting shirt with the skull of an
Indian but instead of feathers it's
swords because birds are for [ __ ] bro
and it's been like three minutes since
someone [ __ ] with offered me
delicious knock it off cartoon dick
look and then through my head and line
at the Jack the Box almost had an
aneurism and died which is no way to go
out so the next 10 seconds imagine a
totally different scenario he said man I
don't want to live in that world with
that guy that guy sucks so the next 10
seconds imagine a totally like a
hardworking man a bluecollar man
somebody from like Bruce Springsteen's
Nebraska and [ __ ] he's got a real shitty
job he works all day to plant that
manufactures like tumors yeah and his
job is take tumors and put them into
boxes and mail them to unsuspecting
children in the mail and it's gray and
Joy Division and Marilyn Manson is
always playing and he drives a real
shitty Mazda with real shitty windshield
wipers and three times a day it rains
kittens so when the kitten hits the
windshield he has to push it off real
slow and the rest of the day he's
haunted by the ghost of the Cat that
should have been and he works at this
shift and his one Saving Grace is that
at the end of his shift he gets paid in
one [ __ ] stained sock with pennies enough
pennies to buy one big Texas
cheeseburger and fine at the end of his
shift they blow that thing like The
Flintstones but it shoots out meth and
sadness instead of steam and he gets in
his car and level Terrace apart is still
playing on an endless loop cuz [ __ ] this
gray world and he drives really fast
he's really stoked to get that burger he
three kids on the way there but [ __ ] it
he saw pet cemetery twice and he knows
they'll be fine in the end cuz you have
to bar on around here shut up Herman
Monster and he drives really fast till
finally he's in line of Jack in the Box
places his order and finally he's second
in line he looks to his left and there
like a beacon from The Culinary Gods is
our friend
Jack holding up a big piece of
cheesecake with the slogan it's not too
late and besid besides you've earned
it and finally can't withstand it
anymore his energy builds to a fever
pitch get a huge boner like a baby's arm
holding a hand grenade breaks right out
of the window like a chest burster from
Aliens 3 the good one explodes like a
fourth graders volcano with a science
fair that actually works unleashes a
gigantic money shot big enough to
impress both porn star Peter North and
Lord [ __ ] Poseidon from Clash to the
Titans himself hits Jack right in the
forehead Jack looks back and says that's
okay buddy you've earned that too
that's the world I want to live in my
name's JT I got to go thank
you thank you aimo