[Applause]
all right we'll get right to the uh
topic on the Forefront of everyone's
mind the rise of uh prolapsed anal
porn that's a thing that exists I'm no
prude obviously but if if that turns you
on you're a [ __ ] monster and you
should be run out of town with torches
and pitforks no amount of the VHS series
Faces of Death I watched as an eighth
grader could have prepared me for The
Accidental viewing of the unfolding of
that porkloin wind sock just like what
what is that don't kiss that what are
you doing don't make out that nothing
that red is sexy all right pink is sexy
red is an immediate [ __ ] emergency
all right you get help for that woman
you and I know it's called Rose budding
I know it's called Rose budding [ __ ] it
I don't care who directed you sir I know
orsid Wells [ __ ] it [ __ ] you all
right now l
I know it's a sexy Saturday night in
Texas and uh some of you may be feeling
a little frisky after the show who's
[Applause]
drinking may find yourself after the
show back in your apartment with your
fella or your lady or
whatever and the next thing you know
you're putting on some sexy music like
some uh Barry
White or some Journey
or some
uh or some
Enigma and the next thing you know
you're bent over like a foosball
table or a bean bag
chair getting railed in your prolap
danis yeah ladies if you find yourself
in this
predicament just attach it on his boner
and run for help just run as fast as you
can it'll grow back like a Tale in two
to three weeks I have Discovery Channel
I'm pretty sure that's how science
Works [ __ ] yeah so I'm a feminist