stop [ __ ] me for my
brain
okay he definitely turned and saw that
yeah as he would um thank
you so are you so uh first off who are
you I'm Jenny Zago hey Jenny Z comedian
actress writer
sex machine so I live in LA now I don't
live here anymore I live in Los Angeles
California has anyone here been
there yeah yeah [ __ ] there's no water
we're dying but I live there and in in
lovely little La that I live I don't
live in like a cool area like in cool
parts of town people love to jog with
their dogs which is dumb okay I'm not
jog with my dog we even understand it we
have very similar body types we're kind
of short stocky Barrel chested eight
nipp we're not going out together I so I
grew up uh in the midwest so I have like
kind of a Midwest sensibility I'm very
nice like I like everyone to be happy
and nice and um very uh you know uh keep
my feelings deep down inside but then I
have the East Coast part of me that's
like one two punch like I'm going to be
gross and weird I don't give a [ __ ] who
cares I'm going to be me just loud and
big and I love being loud and big I love
big loud women I think there needs to be
more loud women in the world so I'm
going to fill that void and just be a
loud badass [ __ ] that's what I want to
come across as I work you were in Bad
Santa 2 how was that bad santa 2 was so
much fun it was so great um I'm still
friends with people from it and uh it
was just like a great like big Movie
experience to like you know be there and
like you know just be right up there
with like crew and acting and watch
everything work and just you know stuff
where you're like oh my God uh when
you're a kid you're like I want to be a
movie star and then like you do it
you're like what this is crazy so I'd
have a lot of like I'd have to go to the
bathroom in between takes and just
scream into the mirror and be like
ah that kind of stuff yeah yeah um so
what' you think when you saw yourself on
the big screen I mean oh I hate it I
hate it I uh I was in 50 Shades of Black
which is Marlon Wayne's movie and um
that was fun to shoot but really hard to
watch same with like bad santa I don't
like watching myself I would rather
specific about Shades of Black that was
hard to watch well it's a lot of sex
scenes and uh I wore a lot of really
tight fitting clothing I didn't look uh
what I would consider my
sexiest um but other people uh on
Twitter have told me that I looked very
sexy and that they say on Twitter that I
wife
material yeah apparently that's the
nicest thing I've ever heard anyone
Twitter that you get like from a movie
where no one's ever met you or knows
anything about you they just see a
character that you played cuz you're
acting and they're like oh I'd marry you
um you're all famous I'm kind of famous
like I don't really get recognized but
sometimes I do I drive I have to drive a
lot in LA and I used to live in New York
before that and this was a great thing
about New York okay you could hop on a
train drunk 4 in the morning boom your
home no problem in La I got a I got to
drive so I sleep on people's couches if
I get too drunk here's the problem
Hopkins if I get really drunk I get
horny anybody else does anyone have a
[ __ ] pulse in this room are you guys
alive of course you do look you're ready
right now
lady so I'm at my friend's house right
we have a great time I got a little too
drunk I got to sleep on the couch guys I
don't like to admit this um but I H I
ended up masturbating on my friend's
couch
yeah I feel I feel so bad about it
because now that couch will not stop
texting me
what thought I was pregnant thank God it
was a pull out
what
[Music]
yeah oh I know it's dumb don't worry
guys but most of my humor is very
stupid my album is entitled Jay-Z's new
album cuz I'm the original Jay-Z before
that jerk and uh it
is um it's my first album and it's
basically like a culmination of like you
know six years of work and just trying
to uh you know really be a great
comedian and I was like you know this it
came to a point where I was like okay
I've got the material that I really love
and like working with and I never want
to do it again so let's put it on an
album and get rid of it
it's funny Obviously good that's great
um I'm very silly I do some crowd work
in it um I like my shows just to be fun
like for people to like come and have a
good time and laugh and like I'm really
gross and cheeky and you know it's very
tongue and cheek and um I think if
people listen to it they're going to
have a great time you know it's a really
great thing to listen to when you're in
traffic maybe you're you know got some
friends in the car and you're just kind
of done talking to them I'm uh I'm 30 wo
um um it's stupid how old are you 38 38
does it get better no okay great thank
you thank you wow that is some Minnesota
optimism right there really missed that
[ __ ] uh yeah at 30 I don't like it I
don't care for it but things are
changing they're really changing a lot
like I remember being like 21 go to a
party guy who brought the drugs right he
was the cool one he was going to have
sex we all knew it now I go to parties
it's the guy who brings a cheese plate
who going to be Knee Deep and puss the
whole night right you're like did this
[ __ ] bring
Mana like women start throwing their
panties you want to make a woman in her
40s come give her a slice of 12age guda
she'll fure
out so what's next for Jenny Zino what's
next for Jenny Zino is I'm going to sell
a TV show I'm G to sell a movie I'm
going to build a comedy Empire that is
going to rule the world and then I'll
get a backlash and then I'll disappear
for like 10 years and then I'll
resurface and I'll be a God thanks Jenny
thank
you my lips are on point
okay