hello I'm Phil
Crosby you know kids are a lot like
regular people they don't say a lot and
they're pretty boring unless of course
they've been drinking and when they have
been drinking kids say the darnest
things when they're drunk
let's get them
started
[Music]
cheers looks like someone's got the
other foot into the pickle
jar you have a friend in the diamond
business you don't know nothing no you
don't know nothing you don't know
nothing you don't even know
it I guess the mattress is driving
itself to
church tell me about your puppy I'm up
tomor ping
crap take my mouth shut and bury me
alive I hear you had a girlfriend yeah
she left me and took everything but the
book what books are good right I can't
can't
read looks like someone's nose has been
sniffing around the Brandy
patch this will fit in the are you drunk
young man no I think you are no I'm not
yes you are you can't have any more of
this stuff yes I
can we'll leave the hooker in the tub
cuz she ain't breathing
you are a big
fat
what sir I think it's time to cut you
off give me this
thing there we
oh
Claire well that's where my career at
see you next time with old people say
the dest things when we slap them around
and take their pills and
stuff hey wait a second can I get a
little bit of that get your own
[Music]