[Music]
and now another fine product from
Redneck Trailer
Farms breakfast is boring and ethnically
impure hey
kids you ready to segregate breakfast
from other meals of the day yeah it's
the brand
wizard
yeah run
run uhoh this Cal's in the wrong
neighborhood I better say the magic
words NASCAR
Kazam yay thanks Brand wizard hey no
problem kids Clan brand is pure bleach
white O Cereal it's great for breakfast
or lych
yay it's nice and soft because RAC
people got rotten
teeth hey guys check this out the milk
stays white
yeah hey who wants more Clan brand I do
I do
yeah Clan brand cereal from the makers
of separate but total