[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
let
[Music]
[Applause]
mermas
R
the
ladies and Gentlemen please welcome my
good friend Keith lol
[Applause]
Jensen
w thank you thank you Merry
Christmas Merry Christmas Merry
Christmas I love Christmas I can't get
enough of it it's my favorite time of
year I even like the mall this time of
year I go there late after most of the
idiots have gone home but I love it I
love Christmas thank you guys for coming
and celebrating this wonderful holiday
Christmas with
me
Christmas it's a Christmas tree
Christmas stockings
Christmas love
it thank you for accepting that about
me I get grief I get grief about my love
of Christmas from
Christians we
say oh no no no no no no no no you can't
you can't reject Christianity all year
then all of a sudden embrace it when
it's fun no
no no
no it's like they think I found some
kind of Life Hack or something some
Cosmic cheat
code one of them actually said to me you
got to take the good with the bad and I
said that's
weird that's the first time I ever heard
you admit there's a fair Shake of
[Laughter]
bad no no no you can't do that you can't
have guilt-free masturbation all year
and then still get a gift wrap copy of
America's best Comics under your tree
Christmas morning
no you have to wake up 52 Sundays a year
early to go be bored out of your skull
by some dude who has no business being
on a stage except that he excels at
self-righteousness and then and only
then can you get a little red stocking
with a little reindeer in it that poops
little chocolate covered raisins when
you push on the time quarters you got to
earn
it and if there are any Christians here
tonight and I hope there are because I
love you guys you're totally welcome I
want to tell you good job on the
reindeer I love that thing that is the
most
awesome
that's that's me Christmas morning every
Christmas morning I'm there I I wear
them out by February and I have to wait
and get a new one the next year I'm just
doing it right into my
mouth my family's laughing look it's
pooping in his
mouth happy birthday baby Jesus oh this
is
great when Christians are upset at
seeing atheists enjoying Christmas I
feel like I have to explain to them what
an atheist is like I'm an atheist that
means I don't believe in God that's all
it means it doesn't mean that I reject
everything in their Bible there are
parts of their Bible that I really love
parts that mean a lot to me parts that
are beautiful like I love in their Bible
where it says that you should go out
into the woods and fell a tree and then
drag it back to your house and stand it
up and decorate it all in astrological
symbols it's good
stuff being sure to do so right around
saturnalia Ule New
Year's it's a beautiful passage in that
holy
book there are Christmas traditions that
I love like in every town they have the
one rich neighborhood where people go
crazy and they spend like my food budget
for an entire year on their Christmas
light display you know showing off that
they can pay their electric
bills and in the spirit of Christian
generosity they then invite us poor
people to come out and look at their
houses until
10:00 and then get out of
here I went out to do the Christmas
lights with my wife and my daughter and
my mom and my mom she loves Jesus and uh
my mom is champing at the bit to get my
daughter a nativity set and nativity
sets are sneaky cuz they look like
toys that's not playing Fair they with
toys you little s
dolls uh and I told my mom like like I
want my daughter to be exposed to the
cultures that are around her I want her
to be exposed to different religions
just not yet like Mom she's three like
that's a bit young to find out that
she's
evil it can wait so we're out there
we're walking we're looking at the
lights and uh one of the families they
were setting up their nativity set and
they had one of those big plastic light
up ones like Jesus would have
wanted and they had just started so
they'd only put up the uh the teens in
crisis that are Central to the
story
and and the the still empty
manger and my daughter sees this and she
says daddy daddy uh who are those two
women and why is their nest
empty my mom Pricks up her
ears I said listen listen sweetie let me
explain that to you uh that's Mary there
on the left and now next to Mary that's
her partner
Josephine
and that Nest is empty uh because it's
really really hard to find a white baby
in the Middle
East I got I got nothing for my mom for
Christmas that
year
and lo there came unto them a
reindeer who was unlike the other
reindeer and that his nose glowed with a
great
luminescence and his poop was of dried
fruit and
chocolate it's a beautiful
religion I respect it I have a special
attachment to Christmas because I once
performed comedy at Santa Claus's
funeral I'll explain
uh wonderful man Dale black some of you
may have known him he's a good friend of
mine thank you for Dale and uh Dale
played Santa Claus Dale black played
Santa and he was a real beard Santa and
I if you know that that's a thing but
among Santa Clauses a real beard Santa
really looks down on a fake beard Santa
like if you're a fake beard Santa don't
step foot in a real beard Santa bar okay
not be
welcome uh Dale did not stuff a pillow
in his Santa outfit he had the real
belly if you don't think that we live in
a beautiful age you need to listen more
carefully to what I'm telling
you Dale made a living working a couple
of months a year and his job description
was don't shave never say no to
dessert Dale had it figured out
and then he
died yeah it was it was very sad uh
Dale's Widow went about putting together
the services and the thing is Dale is
one of these guys that said when I die I
don't want it to be a sad Affair I don't
want some sad weepy Affair I want it to
be a party I want my friends to all come
together and celebrate my life Dale
wanted the
funeral
now a lot of you have probably said that
or heard that and thought it was cool
and here's the thing it's not it's not
cool at all because if you die your
friends should be allowed to get
together and be sad and not pretend like
they're happy you know uh and if you do
go ahead and do the funeral anyway can
you leave it in your will or whatever
that they not play The Beatles In My
Life
because if you want me not to cry you
don't play in my life cuz that's a
crying song all right I could be having
sex while eating a snow
[Laughter]
cone but that that's my happy
place but that song comes on I'm
balling both
[Laughter]
spellings w
thank
you so Dale's Widow is putting together
the services and uh she turns my friend
Matt she says Matt Dale always loved
your music would you put together a
small band played Services Matt says oh
of course absolutely you know we get
together some other guys that Dale loved
and she turns to John and she says John
Dale always loved your poetry would you
come read a poem for Dale you know oh of
course I'm there shs me she says Keith
Dale was a fan of yours he always made
him laugh uh would you come do a set and
I said I will be honored and then the
intelligent voice in the back of my head
it's very small but uh sometimes loud
and it said you're a comedian idiot you
just agreed to perform at a
funeral like oh it did didn't
I so uh so I show up and it was going
well there were great incredible
musicians and poetry and everything else
uh and as I go on stage I notice that a
lot of the people in the audience were
much older than me uh they were old
folks is what I'm saying and uh so I let
them know that I I would have business
cards in the
lobby you got to stay ahead of the
business you got to stay ahead of the
business I went on stage and I told him
I said hey uh you know I know a lot of
you know me and and you know that I'm an
atheist and uh and so I'm raising my
daughter with different beliefs than
than a lot of you raised your children
with but I do want you to know that
thanks to our friend Dale black my
daughter is growing up believing in a in
a kind generous and beautiful man named
Santa
Claus and then for the first time in my
adult life my filter kicked in it had
never happened before and I didn't say
the rest of that which was and also
thanks to Dale she will forever believe
that Santa Claus died when she was two
[Applause]
[Laughter]
which is Gonna Save my wife and I a lot
of
money thank you very much for
that I mentioned my daughter I should uh
I should let you know she's a tiger I
don't know if I remembered to mention
that or not my little girl's a tiger uh
she's a tiger because she really likes
tigers and so she decided to be one she
came to me and she said Daddy I'm a
tiger and I was like okay cuz I support
that kind of
self-actualization now the thing about
my tiger is she has three grandmas okay
uh she's lucky that way a lot of kids
only get to have two she gets to have
three grandmas because grandpa doesn't
know how to behave
himself and the grandmas did didn't know
that they were going to get a tiger so
they buy her really boring little girl
presents things that are of no use to a
Savage orange and black striped
Beast like the three baby dolls that
just sit on her bed
untouched until a couple weeks ago when
I see her walking down the hallway and
she's pulling a box behind her and in
the Box are nestled all three baby girls
little dish towels over them it was
adorable I said sweetie that's great
you're playing with your baby dolls she
said tiger food
dad in the morning
[Laughter]
[Applause]
room I
said Tiger's got to
eat then I did what a responsible parent
does in this day and age I went and I
grabbed a
camera cuz I need the YouTube
[Laughter]
hits and uh as I was recording her she
did an amazing thing she she took one of
the baby dolls and she went over to a
filing cabinet and opened the drawer and
put the baby doll in and shut the drawer
and I said uh sweetheart what are you
doing she said oh it's the oven
daddy you got to cook
[Music]
them I said all
right let's just see how deep this
Rabbit Hole
[Laughter]
goes tell me precious daughter of
mine how long do you cook a baby
girl she says oh you know about two
hours or until they stop
squirming
yeah wasn't ready to hear that come out
of my little girl's
mouth people say does that worry
you no no it doesn't worry me it
shouldn't worry me it's unbridled
imagination okay it's just the Fantastic
imagination of a child who hasn't been
told that it's wrong that's all that is
and it's awesome and I love it and I
can't wait to see that fantastic
imagination takes her I'm going to be
proud I'm going to be proud dad that's
my role and cuz my friends are jerks
they go oh yeah oh yeah what if she
becomes a serial
killer to which I say well female serial
killers are
[Laughter]
rare this is my precious
gem and I can just see myself bragging
someday
oh oh I'm sorry excuse me uh that's
actually 17 known
[Applause]
victims it's my little
tiger I uh I get people that worry that
I'm getting material from my kid they're
like oh are you exploiting her taking
advantage of your kid no no I'm not
she's on my writing staff all right
chill I pay her pay her in oatmeal and
raisins but listen she has full health
and
dental so she's doing better than most
of the comics that you've seen in this
town good for
her I woke up one morning and I had a
goal that morning my goal was I'm going
to write one joke I'm gonna write one
joke before I go back to bed again and I
walk out and she yeah yeah that's a
pretty great way to live
huh thank you for
appreciating how awesome my life
is I walk into the kitchen and there she
is already having breakfast and she
looks up at me and the first words out
of her mouth Daddy I wish that I had
tongues on the bottom of my
feet so that I can kick things and taste
them
to which I
said good
night I have a wonderful wife I love her
very much uh we are celebrating in
January 20 years together as a couple
yeah
yeah thank you for that I I didn't do it
for the Applause it mostly the sex
uh that's a nice added benefit um and
I'm proud of it I'm proud that I've
managed to maintain a relationship with
such an amazing person for two decades
uh but I also sometimes feel weird about
telling people CU I think that when you
say to someone I've been in a
heterosexual monogamous relationship for
20 years what they're thinking is yeah
this guy's boring in the
bedroom right because being in a
relationship for two decades like that
it seems like you'd probably be pretty
vanilla Between the
Sheets not true
okay I'm here to tell you I'm kinky as
heck my big kick is I just really want
to bang an old
lady and I'm super
patient I can give you a minute with
that
one you'll know you got that joke when
it Dawns on you that it's actually very
sweet like I would wager it's the most
romantic way that anyone has ever said
the words I want to bang an old
lady Hallmark are you
listening I uh I think we need to lie to
Children atheists in the room I'm
talking to
you listen any religious people atheist
meeting real quick you're welcome to
stay but we just need to talk for a
second uh guys we need to lie to the
kids we need to lie to the kids or we're
going to lose okay because they're lying
to the children and we can't stay on our
moral High ground and refuse to fight
fire with fire it's time to lie to the
children do you know that they're
telling kids that condoms don't work by
using this scientific tidbit the pores
in a condom the little microscopic pores
in a condom are actually bigger than an
AIDS virus so the AIDS virus can get
right through them of course because we
all know that aids viruses ride tiny
little bicycles and travel on their
own
we need to be willing to lie to the
children we need to say kids kids kids
listen listen the reason they're so bent
about condoms is that there's actually a
loophole in the Bible and sex with a
condom doesn't actually count a sex at
all it's
true just bang all you want you can
still wear a white dress on your wedding
day it's
awesome how about it kids
[Laughter]
they uh they don't let me talk to the
children they don't let me talk to the
kids I wish they would I wish they would
let me talk to the kids I have some
stuff to
say I'd like to have a public service
announcement I wish they would let me do
public service announcements cuz I did
drugs and I drank alcohol and they were
fun and then I was done and I didn't do
them anymore I'm not an AA or anything
else I was like yay that was great now
I'm going to go be an adult and I just
moved on I could give good advice
instead they always have somebody who
was terrible at
it come and talk to
you and they don't give you advice it's
going to help you it's just say no yeah
oh that's brilliant did you come up
without
yourself no imagine if I had a public
service announcement they'd zoom in on
me I'd say hey kids
listen who we kidding I know you're
going to do
drugs here's the thing stay away from
the white ones all right those are
trouble you'll do all right co-pilots
really good idea uh and one other thing
at 3:00 a.m. don't go to Denny's when
you're
high sounds like a good idea they're
open they have
Edibles uh no cops hang out at
Denny's and the waitress there she is a
waitress at Denny's at 3 in the morning
because she didn't stay away from the
white drugs and she's gonna mess with
you cuz she's
bitter it's a negative trip and then the
star goes across the screen the more you
know where's the
camera
kids kids listen to me masturbation is
awesome and totally
healthy great stress relief one piece of
advice conditioner a okay shampoo real
freaking bad
idea the more you
[Applause]
[Laughter]
know they should let me talk to the
children I uh I went to church camp when
I was a kid uh real quick how many
atheists are in the room right
now all right and real quick how many of
you went to church
[Applause]
camp I hope they never figure out how
badly those things are backfiring
on they're the most awesome little
atheist factories it's
just so
great so I went to church camp and I got
up early in the morning to go use the
swimming pool and uh I get to the
swimming pool and there's one other
person already there and she's swimming
across the pool so I sit down and uh she
gets out on the other side and I realize
that she's swimming in nothing but a
t-shirt with nothing
underneath I don't know if you guys know
what happens when a t-shirt is soaking
wet there are
contests
uh I'm not sure if she was training to
compete or not uh but she could have she
could have I would have given her a 10 I
was pleased to be there at that moment
and so she walks in front of me and I
expect her to keep going embarrassed and
leave but no she walks around to the
other side of the pool and jumps back in
and gets back out on the other side
again which means she now knows I'm
there and is fine with it and this gives
me the most tremendous erection I've
ever
had she walks in front of me again she
jumps in the
pool
she gets out on the other side and I'm
sorry to say this please be generous I
was very young but it was at that point
that for the first time I actually
looked up at her
face shouldn't have taken so long I know
but when I looked at her face I went oh
I know her that's my friend Sue and Sue
is developmentally
disabled yeah which screwed up this
whole consent she knows I'm looking
thing and made me feel really horribly
guilty I said my friend Sue has a
disability and I just exploited her she
didn't know what she was doing and I
took advantage of it and I felt terrible
I was horribly morally conflicted and I
say conflicted because not all of me uh
had a problem with
this there was one part of me that was
like
still like do you have a soul and then
he was like what you're still looking
and I was like damn it I know I
[Laughter]
am Sue walked by again and as I my gaze
followed her I noticed that Kenny had
entered the pool area and Kenny was one
of the counselors at this church camp
and I thought these are the kind of
moments that these counselors are here
for so I strategically arranged a towel
and then walked over to talk to Kenny
and I get there and I say hey Kenny and
he says hey little dude and I said can I
talk to you for a minute he says sure I
have a seat and I sit next to Kenny
Kenny and Kenny is playing with a huge
gash that he put in his knee uh hiking
or skateboarding or something and he
hadn't taken care of it and it was
swollen up and disgusting looking and he
says check out my knee bro and I look at
his knee and he
says doesn't it look like a
[ __ ] my answer to Kenny was
two-part
the first part was I don't
know the second part was oh my God I
hope
[Applause]
[Laughter]
not but my erection had gone
away so that was
cool then a female counselor came out
and saw Sue and went over and wrapped a
towel around her and took her away to
teach her about undergarments and I want
went back to my cabin and masturbated
and became an
atheist that's not the true story of how
I became an atheist it's a true story
but not the true story of how I became
an atheist but the true story of how I
became an atheist involves books and
reading and all this boring stuff I like
that one
better
how'd you become an atheist [ __ ]
[Music]
knee I think it's a good
answer you guys get Robo calls oh yeah
yeah why'd you sound so
unhappy you gotta you gotta maintain a
child sense of wonderment about these
things think about it when you were a
kid if they told you that in the future
you were going to get phone calls from
robots that would have sounded way
cooler than it has actually turned out
to
be oh heinan how you've disappointed
me I like to imagine that the robots
calling me are at least wearing high
heels and some
leather something exciting is going on
we get we get one Robo call all the time
uh or we were getting it you answer the
phone and you hear Google that's right
Google and we got it so often that that
became a greeting at my house like I'd
walk in and say Google and my wife and
kid would say that's right Google and
then we would go about our night
together so it was funny it was funny
for a while but then I got tired of it
so I answered found Google that's right
Google and I wait through the whole
recording
and then they get to the end and they're
giving you the options you know uh to be
annoyed in another language PR you know
uh and then finally I he to talk to a
live operator hit this button I hit the
button uh they Place him Antonio Carlos
shim which is cool uh yeah that one was
for you sir
um no it's beautiful music and they
shouldn't be abusing it that way it's
just wrong uh and then the guy comes on
and he says would you like to be on the
front page of Google
and I was like oh man I think I'm
talking to the guy that made the
recording this is
amazing but then it Dawns on me I hadn't
come up with anything clever to say like
I just dialed right away and I'm
thinking I'm supposed to be a comedian
I'm supposed to be quick on my feet
think of something to say come on do it
so I
say
gole and he replies yes
Google like this is the most enthusiasm
he's had all day like I hear other
operators coming and gathering around
him like come on Jeff's got one on the
line you know you can do it buddy you
can do it I gave him another one
Google he says yes yes we'll get you
right on the front page of Google and
then he starts explaining to me how
they're going to do it and it's really
complicated considering I've presented
myself as a not that smart cave man at
this point it's got algorithms and all
this other stuff and the weird thing
about these sales people is they expect
you to cut them off they expect you to
hang up so they try to just talk as
quick as they can and if you don't stop
them they will stumble right into
personal business it's amazing oh Google
and we'll do this and we'll get you on
the front page and oh you're really
going to like it I hope so you know I
deal with a lot of rejection in this
business my uh my wife thinks I don't
work that hard cuz I get to sit down for
a living but you can really start
feeling bad about yourself your
time the guy finishes and he's given me
a lot to think about you
know I'll think it over and I
say
Google at which point he
says
yeah
Google and then I remembered something
that a friend of mine who did phone work
had told
me which is that they're not allowed to
hang
up and I had nothing to do that
night like
cool this poor guy is like pulling out
the employee manual and just reading
everything to have something to keep
saying and I just keep
Google
then after a
while he says yeah yeah Google we can
get you on front page Google listen we
can also get you on the front page of
Yahoo and much to my surprise I found
some brand loyalty had kicked
in when he said Yahoo it got my dander
up and I replied
Google
and to my
delight he started playing
along and in a perfect Clint Eastwood he
said
[Applause]
[Laughter]
Yahoo I looked outside and it's humble
weed blew by
incredible and I said go go go go go go
go go go go go go go go and he said
Yahoo Yahoo Yahoo Yahoo and I
said and he
saidah and two full grown
men for like three straight
minutes yelled highly patented but
completely nonsensical sounds at one
another possibly thousands of miles
apart from one
another and and then my favorite thing
happened I
heard all right thanks brother man you
have a good weekend
click
Victory but the more I thought about it
and started telling other people about
it it started Dawning on me what a
magical thing it was that had happened I
mean two adults two adult
strangers paused in their day to to play
like children to tap their imagination
in the way that we don't do often enough
as adults and to just be creative and
silly and ridiculous together and I
thought man that's really cool I should
share this story I thought I should blog
this story I should YouTube this story I
should get this story out there and you
know what if the story gets back to the
dude he'll know how to get in touch with
me through my blog through YouTube you
know I'm easy to
reach and then I thought what I really
need to do is I need to find a way to
get this story on the front page of
Google but they don't call me
anymore thank God it's Friday that's the
thing people say thank God it's Friday
really CU as I remember it God was
actually a big proponent of the six day
work
week if you don't mind I'll thank a
union member it's
Friday thank very
[Applause]
much I recently reread the book
1984 it's a fun book to read on this
side of
1984 George Orwell had some ridiculous
ideas
do you know that he supposed that by
this point in our history we would all
be speaking in some kind of hyper
efficient news speak I tell you what
when I read that I just l m AO you know
what I'm
saying I just loled and L and L and L
and L L
L it's interesting is the thing that
Orwell never could have foreseen is that
we would all go out and buy the cameras
ourselves and that our biggest fear
would be that no one's
watching I I really love the band Joy
Division they're one of my favorite
bands I really love the band new order
another one of my favorite bands I
realized recently that I actually like
New Order better than Joy
Division yeah it's troubling to me
makes me feel guilty because it kind of
feels like I'm saying that Ian Curtis
might have made the right
[Laughter]
decision that guy will explain the joke
to you after the
show I've been doing some writing I'm U
working on a country song I haven't
gotten past the title but I think it's
pretty darn good
it's called her safe word was
[Laughter]
goodbye if you know a couple of chords
and some words that rhyme with goodbye
hit me up after the
show I've writing a lot of suicide notes
lately
[ __ ] don't worry about me
bro no no no don't worry about me it's
just uh I think that it's an
underappreciated art form and I thought
I would take a stab at
it came up with one that I really like
it says
goodbye you can have my
records but I'm taking all my
pills
[Laughter]
kisses I do suffer from depression a
little bit I think that's thing is I'm
not sure if I suffer from depression or
if I'm just legitimately sad about
things that are perfectly valid to be
sad about you know like maybe I'm
depressed or maybe I just have this
creeping Sensation that I'm trapped on a
rock hurdling through space with a bunch
of people who instead of using their
resources to figure out how to get off
of the damn Rock are committing most of
their resources to blowing pieces of it
up that gives me a
sad
there's a lot of stuff to make you sad
out there I had to go and buy life
insurance because I have a kid and if
you're poor and you have a kid you buy
life insurance lest you be a
jerk so I go into buy life insurance and
I'm sitting across from the insurance
broker she's a nice lady well-dressed
smelled like soap and she's explaining
it to me and she's throwing around
numbers that I'm not used to I don't own
a house I drive a hand me- down car I
don't deal with numbers of this size
they're all abstract to me but as she's
throwing these numbers at me it Dawns on
me holy
Toledo for the first time in my life I'm
worth
something I sign that paper I'm actually
something if I
die and because I have no filter I say
this out loud to
her and cool as it cucumber she responds
well suicides not covered for the first
months
whoa just tell me I can kill myself in
four
years I have 17 months
left I didn't intend to keep count that
was never my intention but when someone
tells you something like that you can't
help it
like every look at the calendar becomes
this really depressing thing like to me
now every calendar is a really morbid
Advent
calendar you peel back the date instead
of a piece of chocolate there's like a
Zoloft or
something but it's a depressing thing to
to be worth all that money if I die when
when your three-year-old experiences
death cuz the neighbor's rat dies and
she's exploring her own mortality and
she says to you Daddy I hope you never
die your first thought shouldn't be are
you
[Laughter]
sure you know you could go to
college I uh I do have suicidal thoughts
and impulses and I have since I was a
kid uh it happens all the time um and
I'll I'll tell you it's funny cuz they
never never happen with like the
legitimate heavy stuff that you would
think would make one want to take their
own life it's never because of losing
some job that meant a lot to me because
I've done that a lot uh never happens
because someone breaks my heart those
are the moments when I feel most alive I
know how to get on top of that stuff you
know it's for stupid reasons uh like
embarrassing myself that's the number
one thing that'll trigger a suicidal
impulse In Me Is embarrassment like if I
bomb in front of a comedy audience for
instance no pressure
um or if I farted a party that's a big
one like like it's weird that that's
such a huge fear to me like I have
actually not done some things in my life
that probably would have been amazing
because I'm like oh what if a fart you
know just kept me home
alone think of all the horrific things
that could happen in life it shouldn't
be that high on the list that I might
walk into a party and have like Keith
Mark Mark Keith oh hey Mark oh my God
I'm
sorry walk
outside because then the next day nobody
would be talking about the fact that I
farted at the
party they be like oh man you Keith blew
his brains all over the lawn at the
party last night uh or my luck they'd
actually say yeah it was
amazing dude walked into the house just
said went outside boom I think he was
telling us all to go [ __ ] ourselves
I become a
martyr I had a really terrible
embarrassment recently uh this was a
really bad one I I went to my
gastroenterologist I have a disease
called ulcerative colitis uh don't worry
about me it's managed very well thank
you science
uh but I have to go and get a finger
stuck up my ass a little more than I
might otherwise so it's not a big deal
you get used to it which is funny cuz
there was a time in my life where I
didn't think that that could ever be the
case uh when I was a kid about eight or
nine years old I was playing at my
friend Mitch's house and his dad comes
home and I say oh hey Miss uh Mr mcneel
how you doing and he says uh oh not good
Keith I said oh why is that and he said
the doctor just stuck his finger in my
ass and I said oh God
why to which he said to make sure I
don't have ass
cancer and oh the innocence of Youth I
said [ __ ] that I'd rather have ass
[Laughter]
cancer if there was a god at that moment
he'd be all lots of fingers up your butt
your
future so I go into my
gastroenterologist and I want want to be
mature I know it's not pleasant for him
either you know uh probably more
pleasant with me than some other people
that's one of those thoughts that makes
you feel a little bit better you're like
I bet I bet this isn't the worst ass he
has to stick a finger
in I'm not going to ask him like it's
nice right it's
[Applause]
nice I go in and we have a ritual that
we do he says hello we talk conspiracy
theories for a while he's a cool doctor
then he comes over and he and he feels
my glands and he feels under my ribs for
pressure and then he goes over to his
little table now I know when he goes
over to his little table that's my queue
and I undo my belt and I unbutton my
pants and I unzip my pants and I open my
pants up because he's getting a glove on
and getting looped up at that point
right only on the last occasion he turns
around with no glove and then sees me
and goes no no no not
today and then stands there and watches
as I have to do the zip of
Shame as if I had enthusiastically
prepared and I'm now suffering from
rejection from some jerk whose finger I
didn't even want up my ass
[Laughter]
anyway doc are you allowed to prescribe
zolof is that a thing you can
do um I do know that I've been talking
about a lot of depressing stuff and
suicide and kind of buming you guys out
but I did warn you that this was going
to be a Christmas special
so set a goal for myself that I wanted
to make the most depressing Christmas
special since Charlie
Brown and that's a high
bar a high bar that brilliant brilliant
special so uh I have I I've hit a point
where I I think I had a breakthrough I
think I'm actually doing better than
I've ever been doing in my life and
here's the Breakthrough I realize what
happened with me my life just peaked
early that's the thing that happens you
know your life just Peaks early and
sometimes sometimes life goes on long
after the thrill of living is gone to
truism and I'll tell you about when my
life peaked and what happened uh so when
I was in the fourth
[Laughter]
grade I went out to the lunch area at my
school and uh we used to take pieces of
our pizza and throw them to the seagulls
and we had this crowd of Seagulls that
would always be flying over our lunch
area and on this one day I go out and
this sixth grader is standing there with
a handful of Pebbles and he's throwing
pebbles at the seagulls and what a jerk
you know sat down eat my lunch and then
he hit one of the seagulls and he hit it
hard and the seagull cried have you guys
ever heard a seagull cry and I don't
mean that sound that they make that
means hey throw me another pizza crust
bro they make this noise this sound of
just betrayal and sadness and I'm sorry
Prince I'm sure when dobs cry it's
heartbreak
but this turned me inside out this is
what you should have wrote the song
about and I turn to the kid and I'm
expecting to see remorse and instead I
see yeah bro I got one give me five and
he puts his hand out and at exactly that
second a bird [ __ ] in his
hand
and I said oh wow that was
awesome I will probably never see
anything that great
again
damn I would have would have lik to have
saved
that there's this documentary about
something they call the moonman syndrome
and it's about the men that went to the
moon and then came back they actually
stood on on the surface of the Moon and
looked at the Earth just a little Blue
Marble floating in space and when they
came back from that they were hit with
the most
powerful
depression because what do you do after
you've been to the moon like catch up on
the dishes you know obviously have sex
with a lot of people but that would get
boring after a while I suppose I'd have
to imagine
uh and as they're talking to these men
about this experience and they're
zooming in on their faces and I'm
looking at that lost expression in their
eyes I
thought I got you on this one I
understand I once saw a bird [ __ ] on a
sixth
grader and don't get me wrong I'm not
saying there haven't been amazing
moments in my life cuz that would be
wrong of me there have been in I've had
insanely wonderful life I got to stand
this close to the woman I love's face
and watch her say those magic words I do
and a short time after that I got to be
equally close to her as our child came
into the world through her body this is
all amazing stuff but the thing that you
have to understand is that the bird [ __ ]
right in the middle of his goddamn Palm
at exactly the right second perfectly
executed Aven Revenge [ __ ] five and I
was there to see it
[Laughter]
was
beautiful I uh I mentioned that I have a
big anniversary coming up um another
anniversary I'm selling uh or
[Applause]
celebrating damn you
Freud
we can fix this in post
uh another anniversary I am
celebrating uh is that of my niece uh my
niece uh she'll be soon celebrating her
second anniversary uh she married her
wife and they got married down in Long
Beach California now I'm telling my
friends about this and uh I'm excited it
was uh it was a really cool thing her
father who is a Christian minister
actually performed the service and
married his daughter to the woman that
she loved which is really cool they're
beautiful people I love telling people
about it but then I have people do the
math and come back at me and go wait
that doesn't make sense how they get
married in Long Beach gay marriage
wasn't legal in California when they got
married well that's the thing I forgot
to mention my niece she's a
badass this badass said oh oh State of
California guess what you don't get to
decide if I'm married or
not
pretty badass you know who it reminds me
of you know the other little badasses it
reminds me of those Who's down in
Whoville
right cuz the same thing happened to
them some Grinch went tried to take
their Christmas tell them they couldn't
have Christmas Even though they had
every right to have Christmas took all
their stuff went on up into the Hills
what did those who's
do they said guess what
Grinch you don't get to
decide whether or not we have Christmas
and they had Christmas anyway
[Laughter]
badasses but the thing I want you to
remember is that that story had a very
happy ending because what happened to
that
Grinch his heart grew three sizes that
day and I think that that can happen to
our homophobes here in this country I
hope that it can I think that their
hearts can explode in their [ __ ]
chests Merry Christmas good
[Applause]
[Music]
night
let
this
mer
Christmas
R
the
a W
wo W
[Music]
wo