[Applause]
[Music]
standup records presents Londa Lester
Shandi Superstar imported from
Detroit it's a new year uh I'm trying to
be optimistic not really going well uh
it's a lot of weird [ __ ] happening and
you know I was looking at the news I was
like oh [ __ ] we beefing with the
Russians
again how the [ __ ] did that happen like
I am a child of the 80s and I remember
all them propaganda ass movies the
Russians are not to be [ __ ] with
okay anybody who would wait in line for
14 hours for a bowl of porridge ain't
got [ __ ] the move
that [ __ ] ain't even got no butter and
sugar in it
damn I don't know man so the other day
Jehovah's eyewitnesses stopped
by usually I'm like hey get the [ __ ] off
the way from around here with that no
birthday
[Laughter]
[ __ ] however the way things have been
going I was just like hey come on in I
got some question
questions you know like is this it like
is this how is this [ __ ] going to jump
off like that and you know they told me
some [ __ ] it was kind of heavy I was
like you know thank you for the
information and ruining my
[Music]
house that's that's cool the guy's like
do you mind if I leave some watchtowers
I don't know it really depend how y'all
feel about birthday
still oh y'all don't no oh yeah don't
come back with mm-m
I would hate to have to sck my dog on
you that's Lea Lester Shandi Superstar
imported from Detroit
[Music]