[Applause]
and keep that Applause going for Londa
ler oh I'm so glad to see y'all how you
doing
tonight awesome this is way better than
the last show I did I did a show for
some
nerds it was a convention talking about
the future of Bitcoins
[Music]
I was like Bitcoins what the [ __ ] is
that let me look on my phone looked that
[ __ ] up and was like oh hell no uh
excuse me before any jokes get started
are y'all trying to pay me in
Bitcoins cuz if I had a choice between
that and some chuck-e cheese tokens
[Applause]
I'm [ __ ] with them tokens all
day cuz at least I know they street
value Bitcoins what is that [ __ ] B by 12
Snickers bars of the [ __ ] Magic
Gathering card like
what y'all ain't even on the gold
standard hell
no oh man I got called out for sludge
shaming last
week right
this what happened so I'm downtown
smoking a cigarette outside with a
friend of mine and we see this girl come
running by without no shirt on so I was
like damn girl if you got your titties
out on a
[Laughter]
Tuesday [ __ ] you going to do with Friday
get
here and my friend was like oh my god
did you just [ __ ] shame that girl Asanda
and I'm like [ __ ] I would
never what's slush
shaming and then she explained to me
that it was wrong that I had made fun of
that girl's raw ass titties like
that I should have been proud that she
was confident enough in her body to
share said raw tiedes with the
public and I'm sitting here like
mm and in my head I'm like see this why
I don't even be [ __ ] with white
people on Tuesday
nights always got to be some [ __ ] in
the
game hold on girl let me get this right
are you saying we can't talk about hoes
no
more who said
that the Huffington
[Music]
[Applause]
Post that sound like something some hoes
came up
with no
MM girl hoes make up like 32.4% of my
comedy material
it took me a long time to get them jokes
[ __ ] you can miss me with 68.1% of that
[ __ ] oh man I've been going on a lot
of auditions recently cuz I'm trying to
be famous not cuz I want to be rich I
just want some better [ __ ] to eat that's
all like my idea of making it would be
to be able to drive down I35 with a
plate of stakes in a passenger
seat and just ever so gently reaching
[Applause]
over that's
all I ain't got much I I don't ask for a
lot I went to this one audition that I
found on backpage.com I should have been
like what the [ __ ] but whatever I was
desperate uh so I go to this audition
and this dude is very excited about
reaching his Kickstarter goal and his
project so I'm like okay so he's like
okay so right like this young lady right
here she's going to play your best
friend she's got something very
important to tell you I want your
natural reaction do you have any
questions Eh this ain't really a
question more of a
declaration I wouldn't be hanging out
with this [ __ ] in real
life no offense
girl that's why they call it
acting I'm
ready action hey
girl hey girl I have something very
important to tell you oh what's
up I'm
bipolar damn
and the director was like
cut what the hell was
that that was my natural
reaction check this out I'm from
Detroit Motown the murder
Mitten and we don't have cute nicknames
for mental illnesses
either you is
crazy or you crazy than a [ __ ]
like we don't even need to bring WebMD
into none of
this so he tells me what he looking for
he basically like I'm looking for a big
personality oh you want some ghetto [ __ ]
I got you please forgive my fox paw
[Applause]
let me try that [ __ ] one more
time action hey girl hey
girl I have something important to tell
you I'm
schizophrenic I [ __ ] knew
it [ __ ] I knew was
crazy I knew you was crazy when you had
a Bluetooth and that [ __ ] was even
hooked up to a cell
[Applause]
phone I said it to myself this [ __ ] is
off and the director was like cut get
the [ __ ]
out which is why my ass is back for the
third year in a row in the finals trying
to win this [ __ ] thank you very much
have a good one
Le
ler and ladies and gentlemen this year's
funniest person in Austin winning $3,000
in that sweet laptop right there
everybody leand ler
oh man this is crazy cuz I'm drunk than
a [ __ ] right
now oh man this has been wow this is
crazy as hell I didn't think I was going
to do it I thought I was going to have
to beat up the judges this year
we cool though we cool oh thank you
thank you so
much it has been a very trying year for
me um I suffered kidney failure right
after last year's fpia so I'm on
dialysis right now and this is just so
oh man y'all going to make me cry I'm A
Thug [ __ ] from Detroit I can't
cry we work so hard doing this [ __ ]
y'all don't understand we be writing
these [ __ ] jokes and telling them in
front of four people and be like [ __ ]
what you think
like I love my Austin comedy people I
love the [ __ ] out of y'all we work hard
I promise I ain't going to embarrass the
crown of no [ __ ] uh thank you C city
thank you judges thank you Maggie M girl
black girls Rock black girls rock that
you B I'm going go get [ __ ] up thank
[Applause]
you Detroit Pimp [ __ ] Detroit pimp sh
thank you
[Music]