this is my mom Marilyn Bamford and this
is my poppy Joel Bamford and uh this is
Blossom and I'm Maria Manford and I'm
sitting sandwiched beneath between my
loved ones sandwiched oh I think Maria
is definitely the funniest she's I mean
she was funny when she was a little girl
sah she was a little girl she was
constantly funny I mean her sister Sarah
is very funny but in a different way but
but Maria was always looking for the
laugh and for the joke was always kind
of making fun of herself it was between
you were between like these I remember
you we these two wicker chairs and you
would you know hold on to both of them
and then do upside down
somersaults and we would be excited by
that and she'd think that was great we'd
laugh and that's really more of a cry
for
help you were liking it no I did enjoy I
remember flipping but flipping suggests
career in acrobatics much more than I
know but you like the Laugh you liked it
when we laughed I do like it I like like
that people laughing yeah I was a quiet
kid though I'd say you were quiet and
you enjoyed things like that was that
would have been a performance where you
get some action but I you you were doing
it for yourself and then we get to watch
that's what my career is like I'm doing
it for myself exactly and would wants to
show up that's cool yeah
yeah oh that's funny well I think it's
you know you're really remarkable being
able to put yourself out in front and
and see if people laugh and be able to
say well I didn't laugh at that um maybe
you shouldn't have paid for a ticket
yeah yeah
exactly maybe you buddy shouldn't have
paid 25 bucks to get in here if you
don't get what I'm doing
[Music]
Skyway
Skyway you get it it's a way to walk
through the
sky but it's usually just a
a kind of a brown Bridge with
Windows uh Plan B is
uh I did always want to be on a sitcom
and then I tried I auditioned and I did
uh a couple little tiny tiny parts and I
and uh I every time I went on a sitcom I
I thought a sitcom was going to be more
like you know actually the sitcom story
like where it's like so and so and and I
mean I was I was a guest star so uh you
know maybe it's not I'm not more of a
temp than a family member and um but it
wasn't that much fun like it was kind of
stressful and you had to put on a lot of
makeup and outfits and it was kind of it
was kind of a bad experience for me and
then I didn't I I
didn't uh I didn't enjoy it was really
because there's so much money involved
with sitcoms now I mean maybe it's
different on a like like a lower amount
of money but people seem really
terrified like of losing their jobs like
so everyone's
like cuz and they pay so much attention
to the script that it almost doesn't you
know I don't know it just doesn't it did
what didn't seem as fun you know cuz I
like from standup you know you just say
whatever you think is funny and you
don't have to have 70 people
going
no I think I think a banana is funny
sure I mean but the classic the banana
that's
funny why don't we go though let's
zigzag and go with a tangerine instead
like was all like talk like sort of like
the what's funny or something and it
just made me sad and tired but maybe
that's because I didn't get more parts
uh I'm sure if I got more parts maybe it
incredible it's very easy to uh to
criticize something that you can't get
into yeah that stuff's [ __ ]
that whole Fame and success thing you
know it just brings you down I'm not
into
it oh yeah so so but um it was yeah so I
did a couple things what was the other
thing on that oh and then I found every
time I was on a sitcom which is twice uh
this isn't a very thorough study uh but
I had to wear these giant boobs boow and
you know they said that was a part of
the character and that you know like
somehow I just thought that was so funny
I was like but you hired me to like I
don't I just so anyways the point is I
was frustrated that oh I want to do my
own sitcom cuz there's this whole
process of doing a sitcom too where you
have to meet with development people and
then they they they hire writers and it
just seems so like such a long way that
I could never I me know just seem so I
thought do it myself do it myself do it
myself and without
you know that I don't need anybody's
help I find that I mean maybe it's
antisocial but I think that's the best
way sometimes to do things is when you
don't need anybody's help so then nobody
can criticize it cuz it's just like you
can do whatever you want so that's
that's why I did that's that's what
that's what that's why I did I also had
a fantasy of moving home to duth
sometimes when I get depressed which is
every day uh so uh I think well you know
if you transplanted everything to a new
city you go oh maybe then I would you
know then I'd wear different outfits and
I'd have different coffee shops to go to
so I'd feel different and um so then I
thought so that was a way to act out my
fantasy of we to to and how it might
actually be so um but I might I might Mo
I don't know it's pretty sweet
here my current
one I do like dtor anonymous dead
Anonymous they just opened a there's a
meeting up here in in duth and that's
for it's for under earning and it's for
people if you have any problems with
like money if you're getting into too
much debt or you just if all you think
about as money and stuff like that
that's an awesome one I love a 12-step
program uh anyway you slice it uh love
it cuz it's free people talk about their
feelings I can't get enough that I love
people talking about their feelings and
uh and you get to
and they're at night and they're calm
and kind of it's nice um yeah I went to
I know I shouldn't say you
know yeah there's anonymity or whatever
that's good for people who care about it
but uh I I don't really care too much
but I love that's my favorite one for
now I don't want I switch over um da
also a lot of times they have pretty
good snacks cuz they're into abundance
the meetings in Los Angeles have have
tons of good snacks there oh forg to go
to an overeater town house meeting
that's kind of a bummer cuz there's no
snacks and uh there's a lot of
sugar-free
cocoa that's fun and then AA that's a
good one I can only go to opening me cuz
I I drink but I I just like to go and
hear people talk and uh and uh they
usually have good snacks too they have
cakes and stuff if cuz if you have a
certain amount of time ready to get a
cake that's
nice I always thought when I was a kid
it'd be fun to be a prostitute because
you don't realize what it is like cuz
you always see them on TV and they're
wearing fancy clothes then they go
shopping and then they they like meet up
with some kind of older guy or like a
business guy and he's nice and then they
just go and then it's the next day and
then they get to go shopping again
you're like oh that sounds good uh but
then they didn't show the part where
you're not enjoying yourself presumably
from what I've heard about the sex
industry is it's not all fun it's not
all good
times sometimes the guy isn't very good
looking or he isn't so
nice uh Del awesome
Australia some
sometimes
Australia that's my Australian accent I
was on a radio station in Australia and
um the radio announcer said you you
Australian exent is
terrible terrible it needs a lot of work
inside I tell her to get fued which is
an old Australian say no no that no I I
I don't do a very good Australia I do
love Australia though it's beautiful
it's wonderful and they're lovely and
it's and not just that it's got a
wonderful comedy and arts scene they
have they still have wonderful funding
by their
government for the Arts which is
something we could get
into we'd have to move to
Australia which is only a boat ride away
we could uh yeah get a boat get over
there
this is Lake Superior which is I think
the deepest of the Lakes I don't think
it's the biggest I'm not sure on that uh
maybe you can Google it uh anyways
beautiful Lake and I I've been on the
lake I've been on a Vista Cruis or too
over time I've also been out on a
sailboat uh sailboats make me nervous
cuz it always sort of activities you got
to do uh my dad would yell at us hardly
hardly coming about coming come on Jesus
come on Pull It in
pull oh was terrifying cuz part of is
where you go up high and people like
that when one side looks like it's
tipping over people like that part uh
that's not my favorite part my part is
when I
sit and eat a cracker with cheese spread
on it
and then it's kind of there's no
wind I find it funny and weird to uh
that I'm uh
talking about stuff in front of my
parents they're right here I didn't tell
you that they're right here that's weird
now now it's like an intervention woo oh
but on who who is the intervention on
we'll find
out Mom we have something to talk
about um every
time you buy fat-free ice cream I feel
angry and I feel scared because I like
regular ice
cream dad did you want to say your
feelings when she buys fat free ice
cream no okay I bought
sugarfree I like to be as comfortable as
I
can when I'm back in my hometown just
try to get
comfortable they don't have a lot of
benches down here so you just got to do
what you
can that'd be the first thing that I'd
do is i' if I had any money I'd dedicate
to my hometown like a like a couple
benches could sit
on yeah I used to impersonate things off
the TV so like things
off ladies talking on television about
things like I I did that on uh yeah that
there was a drops tooth polish
commercial that I like to impersonate M
Pearl drops tooth polish it's a great
feeling do you like do you like that Mom
was that pretty good I was like five
that must have been creepy but uh but uh
yeah so I did I did those kind
of when I come back home I think I
probably shouldn't be doing
impersonation to my family that and
somehow it seems like maybe it's not as
funny as I think it is just because you
know that what if it hurts their
feelings but then they think it's fun to
a point but then they oh I don't know
it's a mixed psychological bag but uh
but they're Pro I mean they let me in
here you
know this is where I went to you know
what prom how you go to prom you go for
dinner that's where I went here and we
went to
sneakers and in our prom
outfits and it's sneakers you could get
these big puffs of hot
bread what are those called powder Puffs
always Puffs the hot bread and it was uh
that minute was fancy and still means
it's
fancy this used to be a sleazy kids
clothing store too Tri go to and buy low
cut
outfits for the
winter you need to have plenty of low
cut outfits for the winter up here
there's nothing else to do but dance in
the
basement people say I sound like my dad
that I'm more like my dad naturally than
I'm you
know you know I don't say you know and
then he hasn't said anything
you know like you're like what you know
you know come on you know what I'm
talking about no I you haven't even
started a sentence how would I know what
you're talking about okay well if you
don't get it then that's your
thing could you start again at the
beginning of this conversation and uh
yeah so I think I'm more like that where
I just say phrases that I think people
are going to understand and they're like
what uh you know uh book uh
uh dog uh
duth not a lot of people you know know
me downtown know me you know it's it's
pretty safe for me to walk down
here so
okay it's good coming home nice to just
kind of
you know be myself you nobody gives me
any [ __ ] you know cuz I'm not I'm not
recognizable it's okay though I don't
need people to know me you know to get
me do you do you recognize this woman
man do you know who she is no I don't no
it's okay don't worry about it it's all
right it's okay I
don't see
that's what it's like man you try to get
yourself you know some kind of Fame and
that you know your target audience is
like who are you that's all right though
pretty soon we're all going to be I
don't do this for
recognition I bet if we went up to
Miller Hill Mall some people would know
me up there