Hey, thanks for watching my DVD.
Uh, this Is a one person sitcom, uh,
me moving back to Duluth, Minnesota.
And so, uh, thanks for watching.
And, uh, the bridge is going up.
So it's time to start the show.
That's super nasty. Yes.
Um, listen, so here I'm gonna, if some of you guys seem
to came to see standup, uh, it might be a bit disappointing
because this is a one person shoe
and, uh, uh, then, uh,
but that the thing is, the cool thing about that is that it,
the theme of the show is disappointment. And that, uh,
Sometimes Life doesn't almost turn out as you planned,
but something magnificent and incredible
and magical that you never could have dreamed
of happens instead or not.
So, uh, like all of us here tonight, uh,
I have always believed I deserve to have my own sitcom.
And, uh, I've been to Hollywood, I've auditioned, uh, Maria.
Uh, so read through the part and just be yourself.
That's really my only note. We just wanna see who you are.
So be yourself. Have fun with it. Any questions? No.
Okay, go ahead. Uh, and then I read the part
and I be myself, and I say, okay, um,
I know I told you to be yourself, um,
but we really need the character to be likable
and, uh, oh, we got the wrong person.
Uh, so I went, uh, uh,
have an agent and she's real positive. Maria,
This industry has a DD right now.
I'm looking at you and you're amazing,
and your brilliant you, you're superb,
and you're everything that we are looking for.
And then suddenly it's gone. And I'm bored, I'm irritated.
I wanna get a cup of coffee or something to eat.
And then I don't know what it is you did or didn't do,
but I am back in again.
And you are superlative and you are hyperbole,
and you are a polar bear in the jungle,
and you are a giant, within a giant being a
giant bowl of jello.
And it's gone get outta my office.
And, uh, so I got a lot of, some
of my friends are really successful in show business
and, uh, they go to a lot of groups for support.
We go to a lot of sport groups and, uh, groups for support.
And, uh,
Hi, my name is Linda. I am
Hi Linda.
I am a sex addict, alcoholic, codependent and clutter.
Um, I'm a codependent clutter, actually.
And, um, I'm no longer storing other people's watercraft.
Um, I'm literally not taking people's s**t anymore.
And, um, I was thinking, um, you know,
where my pain comes from.
And I started, I started, uh,
modeling when I was two months old,
and I went straight to the top.
And then somebody said, why don't you try acting?
And I said, fine. And,
and I was recently weightlift, uh, waitlisted
for an Academy Award
and let, let a lot of people know
about the weightlifting system.
But, um, I thought, you know,
I'm gonna do something this year that I have no talent
and no gift, no and no desire to do.
And I, so I started working with Clay
and started throwing pots.
And guess, guess who has a,
A Two year Guggenheim Fellowship and ceramics.
It's like everything, everything I touch
Turns to gold.
So I'm a I'm gonna make my own sitcom.
I don't need any help. I don't need, I don't need a,
you know, a a a network.
Uh, okay, or a, a script
or a, you know, a I got friends, right?
Uh, I don't, I everybody loves Maria,
or everybody hates Maria.
Whatever pop show is more popular right now.
Um, here, here's the premise.
Let's just say, uh, slightly built, uh, except
for a Sky Dancer.
Uh, I'm currently current calling this area
of my Body Sky Dancer 'cause she's so beautiful at night.
Oh, Oh, oh, good night, sky Dancer. Oh, oh, good night.
So, uh, uh, yeah, slightly built, 30 5-year-old comedian,
uh, suffer as a nervous breakdown on stage at the Detroit
Cavity castle, and is forced to move home with her parents.
Oh, let's just say that happened.
And, uh, I was doing my hilarious comedy jokes,
stories on stage at the Detroit Comedy Castle.
Uh, when the gentleman stood up in the front row
and said, I'm so f*****g bored.
I'm so sick of you and your voices.
Why don't you bring the other guy on?
I thought, I completely agree with your level
of frustration, sir, because this is the problem
with comedy clubs, because there is too vague
and they're advertising.
I said, we're gonna be having some comedy.
What kind of comedy? Well, it's gonna be comedy,
so it's gonna be hilarious.
Well, is it gonna be the kind of comedy that I like,
which is barrel trusted Polynesian men
who tell caustic one-liners,
Not necessarily Ladies drink free.
You know, I told the guy, I said, Hey, listen, buddy, uh,
I totally know I like a certain kind of comedy.
I only like phone-based prop work and political magic.
Uh, that's it.
And, uh, I go to some show, I have a couple drinks,
sit in the back, get angry, start, you know, some,
because it would be some guy, you know,
talking about his kids
or some lady making balloon and animals mama.
And I'd say, this isn't comedy. They'd be
like, get it off stage.
You suck. Tell us a joke.
And then I learned to read,
and now I sound it out.
I go, I look at the marquee and I'm like, who's up tonight?
Okay, Maria, hold it right there.
I don't like women and I don't speak Spanish.
I'm not gonna go see that show.
And, uh, so I, anyways, so, uh, I did the rest of my set,
uh, with tears coming slowly, uh, from my eyes,
which is really quite funny in retrospect.
And, uh, I, I went back to the hotel
and I did this weird thing.
I was trying to write jokes, but while I did it, I,
I heard this screaming,
and it turns out it was coming from me
and it wouldn't stop for 10 months.
And that was kind of weird. And, uh, so I just said,
I'm gonna take some time off, go back to Duluth, uh, to, uh,
which is, uh, near, uh, Canada,
where the kind of gentle people are.
And, um, take an undisclosed amount of time off.
Just take a break. And I was on my way home
and I was reading the Northwest Airlines in Flight Magazine,
where I get most of my spirituality.
And, uh, I read, uh, they did this study about happiness.
And they said, uh, the variables in an economic study, uh,
that make people happy are, uh, relationships, uh, ah,
modicum of food and shelter,
and then, uh, some sort of safety, you know,
and then, uh, that money property like stuff
and, uh, prestige or success have no effect on people's
level of happiness.
And I thought, oh my God, I have been totally
focusing on the wrong things.
I have gotten my priorities all screwed up.
I don't want to be happy.
Oh, I want to be rich, famous and miserable.
And, uh, so that, that's of course not true
because I, so what I was, uh, travel with my pug, uh,
blossom, uh, blasting as a pug,
come here bossy.
I bought blossom for, uh,
$30 from a disreputable breeder in Costa Mesa, California,
who told me she was 1-year-old.
And then I brought her to the vet.
The vet said she is eight years old, and she's a day,
and she spanks.
She has, uh, has three teeth, which is really all I need
to make cook work of a sausage.
And, uh, she, uh, has these,
I don't know if you can see in these long cow,
like s which is, you know, uh,
because she had lots of babies,
and, uh, we don't know where they are,
but she's open to them contacting her.
Uh, so bla
sometimes when we touch,
The Honesty is too much.
And I have to, okay. Alright.
Um, so when I go home to Duluth, I stay in my parents', uh,
guest bedroom, which is really a pillow museum storage unit.
And, uh, uh, my parents, I usually get home late.
So my parents are, uh, asleep. Mom, mom, Hey mom. Honey,
Where Your sleeping?
Your father has a sleep mask on, sweetie, your father?
I just, I just wanna tell you guys,
just don't wake me up early tomorrow morning, okay?
Because I, I've got in late, so don't, don't wake me up.
Hey, honey, we're not gonna wake
You up. It's
good to have you home.
It's good to have you home, sweetie.
Love you to pieces, love you to
Ow Okay?
Well, just don't wake me up, you guys,
Honey, we're not gonna wake you off.
Okay? That's, that's clearly blossom,
okay?
Okay. Sorry, that was me.
So I, I get gas,
rise and shine, and give God your glory.
Glory rise and shining. And kiddo, give God your glory.
Glory. Listen kiddo, I know you didn't wanna me
to wake you up, but it's noon and you Ms. Church.
And we're gonna go to Target to get a fun island.
And I just thought you might wanna come. Sweet.
Did you wanna die at Coke for breakfast? Hello, blossom.
Sweetie. You need to get the, the, the, the sheet
between your skin and the quilt because your skin has oils.
Honey. It has oils. Can I just get in there?
Can I just get in there? You don't have to get up.
You don't have to get up, mother.
I must wash the sludge of humanity from my skin.
Well, honey, honey, glass of listen, honey, sweetie,
are you gonna go take a shower?
Can I tell you something real quick there?
Can I get, can I get in there real quick?
Can I just, oh, I just,
I just, I didn't know you were naked.
You got undressed so quickly.
Honey, listen, listen
honey, if you want, if you wanna get breast
implants, we will support you.
You know, not, not, not financially, but, but emotionally.
Do not push your mother. Do not push your mother.
Listen, listen, that basket
of socks is in there for a reason.
Because you, when you're wet, feet come out of the bath,
they're wet, and then they, I know you can't see it,
you don't believe me, but there's a layer
of dust on the bathroom floor,
and then it hits the white carpeting
and it creates a grime, honey,
It creates a crime.
I said, hello, blossom. How are you to it?
I know I wouldn't, I would pet you, but I'm allergic.
I I have distended teeths too, honey.
Listen sweetie, maybe we should get her a T-shirt
or something so she could have some privacy.
Listen, I'm just worried
what you're gonna be doing this week
because I, I, I got a lot of things going on.
I've got man a pedicure on Tuesday,
and then Rita's coming to clean.
So I'm trying to keep things clean for when she comes
to clean, and I'm just exhausted, sweetie.
Listen, sweetie.
So what do you, sweetie?
You're gonna, you're gonna put on some makeup, right?
Put on a little makeup for your mother. Mom, I'm off work.
I don't have to put on the clown mask, sweetie.
Aren't you worried? You know, what if Mike's at the,
at the at target?
What if you see him, mom,
he's married and has three children.
I don't think he's gonna ask me to the prom.
See, when you don't wear makeup, you look mentally ill
Mother, you,
You don't want, you call yourself a Christian.
And yet Jesus Christmas would say, I look.
He would say, I look hot.
You know, he would say, I look Really, really?
Jesus doesn't know anyone at Target, honey.
No, listen, so whatcha gonna be doing with yourself
because I just wanted, I can't entertain you, mom.
I've got tons of stuff.
I just, I saw, uh, I saw a friend from high school,
Amy Averson at the airport.
So we maybe we're gonna maybe hang out, right?
We're gonna, oh
My God, up for jury.
Remember? Do you remember me, Amy,
From high school?
Do you remember me?
Yes, I remember you. Oh, my.
Yes, I remember you. You're so funny.
So anyways, are you coming?
Your mom, since you're living in Hollywood,
what are you kind of, are you having a nervous breakdown?
Is that, that's what always happens on eat true Hollywood.
Hollywood. Eat your story.
You always have like some nervous
breakdown and they come home.
Are you having a nervous breakout?
Yes. So I saw her
Rob at Jubilee Foods.
She's so funny. She says, she says Maria's depressed.
She's on Prozac. Which is so funny because I cut myself.
So I'm on Effexor and antipsychotics. Brian.
Brian, get over here.
I remember Bri, we had IES a couple years ago,
and neither of us had any health insurance.
And then, but we were, you know, so we didn't cooperate.
It was a soft cough case.
We got hundred thousands of dollars in debt.
And I was just so stressed out. Brian didn't had a job.
And then we just, we had ies,
premature babies, little girls.
And so I would just cut myself just to relax. Just to relax.
And now I just wanna watch.
I watched my tbo episodes
of Survivor Pal out, and I just cry.
So remember that one time in high school?
Do you Remember? Yes.
Oh my God, right? So Ran,
she says we were playing volleyball.
And Marie goes, we were playing,
and this volleyball hits her in the head
and she act like she's acting like no big deal.
Volleyball just hit me in the head. No big deal.
Like you, like it didn't hurt her.
And then another one hit you in the head,
and then another one,
and it's like your head was attracting volleyball.
And I says, oh my God,
I'm in here, her in the head on purpose.
This is the look on your face.
And then I Did you remember what you said to me?
Do you remember he said, you said Amy said
Go to hell. Which is
So funny. I'm
a Christian, I gotta get out here.
I work at pro staff, temp people, staff pro people,
training staff, pro and downtown.
And so you gotta come, I gotta get outta here
before I fall over laughing.
So mom, I have plenty.
I have places to go, people to see, things to do.
I'm very busy, very, very busy.
Honey, why would you please put, you know,
just a little concealer on your upper lip
because you have a darkening.
It's called a melasma,
and it's caused by having too much estrogen
pigment in your skin.
It c creates a pistachio effect.
Just, I'm gonna go get your father. Joel.
Joel. Oh my God. Just got out.
She's everywhere. Joel,
Jesus Christ.
I'm right here. I've been here for 40 years.
Where almost am I gonna go? What?
Oh, there it goes. That dog.
Okay, I got her. Okay,
You got,
Okay, Now I wanna wanna go for a ride, huh?
Blessy down by the river. Your poppy. Yeah.
Motorcycle ride with a bag
and some rocks, Joe.
Oh my God. Oh, you scared me. You scared me.
Oh, I didn't know. I
listen Honey Maria,
I was watching Maria upstairs take a shower,
and she was, has this mole on her butt,
and it just looks odd.
And I just think as a dermatologist in the family,
you should take a look at it.
Jesus Christ. Marilyn,
I'm not gonna take a look at my daughter's, you know?
Yes. She, she has, she has healthcare.
She, she can get a, you know, a referral.
Um, besides, I don't think a,
a melanoma would be the first thing you would
notice about her.
My goodness. Looking very, very good. Maria. What?
Oh s**t, Maria. What mother?
I'm wearing makeup.
I'm wearing thick green eyeshadow
and a line of lipstick around my lips.
Maybe look pretty now. Mommy,
Mary.
Okay, sweetie. What? It's just too much.
Why don't you stay at your sisters, honey?
Is your sisters okay? We love you. We love you. We love you.
We love you. But it's hard to be around you.
So I'm gonna go downstairs. I'll see you at Target, honey.
Very funny.
I see my new invention.
Yeah, dad, totally. Okay.
You know, patients come into me,
you know, I'm a dermatologist.
Patients come into me and say, oh, Dr.
Banford, I have a, you know, rash on my arm.
Okay? And, uh, you know,
and, uh, you know, I say, well put a topical cream on it,
you know, you know.
And, uh, if you, if you need to wash it, don't use soap.
Don't use soap. Soap is drying irritating to the skin.
You need to wash it. Pat, pat, pat. Wet wash cloth.
Hair dry. Hair dry.
You know, one of people always say to me,
they say, oh, but Dr. Bradford isn't there some kind
of special, so I can
use little soap.
Soap, soap is drying irritating to the skin.
You need soap with wet,
and then it never stop.
You go, oh, salt, salt.
So I went on in my wood shop
and I came up with this, okay, it's a bar of wood, okay?
Shaped like a bar of soup.
And, and I, uh, I say, oh, why don't you try this?
And then they say, oh, Dr. Bamford, I'd say, bar of wood.
Won't I get splinters?
I say, oh yeah, better not use it.
Pretty good, huh? Wait, what?
That, that is the most long-winded, passive aggressive way
of getting someone to do something.
And I like it.
Uh, what is your agency?
I want you No, you don't much time off what?
Your agency. I didn't, she doesn't care.
Last time I saw her, she said,
Maria, when I first met you, I was concerned.
I was gonna be annoyed by you
because you have a high grading childlike voice.
You, you need to know that about yourself.
I don't, I don't think she'll be missing me too much. Mom.
You see one down taking your meds.
Yes, I'm taking my meds. Are you taking your meds?
I got about seven going right now. Yeah. I got a zero tech
Acid reflux.
Uh, you know, and then I got a, uh,
taking Prozac for the darkness.
And then I got, uh, I got this, this is new
after the prize to eat surgery.
I got, uh, it is just, you know, temporary.
But it's a, it's a little pee bag and don't tell blossom.
But I've been marking s**t around the house.
It is just the stuff that's mine.
And, uh, you know, so, and then I got this new medication.
Get this. It's a heart medication.
If I don't take it for one day,
It's Ra.
Can you believe it? Oh, I just, you know,
got caught up in something.
Goodbye. Well, I just don't know.
Just got busy and then I forgot o
Dad.
Uh, did you, did you take that medication today? What?
Oh s**t. So I
usually end up at my sister's house.
Uh, my sister, uh, come on glossy.
Uh, my sister is a pathologist though.
I like to introduce her as, this is my sister Sarah.
She cuts up the dead into chunks and, uh,
'cause she's my older sister.
And, uh, she, uh, she has a pug too. Hey, buttercup.
Buttercup blossom. Buttercup blossom.
Uh, so ramp, do you get kicked outta the house? Uhhuh.
Uhhuh? Do you want a diet Coke? Should we bring out three?
Do you want three Diet Cokes? Do you want five?
We can bring 'em. I mean, it's no problem. They're cool.
Okay. They're chill. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, you're ready. Okay. Hey, mark, mark,
Mark, mark, mark, mark, Mark, mark.
Mark. Mark, mark. Okay, I am leaving for Target with Maria.
I told you, I told you. Okay. I forgot. I did not tell you.
I am sorry. Dr. Phil. I'm sorry, Dr. Phil.
Well, you're gonna have to wrap
that white light and let it go, Oprah.
Okay? Listen, listen.
Location of your children, one outside, other is
underneath the dining room
table playing with their Polly pockets.
One is aimlessly wandering with a spatula,
and the other one is taking up a nap.
20 minutes and counting. Okay?
Put down the book, Lord of the Rings and
Watch your children, Okay? Okay. Alright.
I Love you too, lady.
Liberty is on the move. Okay?
So we got two dot cos Hey, Maria. Maria. Maria, Maria.
Listen. Would you open the door? Open the door.
Oh, oh, oh, oh. It's already open. Okay. Sorry.
Sorry, sorry. Okay, so, um, so, um, so, uh,
mom said you had a new joke about me.
What's your joke? What's your joke?
It's not even a joke about you,
it's just a generic sister joke.
Mm-Hmm. Take a left. Hey, what's your joke? Joker.
Okay. It's about, it's a, it's okay. It goes like this.
Uh, my sister and I had the same voice, so, uh,
over the holidays though, so it's hard for me
to do impersonation of her, but she can take a left.
Take a left. Take a left up here. Okay. You did it.
You did it. You're doing it. You're doing it. Okay, great.
Do you wanna hear? Do you wanna hear this or not? No, no.
I'm listening. I listening. You're doing what I'm saying.
You're doing what I'm saying. It's cool. Okay.
My sister, we have the same voice,
but she came up with an impersonation
of me over the holidays, and it goes like this.
My name is Maria, and I think I'm a big deal,
so I don't have to do the dishes or
We up before noon And blah, blah, blah.
Jib, jib, jib, Clang, clang, cl.
And then I say it's a pretty good likeness.
Maria, Bri, Aaron noticed every joke you
tell, you're the victim.
And yet, and yet every,
every joke you tell you do an impersonation of someone else.
Okay? Or someone from our family.
Who's the victim now, buddy?
Huh? Who's the victim now?
Hey, Maria, you remember how, uh, you know,
I was reading this medical journal, I forgot to tell you.
Okay? You have, you have
that one dark curly hair that comes outta your neck.
You've seen it, right? That one dark,
curly, creepy, disgusting hair.
You've seen it. I'm just
Trying to help you.
Okay? And then your breasts will look really small, dude.
It's called cs. It's a syndrome.
You gotta get your hormones checked other way.
You're gonna be like, I'm like, wake up next day
and be like, covered in fur, like a werewolf.
Shut Up, Sarah. Oh, you shut up
Fast. Watch
Yet,
Sarah, maybe I tell a joke from being a victim because I,
because I am a victim, you know?
Mm-Hmm. Listen, we all have genetic defects.
Look at me, at me.
I got giant horse teeth.
You don't see me crying.
Why don't you go to one of your groups,
One of your groups for support?
Support.
You are just jealous. 'cause there's no support groups
for bossy people with horse teeth.
I'm going to my groups totally helping.
I, I just, I've been, you know, people call me
and, you know, we support each other or whatever.
And, uh, I just got a call it, eh,
It's Linda.
Oh my God. What's going on? Are you okay? Are you okay?
Okay. Uh, I'm at the Tate Gallery in London.
Um, they're, they're doing a retrospective on my
ashtrays and toothbrush holders.
Um, okay.
Um, you know,
a apple sauce?
Yeah. Like what is in a six,
six compartments.
And Then it has aluminum foil over the top,
and then it's
Like, like a picnic pack, like a, like a snack pack.
Oh my God. It is so great to talk to someone
who knows what I'm talking about.
It's like, you know, sometimes I just think,
you know, where am I going?
You know, what am I doing? You know?
And am I always going be like this? You know? And
Me too. I mean, I don't
know. I don't know what's going on.
I don't, I mean, I don't have any plan. You know? It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Yeah. And then, you know, sometimes you have that,
you know, when you, like, you, you realize,
you know, everything's okay.
You know, like, like I was walking past Barney's last week
and I said, okay, if it's meant to be, and I went inside
and that cashmere tube top was, was 25% off.
And it's like, okay, I, I get it. You know, there, there is
A God, there is a plan.
I'm on A path. Yeah.
I mean, that's, that's, that's, yeah.
That's, that's what it's about. I guess. You know,
Can I, you know, my, my publicist is on the other line.
Can, can I put you on hold for 45 minutes?
Why don't, why don't you just call me back?
I'd really rather put you on hold for 45 minutes.
Well, I don't think my, my cell phone will last that long.
Okay? If I feel angry and disappointed,
but I will call you back after my water karate class.
So, Sarah, I'm, you know, spiritually centered, you know,
I have some philosophy with which to guide me.
And you're in this ruling retail vortex of target
beneath the, you know, fluorescent lights and,
and you don't have anything, you know, pushing forward,
you know, pushing you forward from it.
Uhhuh Maria, where's your cart?
I'm not, I'm not getting anything. I don't need a cart.
Dude, if you get a cart, mom won't buy you s**t. Get a cart.
Sarah. Maria. So Maria,
where's your cart, mom?
I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna get anything.
Maria, don't be a martyr. Get a cart.
So listen, kiddo, Sarah, why don't you go fill up,
fill up the whole cart with giant Coke.
You know what? Why don't you add two carts
and make a wagon train and just fill it.
Just fill it. Listen sweetie,
you see, look at this.
This is darling. Look at this.
It's a pair of coots with a matching stationary set.
Maria, look at that. You're getting it. You're getting it.
So listen, sweetie, you see him down?
You seem, you seem depressed. This is fun. Look at this.
It's like a picture frame, but it spins.
So you see the picture and you see it over.
Did you see that? Honey,
sweetie, you're getting it.
Listen, can I just please,
so listen, look at this.
Oh, okay,
okay. You know,
It's like I Told you.
Look at these baby babies, sweetie. They're on sale.
They're mom. Those were probably made
by like a 5-year-old in Guatemala.
Well, they certainly weren't supervised
'cause they are not made that well, I mean,
these kids are not working that hard, huh?
Okay. What you do is you get six penguins
and six kangaroos.
Next time you go to Australia, you got gifts to bring back.
You think ahead, honey, let's get six of each. Think ahead.
Think ahead. So Liz, I told you, you know, if you wanted
to be in show business, you're gonna have
to prepare yourself for a life of rejection.
And if you do finally make it via the casting couch,
or lady luck, soon enough, your beauty will fade away.
And with it, your false friends leaving only the glow
of stardust memories to keep you warm as you
lay in the gutter or the boulevard of dreams.
But you are a star, honey, you're a star.
We walk down these aisles and people say, who's that?
Who, who's that? Uh, that's because you're yelling at me.
Mother, sweetie. Mom, mom, mom. Yes.
Sarah, mom. Am I a star too? Am I a star?
Yes, of course you are a star, sir.
You are a different kind of star though.
You are a pathology star.
People look at you and they think science.
So listen, I'm gonna break into a run here
and get a fun island,
but I'll meet you at the checkout register in town.
Okay? Hey, Maria.
Maria, what do, do you think I'm,
you know, like, do you think I could be on tv?
Do you think I I I could be on tv.
Yeah, anybody can be on tv. Okay. Okay.
So here's my idea for a show. Okay?
It's like, it's like a cooking show where you have like,
you know, you can see what they're doing, right?
With the mirrors and stuff. And,
but then it's like autopsies
and it's like celebrity auto autopsy.
So you have like Charlton Heston movie,
and then you take a clip and then you go
and here's his liver,
Right?
That's, that's an incredible idea, Sarah.
That's really, that's really, okay, so, right.
Okay, so here's another one coming at you.
So, um, I'm doing like, it's like a diet plan that,
you know, people go crazy for.
It's like, you can have whatever you want,
whatever you want, but it has to be out
of dollhouse furniture.
So like, you can have like,
you can have like a hot fudge sundae,
but it has to be out of like a dollhouse tub.
So, right. So like, you can have like a,
like you can have like a sirloin steak, right?
But it's gotta be a dollhouse sized steak. Get it?
That's, that's, that's a great, okay,
here's my, this is the awesome idea.
So me and my friend Suzy, we okay, we,
it's like a home makeover.
Shush. We come to your house, right?
We come to your house and um,
we just tell you everything's wrong with your life, right?
Everything that's wrong, we just go, this sucks.
And you need a new haircut. And like, just all that stuff.
We just say everything's wrong.
Um, like with your kids and like your looks stuff, it's,
and then we just leave them there
and we don't tell 'em or help 'em how to fix it.
That's a really good idea. That's, that's, that's good.
Hey Sue, how dad's doing? Okay, right?
He, uh, he's doing okay, right?
'cause uh, I mean he just, the prostate surgery,
so he seems really good.
I don't know, maybe he's got two ears or something.
What? I dunno.
No, this is why we can't talk about this s**t with you, is
because you can't handle it.
You freak out. Well, so his dad, I mean his dad,
he's gonna die or something.
No, I'm just saying, any of us could die at any moment.
Like right now, I could have an aneurysm. Oh. Oh, I'm gone.
See what I'm saying? Like, you, you drink so much diet Coke,
you could have like a calcified tumor growing diet coke like
in your shoulder or something.
I don't know. We're all gonna die, Maria.
We're all gonna die. But dad's, but dad's fine, right?
Yeah, he's stole.
He's probably gonna last forever, like,
you know, 50 more years.
But I'm just saying we will die.
I know that. Okay.
Hey, do you remember Christie C***s from high school?
You mean my, my arch enemy?
Uhhuh Mom's checking out with her at the register right now,
and you are gonna die.
Hello? Christie. C***s. Wow. What a surprise.
No, you were in Maria's class, right? Okay. Okay.
Marilyn Banford. Listen, listen.
So I love what you've done with your hair,
with the bla the dark root
and then the, the the perm and then the blonde.
That's fun. That is fun. Listen, are you singing?
Are you singing now? Are you,
because you were such, such a lovely voice.
No, no, no, you're not. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. That's hard.
That's hard. That's hard. Well, listen.
Uh, Sarah of course, is my older daughter
and she is a doctor and her husband's a doctor
and they have four beautiful children
and they live on the east side of town.
And they're just, you know, going gangbusters.
And then Maria is who's hiding behind the Shrek two DVDs.
Maria, she is a comedian
and she has been on Conan O'Brien in 1997,
which, you know, she was only on there twice.
And then they said never again.
I mean, they didn't say that, but that's how she felt.
You know? And it's like she just keeps putting herself out
there and you just keep trying.
Listen, I am in a real hurry here
'cause we gotta go to the Blackberry Indian Casino.
We got reservations out there.
So I'm just gonna slide my card
and the other, the girls can sign for it.
But good to see you, Christy. Good to see you.
Good to see you. Hey, Christy.
Yeah, I got four carts, about 20 a piece. Uh, diet Coke.
Hey, uh, listen, I gotta go because I got four kids
and you know how it is, but, uh, good to see you. Oh
My God, You're gonna die.
Uh, hey Christie. Hey, how, how, how?
Congratulations. I was, I mean,
this is like 15 years too late now,
but, uh, uh, uh, you got married, uh, to Todd.
So, uh, anyways, ations and stuff.
And, uh, we got divorced.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
I mean, or you know, I mean, whatever is is appropriate,
you know, or what, uh, uh, I'm so, um,
uh, so he brought over your video, Todd
to watch the kids or something?
I don't know what it was, but, oh my God, that's so nice.
Oh, oh wow. It is just like in high school.
It's like, you are not funny. You're just weird.
Well, you know, comedy is subjective, you know, it's, it's,
it's, it's an art form, you know?
So, uh, so are you gay?
'cause I hear like a lot of women comedians are gay.
No, no, no, I'm not.
I mean, it'd be okay if I was, uh, not okay.
If I, if I was, uh, that's great.
'cause I remember, um, remember we, I all went
to Christian Bible camp and you went, um,
we all went skinny dipping,
and you went take your shirt off.
And I'm like, oh my God, you got nothing to show anyway.
And then you, you took your shirt off
and me all gave you t***y, twisters.
I was like, oh my God, if you're a lesbian,
you'd have been all turned on by that.
And I just got all grossed out.
Press D or credit.
Well that, that's a, that's a horrible memory. My gosh.
It's like, you think you're such a big deal,
but people, you know, people make fun of you.
Like Patterson is that he is a, he is a bar.
Like, um, I don't know if I can do,
if he doesn't impersonation me.
It's so funny. He goes, uh,
he goes, I don't know how you can do it.
He goes, hi Maria or something.
And then, um, Mike should ski.
He goes, he's so funny.
He goes, he said, he said, I wouldn't have f****d
that freaking high school and I wouldn't f**k her.
Now,
uh, Christy, why don't,
why don't you go suck it?
Why don't you go suck it?
F**k you, f**k you too.
Do you need any help out the car with your bags?
So, uh, this, this is the point
where you start to think to yourself, Hey, maybe, you know,
maybe, maybe, you know, when you try to think, oh, well,
things that, you know, almost change inside yourself
and you feel better about yourself.
Or maybe, you know, maybe you should, you know,
maybe you don't need anybody you know, you don't need,
or you know, you don't even need, you know,
'cause I, you know, you're just kind
of freaking out or whatever.
You just feel kind of like, you kind of, you know, like,
okay, this isn't good.
And uh, and then, and then,
and then Dustin Hoffman is Rainman.
Dustin Hoffman. Rainman. Hey, we got a table.
We got a table at the Black Bear.
Do you wanna come in and sit down?
I don't know what you're doing. You're talking to yourself.
Okay, great. Um, we're ready to order. Yeah.
Um, I, hi.
I'm gonna be ordering for the four kids and my husband.
Okay. Just over here.
I don't know what these other people want. Okay.
Um, so we're gonna have the cheese pizza
and then, um, orange juice
and um, yeah, that's what you're getting.
And then, um, my husband wants the surf and turf.
Well, that's what you said you wanted.
Well, I dunno what you want.
No Remus, He'll
have the surfing turf.
Oh my God. And then I'll have the Cobb salad
and a Diet Coke order, diet Pepsi, whatever you have.
And, um, I don't know what this guy wants.
Um, he's gonna have to tell himself. Dad. Yeah.
Uh, I like to have the, uh, uh, what is your name?
Young waitress. I'm sorry I didn't get your name.
Tina, nice to meet you Tina. Go bad.
Uh, so I've been looking at your menu here
and, uh, uh, got a, you know, very nice pictures
and, uh, couple.
Let see. I think I'd like to have a, uh, you know, hoo.
And uh,
thank you very much, Nina.
Thank you very much. Oh,
I'm sorry they didn't hear me.
Enunciate hellan color.
Nobody knows what you're talking about. Dad. Enunciate who?
Sorry. Oh geez. Uh, uh, oh, my dad.
The cheeseburger cheese burger.
Uh, hash browns my pants brown.
I don't know if you, you know that you need that
as a reference cup of coffee.
I can get it over there. I've seen it over there, so,
you know, a short little walk away.
I can get it myself. Hey, you Tina.
People don't listen. Hi,
I'm Marilyn Bamford.
And listen, let's just start out with
two pictures of Diet Coke.
And listen, Tina, oh God.
I hate to shoot the messenger,
but Diet Pepsi is not okay.
No, it is not. And I know you aren't making these decisions.
It's the big wigs upstairs. Am I right? Yeah.
And it's like they just, you know,
there is a big difference.
And I'm just trying to protest here at the grassroots level
and kind of shift the paradigm, you know, person by person.
But Dye Pepsi's fine. That's fine.
And, uh, I am on a combination of the South Beach
and Weight Watchers and
so I have six points left and a fruit.
And uh, so what, what can I do? What can I do here?
What can I do about a French fry or a curly fry?
Listen, I, a curly,
I think a curly has more fiber, don't you Tina?
Yeah. Yeah, let's go with that.
And then I need to have the fruit.
And that needs to be a fresh, a Raman. A Raman.
Isn't that what you use in the industry? Raman?
A fresh raspberries. Okay. And uh, you don't have that.
What would you have That would be the equivalent?
Strawberry pie. Strawberry pie. That's fine. That's fine.
Listen, this is my daughter Maria,
if you didn't recognize her already.
'cause she has been on the late, late,
late late show, honey.
Which, what is it? Is it the Late late show
or is it the late, late late show?
Or is it, or is it the late? Just the late?
No, no, it's the late, late mother. It, it's okay.
I don't, I don't think she needs to know.
She doesn't need to know how poorly my career is going.
Um, I I I like to have the Chicken Caesar salad
and a Diet Pepsi and thank you so much.
You know, thank you so much for, for helping my family.
Thank, thank you. Thank, thank you.
Hey, you guys, um, I have a, a announcement to make.
Oh, you're not just gonna have to wait
because I have an awesome story.
So, um, I'm doing this autopsy, right?
That's not even the story.
So Steve comes in from down the hall,
he is doing like laser surgery, right?
Like burning flesh. Burning flesh, right?
And it's right lunchtime.
And it's like, he comes in, he is like, oh my God, I had
to get outta there 'cause I'm so hungry.
And it smells like a barbecue Because
we're just meat.
You guys
just meat.
I probably taste pretty good. I have a high fat content.
Maria wouldn't taste pretty good. She tastes like
diet Coke jerky.
Okay, tell your story, Maria. Try and top that.
Okay? Uh, it's not, it's just an announcement.
Um, I just, I've been thinking about it
and, you know, I wanted to, you know, do a sitcom
or whatever and do, you know, show business stuff.
And I realized, you know, that I don't,
I just wanna live in a sitcom, you know, where you have,
you know, experiences with people you love and,
and they're funny or, or not funny.
And then, uh, you don't have to act them out.
And, uh, so anyways, I'm moving home.
I'm gonna move home, home to Duluth.
So I just wanted to, uh, let you do. So I'm excited.
And, uh, and so, okay,
Marie, do you think you're gonna be avoiding, uh, pain
and rejection by moving to Duluth?
You got another thing coming? All right, mark. Am I right?
Okay. I was crabby for about two years, okay?
And, um, because I had Josephine
and, um, I had, you know how they say you get after kiss?
Okay? And they say they're like this small nudes,
the size of apples,
The size of apples.
And the only way to get rid
of those things is you gotta time off
with a rubber band until they burst.
Okay? And not like a medical rubber band, just a regular
Rubber band.
So don't tell me about pain and humiliation. Okay?
Me, you Know, it's right.
You know, it's tough all over. You know, my job, I, uh,
You know, I got written up at my job
as patient came in, you know,
and they wrote a letter complaining, you know, they said,
uh, I think Dr. Manford
A you know, I think Dr.
Ba,
I know what she said. You know, she
said, uh, I, I think Dr.
Manford said a little,
Okay, Okay.
Crazy
Marie, Sweetie.
Oh God, you can't move home, honey.
You, you are not welcome at home.
And I say this because you, I wasn't gonna tell you this,
but we were having a prayer vigil.
Uh, Benny Silver Dean was, uh, dying of breast cancer.
And we had a, a prayer vigil around it,
and we kind of, we were there for a couple hours.
We kind of ran outta things to pray for.
And, uh, I says, I says, let's pray that Maria
gets it a sitcom and a husband.
And I just think, I know you don't believe in him,
but Jesus wants you to have, you know,
a MySpace page and a, and, and, and, and merch.
And he wants you to.
He just how you can't move home, mom, don't wor don't worry.
It's you guys. It's, it's a, I'm act. I'm act.
I mean, it's just, I'm not actually moving home.
It's just a, it's just a show.
So there's, there's people here.
It's, it's just a, it is just a show. It's just a show.
Oh my God. Oh, that's funny. Okay, I get it.
I get it. I get it. I get it. Funny, funny, funny, funny.
Okay. Maria exaggerates so much of this is not true.
It's true on an emotional level,
perhaps, but in no way.
It's more of a are we gonna be on tv?
Does is this mean we're gonna be on tv?
Well, no, it's just, it's kind of in my head right now,
now just doing it in theater, right?
That's, that's pretty good, right?
Maybe if you put my, your hands like this,
it'd be kind of like I'm on tv.
Like, yeah, you should, you should put it, you should put,
it's just, oh s**t about me dying.
No death. See, that's the thing in the show is
that no one ever dies.
Oh, okay. Yeah. I wanna be in every episode.
Maria, this amazing show. It's brilliant. You're fantastic.
This is amazing. This is a breakthrough.
And we need to recast you.
You can't, you can't recast Maria.
I, I don't wanna be in your show, so don't put me in it.
I don't want you to be in my show.
So why don't you go to hell in a hand basket?
Why don't you go suck it? Why don't you f**k off?
Girls, girls, girls, girls, girls.
Listen honey, the reason,
and Christie is so hostile is
because she wants, she just, she's just jealous, honey.
And she, why, why don't you give her a part in the show,
honey, why don't you give Christie a part in
your sitcom, mom?
It's just basically in my, oh my God, Maria,
am I gonna be on job?
This is so funny. I get that.
Okay, you're gonna be in, put little parts of the show.
Just little parts. Not, not the whole, okay. Okay.
I Little parts, I'll just be a little parts,
little parts of your show.
So Maria, I wanna introduce you to somebody.
I wanna introduce you. My God, Maria, I'm so sorry.
Um, they, I didn't wanna act anymore
and um, I didn't even audition for the sitcom in your head,
but I, I got the part.
You guys can't, okay, I'm gonna do my own sitcom, okay?
This is just gonna be, this new sitcom
is just be me and a monster.
And, uh, we end up having to live together.
'cause the monster is like a, he's like,
he's like unemployed and then I'm like a dancer or something
and we have to live together
and the monsters like starts, you know, I'm like,
I can't live with a monster.
He's 7,000 pounds and he is all scaly and slimy
and he has put half his hind feet in the backyard
and his front feet upstairs and there's no place to sit.
Monster is nowhere to go.
Nowhere to go for Monster.
And he says, borrow my clothes and stuff.
He's like, I'm like, you can't wear my Capri pants pretty
Bad,
Honey. That needs
a lot of work.
And it, it, it also, you need
to have some kind of love interest.
Mom. I am try. I am dating. I am out there.
I am available. Well, I mean, just somebody Mom,
you guys, why don't you get your own dang sitcom.
Thanks.
Alright.
Uh, and please welcome to the stage, uh, as I, we,
we read the credits, uh, of the show.
Uh, this is going to be the, uh, redo
or, uh, uh, the, the, the, uh, we're, uh, bringing back.
Um, my good friend Christy Coombs from high school,
and she's going to, uh, read out to her 1988, uh,
high school production role of eight Oh, Annie in, uh,
Oklahoma as I read over the credits.
So Christie, uh, take it away,
Annie, so much, uh, question.
I'm not knowing what to do.
I know what's written wrong since I've been 10.
I hear a lot of stories
and I reckon are true about
how girls are put upon by men.
I know I must have fallen into the pet,
but when I am with, uh, Fowler, I forget.
Um, thank you so much to everyone
who helped in this production dance, just especially
and, uh, everybody on the crew
and the amazing, uh, varsity theater and Dickie talent
and everybody who came in Minneapolis and,
Uh, all my directors in the past, uh, ju Shelton, uh, uh,
Adam Blackford, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, Nelly Thomas.
And, uh,
Are you like, are you gonna keep talking?
That's it. That's it.
I'm just a girl.
I can't say no, I'm in a terrible fact.
I always say, come on, let's go. Just win.
I gotta seat next. Shut up.
I, uh, the girls, I mean,
girls are so co and sweet,
but other girls ain't having any fun.
Every time I lose a RA match,
I have a money feeling that I want.
I'm gonna suffer. Lights are low.
I can't be pri and queen. That is
No,
Uh, this is the Duluth AEL lift bridge used to be able
to go up with the wi with, with the bridge,
but now you can't because then one year somebody jumped off
and they got caught up in all the P pulleys and the weights
and they got sliced right in half, right in half.
Which is, I mean, that's, that's a good way
to go really.
But it might have inspired copycat.
Um,
that's, that's about it.
A cash
I run.