[Applause]
hey thanks for watching my DVD uh this
is a one person sitcom of me moving back
to duth Minnesota and so uh thanks for
watching and uh the bridge is going up
so it's time to start the
[Music]
show
[Applause]
w
that's super nice he yes um listen so
here I'm gonna if some of you guys seem
came to see standup uh might be a bit
disappointing because this is a one
person shoe and uh uh then uh but that
the thing is the cool thing about that
is that it the theme of the show is
disappointment and that uh sometimes
life doesn't almost turn out as you
planned but something magnificent and
incredible and magical that you never
could have dreamed of happens
instead or
not so uh like all of us here tonight uh
I always believed I deserve to have my
own sitcom and uh I've been to Hollywood
I've auditioned uh Maria uh so read
through the part and just be yourself
that's really my only know we just want
to see who you are so be yourself have
fun with
it any questions no okay go
ahead uh and then I read the part I be
myself and I say okay um I know I told
you to be yourself um but we really need
the character to be
likable and uh oh got the wrong person
uh so went uh uh have an agent and she's
real positive Maria this IND has addd
right now I'm looking at you and you're
amazing and you're brilliant and you're
you're superb and you're everything that
we're looking for and then suddenly it's
gone and I'm born I'm irritated I want
to get a cup of coffee or something to
eat and then I don't know what it is you
did it didn't do but I am back in again
and you are superlative and you are
hyperb and you are a polar bear in the
jungle and you're a giant within a giant
eting a giant bowl of Jello-O and it's
gone get out of my
office and uh so I got a lot of some of
my friends are really successful in Show
Business
and uh they go to a lot of groups for
support we go to a lot of support groups
and uh groups for support and
uh hi my name is Linda I am hi Linda I
am a sex addict alcoholic codependent
and clutterer um I'm a codependent
clutterer actually and um I'm no longer
storing other people's
watercraft um I'm literally not taking
people's [ __ ] anymore and
um I was thinking um you know where my
pain comes from and I started I started
uh modeling when I was two months old
and I went straight to the top and then
somebody said well I don't you try
acting and I said fine and and I was
recently weight lift uh weight listed
for an Academy Award and not not a lot
of people know about the weight listing
system but um I thought you know I'm
going to do something this year that I
have no talent in no gift no no desire
to do and I started working with clay
and started throwing pots
and guess guess who has it uh to your
Guggenheim fellowship and Ceramics it's
like everything everything I touch turns
to
Gold so I'm a I'm going to make my own
sitcom I don't need any help I don't
need I don't need a you know uh uh
network uh okay or a a script or uh you
know uh I got friends right uh I I
everybody loves Maria or everybody hates
Maria or whatever pop show is more
popular right now um here here's the
premise let's just say uh slightly built
uh except for a Sky Dancer uh I'm
currently calling this area my body Sky
Dancer cuz she's so beautiful at
night oh oh oh good night sky dancer oh
oh good
[Laughter]
night so uh uh yeah slightly built
35-year-old comedian uh suffers a
nervous breakdown on stage at the
Detroit Cav castle and is forced to move
home with her parents oh let's just say
that happened and uh I was doing my
hilarious comedy joke stories on stage
of the Detroit Comedy Castle and when
the gentleman stood up in the front row
and said I'm so [ __ ]
bored I'm so sick of you and your voices
why didn't you bring the other guy
on I thought I completely agree with
your level of frustration sir because
this is the problem with comedy clubs
cuz they just too vague in their
advertising they said we're going to be
having some comedy what kind of Comedy
well it's going to be comedy so it's
going to be hilarious well it going to
be the kind of Comedy that I like which
is Barrel chested Polynesian men who
tell costic one liners not
necessarily
ladies drink free you know I told the
guy I said Hey listen buddy uh I totally
know where I like a certain kind of
ComEd I only like Pham based prop work
and political magic uh that's it and uh
I go to some show I have a couple drinks
sit in the back get angry start you know
some because it would be some guy you
know talking about his kids or some lady
making balloon animals M I say this
isn't comedy be like get off Sage you
suck tell us a joke and then I learned
to read
and now I sound it out I go look at the
Marquee and I'm like who's up tonight
okay
Mar hold it right there I don't like
women and I don't speak Spanish I'm not
going to go see that show and uh so
anyways so uh I did the rest of my Set
uh with tears coming slowly uh from my
eyes which is really quite funny in
retrospect and uh I I went back back to
the hotel and I did this weird thing I
was trying to write jokes but while I
did it I I heard this screaming and it
turns out it was coming from me and it
wouldn't stop for 10 minutes that was
kind of weird and uh so I decided I'm
going to take some time off go back to
duth uh to uh which is near uh Canada
where the kind of gentle people are and
um take an undisclosed amount of time
off just take a break and I was on my
way home and I was reading the Northwest
Airlines inflight magazine where I get
most of my spirituality and uh I read uh
they did this study about happiness and
they said uh the variables in an
economic study uh that make people happy
are uh
relationships uh a mod come of food and
shelter and then uh some sort of safety
you know and then uh that money property
like stuff and uh Prestige or success
have no effect on people's level of
happiness and I thought oh my God I have
been totally focusing on the wrong
things I have gotten my priorities is
all screwed up I don't want to be
happy oh I want to be rich famous and
[Laughter]
miserable and uh so that that's of
course not true because I so what happy
I was uh travel with my pug uh Blossom
uh Blossom some
pug
come here blessy I bought Blossom for uh
$30 from a disreputable breeder in
coasta Mesa California who told me she
was one-year-old and then I brought her
to the vet the vet said she's 8 years
old if she's a day and she
stinks blossy she is a has three teeth
which is really all I need to make quick
work of a sausage and and uh she uh has
these I don't know if you can see these
long cowlik utters which is you know uh
because she had lots of babies and uh we
don't know where they are but she's open
to them contacting her uh so I'm
blossy Sometimes When We Touch the
honesty is too
much
and I have to okay all right um so when
I go home to duth I stay in my parents
uh guest bedroom which is really a
pillow Museum storage unit and uh U my
parents I usually get home late so my
parents are uh sleep Mom M hey Mom honey
where we're sleeping your father has a
sleep Mas gone sweetie your
[Music]
father
I just I just want to tell you guys just
don't wake me up early tomorrow morning
okay cuz I I've got in late so don't
don't wake me up honey honey we're not
going to wake you up it's good to have
you home it's good to have you home
sweetie I love you to pieces
I okay well just wake me up you
guys honey we're not going to wake you
up
okay that's that's clearly
Blossom okay okay sorry that was
me I I get
gas
rise and shine and give God Your Glory
Glory rise and shine and K give God Your
Glory Glory listen kid I know you didn't
want me to wake you up but it's noon and
you miss church and we're going to go to
Target to get a fun Island and I just
thought you might want to come sweetie
do you want a Diet Coke for breakfast
hello
Blossom sweetie you need to get the the
the the sheet between your skin the
quilt because your skin has oils honey
it has oils can I just get in there can
I just get in there you don't have to
get up you don't have to get up mother I
must wash the sludge of humanity from my
skin well honey honey glass listen honey
sweetie are you going to go take a
shower can I tell you something real
quick there can I get can I get in there
real quick can I just oh I just I just I
didn't know you were naked you got
undress so quickly honey listen listen
listen honey if you want if you want to
get breast implants we will support you
you know not not not financially but but
emotionally do not push your mother do
not push your mother listen listen that
basket of socks is in there for a reason
because you're when you're wet feet come
out of the bath they're wet and then
they I know you can't see it you don't
believe me but there is a layer of dust
on the bathroom floor and then it hits
the white Carpeting and it creates a
Grime
honey it creates a
crime hello Blossom how are you
doing I know I wouldn't I would pet you
but I'm allergic I I have distended
teeths too
honey listen sweee maybe we should get
her a t-shirt or something so she could
have some privacy listen I'm just
worried what you're going to be doing
this week because I I I got a lot of
things going on I've got a Mana pedicure
on Tuesday and then Rita's coming to
clean so I'm trying to keep things clean
for when she comes to clean and I'm just
exhausted sweetie listen
sweetie so what do
you sweetie you're you're going to put
on some makeup
right put on a little makeup for your
mother Mom I'm off work I don't have to
put on the clothes clown mask sweetie
aren't you wor you know what if Mike
shitsky is at the at the at Target what
if you see him mom he's married and has
three children I don't think he's going
to ask me to the
prom see when you don't wear makeup you
look mentally
ill mother you you know what you call
yourself a Christian and yet Jus
Christmas would say I look he would say
I look hot you know he see I look really
really Jesus doesn't know anyone at
Target honey now listen so what are you
going to be doing with yourself because
I just S I can't Entertain You mom I've
got tons of stuff I just I saw uh I saw
friend from high school Amy serson at
the airport so we're maybe we're going
to maybe hang out right we're going to
oh my god do you remember me S son from
high school do you remember
me yes I remember
you oh my yes I remember you you are so
funny so anyways are you coming your mom
says you're living in Hollywood what are
you coming are you having a nervous
breakdown is that's that's what I was
having that E True Hollywood Hollywood e
true story he always have like some
nervous breakdown they are you having a
nervous
breakdown
yes so I saw your around at Jubilee
Foods she's so funny she says she says
Maria St pressed she's on prac which is
so funny cuz I cut myself so I'm on a
effector and anti
psychotics Bri Brian get over here I
remember we had pre a couple years ago
and neither of us had any health
insurance and then but we were C you
know so we didn't C it was a soft cop C
so we got hundred thousands of dollars
in debt and I was a soft for so Bren had
a job and then we just we had pre
premature babies little girls and so I
would just cut myself just to relax just
to
relax and now I just watch I watched my
t-o episodes of Survivor palow and I
just
cry so you remember that one time in
high school do you remember rall
practice
yes oh my go so Mar she we're playing VI
and Mar goes we're playing and this
volleball hits her in the head and she
act like she's act like no big deal
fball just hit me in the head no big
deal like you like H and then another
one hit you in the head and then another
one and it's like your head was
attracting
volleyball and I says oh my God I'm
going to hit her in the head on purpose
this is see the look on your face and
then I did you remember what you said to
me do you remember what you said you
said am severon go to hell you're just
so funny cuz you know I'm a
Christian so listen I got to get out
here I work at Pro Staff temp people
Staff Pro people training Staff Pro and
don't tone and so you got to come down
and see me I got to get out of here
before I fall over and PE my P laughing
so Mom I have plenty I have places to go
people to see things to do I'm very busy
very very busy honey why would you
please put you know just a little
concealer on your upper lip cuz you have
a darkening it's called an aasma and
it's caused by having too estrogen and
pigment in your skin it creates a
Mustachio effect just I'm going to go
get your father
[Applause]
Joel Jo Joel oh my God Blossom just got
out she she's shutting everywhere
Joel Jesus Christ right here I've been
here for 40 years where I was am I going
to go
oh
what oh there goes that dog okay I got
her okay I got
you okay now want to want to go for a
ride huh blessy down by the river your
poppy yeah motorcycle ride with a bag
and some
rocks Joel oh my god oh you scared me
you scared
[Music]
me listen honey Marie I was watching
Maria upstairs take a shower and she was
has this mole on her butt and it just
looks odd and I just think as a
dermatologist in the family you should
take a look at it Jesus Christ
I'm not going to take a look at my
daughter's you yes she she she has
Healthcare she can get a you know a
[Music]
referral besides I don't think a a
melanoma would be the first thing you
would notice about her my goodness
looking very very good Maria what oh
[ __ ] Maria what mother I'm wearing
makeup I'm wearing thick green ey Shadow
and a line of lipstick around my
lips baby look pretty now
[Laughter]
[Music]
Mommy Mar okay sweetie what is just too
much why don't you stay at your sisters
honey your sisters okay we love you we
love you we love you we love you but
it's hard to be around you so I'm going
to going to go downstair I'll see you at
Target
honey very
funny want to see my new
invention yeah Dad totally okay you know
patients come into me you know I'm a
dermatologist patients come into me say
oh Dr bford I have a you know rash on my
arm okay
and
uh and uh you I say well put a topical
cream on it you know you know and uh if
if you need to wash
it don't use soap don't use soap soap is
drying irritating to the skin you need
to wash it pat pat pat with the what
washcloth hair dry hair dry you know
what do people always say to
me you say oh but Dr bford isn't there
some kind of special soap I can
use
soap soap is drying irritating to the
skin you need soap wash with wet wash
[Music]
hairir and then it never shops you know
stop
stop so I went on to my wood shop and I
came up with this okay it's a bar of
wood okay shaped like a bar of
soap I say oh why don't you try
this and then they say oh Dr banford I a
bar of wood won't I get
splinters I say oh yeah better not use
it pretty good huh very
funny that that is the most long- winded
passive aggressive way of getting
someone to do something and I like
it what does your agenty what
you you almost time off what's your
agency I she doesn't care last time I
saw her she said Mar when I first met
you I was concerned I was going to be
annoyed by you because you have a high
grading childlike voice and in you need
to know that about
yourself so I don't I don't think she'll
be missing me too
much Mom you seem a little
D taking your
[Music]
meds yes I'm taking my meds are you
taking your meds oh yeah I got about
seven going right
now yeah I got a Zer
techci reflux uh you know and then I got
a
uh taking proac for the darkness and
then I got a I got this this is new
after the prostate surgery I got it's
just you know temporary but it's a it's
a little pea bag and don't tell Blossom
but I've been marking [ __ ] around the
house just the stuff that's mine and uh
you know so and then I got this new
medication get this it's a heart
medication if I don't take it for one
day it's cyanura
can you believe oh I just you know got
caught up and some
goodbye well I just you know just got
busy and then I forgot
aista dad uh did did you take that
medication
today
[ __ ]
I usually end up at my sister's house uh
my sister come on
blessie uh my sister is a pathologist
though I like to introduce her as this
is my sister Sarah she cuts up the dead
into
chunks and uh cuz she's my older sister
and uh she uh she has a pug too hey
buttercup buttercup Blossom Buttercup
BL so r r do you get kicked out of the
house uh-huh uh-huh do you want a Diet
Coke should we bring out three do you
want three Diet Cokes do you want five
we can bring them I mean there's no
problem they're cool okay they're chill
no no no no no no no okay you ready okay
hey Mark Mark Mark Mark Mark Mark Mark
Mark Mark Mark
Mark okay I am leaving for target with
Maria I told you I told you okay I
forgot I did not tell you I am sorry Dr
Phil I am sorry Dr
Phil well you're going to have to wrap
that in white light and Let It Go Oprah
okay listen listen location of your
children one outside other is underneath
the dining room table playing with their
poly Pockets one is aimlessly wandering
with a spatula and the other one is
taking up a nap 20 minutes and Counting
okay put down the book Lord of the Rings
and watch your
children okay okay all right I love you
too Lady Liberty is on the Move Okay so
we got two do Coes hey Maria mar mar mar
listen would you open the door open the
door oh oh oh oh it's already open okay
sorry sorry sorry okay so um so so uh
mom said you had a new joke about me
what's your joke what's your
joke it's not it's not even a joke about
you it's just a generic sister
joke take a laugh hey what's your joke
Joker okay it's about it's a it's okay
it goes like this uh my sister and I
have the same voice so uh over the
holidays though it so hard for me to do
impersonation of her but she can't take
a left take a left take a left up here
okay you did it you did it you're doing
it you're doing okay okay do you want to
hear do you want to hear this or not no
no I'm listening I'm listening you're
doing what I'm saying you're doing what
I'm saying it's
cool okay my sister we have the same
voice but she came up with an
impersonation of me over the holidays
and it goes like this my name is Maria
and I think I'm a big deal so I don't
have to do the dishes or wake up before
noon and blah blah blah jibber jabber
jibber jabber clang
clang and then I say it's a pretty good
likeness you ever notice every joke you
tell you're the
victim and yet and yet every every joke
you tell you do an impersonation of some
someone else okay or someone from our
family who's the victim now buddy huh
who's the victim
now hey Maria you remember how uh you
know I was reading this medical journal
I forgot to tell you okay you know how
you you have that one dark curly hair
that comes out of your
neck you've seen it right that one dark
curly creepy disgusting hair you've seen
it I am just trying to help you okay and
then your breasts are look really small
dude it's called tosis it's a syndrome
you got to get your hormones check other
way you're going to be like like wake up
next day and be like covered in fur like
a
werewolf shut up
Sarah oh you shut up
Sasquatch
[Music]
Yeti Sarah maybe I tell a joke for being
a victim because I because I am a victim
you know mhm listen we all have genetic
defects look at me look at
me I got giant horse
[Music]
teeth you don't see me
crying why don't you go to one of your
groups one of your groups for
support support
group you're just jealous cuz there no
support groups for bossy people with
horse teeth I'm going to my groups
totally helping I I just I've been you
know people call me and you know we
support each other or whatever and uh I
just got to call
it it's Linda oh my God what's going on
are you are you okay
okay I'm at the take Gallery in
London um they're they're doing a
retrospective on my AST trays and
toothbrush
holders
okay you know what
app
applesauce
yeah like when it's
in compartments and then it has aluminum
foil over the top and then it's like
like a picnic pack like a like a snack
pack oh my God it is so good to talk to
someone who knows what I'm talking
about it's like you know sometimes I
just think you know where am I going you
know what am I doing you know and am I
always going to be like this you know
and me too I mean I don't I don't know
what's going on I don't Ian I don't have
any plan you know it's okay it's okay
it's
okay yeah and then you know sometimes
you have that you know when
you like you know you realize you know
everything's okay you know like like I
was walking past Barney last week and I
said okay if it's meant to be and I went
inside and that cashmir tube toop was
was 25% off and it's like okay I I get
it you know there there is a God there
is a plan I'm on a path yeah I mean
that's that's that's yeah that's that's
what it's about I guess you know
can I you know my my publicist is on the
other line C can I put you on hold for
45 minutes why don't why don't you just
call me back I really rather put your
one pH for 45 minutes well I don't think
my my cell phone will last that long
okay if I feel angry and disappointed
but I will call you back after my water
karate class so Sarah I'm you know
spiritually centered you know I have
some philosophy with which to guide me
and you're in this whirling retail
Vortex of Target beneath the you know
fluorescent lights and and you don't
have anything you know pushing forward
you know pushing you forward from it
uh-huh Mar where's your
cart I'm not I'm not getting anything I
don't need a cart dude if you get a cart
mom won't buy you [ __ ] get a
cart Sarah Maria
so Maria where's your cart
Mom I'm not going to I'm not going to
get anything Maria don't be a murder get
a cart so listen kiddo Sarah why don't
you go fill up fill up the whole cart
with G Coke you know what why don't you
add two carts and make a wagon train and
just fill it just fill it
listen sweetie you seem look at this
this is Darling look at this it's a pair
of kolots with a matching stationer set
Maria
look at that you're getting it you're
getting it so listen sweetie you seem
down you see you seem depressed this is
fun look at
this it's like a picture frame but it
spins so you see the picture and you see
it
over did you see that
honey sweetie you're getting it
listen can I just please so listen look
at this
oh okay okay you know it's like I told
you look at these Beanie
Babies sweetie they're on sale they're
mom those were probably made by like a
5-year-old in
Guatemala well they certainly weren't
supervised cuz they are not made that
well
I mean these kids are not working that
hard
huh okay what you do is you get six
penguins and six kangaroos next time you
go to Australia you got gifts to bring
back you think ahead honey let's get six
of each think ahead think ahead so this
I told you you know if you wanted to be
in Show Business you're going to have to
prepare yourself for a life of rejection
and if you do finally make it via the
casting couch or Lady Luck soon enough
your beauty will fade away and with it
your false friends leaving only the glow
of Stardust Memories to keep you warm as
you lay in the gutter of the boulevard
of
dreams but you are a star honey you are
a star we walk down these aisles and
people say who's that who's that uh
that's because you're yelling at me
mother
sweetie yes
Sarah am I star too am I a star yes of
course you are a star s you are a
different kind of star though you are a
pathology star people look at you and
they think
science so listen I'm going to break
into a run here and get a fun Island but
I'll meet you at the checkout register
in 10 okay
[Music]
hey Ram R what do do you think I'm you
know like do you think I could be on TV
you think I I I could be on TV yeah
anybody can be on
TV okay okay so here's my idea for a
show okay it's like it's like a cooking
show where you have like you know you
can see what they're doing right with
the mirrors and stuff and but then it's
like autopsies and it's like celebrity
autopsy so you have like charlon H movie
and then you take a clip and then you go
and here's his
liver
right that's that's an incredible idea
Sarah that's really that's really okay
so right okay so here's another one
coming at you so um I'm doing like it's
like a diet plan that you know people go
crazy for it's like you can have
whatever you want whatever you want but
it has to be out of dollhouse
furniture so like you can have like you
can have have like a hot fudge Sunday
but it has to be out of like a dollhouse
tub so right so like you can have like a
like you can have like a sirloin steak
right but it's got to be a dollhous size
steak get it that's that's that's a
great okay here's my this is the awesome
idea so me and my friend soy we okay we
it's like a home makeover show we come
to your house right we come to your
house and um we just tell you everything
that's wrong with your life right
everything that's wrong we just go this
sucks and you need a new haircut and
like just all that stuff we just say
everything's wrong um like with your
kids and like your looks and and then we
just leave them
there and we don't tell them or help
them how to fix
it that's a really good idea that's
that's that's good hey Sarah how Dad's
doing okay right he uh he's doing okay
right cuz uh I mean he just had the
prostate surgery so he seems really
good I don't know maybe he's got two
years or
something
what I don't
know H this is why we can't talk about
this [ __ ] with you is because you can't
handle it you freak
out well so his dad I mean his dad he's
going to die or something no no I am
just saying any of us could die at any
moment like right now I could have an
aneurysm oh oh I'm gone you know what
I'm saying like you you drink so much
Diet Coke you could have like a
calcified tumor growing of Diet Coke
like in your shoulder or something I
don't know we're all going to die Maria
we're all going to die but Dad's but
dad's fine right yeah he's St he's
probably going to last forever like you
know 50 more years but I'm just saying
we will die
I know
that okay hey do you remember Christy
kums from high
school you mean my my Arch
Enemy uh-huh mom's checking out with her
at the register right now and you are
going to
die hello Christy cools wow what a
surprise now you were in Maria's class
right okay okay Marilyn Bamford listen
listen so I love what you've done with
your hair with the black the Dark Root
and then the the the perm and then the
blonde that's fun that is fun listen are
you singing are you singing now are you
cuz you were such such a lovely voice no
no no you're not oh oh oh oh oh that's
hard that's hard that's hard well listen
uh Sarah of course is my older daughter
and she is a doctor and her husband is a
doctor and they have four beautiful
children and they live on the east side
of town and they're just you know going
gang busters and then Maria is who's
hiding behind the Shrek 2 DVDs
Maria she is a comedian and she has been
on Conan O'Brien in
1997 which you know she was only on
there twice and then they said never
again I mean they didn't say that but
that's how she felt you know and it's
like she just keeps putting herself out
there and you just keep trying listen I
am in a real hurry here cuz we got to go
to the Blackberry and in Casino we got
reservations out there so I'm just going
to slide my card and the other the girls
can sign for it but good to see you
christe good to see you good to see
you hey christe yeah I got four carts
about 20 a piece uhuh Diet Coke hey oh
listen I got to go because I got four
kids and you know how it
is but uh
good to see you God you're
die uh hey Christie hey how
how congratulations I was I mean this is
like 15 years too late now but uh uh uh
you got married to Todd so uh anyways
congratulations and stuff and
uh we got
divorced oh my God I'm so sorry I mean
you know I mean whatever is is
appropriate you know what what uh uh uh
I'm so um uh so he brought over your
video T to watch the kids or something I
don't know what it was but oh my God
that's so nice oh oh
wow it's just like in high school it's
like you're not funny you're just
weird well you know comedy is is sub
subjective you know it's it's it's an
art form you know so uh so are you gay
cuz I heard like a lot of women
comedians are
gay no no no I'm not I mean it' be okay
if I was uh
not okay if I if I
[Music]
was that's great cuz I remember um
remember I went to Christian Bible camp
and you went um we all went skinny
dipping and you would take your shirt
off and I'm like oh my God you got
nothing to show anyway and then you you
took your shirt off and we all gave you
titty twisters I was like oh my God if
you were lesel you'd have been all
turned on by that and I just got all
grossed
[Laughter]
out press debit or
credit that that's a that's a horrible
memory my
gosh it's like you think you're such a
big deal but people you know people make
fun of you like patteron that he was a
he was a bar and he's like um I don't
know if I can do if he doesn't
impersonation to me was so funny he goes
uh he goes I don't know how you do it he
goes hi Mar or something and then
um Mike shitsky goes he's so funny he
goes he said he said I wouldn't have
[ __ ] that freak in high school and I
wouldn't [ __ ] her
now
uh
chy why don't why don't you go suck
it why don't you go suck
it [ __ ]
you [ __ ] you
too do you need help out the car with
your
bags
[Applause]
this this is the point where you start
to think to yourself hey maybe you know
maybe maybe you know when you try to
think oh well things you nor almost
change inside yourself you feel better
about yourself or maybe you know maybe
you should you know maybe you don't need
anybody you know you don't need or you
know you don't even need you know cuz I
you know you're just kind of freaking
out or whatever you just feel kind of
like you're kind of you know like okay
this isn't good and uh and then and then
and
then Mar Dustin Hoffman as Rainman
Dustin Hoffman Rainman hey we got a
table we got a table at the black bear
do you want to come and sit down I don't
know what you're doing you're talking to
yourself okay great um we're ready to
order yeah um I hi I'm going to be
ordering for the four kids and my
husband okay just over here I don't know
what these other people want okay um so
we're going to have the cheese pizza and
and then um orange juice and um yeah
that's what you're getting and then uh
my husband wants to surf and turf well
that's what you said you wanted well I
don't know what you want
Nostradamus he'll have the surf and turf
oh my God and then I'll have the cob
salad and a Diet Coke water diet peny
what you have and um I don't know what
this guy wants um he's going to have to
tell himself
dad like to have the uh uh what is your
name Young waitress I'm sorry I didn't
get your name Tina oh nice to meet you
Tina B uh so I've been looking at your
Min here and uh got a you know very nice
pictures and uh couple let me see I
think I'd like to have a uh you know
there
and
thank you very much Tina thank you very
much oh I'm sorry you you can hear
me enunciate Helen color nobody knows
what you're talking about Dad in who who
oh je Tina I like to have the cheese
bger cheese
bger uh hash browns my pants brown I
don't know if you can you know that you
need that as a
reference a cup of coffee I can get it
over there I see it over there so you
know sure walk away I can get it myself
thank you
[Music]
Tina just you people don't
listen hi I'm Marilyn Bamford and
listen let's just start out with two
pictures of Diet Coke and listen Tina oh
God I hate to to shoot the messenger but
Diet Pepsi is not okay no it is not and
I know you aren't making these decisions
it's the big wigs upstairs am I right
yeah and it's like they just you know
there is a big difference and I'm just
trying to protest here at the Grassroots
level then kind of shift the Paradigm
you know person by person but Diet Pepsi
is fine that's fine and uh I am on a
combination of the South Beach and
Weight Watchers and so I have six points
left and a fruit and uh so what what can
I do what can I do here what can I do
about a french fry or a curly fry listen
I a curly I think a Curly has more fiber
don't you Tina yeah yeah let's go with
that and then I need to have the fruit
and that needs to be a fresh a Ramic a
Ramic isn't that what you use in the
industry Ramic of fresh raspberries okay
and uh you don't have that what would
you have that would be the equivalent R
strawberry pie strawberry pie that's
fine that's fine listen this is my
daughter Maria if you didn't recognize
her already cuz she has been on The Late
Late Late Late Show honey which what is
it is it the Late Late Show or is it the
Late Late Late Show
is it or is it the late just the late no
no it's The Late Late mother it it's
okay I don't I don't think she needs to
know she doesn't need to know how poorly
my career is going um I I'd like to have
the chicken Caesar salad and a Diet
Pepsi and thank you so much you know
thank you so much for for helping my
family thank thank
you thank thank
[Laughter]
you hey you guys um I have a a announc
to make well your announcement is going
to have to wait because I have an
awesome
story so um I'm doing this autopsy right
that's not even the story so Steve comes
in from down the hall he's doing like
laser surgery right like burning flesh
burning flesh right and it's right
lunchtime and it's like he comes in he's
like oh my God I had to get out of there
because I am so hungry and it smells
like a
barbecue cuz we're just meet you guys
just
meat I probably taste pretty
good I have a high fat content Marin
tastes very good she tastes like Diet
Coke
jerky okay tell your story Maria try and
top
that okay uh it's not it's just an
announcement um I just I've been
thinking about it and you know I wanted
to you know do s kind whatever and do
you know show business stuff I realize
you know that I don't I just want to
live in a sitcom you know where you have
you know experiences with people you
love and and they're funny or not funny
and then uh you don't have to act them
out and uh so anyways I'm mooving home
I'm going to move home home to dulu so I
just wanted to uh let you do so I'm
excited and uh and so
okay Mar do you think you're going to be
avoiding uh pain and rejection by moving
to duth you got another thing
coming am I right Mark am I right okay I
was crabby for about two years okay and
um because I had Josephine and um I had
you know they say you get hemorrhoid
after kids okay and they say they're
like this small dudes the size of apples
the size of
apples and the only way to get rid of
those things is you got to tie them off
with a rubber band until they burst okay
and not like a medical rubber band just
a regular rubber
band don't tell me about pain and
humiliation
okay you know right you know that's
tough all over you know my job I uh you
know I got written up at my job as
patient came in you know and they wrote
a letter complaining you know they said
uh I think Dr
B you know I think Dr B
[Music]
I what she said you know she said uh I I
think Dr a loose
canon okay okay
crazy Maria sweetie oh
God you can't move home honey you you
are not welcome at home
and I say this because
you I wasn't going to tell you this but
we were having a prayer vigil uh Benny
silveran was uh dying of breast cancer
and we had
a a prayer vigil around it and we kind
of we're were there for a couple hours
kind of ran out of things to pray for
and uh I says I says let's pray that
Maria gets a a
sitcom and a
husband and I just think I know you
don't believe in him but Jesus wants you
to have you know a MySpace page and a
and and and and
merch he wants you to he just you can't
move home mom don't wor don't worry it's
you guys it's a I'm actually I'm
actually I mean it's just I'm not
actually moving home it's just it's just
a show there's there's people here it's
this it's just a it's just just a show
it's just a
show oh my god oh that's funny okay I
get it I get it I get it I get it funny
funny funny funny okay Maria exaggerates
so much of this is not true it's
true at an emotional level perhaps but
in no way it's more of a all right right
are we going to be on TV is this me
we're going to be on TV well no it's
just it's kind of in my head right now
now just doing it in theater right
that's that's pretty good right maybe if
you put my your hands like this it' be
kind of like I'm on TV like yeah you
should you should put it you should
put this is all [ __ ] about me dying you
no death see that's the thing in this
show is that no one ever dies oh okay
good yeah I want to be in every
episode Mar this is amazing show it's
brilliant you're fantastic this is
amazing this is a breakthrough and we
need to recast
you you can't you can't Maria I I don't
want to be in your show so don't put me
in
it I don't want you to be in my show so
why don't you go to hell in a hand
basket why don't you go suck it why
don't you [ __ ] off Girls Girls Girls
Girls Girls listen honey
the reason Christy is so hostile is
because she wants she just she just
jealous and she why why don't you give
her a part in the show Honey why don't
you give chrisy a part in your sitcom
Mom it's just basically in my oh my God
Maria am I going to be h a show that is
so funny I can okay you're going to be
in little parts of the show just little
Parts not not the whole okay okay I'll
be little parts I'll just be in little
Parts Little parts
[Music]
[Applause]
of so Maria I want to introduce you to
somebody I want to introduce you oh my
god Maria I am so sorry um they I didn't
want to act anymore and um I didn't even
audition for the sitcom in your
head but I I got the
part you guys can't okay I'm going to do
my own sitcom okay this is just going to
be this new sitcom is just to be me and
a monster and we end up having to live
together because the monster is like a
he's like he's like unemployed and then
I'm like a dancer or something and we
have to live together and the monster
like starts you know I'm like I can't
live with a monster he's 7,000 lb and he
is all scaly and slimy and he has to put
half of his hind feet in the backyard
and his front feet upstairs and there's
no place to
sit
monster has nowhere to
go nowhere to go for
monster he starts borrow my clothes and
stuff he's like I'm like you can't wear
my capri pants Oh capri
pants honey that needs a lot of work and
it it it also you need to have some kind
of love interest mom I am I am dating I
am out there I am
available well I mean just somebody mom
you guys why don't you get your own dang
[Applause]
sitcom oh right uh please welcome to the
stage uh as I we we read the credits uh
of the show uh this is going to be the
uh redo or uh uh the the uh we're uh
bringing back uh my good friend chrisy
kums from high school and she's going to
uh rect her 1988 uh High School
production role of Adan in uh Oklahoma
as I read over the credits so christe uh
take
away so much a question I'm not knowing
what to do I know what's written wrong
since I've been
10 I hear a lot of stories and I reckon
they are true about how girls are put
upon by
man I know I must fall into the
pit but when I'm with a fell I
forget um thank you so much to everyone
who helped in this production Dan
especially and everybody on the crew and
the amazing uh Varsity Theater and Dicky
town and everybody who came in
Minneapolis and uh all my directors in
the past uh julus Shelton uh uh Evan
Blackford uh Nelly Thomas and uh are you
like are you g to keep
talking that's that's it I'm just a girl
who can't say no I'm in a
terrible I always see come on let's go
just when I got see next shut
up
all the girl every girls are Al Co and
sweet but other girls ain't having any
fun every time I lose a Ry match I have
a funny feeling that
I
justs are I can't Bey on queen that is
[Music]
to I want I
can't I
[Music]
can't
no back thank you thanks everybody on
the light wonderful job thank you very
[Applause]
[Music]
much
this is delial lift bridge used to be
able to go up with the w with with the
bridge but now you can't because then
one year somebody jumped off and they
got caught up in all the pulley and the
weights and they got sliced right in
half right in a
half which is I me that's that's a good
way to go really but it might have
inspired
copycats
um that's that's what
[Music]
it
the gets gone with a bag of cash oh man
home tanks
doneas got
get for
rehearsal no get St foret about the take
parade I'll R the river and slide
forever and eat whatever
will Comm
commercial
commercial commercial
[Applause]
[Music]
commerci young woman no PO pan summer
blades and a cut
upboard like auns for LS in the future
the show won't even cover I like the
walkers and the PO BL talking in the
beautiful day like new AR My Life Time
like a shine as a last new in
the
commercial