hey everybody thank you again for tuning
in to another episode of modern day
philosophers it's a great show coming up
my talk with Bill Burr is fantastic Bill
Burr has been a great supporter and
friend of mine over the years but he's
also one of my favorite comedians I
apologize I'm going through some
allergies here and I'm a bit congested
hopefully it doesn't come too strong
through in the interview but uh if it
does I apologize and if you feel like I
should have to apologize for allergies
then I don't apologize I resent it
because why should I have to but if I
don't have to then I do you know what I
mean okay before we get into anything
else I want to tell you that this
episode is brought to you by
standup.on records standup records the
label that put out my album some kind of
comedian which is available at
standup.on the holidays are long drives
to places that none of us want to go so
we can see relatives we only see once a
year and argue with them after that who
couldn't use a good laugh right come to
standup records new online shop at
standup .c and bu the best and fresh
independent comedy that's standup
crap.com and I can't stress to you
enough how great of a guy Dan schle is
who runs the record label that I'm on
and what a great supporter of Comedy he
is and he's such a great supporter that
he's even supporting this very show that
you're listening to it is brought to you
once again by standup crap.com go there
pick up my album go pick up Brandon
Burns's album brenon Burns pompously
lectures Americans that's available also
on standup crap.com
at a great discounted price for the
holidays okay now without further Ado
except for the song the intro song I
guess that's a little further Ado but
aside from that without further Ado
here's my talk with Bill Burr enjoy
everybody hello and welcome to modernday
philosophers modern day philosophers
having failed to pay attention in school
Danny LEL now older and wiser will
attempt to learn basic philosophy 101
our young hero will be joined by today's
top comedians philosophers all their own
ladies and gentlemen here's Danny LEL
mod day
[Applause]
philosophers all right we are here with
uh one of I I'll be I'll be flattering
to your face you are one of my favorite
comedians Bill all right I'll take it
thank you for being here getting better
day taking compliments thank you I don't
as I look around the room I'm not
getting them as much as you but I'm I'm
finally starting to uh I used to reject
them right away when somebody that's
good then you had the proper uh
childhood to be a comedian yeah I'm
reading that new Johnny Carson book you
got to you got to read it man the one
that his lawyer wrote his mother was
brutal brutal really one of the stories
not going to ruin the book but a quick
excerpt he he sent his uh he sent his um
parents on a trip around the world 48
day trip they saw the world so they're
like 30 days in on the trip and uh they
haven't called them haven't you know
nothing didn't check in or anything yada
yada they get back and he's waiting for
the phone call they're home for five
days no phone call so according to the
book now this isn't Johnny saying this
you know so take it with a grain of salt
but according to this lawyer he said
Johnny calls a his mom up after 5 days
and just like
mom and she's like yeah hey he's like uh
how was it and she's just like oh Johnny
we're just so happy to be
home so he used to I guess relay these
it was a very like standup comic thing
where he would relay these
stories of um unbelievable hurt and pain
with his mom to his lawyer and his
lawyer after hearing the story would
then just laugh and then Johnny would
laugh and I and I thought like that was
really like the the backbone
of uh just how when you you you you go
down the comedian route where if you
actually like oh my God Danny that's so
I feel so bad for you blah blah blah
blah then you're an actual like human
being and you're probably going to get a
real job but if you just start laughing
right you have that uh I don't know that
thing that makes what makes me love and
hate all
comedians did you ever see that
documentary uh Wild Man Blues the Woody
Allen documentary by his jazz band oh
you did I ever rent that one D Rose is
always he's big Woody Allen he is always
telling me to rent those things I
watched a lot of I don't think I rented
that one though that's a good one too
that's uh Woody goes to his parents and
they're like in their 90s and it's I
don't know if it was done like maybe 10
15 years ago not that long ago mhm and
uh there's these two 90-year-old people
his parents are sitting there and
they're still not proud of him at all oh
they're still uh they're still saying
they wish he would have gone into
there's got to be something out there
like like where you can detox from
heroin same kind of thing where there's
got to be something where you can detox
from parental Improvement if it's just
terminal I got great parents thank God
they they've always said that they're
proud of me and they totally encourag me
and everything um but there has to be uh
at some point you got to take control of
your life and just be like look this has
nothing to do with me this has to do
with whatever the hell happened to them
as kids and I need to to break this
thing because I definitely through
reading this Carson book like there's a
lot of stuff that he does that I
completely relate to there's a lot of
things like you know the compliments he
doesn't like compliments there's a lot
of the U when somebody really needs him
it causes them to be cold and wall them
off I'm not that guy anymore but I used
to be like that and that that definitely
comes from you know uh similar sort of
background it it it's just like an I
don't know I think like an East Coast I
don't know what it is no he was from
Nebraska but my parents were from
Midwest so I don't know I know if it's
that there's
that just uh there that um I don't know
there's people who are just touchy
trying to regionalize it but I think
it's it's probably spread out amongst
everybody yeah yeah I don't know just
well I just kind of related to the a
little bit of the the the
coldness I just think coldness is too
harsh to say about my upbringing it was
just not you know it was the love was
implied you know what I mean like I got
hit by a car when I was a kid and my
mother her response was well that's what
you get for riding the street you idiot
and that was
her she she was angry I think at the
love she had for me and the fear of
losing me oh yeah so rather than like
going oh my God I don't ever use yeah it
becomes like this you get mad if you
could detox from having those kind of
parents and then you knew that the risk
of doing so might be might be less funny
Would You Do
It um I don't think you can become less
funny so I would do it you really don't
think you become yeah there's there's
that thought that don't get too happy
don't lose your Edge don't mellow out
don't blah blah blah it's just like you
know I I don't think I think that's a
fear a lot of us have is that you can
become less funny you don't think it's
possible no no because you you what you
have is the you can now what you can do
is laugh at your well I've gotten to the
point now where I laugh at myself I
still have the temper but I'm not the
angry guy I was in my 20s and 30s where
it was literally consuming my guts it
felt like um now it's like you know I'm
flipping out and I'm as I'm doing it I'm
observing myself going look at you
losing your temper again so I mean I've
kind of gotten to that point and then
when I'm on stage where back in the day
I think it was more of like you know
have you gone to these cell phone stores
what's up with that it's more like now
I'm kind of taking it from a place of
like so I go to the cell phone store you
know I'm a real impatient guy and I pick
out the stuff that bugs me but I'm also
sort of like psychologically breaking
down uh what an idiot I am for always
taking the bait and getting this mad
over a cell phone or or or or what
whatever the hell it is I'm trying to do
so and I and I think that it adds a
uniqueness to what you're doing as
opposed to I mean there's enough it's
more self-aware you know it's definitely
more self-aware but I'll try and use
that as a transition to get into
philosophy our philosophy um so the guy
Alex picked for you is Adam Smith and uh
he that might be the most boring name
ever for a philosopher I thought it was
going to be some sort of Greek name Adam
Smith just Adam
Smith did he change his name to that
because what's in a
name probably had some 20 syllable last
name all right Adam Smith Adam Smith uh
I usually say when he lived from he was
from
1723 uh to 1790 and he was a Scottish
moral philosopher and Pioneer of
political economy and he he lived in
Scotland he lived in Scotland he studied
at uh University of Glasgow I'm going to
glas go next month oh yeah I got a gig
out there oh cool and I like Scotch we
we hung out in Glasgow last time briefly
at the stand yeah I didn't you know I
ran into those guys Kevin Bridges and
all those guys when I was in New York
doing I love Kevin Bridges oh dude
there's nothing better than drinking
with a Scottish guy you can't understand
him at the beginning of the Night by the
end of the night
especially [ __ ] I like they don't say
yeah they go hey you feel like you're
hanging out with a bunch of pirates and
and he wrote the book wealth of The
Wealth of Nations which was published in
17 1976 okay Bill bur Adam Smith I like
it yeah I added I added a
syllable moving up in the world Alex
picked him he said because he found
somewhere that you are distrustful of
Bankers oh yeah am they're the biggest
criminals on the planet you go high
enough up they're literally
counterfeiting money just I'm
distrustful of money I don't even you
know it's just I I just find it
hilarious that like I just love that
thing how we all work all week and then
when you're done you just get this piece
of paper with like numbers on it and
then you go down and you hand it to
these guys who are some of the biggest
criminals ever we're too big to fail you
deal with it you pay our tab like these
absolute gangsters and just still
throughout all of it you just hand it to
them these guys who gave like homeless
people half a million Lo let's say you
don't give them the piece of paper with
the numbers on it I still don't trust it
I don't trust the piece of paper with
the numbers on it that that's that
equals my work it's a belief system it
whenever I travel and do gigs overseas I
just what would you get paid in barley
and flour gold I want the gold stand
yeah you know what that's better
actually would be a good mix barley
flour and some gold what you really want
is silver you're not going to give
somebody you don't give somebody gold
for a sandwich you give you give them
some silver that's worth like 20 bucks
right I want something that like a I
love your dogs by the way yeah sorry
about that by way no that
dog's that was your dog yeah it's
awesome dogs don't dogs barking don't
bug me and babies crying on airplane do
not bug me why don't babies cry on just
because that's how babies are you just
give them the no but what beyond that
they're expressing exactly what I'm
feeling the second I get on there and
I'm like oh God another 5 hour flight or
whatever 10hour flight depending on
where I'm going they're just honest you
love their honesty I would love to be
able to do that let out a whale and just
get it out of you you know so just when
I watch people putting their jackets in
the overhead compartment as they're
saying don't put your jackets up there
and they're deliberately ignoring it and
in that moment I see why it's never
going to work like how people are never
it we're never going to get to a Utopia
yeah just in that moment of watching
that guy as they're like you know people
please don't put your jackets up in the
overhead compartments until all the bags
are up there and somebody stuffing this
I'm going to Antarctica snorkel jacket
up there when I just see that that
selfishness yeah and I'm not judging the
guy because I can relate because I'm
selfish and I just just look at it and
they go that's right there is the reason
yeah that right there is the seed of why
we're never going to we're never going
to get along I kind of I think that's
good too I I don't know if I'd want to
live in a Utopia it'd be too boring
there'd be nothing there's nothing to
strive for I yeah which is why I don't
have that desire for the afterlife with
you go to heaven you go to heaven to me
people are still breaking
balls and like there's still the
pettiness you still see somebody like
like trying to pick something up with
their foot cuz they don't want to get
off the couch and you know and take some
an extra two minutes just watching human
behavior like that like if it's like
this I don't who knows I mean obviously
nobody knows what happens when you die
obviously maybe you go to some Enlighten
thing I think it's over I mean it makes
sense that it's over and I think that
you
know and people well life is too short
it's like yeah but you you came out as
the highest level being right you really
hit the lottery you mean what if flies
live like what 8 Days mhm you know what
I mean or like you know you watch these
Discovery things where for the most part
you're going to die by getting eaten
alive murdered or something if you're
lucky it's a big cat and they'll just
kind of choke you out UFC style except
they use their mouth but like you know
the kodo dragon is just that's just the
most brutal one do you give much thought
to to that stuff to the afterlife to God
the existence or do you just sort of not
as much as I used to I I uh I don't know
if it's arrogance or whatever but I just
I once I I was able to kind of wrap my
head around that religions are all based
in the
same uh just natural feeling you have
that if you do something good you feel
good if you do something bad you feel
bad um that moral compass thing that
once I just kind of looked how they they
just sort of
exploit all of it and it's hypocritical
and you know just the
whole that like you know people who get
super religious like there's people who
get so religious that they commit murder
because some somebody says something bad
against their religion and the fact that
they can still think that they're going
to be in the eyes of this higher power
as something good is uh it's frightening
and I think what religion does either
deliberately or inadvertently is it
perverts the your moral compass of doing
good things makes you feel good doing
bad things makes you feel bad and like
look believe me dude if I you know when
I die if I am going to get judged I am
not going to make it I have done some
horrible horrible things and I would
literally I don't what I would have to
do I would have to save a city
single-handedly from a
fire while suffering you know third
degree burns just to get I think back to
even I'm like that like Gambler that's
just like I'm just down forever and I
should just walk away I'm never going to
get even I'm not even going to get close
so um you know I was a piece of [ __ ] for
too long so there you go that's
uplifting what about what if the what if
God is not tied to religion know what
I'm saying is God there's a Creator he
makes beings he puts them here and then
that's it hands off that's how I view
him that's how I view them like I don't
view like you you can't sit there and
make seven billion of something give
them freedom of choice and not think
that some sort of chaos is going to
ensue um I think Carlin or somebody said
something about how it's just his
entertainment he just made these things
to watch I feel like uh you do believe
that something made us a Creator made us
it's not just Rand
no I I I I have my honesty is I don't
know what happened I have no idea what
happened but I I am more likely to go I
go will go 70% science 30% philosophy
and 0% religion it's how I do it but I
like the the ground floor of every
religion where it's like you know you
know don't kill people honor your
parents don't steal and that type of
thing although I've broken a lot of
Commandments
um all right going back to money let's
talk about money a little bit so uh we
went we went for barley and flour and
gold right just thing to me seem like
things like a troll might give you yeah
for working but then but then the the
thing about it is is like getting mugged
then is way worse losing a City bank
card or your debit card as bad as that
is it'd be harder to mug you they have
to carry a whole sack of flour I know
but the
devastation of like if people get paid
barley and flour now I'm assuming that
you're making your own bread pastries
whatever the hell you're doing and like
you have chickens at home like that's
like you know they used to they used to
hang you for stealing horses and cattle
rustling because that was that was the
level it's like dude you're you're
[ __ ] with my ability to eat here um
so now that we have supermarkets you can
steal a car which is a modern-day horse
and you know you just it's that's is a
felony but I mean yeah you're not going
to get put to death well just the idea
like when I go overseas and do shows and
I have dollars on me and I I run out of
like whatever the currency is where
there and I oh sorry I only have dollars
they don't even want them and it just
makes you feel how useless and
meaningless this stuff is because once
you leave once you leave the they don't
believe in that God right they don't
believe in that they believe in their
God which has their guys on it no but
this is It's dollars it's you could buy
I work for this it's good I would love
to talk to somebody in Europe like what
was what was it like when you went from
like Deutch marks to Euros or Franks
Franks however you say it to to Euros or
whatever like I don't even know who's
who's on it and who isn't I know uh
England still has the pound but like
what that was like you know when you had
that old pair of golf pants in the back
where you got a $20 bill with your guys
on it you know and then all of a sudden
it's the Euro um I mean I don't believe
in all of that that that helps the
economy like I just believe that that
helps the banks sew up more territory it
helps people at the top do business more
I read a book recently where they you
know just the way that we approached
Japan and they didn't want to deal with
the outside world and how we just were
like no you're going to deal with us and
you're going to trade with us or we're
going to come back and basically start
shooting cannonballs at you it's just
like the the [ __ ] arrogance the
[ __ ] arrogance of it was is just it
was one of those things that you know I
read books and occasionally and I
immediately forget everything in them
but every once in a while there's
something that stands out and the the
[ __ ] arrogance to that I just
couldn't get I couldn't get past it what
what do you make of it when people say
oh China own owns us they that doesn't
translate into anything for me what do
you mean China they bought up our de on
paper but there's one of those things
where
uh I I think that that was uh golden
handcuffs where now they got drawn into
our horrific Financial mistakes and I
think that's all part of some sort of
brilliant plan to suck them into our
economy and get every body with the
money with the same guy's face on it
they'll probably have uh George
Washington on the front and one of their
their guys on the back and that'll be
the big battle how come we're on the
back and then the philosophers is going
to be like well there's really no front
and back if you look at it just depends
on where you're standing right right but
it doesn't mean anything for guys like
you and me right we're just the I think
it does I think that would be a major
shift if if all of a sudden uh you know
I have empathy for all these countries
that we occupy and we sit there and we
say that we're bringing them free
freedom and stuff and even if that is
just what we're doing which I never
believe in I think like I saw how much
they gave a [ __ ] about people in New
Orleans I saw how much they give a [ __ ]
about people who got screwed by bankers
and are upside down in houses right now
that they'll never get out from
underneath I saw how much they care and
this is allegedly their own people mhm
there's no
way they give a [ __ ] about anybody it
always comes down to like it's a Strate
IC point to put an army or there's some
sort of fluid in the ground that we want
or some sort of trees we want to cut
down it's it's an energy thing it's a
powered thing it's a strategic thing and
then they just dress it all up with like
you know sure we just can't stand that
you want to start a death metal band in
that country and your your dictator
won't allow you to do it you know right
yeah it's never genuine but they can't
they can't be that honest right they
can't be that honest without make and
make it go smoothly they can't say hey
we're here to take what's yours well
because they need regular people to
fight the war right cuz they're not
going to go and do it so what they have
to do is is give this righteous re they
have to have a right good reason for
doing it and who knows maybe they
actually believe it but um I I don't
know man I mean you go into the average
comedy club and there's all kinds of
schemes and crap going on and just like
don't I just I don't feel like you get
to it like I love how people like people
who aren't into conspiracy first of all
the immedately the first thing they do
when you say you're into conspiracy they
think oh you think there's flying
saucers and aliens and all that like
they make you out to be crazy for crazy
and I always just say well this country
came about through a conspiracy that's
how it came about people conspired and
if if they lost they would have been
hung for being a traitor sure but we won
so now they're Heroes and I think
there's an effort bill to make people I
think there's an effort coming from the
top to to say hey if you hear about
conspiracy they're crazy I think that
that's in I think that's a conspiracy
right there I think well I would
actually argue that it's
more you you you you are
defined by your uh beliefs no you're
defined by the least of you it's like
Jerry Springer Jerry Springer Show has
the worst example of every cross-section
of whatever you're going to do the
Southern Man the
africanamerican the the the Asian
whoever it's just it's never going to be
a good thing and I feel like with with
like conspiracy theorist you're going to
be defined by those people like that
that character Mel Gibson played in that
movie where he drove the cab and he had
all all the conspiracies but do you
think that there's there's a reason
there are people behind that to try and
be like look if anybody starts telling
you things aren't the way they are look
at these guys look at these examples we
put forward for you I I also think
conspiracy theorists are annoying like
it's like you're having a good day and
then they come along they tell you that
the money isn't worth anything saying
how the Sun is burning out the polar ice
caps are coming down and and you know
the bushes are buying up land in South
America it's all on aquafers and but at
some point I have to take a break yeah
but you have to hear it too right you
can't just shut it all out otherwise
you're just living mindlessly and you're
like I am living a good life be quiet be
quiet you're not living mindlessly I
don't feel you are because I I think
that it is um it's set up to it's we're
just this is our
destiny it's just whatever it is we're
staring it into the sun you don't think
we should fight fight for a better
Destiny or um try and control the one we
have yeah no no I would never say don't
do that but that's not my lot in life
like I'm not a uh I don't know how to
organize something like that all I know
is how to read about this stuff get
informed on it and then you like it
makes you overwhelmingly depressed you
try to talk to people about it oh you
one of them conspiracy theories yeah
what's going on on Saturn and you're
talking about
Banks and um so what I did was I just
look I educated myself as much as I
could to whatever the game was playing
where you know like I bought a house and
I have a mortgage okay now I could go
out and buy a bunch of flat screen TVs
and and widgets and all that crap and I
don't I don't have a dining room table I
have I drive a seven-year-old hybrid and
all I do every month is I knock the prin
principle down because I educated to
myself about how they frontend load the
interest and how if I took actually took
30 years I would pay two and a half
times the loan price and with the taxes
and the maintenance and all that I would
be lucky if I broke even and by the time
I pay it off I'm in the final third of
my life when the kidneys go or whatever
and then I have the and I know the deal
like they don't I'll tell you a quick
story I had some water damage on my
house and I had insurance so I put in
for the claim and when the insurance
money came it came to me it was made out
to me my wife and and the loan my my the
the the bank that that I have my
mortgage with so I call them up and they
and they told me that I had to sign the
check over to
them and I was like why I
go it's it's my insurance it's my money
and they go yeah well we have a vested
interest in the house in the property
it's like so do I I live here and I
start to understand what it is is they
own it they own it like when people buy
a house they go oh I own it it's like no
you don't own it you just switched
landlords now you have rather than a
landlord you have a banker so basically
like back in the day you got your
insurance money so I I basic I just kept
saying why and they go well because it's
an over $10,000 claim I said I know but
why they go I just explain it I said no
you told me what your policy is I want
to know the reasoning behind it and
basically what it is is too many people
nowadays when they were when they were
getting the insurance money they weren't
fixing the house they would just go buy
a car have a keg party do whatever they
they buy some sneakers whatever they did
and then they default on the loan and
and the banks would get the houses back
and not only did they have this house
they had to sell they also had a hole in
the roof and what it really was was they
[ __ ] over so many people they had so
many people upside down in houses paid
280 for a house that's now worth 210 and
it's got $10,000 worth of damage what do
I give a [ __ ] now I'm down 60 I'm going
to go and go buy a Dodge Challenger you
know put the top down or whatever
sunroof whatever you got in that car and
go drive around
so it's like they never lose it's like
you [ __ ] us and now I'm paying the
price and I dude I had to fix it a third
at a time and they come at me like I was
a child to make sure all the work was
done and they were inspected and
infuriated me so all it did was made me
work harder pay it off quicker and my
goal is to pay off the house before the
job's done so I can go all right now
it's mine you don't have a vested
interest anymore you know give me my
money back and like that whole
philosophy too where people sit there
and they have kids and they immediately
start saving up for their college
education I don't understand that at all
you're you're paying interest on your
mortgage
now if you knock that thing down you
have 18 years before your kid and if
your kid goes to school gives a [ __ ] get
a $30,000 loan versus a $300,000 one
that's frontend loaded on the interest
dude they are the biggest piece of [ __ ]
scumbags on the planet and they are
they're wait and they uncontrollable you
you'd have to you'd have to like
literally there have to be Bloodshed to
try to get the whole thing done that's
why I gave up because you know I it's
what would have to go down is insane to
get these guys stop you're talking about
guys who at the top get like bonuses of
10 million to $100 million bonuses
president makes 400 Grand a year the
alleged free leader leader of the free
uh world it's making 400 Grand there's
people with YouTube channels making what
Obama makes and he's supposed to keep
these guys in line
that's why I like Iceland Iceland told
them to go [ __ ] themselves it's like
like that's your debt you deal with it
the way I've always viewed it basically
is uh is that there's country clubs you
know like a country club that you join
and you know they don't want this person
or that person basically the world to me
the way I see it is just a bunch of
different country clubs and they're
playing with their toys you know 100%
agree I I just call them gangs like I
don't think you just like do you think
there's four guys running the planet no
I think there's four five 10 12 giant
groups right trying to join forces and
trying to figure I mean since the
beginning of time people have tried to
conquer the world the problem was it was
just too goddamn big and you would get
stretched out and then eventually the
you know the hillbillies came over the
hill the Huns whoever the rebels uh the
Yanks whoever they came out and they
knocked you out so I I but what's scary
to me is how they're they're ever so
slightly moving their way towards
um you there's no cash anymore so that
prevents you from stockpiling anything
in case you needed to rebel and then you
know all you know C cell phones and all
this crap are all tracking devices then
you know they already microchip dogs and
all it's going to take is that one
fraking case you know goig when it
happens where a kid gets kidnapped and
blah blah blah blah blah and and where I
would probably say that the kid get
saved and thank God and then immediately
I mean the the biggest fear any parent I
would think would have other than a
terminal disease would be that someone's
going to take their child and what's
going to happen is they're going to at
first it's going to be a bracelet and
then it's going to be like what if they
take the bracelet off and then it's just
going to be there's already corporate
guys that they got stuff they have
microchips and they SK scin I love it
too they like work for Coke it's like
what what the [ __ ] are you guys doing
there that you do you have a foreign
object in you I guess women get fake
boobs and they have plastic chemicals
like a big bag of plastic lunch bag of
chemicals under their titties which is
insane for me to do and what's going to
happen I feel is eventually like if
you're just born and it's always there
you don't question it like like federal
income tax and that type of you just
it's just it always has been so you
don't question it and I think that's
what they're going to do we'll die out
sure we just keep getting replaced and
replaced we're worker ants that are part
of a system and we just exist to help
these
no no no no but but I I believe that as
you have to have worker RS you do like
what the thing about conspiracy theory
that I don't like is I don't get so
liberal that I feel like everybody on
the bottom are these Saints and if that
they were in those positions they
wouldn't do the same thing like I don't
I don't think that either sure like
there's there's a lot of mouth breathing
morons that need to be dude I'm not
smart enough to to design a highway and
and have roads and system I mean like
this is if this is is ex like that
YouTube video about human farming and
all that if this really is you know
slavery I mean this is this is the this
is the Johnny Walker Blue top shelf of
slavery you know what I'm going to go do
right after this I'm going to go play
drums and I think tonight I'm going to
go see a movie cuz I tell jokes for a
living I'm killing it I don't want to be
running [ __ ] and I want you're not
you're are the exception too you know
that's that's not ex and also living in
this country I enjoy a level of Freedom
that is is
Indescribable but there's another thing
too like I I don't think that there you
know has to be sweat shops and all that
like I don't buy into that flossy that
if there wasn't a sweat shop that shirts
would then be 200 bucks for for a plain
T-shirt and it's just like yeah or you
could make less money I think there's
also enough shirts if there's enough
shirts that exist think they were making
shirts in this country when I was a kid
it didn't cost my mother I guess the
equivalent of 200 bucks in 1970 to
clothe her children it's complete
horseshit I think if they just sto
making shirts we could go for a good 10
years just reusing the ones we've got
you could went back to darning stockings
and churning butter yeah you know
feeling that soil must sound like Al
Gore um oh man and anybody listening I
realize that I am a [ __ ] so don't even
think that I remotely even think what's
a mouth breathing [ __ ] you said mou I
went to a Clippers uh Golden State
Warrior game the other day Stone sober I
was going through one of my twoe periods
not going to drink uh before I start to
miss it and uh and I basically in a
sober way was able to view my behavior
at games and I was appalled at myself
through these complete strangers that I
was watching I saw this this couple in
front of me and uh they were a drunk
mess it was funny they still loved each
other and every time she stood up he
started playing Bongos on her ass I mean
they were like in their 50s and at one
point at one point she was literally
feeding him nachos in the most lovingly
like lady in the [ __ ] kind of way and
stone sober watching it it was
absolutely disgusting and he kept
putting his arm around her and his elbow
kept hitting my knee and I finally had
to be like listen dude I'm not trying to
get in the way your love here but
elbowed me like 20 times in this quarter
but you're so drunk you don't know I
didn't say you're so drunk and then
immediately I'm the bad guy okay hey now
put my armor around my girl cutting down
on the love he said something like that
it's just IM meeting like that you know
that people look out their own heads
that's their view of the world like they
haven't they can't step outside
themselves enough and basically see my
point of view that's what I'm saying see
see the world how I see it well I think
it's what you were talking about earlier
just about that certain self-awareness
that you didn't even used to have that
now you have more of and I think most
people don't have it if they would just
have it when they were driving I would
appreciate it especially in the city
where there's so many cars if you could
just itch up a little bit further mhm if
you're making a right turn get over to
the right and let me sneak by and maybe
put two wheels on the other side of the
road when it's clear so I can get around
you just do me the solid get all the way
out in the intersection making a left so
that third guy can make it on this light
if you could just [ __ ] do that yeah
but you know they don't do it you know
what I think a lot of it is attributed
to like you ever try to bust balls with
people who aren't in comedy and you're
like oh I think I'm just offending them
you know yeah you got well yeah you
gotta but also where comedies what
comedies where comedians begin MH is
where a lot of uh regular d human beings
stop right but or haven't ventured I
think a lot of the regular decent human
beings aren't self-aware like that guy
at the game because he's got nobody
there to say hey buddy you're you're an
[ __ ] and he could be like yeah you
know I don't think that's a comedian
thing I just think that's who he's
surrounded with like there there are
certain people like Eggheads sometimes
get like a ketchup stain like this giant
ketchup stain but they they could
literally stand in Mirror brushing their
teeth and they don't see it because
they're already like I was going to
throw out something that I don't even
understand quantum physics I don't even
what that is that just sounds
unbelievably complex to me Chaos Theory
whatever the [ __ ] they're doing they're
doing the math on how long it's going to
take for the next uh some sort of moon
does that sound scientific I don't know
whatever they're they're so cerebral
right that they that so it's not a a uh
it's not even that people don't call
them out on their stuff it's just like
they are they're too smart to take care
of normal [ __ ] basically basically take
care of [ __ ] that's that you and I
consider important
right all right let me get back to our
guy here sorry it's easy to get on
tangents but Adam Smith All right so in
his book The Wealth of Nations Smith
states that in a free market unregulated
capitalism where everybody's trying to
maximize their own gain everybody will
benefit let's start with that you think
that's true if everybody tries to
maximize their own everybody's trying to
maximize their own gain and everybody
will benefit before I keep reading on I
like to stop uh yeah I don't see
anything wrong with that I mean I really
think our banking system is is is the
problem you know you know what makes me
this makes me I don't have a solution
though before somebody asked me I don't
have a solution so I don't know if this
is the be if this is the best it gets
then that's the way it is and uh I take
comfort in the fact that I can only die
once my brain goes to the movie you ever
see the movie Bruce Almighty that Jim
Carrey movie where he plays God oh he
played God or was it Morgan Freeman well
Morgan Freeman plays God and then lets
Jim Carrey take over as God for a little
while I saw the first three quarters on
a plane and then we landed okay I
enjoyed it though well at one point at
one point uh Jim Carrey says everybody
everybody's praying for everything he
goes everybody's wishes come true he
just doesn't want to deal with it he's
like I'll just make everybody happy and
when everybody's happy it's chaos you
know everybody who to win the lottery
they all win it but they're getting like
33 cents each like right or the people
who like you know I would love to kidnap
someone and use them as a sex slave
that's my dream like forget that
monsters out there like that that piece
of [ __ ] there in Cleveland people think
that guy took the easy way out like he
took a hell of a roll of the dice
there's no way he believed in any sort
of Afterlife with uh reward and
Punishment because if I ever did some
[ __ ] like that I would be I would go to
jail and I would take the ass raping and
I would try to get on some sort of
macrobiotic
diet and try to even with the ass rape
live as long as I could just because I
don't want to see this dude if the H if
the Hell in the Dante is Inferno I mean
I gotta be like you know well I was
talking about this with Arty Lang when I
was on Hitler at that point that this is
that story broke when I was on art show
and uh he was saying oh well you know he
if there's a if there's a hell this guy
will get it there I said he still gets
the easy way out though because he could
have had hell on Earth and then hell in
hell now he'd only get hell in hell
that's right but maybe is isn't there
something where you're sort of paying
for your
sins by at least I mean there's no way
to pay for what he
did look dude I I'm taking the the the
known hell versus you got to think
you're talking if you believe in in a
higher power like it's just like you're
not going to challenge his hell
okay what I think even prison what that
is that's like the Coors Light Of
Hell he's going to come with a single
malt that you're not even going to be
able to handle
yeah so I would be I would really be uh
or maybe I'm just too much of a coward
to kill myself um it's maybe the maybe
it's the one good thing that he did in
life where he didn't he didn't have
taxpayers maybe have to pay for uh his
bed but you know it's a horrible thing
to wish uh you know rape on somebody but
if anybody [ __ ] deserved it
mhm that you know that dude I don't know
I would have liked to
slower you know I think that's more fair
a slower death because a a quick death
you know is an easy way out to me it's
like ah you know especially if there's
no afterlife how much pain did he have
he hung himself that's pretty quick
death right you snap your neck snaps and
you're out no you can't you can't snap
your neck in a Cell what snaps your neck
is the fall uhhuh so what you're doing
there is you're kind of going out like
that guy in excess he probably was
jerking off when he did it
had one great orgasm and then just fell
asleep but like I don't know how how do
you like hang yourself if you can't tie
your arms like how do you uh you got to
will yourself not to do the natural
Jesus Christ what are we talking about
here this is crazy anyway sorry back to
Adam back to Adam Smith so so yeah so I
think if everybody is maximizing their
own gain I think it's like a Bruce
Almighty type of situation where
everybody's rich and nobody's rich
you know again I don't I don't feel that
uh I I I think that the the it should
meet more in a middle the middle I I
definitely think uh but
like I don't begrudge your wealth that
doesn't hurt somebody you know I mean if
you if you invented YouTube and you're a
billionaire I mean it's not like you
stood on the heads of poor
people um unless you have a bunch of
people in a sweat
shop writing
code um which is probably the case
anytime you see a bunch of coders
they're always in some it's why I think
when they go to put out the YouTube
t-shirts and hoodies for Christmas
that's probably going to be done in El
Salvador Honduras even the program you
ever see a programmer they look like
they're in sweat shops they're just in
some dark like uh Dungey type of place
typing true anyway uh he says uh this is
because the competition between sellers
makes for better products and lower
costs he calls this the Invisible Hand
he says that all will benefit even if
the intentions of those involved are not
good so he's saying it doesn't even
matter if you have bad intentions yeah
this sounds like this was written by a
rich guy Adam Smith uh oh this is the
philosopher yeah this is this is the
philosopher well look it's not like you
know when people go you know communism
socialism capitalism I don't really
know what any of those are I just know
that people uh they do what's good for
them and uh I don't think it matters
what kind of government you have it's
like they're
all flawed because we we are it's all
the same [ __ ] yeah it's it's I you know
when I go to Finland they try to say
that there's no rich people there they
have this thing and they don't it's
reverse Kanye West in that you don't sit
there and talk about all the [ __ ] you
have that's considered really tacky and
then you're also considered nobody's
Rich they pay an insane level of taxes
but everything's paid for mhm you know
you need a [ __ ] heart transplant
they're like all right come on in no
worries lay on the table but then the
the part about that though is the
downside to that is you know there's
definitely the upside but then the
downside is they they said that some
people can just become these lifelong
students and kind of not get on with
their lives but I immediately asked when
they said you know we don't have any
rich people here it's like well do you
have Banks here they're like yeah I'm
like well then do you have some rich
people here yeah they're just good about
I think it's I think it's a different in
mentality between going back to my
Country Club Theory I think the people
who run the country club either have one
of two different this is back to my yeah
they have one one of two different
strategies when it comes to the to the
People Like Us that that they need to
keep it going the taxpayers it's either
keep them living a long time or make
sure they die quick yeah it's a it's a
Ponzi scheme but like I but it works it
you know it doesn't and it it it I think
it it's working the best it's going
going to work and
um I don't have any solutions for like
how to make it work better I I wish that
uh that um we made more stuff here in
this country I wish that you know the
unions didn't drive didn't become what
they were fighting in some ways I wish
that the the the owners of the companies
could have figured out a way to meet in
the middle and uh and then I don't think
that we would I don't think we would
have nearly the reputation we have
around the world it's just and we kind
of let all our Aces go then we had to go
out and take everybody else's stuff it's
it's the the thing that scares me is not
that that there's people powerful people
it's that it just seems like there's a
certain level of just like it there's
never enough like when are you going to
be making enough interest when are you
going to have enough land when are you
going to have enough control and it just
seems like it's a
uh insatiable
sure because there's always somebody
else who who wants to have more land so
it's always it's never going to I don't
think it'll ever end I well I think when
you're when you're trying
to amass stuff in control it's like
empty calories it's just like you know
when you eat shitty food you're hungry
like eat Chinese food you get hungry
well our version of Chinese food when
you eat it you you you get hungry really
quickly it's because there's so little
nutrition in it but your body is still
craving nutrition and you you basically
filled up the void the hunger Pang but
like the reason why you get hungry
instantly after [ __ ] food is because
there's just's so little nutrition in it
so that's your body is still going I
need this vitamin I need this I need
this and it's I'm I'm still not getting
it so I think that's everything it's not
even just food it's all the stuff too
like people buying lots of stuff to make
them feel better but there's still that
emptiness it exists in everywhere yeah
so I don't think that that like that's
the frightening thing about it um I'm
really in way over my head this is way
deeper than
you know and everybody out there all all
of my philosophies two or three
follow-up questions they all come
crumbling to
Earth how how has your relationship to
money changed since you're now making
money um I try
to I try to remain debt free so um
there's no 401K for a comedian so I try
and I I'm not into the stock market I'm
not into to Banks mhm I mean I play the
game sort of required to put a certain
amount into the 401K and then I just put
it on the crap table right um but my
philosophy when when I was investing was
like all right I want to invest in
companies that are getting tangible
stuff like that whole pets.com crap like
I never Bond into that but if like you
were like if you had a gold mine and you
were digging for gold or you you know
you you some sort of Agriculture it just
seemed like it was a you could you know
whatever it was something real it wasn't
in the air or philosophy but then after
a while I just was kind of going all
right so I'm investing in this we'll
just say the gold you know uh the minor
thing right company I'm like at the end
of it I don't get any gold so this is
stupid so then I was wanted to have
something tangible so like to me it was
obvious it's like buy a house so I
bought a house and then I'm just I've
just paid it down like an absolute
Madman
and
um you know it's very sparsely
furnished um and but like the freedom I
have of you know not having credit card
debt because I've lived like that and
had it hanging over my head and it used
to wake me up at night and it was awful
and people would call and where's our
money and all that and I I hated it and
something my brother told me a long time
ago he goes you know what we were
working at the same place we look
looking out over this sea of cubicles
and he was just breaking it down like
all these guys like would working in the
warehouse and then then they would get a
position I want a position and then they
would move out to the carpeted cubicle
area and theyd buy their little you know
shirt and tie and my brother would be
like what's the first thing that they do
and I was like you know what and he goes
they go out and they buy a new car and
it's like now you just change yourself
to your desk you can't you can't leave
and then he goes and then also the
average [ __ ] gets a dollar an hour
raise and they immediately start
spending $2 more an hour so they're just
constantly chasing it and you're just
behind the eightball I mean you're just
completely [ __ ] you know if nobody
teaches you those things or tells you
those things it's like through student
loans and a couple of credit cards and
getting yourself some Transportation you
like these kids today are so far behind
the eight ball like like the amount of
money that they they charge for college
to go into this job market with no
guarantee of any sort of a job it's a
[ __ ] ripoff like had a kid I'd be
like look this is the way to do it go
two years to a junior college you know
pay a you know a couple thousand for the
year rather than 30 40 50 or whatever
and then
transfer to the place that you want to
have on your diploma and only pay two
years you get it for half cost right
there and you're you're better off to
like I think you're just even better off
just going to vocational school you know
you're better off meeting a bunch of
smart motivated people your age that
share a vision and you guys try to start
something yeah you're you're you're
better off doing that than going two
years of a language major in this you
know being in intern here um not totally
[ __ ] on I'm not trying to depress
anybody that's that's on that track but
like I have empathy for that but anyway
so I did that and I resent it I think it
was it was just a terrible waste of my
money it was right my brother also told
me a great thing because he's always
been great with money and he said you
know what true wealth is it said is
going into a mall being able to buy
anything and then you don't
and you just walk out and like those are
the like the lessons that you know stuck
with me it's why I drive a Prius I mean
part of it the reason why I did the
Prius is because I fly every other
weekend I've literally put my own hole
in the ozone layer so I had to do
something and I saw enough people in
these flashy cars you know you got a car
that can go 180 M an hour and you're in
bumper-to-bumper traffic with me so um I
would
rather you know I have one TV people
always give me [ __ ] it's not big enough
for my living room cuz it's the one that
I had when I had a one bedroom apartment
but it's it's paid for and it it [ __ ]
works what am I supposed to do throw it
out
so like those are those are the things
like you know but because I've done that
like today I don't have to work I can go
play drums and go see a movie yeah and
if you're if you're young and you're
listening to this I implore you to go
down that road because if you could tell
from the last hour I am not the
brightest guy
I am not a well- read guy I went after a
passion but you you can have that life
like dude having a life like living as
debt free as you can being able to go to
the movies whenever you want to is about
as free as it gets unless you get to
that Eyes Wide Shut level where you're
going to the Cloak and Dagger move you
know like it's really it's as close to a
[ __ ]
Utopia as you can get to right yeah so
then I do all this geeky [ __ ] like learn
how to make pasta from scratch learn how
to cook learn you know drums I play
hockey it's a [ __ ] my life is a [ __ ]
joke like I just feel like if there is a
higher power they're looking down either
laughing or just shaking their head like
what a this kid isn't doing anything I
think I think the ultimate goal of every
adult is how do you get back to being a
kid you know which is like you know
playing drums and seeing movies and
don't listen I remember when when I when
I was first I was just going to get into
radio and I remember I went to the meat
store went to the butcher with my mom
and uh she mentioned you know he's like
he's like so what is your son doing you
know blah blah doing that whole thing
and I was just was mentioning that you
know I was Major in communication I
wanted to get in radio and the guy was
like you know I don't know I remember he
turned around he's like everybody wants
to be the star like walking away and I'm
just looking at this guy with his bloody
apron talking to me like he had the keys
to true happiness now he might he might
have I mean that was owned by their
brothers and they work side by side they
saw each other and they cut up pork
chops all day maybe they that was their
maybe that was their dream but like I
don't think that he found his dream in
life because he was [ __ ] on mine and
I don't think a truly happy person does
that or he could have been truly happy
and was so drunk with his happiness he
couldn't figure out why I didn't want to
jump over the counter I think he was
just put on a bloody apron and cut up ve
with him yeah I think he's probably just
jealous in other words like if that
works out for you and if doesn't work
out like I took it I took it as a Towny
bar comment yeah hey don't forget where
you came
from matter what you accomplish you know
better than me you're right here like
that those and those for more young
people listening or you know any person
listening like those are the people you
need to cut out of your life yeah like
the beginning of a cancer where you
catch it in time you got to catch it in
time or those [ __ ] people I swear to
God if they're in your ear they could
literally like I have a I have a
philosophy that the the the next Jimmy
Hendricks you know hasn't come because
maybe he's surrounded by the wrong
people and is driving a forklift at Home
Depot it's probably true yeah you know
yeah they're don't it's stupid it's a
dumb dream keep keep your mind on down
and get real job um all right so we
usually uh wrap the show up with these
quotes and I ask the guest to read them
we go through them and that's how I end
it beautiful all right so I read the
first quote here right yeah wherever
there is great property there is great
inequality um I think it depends on your
definition of inequality I think back in
the 1700s where you couldn't start a
YouTube channel yeah and you couldn't be
a bunch of college kids doing bong hits
yeah watching TV not like that's the the
road to success but you're still kind of
like I don't think that they had Rich
the same kinds of rich people that they
do nowadays where you could have like
these fun sort of people like the Mark
Cubans you know and uh the people who
just you know although that dude who
starts started the Facebook I'm judging
him by the movie he sounded he seemed
pretty miserable so I I think I think um
blue blood blue blood wealth caused a
lot of misery yeah so this is no long
I'm basing that off a couple things I
read and uh There Will Be Blood movie
so this is just basically talking about
physical property and now you're saying
there's other kinds of property
intellectual property tell you when I
watched those meum autumn Auto shows
where they auction off like up for bids
you know this rare Ferrari or this
Shelby Mustang and like these people
just spend a million dollars on a car
add of their collection I it does like
why isn't that guy immediately being
audited right like how much you know how
much money you have to have that your
wife isn't going to [ __ ] that you just
dropped you know a million dollars dude
that there's one Ferrari that in from
the early 60s that's like the one that
everybody wants I mean it's selling for
like 12 million 13 million it's
basically it's getting up there to like
Derek Jeter's salary for the year you
know is the same it's insane it's insane
so um I definitely look but you know
just coming from more of an artistic way
I'm living my life you know the way they
look at us like we're bums who don't
work which is a lot of Truth to that I
look at them like you know you know how
many heads did you step on to get where
you're at so I I I still think there's
some truth in that but I I I don't think
it's straight across the board sorry
Adam all right let's move on to the you
got the next one there people okay
people of the same trade seldom meet
together even for mert and diversion but
the conversation ends in in a conspiracy
against the public or in some
contrivance to raise prices I got to
read that like 12 times I think he's
saying that people in the same trade
seldom meet together to have a good time
and just take their mind off work but
they actually have a
conversation that ends in conspir iracy
against the public or in some
contrivance to raise prices like when
people like two people get together
going you know how's business how's it
going he you know you know what we could
do hey dude if I say pork chops are this
and you say they're that we can make
this I think that that's what he's
saying um well we did wind up sitting
together and talking conspiracy so that
part was true right but we didn't
conspire against anybody well this is
once again these are a little dated I
don't think back then yeah that she got
away from the wife and then they brought
in some hookers and stuff yeah yeah I
think he's talking about like you know
the Rothchild type of people they'll get
together and they'll conspire you and I
are just going to I just don't think
there was as many fun trades back then
yeah you know what I mean I mean you
couldn't like go on the road get on a
horse and go do some comedy shows so I
think I think Adam is a great
philosopher but he's uh his stuff is a
has Isn't standing the test of time okay
um we got one more here it is not from
the benevolence I actually looked up
that word the the day benevolence it
just means that you're doing something
for an overall good yeah common good I
think I already forget it's not from the
benevolence of the butcher the Brewer or
the baker that we expect our dinner but
from their regard to their own
self-interest we address ourselves not
to their Humanity but to their self-love
and never talk to them of our own
Necessities but of their advantages
Jesus Christ never slow it down here all
right right it is not from the
benevolence of the butcher the Brewer or
the baker that we expect our dinner so
in other words these guys aren't doing
it to be nice to us they're doing it cuz
they're making money right I think but
from the guard of their own
self-interest which is basically they're
trying to make money off of being this
mhm we address ourselves not to their
Humanity but to their
self-love well what does that mean they
don't want to die so they have to make
money being a baker right and never talk
to them of our own Necessities you know
my dad would never listen to me
can I get some rye I guess they're
saying you never go talk to that butcher
the guy who was telling you forget about
being a radio guy you wouldn't even be
there if you didn't need meat and he
wouldn't even be there if he didn't need
money or does that mean and never talk
to them of our own Necessities but of
their advantages were like maybe I
wanted this kind of meat MH or I needed
it at this price but he sets the prices
I I guess this guy wanted a a deeper
relationship during those little moments
of uh all right who who's next yeah can
I get a pound of
hamburger and he just turns his back see
that's all he cares about all he cares
about them this guy's like this guy I
swear to God I really hope this isn't
true but I could see a really beautiful
funloving woman walking into his life uh
him ruining it for a good well they
didn't have three-year relationships
back then for a good couple of weeks and
then her just hopefully having the sense
to pick up her giant dresses and walk
the [ __ ] out of this guy's life
bit of miserable bastard yeah so I think
that this guy is uh I can relate to him
oh man uh well if you want to read more
of his stuff he also published the
theory of moral sentiments and uh I
actually really enjoyed all of those
quotes it was really deep and it was
beyond me yeah beyond beyond my
intelligence that's what I like about
this stuff it's like I just try and
figure something out that I didn't have
before and sometimes well this what I
like about this guy is this guy isn't
just walking down the street he's kind
of like you know looking at just the
white why people are talking and this
and this sort of uh thought it can
really lead to some massive growth as a
person and massive depression I think
that last quote by the way just you know
my mom is I don't know if you know my
mom is Scottish but oh she that last
quote just sounded very Scottish just I
just I remember talking to you about
that when we were in Scotland you saying
like you loved it out here and I just
remember that well now that you brought
it up now I remember that's just a very
like just Scottish people especially
Glasgow people just go around
complaining did you see that did you see
that he didn't spend he doesn't care
about me all he cares about himself all
he cares about his stupid meat business
I that's a good it's good Scottish
access I remember what the [ __ ] a
[ __ ] podcast you're scared wearing
[ __ ] that's what I get when I go over
there something like that so well listen
thank you for having me this great for
doing this bill this was great I've done
a lot of them man this is definitely uh
in the upper 10% dude this is this is a
fun podcast I'll come on again thank you
very much sound good all right thank you
buddy all right that's our show I hope
you enjoyed it as much as I did hope you
all had a great Thanksgiving hope your
lives are going well I'd love to hear
from you as always at the comical
yahoo.com also if you're interested in
sponsoring an episode that's another
thing you could do with that email
address you could also email me and say
hey I'd like to sponsor an episode and
I'll say sure okay okay and we'll work
it out it's not that expensive it really
isn't so email me atth comical yahoo.com
even if it's to say hi or if it's to say
what you thought of the show or anything
send me an email I'd love to hear from
you also go on iTunes leave me five
stars and a nice review that would help
a lot that's a nice holiday gift you can
give me it is still kanuka folks that's
right I use the kanaka go on there and
leave me a nice review please I could I
could use it go on iTunes help me out
five star s hook it up please uh
anything else is there something else
the Facebook page
facebook.com/ modernday philosophers go
on there check out pictures of me and
Bill Burr from this interview and bunch
of other pictures from different
interviews and links to the philosophers
and quotes that we studied and all sorts
of fun stuff up at
facebook.com/ modernday
philosophers I think that's about it for
now everybody and I appreciate you
listening and I'll see you next Monday
okay okay have a good week bye