hello everybody and welcome to another
exciting episode of modern day
philosophers Today's Show is brought to
you by pod awful pod awul is a New York
City Podcast brought to you by my friend
Jesse PS Jesse describes the show as
imagination terrorism it's now in its
fourth year on the air and Jesse's been
through all kinds of stuff that no other
podcaster has ever had to deal with his
girlfriend has called into the show to
break up with him he was arrested live
on the air he even had the Secret
Service investigate him over content
from his show not a joke but all very
funny PO awful.com is where you can find
every episode of the podcast including
shows with prank calls to Craigslist
weirdos an interview with Andrew WK and
even me Danny LEL co-hosting pot aul is
also live every Sunday night at 800m
Eastern Standard Time pod
a.tv there is a live video stream a chat
room and you can call into the show
Sundays 8:00 pm again Eastern Standard
Time pod
a.tv check it out now let me say a word
or two about
PS Jesse insisted on sponsoring an
episode I would have gladly plugged his
podcast for free but he's trying to help
me out and he's a just a good dude
that's the kind of guy Jesse PS is and
he really really does deserve you to go
check out what he's doing because he's a
mad comedy genius who just I I think
this is all he does I think all he does
is the podcast and he's just cooped up
in his apartment in New York and I think
he's attached to a urine bag cuz he
broke his penis or something at some
point and I think just everything
everything kind of goes wrong for him
but he just turns it into hilarious
comedy which is some of the best comedy
is the stuff that comes out of tragedy
so check out Jesse PS he's a very very
funny good and genuine
guy um now on a on a different note
speaking of tragedy I have a friend of
mine who's very very close to my heart
and I I'll get into that maybe with you
another episode but she's somebody who's
very very special to me and she's very
sick in fact she's in the Intensive Care
Unit at Columbia
hospital and she needs all the help she
can get in terms of those of you who
pray those of you who meditate those of
you who hum or those of you who send
Good Vibes please do it please send them
her way
because she's just somebody who's very
very special to me and I would
appreciate it her name is ITA so if you
can pray for ITA
or or meditate or like I said whatever
it is you do do it because I'd
appreciate it and I know she'd
appreciate it and maybe I'll get into
that with you another time but for now I
want to take you to my oh wait one more
thing almost forgot there's a website up
for the podcast now and you can visit it
for free why wouldn't it be for free
www.mm modernday philosophers. net
that's the website and it's got the
links to everything everything else that
I usually take a lot of time plugging so
it's all in one spot now modernday
philosophers. net you can donate to this
show if you feel so inclined help the
cause send a donation or send an email
to the comical yahoo.com and just say hi
now without keeping you waiting much
longer I'm going to tell you LS black
and I recorded this interview in his
hotel room in Las Vegas before he was
doing shows he's been a wonderful guy to
me for years he continues to be and and
I really had a thrill doing it we
recorded a few weeks ago so if you hear
us referencing that Thanksgiving is
coming up and you're thinking well
Thanksgiving just passed well that
explains it I don't think I need to
explain that to you but I thought I I
thought I'd do it anyway just to be
nice just to put it in some
context so there you have it folks
without
further Ado except again the intro song
my talk with Louis black hope you enjoy
it hello and welcome to Moder day
philosophers modern day philosophers
having failed to pay attention in school
Danny LEL now older and wiser will
attempt to learn basic philosophy 101
our young hero will be joined by today's
top comedians philosophers all their own
ladies and gentlemen here's Danny
LEL
[Applause]
CR all right I am here with one of my
favorite comedians who I've had the
uh Good Fortune of getting to know over
the years a little bit Lewis Black how
are you better every day CU can't
couldn't
be that's a surprising surprising
response from you yeah well it's
sarcastic but still yes it's very
sarcasm yeah still didn't expect it leis
the philosopher that Alex picked out for
us to go through today is someone named
William James have you ever heard of him
wow yeah I have but I don't remember do
thing about him you're you're somebody
who's pretty I I think is pretty
academic right you've well no I went to
school I doesn't make me like you
absorbed it no I did well I I know who
William James is I don't remember what
anything about William James I kind of
know you know I studied I I took one
course in philosophy in college you know
the fact that you were once a playwright
to me puts you like on a whole another
intellectual playing field than me just
just the word playright it just meant I
didn't want to make any money that was
the reason I was a playright I was but
it's it's I wanted to see what it was
like to live at the bottom line of uh of
income still be doing something right
it's like a cultural Pursuit though like
nobody there's no like pop I guess maybe
there are pop playwrights but it's just
not something no not a lot of people do
it I mean there a bunch of people who do
it now I mean and then go on and write
for film and television mainly all right
so I'm I'm making assumptions about you
that might not be correct the reason why
Alex picked him he said that he read
somewhere and and I'll verify this with
you now that you believe in psychics to
some extent is that to some extent I
mean I believe in there's one psychic I
know that uh I think is pretty
extraordinary but I wouldn't say I'm
like a a boy all psychics you know the
woman on the Long Island site K I don't
think I'm buying uh the guy the other
guy who had the show every day at the
same time as dror Phil I don't think I
was I'm not buying a lot of them right
but I do buy um uh this friend of mine
Michael Bodin yeah so you really you
really believe he's legit is he a
psychic medum this is how yeah this I
mean legit uh I mean for me yeah um and
for some other I mean he will
say uh he told a friend of mine before
anybody there's no way he could know who
I was
none um I had no career and I it you
might have stumbled onto me but you
wouldn't know that uh I'm a friend of
this uh comic he wouldn't have known
that um and he was talking to her and he
said you have to stop worrying about uh
you know your friend leis black because
uh he um he's going to be doing really
well and things are going to go great
for him and he went on and on and on uh
without ever meeting me so I went to
meet him and then he uh knew nothing
about me there's no way to know that my
brother was sick and uh and uh at that
point in time and he knew it and he knew
a whole bunch of other things that he
you couldn't have researched you just
couldn't have researched and then it you
know and then even from that it was uh I
would be at a point where something uh
you know either was doing excessive
amount of work or something crazy was
going on and he would call
up
um and say uh you know and basically
describe the situation I was in what
what do you think you can attribute it
to some he says that he talks to dead
people so and it but it's that's the way
he puts it simply and uh uh he's um uh
written a book about it and uh I even I
wrote the intro to the book because I
think I mean it's he uh I think it's
called growing up psychic and um he
attributes it to
um I don't I I mean I don't know what he
I mean I don't know what to attribute it
to but there apparently is uh there's
something out there does this
information change your perspective on
life when you found out that someone
possibly could talk to the dead did you
make you reeval valuate yeah a little it
certainly did where were you before that
and where are you now well I mean I
always thought anything was possible I
think it's kind of ludicrous to sit
around and go you know that's a bunch of
nonsense when you know when look if you
you look at a rose really and that where
do you [ __ ] think that came from mhm
I mean I wasn't like uh I I didn't have
a lot of uh religious belief um or I had
but I certainly had a slight inkling
toward something that was bigger going
on because
it's it's really you know either that or
a petri dish you know and uh and you
know and things just growing in the dish
and uh so it it kind of uh open my eyes
to to certain possibilities and
um and I I experienced the death of my
brother was pretty uh I mean my brother
died and I felt him in the room I'm not
one of those people who does that mhm I
you know I came in and I was trying to
save him and then I realized that I'm
not save him I was told that I had to
give him a mouth-to-mouth
resuscitation uh and uh they his wife
hadn't done it and I came in and there
was no way he was going to do anything
but it was weird because a I knew that
if I had that weird moment I knew if I
brought him back he he'd been very sick
if I brought him back he'd be pissed
because it would be like really we're
going to we're going to have to do this
again yeah um and the other thing was is
but then uh but when I entered the room
I mean when I was doing this and
afterward I felt that he was there now
you know you can say it's conjured and
da D but I felt his presence for a while
and weird things happened afterwards and
and it's not uh to me a a Confluence of
events it was uh doors that hadn't been
opened open
and there was no reason that they hadn't
been open two [ __ ] years before that
M or four years before that stuff just
started to happen and it was a little
strange I've never had an experience
where I felt the presence and i' I'm
kind of like one of these guys I want it
you know like I'm like come on I want uh
I want that kind of thing to happen but
can you can you describe it for me like
what it would be like or what it was
like for you you mean having feeling the
presence feeling his presence I mean
it's just like a weird sense of him it's
uh it was just the sense of him it's as
if he were there it's it's like if if if
you're sitting in a room with six people
mhm uh and you know everybody that's
there and you're talking to one of the
people in the room but you're still
conscious of the others uh it was like
being conscious of his presence just
that he would not that I could turn to
him and talk to himh and not that I had
the experience of him ever saying you
know this but uh uh or that or the other
but my you know I had the sense of him
being in the room and I didn't and I I
experienced that for a while I'll tell
you my one quick story about a psychic
medium yeah I was at Joe Frank have you
ever been to Joe Franklin's
office I I I I think I have been there I
know I I mean I did his show once so I
may have been in that office I I I was
in Joe Franklin Joe Franklin's office is
kind of like Broadway Danny Rose's
office you know yeah I know it's just
full of interesting acts eclectic uh
vaud villian type performers and one
time I was in there
and I want to introduce you this guy
over here he goes this guy Dan L Bell
world class comedian world class you're
gonna love him he goes and this guy is a
psychic medium the best of the best from
England you know so you two should talk
so I I I I being a skeptic I I said you
I don't really I don't know to and the
guy goes oh he goes he goes oh you're a
comedian like Joe say yeah he goes you
going to be massive massive big star I
go well will I be bigger than I don't
remember who I I mentioned somebody he
goes yes much bigger than him I go well
what about this guy he goes much bigger
than him I go will I be bigger than
Rodney
Dangerfield and he goes who's Rodney
Dangerfield I and then I was like ah you
don't even know who Rodney dfield you
shouldn't be telling me I'm gonna so so
we googled Rodney dfield yes you're
gonna be bigger
than so I said uh I said okay do me a
favor when I was a kid
my great grandma used to make me these
banana cakes I lived in New York in like
apartment tenaments and queens with my
grandparents and my parents my great
grandma we all lived in the same uh
complex and I used to get dropped off
that she'd babysit me and she'd make me
these banana cakes and they were like
nothing I've been chasing that high you
know my whole life since she passed away
I've been trying every banana cake
that's why I'm fat people don't know
that but uh I've just been trying every
banana cake and uh I could never find
one like it I said can you get me the
recipe from her and I'll try it and I'll
go home I'll make the cake if it tastes
like my memory of what her cake tastes
like then I know you're legit he goes
okay so he starts talking to her what's
her name I said Anna okay Anna I've got
Anna here and I'm talking to her and
she's saying what's that love three no
four bananas and I'm writing it all down
dash of vanilla you know it's not
exact brown sugar and I'm writing down
the whole thing I'm so excited I get on
the subway I get out and Brooklyn I I I
go right right home I empty my pockets
out I'm going to get the ingredients out
and then figure out what I need and what
I have in the house and go pick it up
and the paper is gone and I I
immediately I go back to Joe Franklin's
office the next day I go where's the guy
he goes what what guy what I said there
was a psychic here yesterday you introd
I don't remember who comes in and out of
this
office I said you said he was the best
in the world I say that about everybody
you certainly did he would have the show
I was on it was like and she's a
wonderful
shant her songs have been heard she she
sang on cruise ships
leis okay whatever we're doing I mean
not that I was anywhere at the time but
it was always like wow we are really
here it's like the uh you know we're
just sitting here at the very end of the
line you it was it was fun though it was
fun to watch it was it was really wacky
God yeah he's an interesting piece of
Show Business yeah he really is
all right so let's find out about our
guy here William James uh William James
asserted that he had free will because
he had the ability to believe in
it secondly he said that determinists
those who believe the future is
determined completely by uh causality of
the past are wrong because they look at
everything in hindsight James uses his
definity Avenue and Oxford Street
example a two- Choice decision-making
process one being presented with chance
to making decisions based on that chance
thus showing how your free will gives
consent to make the chance into reality
I guess he's just I think what he's
saying is Well basically I mean
something you know you got you know it's
that thing you look at a store window do
you want to go in and I'm just saying it
because of Oxford Street but you look at
a store window and there's a a shirt in
there you might want to buy so you make
or you could continue walking down to
have lunch MH so you going to have the
lunch you going you know so that by
chance you see this thing or whatever
this and you go oh I'm going to go in
there MH uh hence you you know it's you
know do you have the you you've made the
Free Will choice to go in there thereby
thereby You' have you know since you've
made that choice you have free will well
I mean that all works well and good
unless it's you know unless it's all
predetermined right and and the and the
shirt was you know you were supposed to
go get the shirt because that's the and
I I kind of you know I you know I just
think if the problem with the you know I
mean they the thing with philosophers
which is really you know which is why I
couldn't do it is this this this you
know the basically the argument is if we
do a and if if a is true what about b b
is true what about c c and then then you
get somebody arguing well you know a may
not be true because right you know and
so therefore your be is a piece of [ __ ]
and they fight over this stuff all the
time to me it's mainly a matter of uh
you know if it's determined then then
then what [ __ ] fun is this right you
know if it's the you know it's um I
don't know uh so I mean to me it's just
a matter of if I want to really en enjoy
it a little
more then I have to believe I'm choosing
something that I'm actually involved in
it right you know well I think he's
talking a little bit about Randomness in
the UN Universe mixed with you know yeah
uh things that are predetermined right
so you get a 50/50 there it's like it's
half fun and it's and it's half out of
your hands yeah it's half out of your
hands well because there's some you know
who knows do you ever look at an
audience before you go on stage and you
you already know this is going to be a
good audience this is going to be a
shitty audience um no because I learned
a long time ago you can't you can't fig
I mean if you looked at my audiences now
a lot of places I go to you'd say really
these guys are going to laugh I mean
there's the mix is crazy I mean it goes
from people wearing suits to people
wearing overalls to people wearing you
know uh you know people who have um you
know uh piercings everywhere to people
who are uh you know to 14y olds so I
don't determine it anymore you know I
mean it's only I the only time I think
it gets when you have a mix you're fine
it's at least is far as I've always been
concerned if you've got one group of
people let's say all Jews all Catholics
all all people who work for Quaker roach
you're you're semi
[ __ ] why is that why do you think well
because because I agree with that but I
don't know why that is well corporate
stuff it's always because they're
looking around and the same thing if you
get a whole bunch of Jews in the room
you know or a whole bunch of Catholics
or whatever that they're it's
homogeneous so there's no bounce to the
room I think you're better off with a
whole bunch of Catholics if you're a
Jewish performer yes you know because if
you're if you're a Jew I think there's
always an attitude of like ah we're all
the same I could be doing this right
yeah exactly but except I did do one
Temple once and uh sorry it worked I did
a temple once and it worked it went
pretty well and I was surprised it did I
that's why I never want to get like into
the Jewish scene of the the Jewish
comedy scene like there's gigs there for
me and I could make money and it I'd be
better off but then there's like this
part of me that's like I think that's
part of one of the one of the waiting
rooms to hell is playing synagogues well
you just do a few remember do one or two
to just keep the the cash flow going
yeah yeah I think the other Wai need to
make it a way of life but you can
certainly use it as a you know an option
I've avoided it this long and now I
think it's time to cave in and start
doing
a but uh yeah I think that's uh you know
also I've I've talked about this on one
of the other shows when I'd go up for
auditions like a standup audition is a
weird thing when cuz you're at you're
asking for a Randomness to work in a way
you know I I'm I have a pretty good
record when I go on stage of doing very
well at this point but uh I don't know
you know nothing you never know yeah so
I used
to really fret about this and then I
realized yeah I'm just going to do the
best I can do and then the rest is up to
the universe that's well it's up to the
drunken guy who owns the club or the the
18 people in the audience the 50 or the
hundred and you know there's just too
many factors you can't control well you
can't control it's anytime you audition
for anything yeah it's uh it's you know
and and who's the you know who who might
be who the other Comics are there's all
sorts of stuff that comes into play in
terms of that in in uh in any audition
whether it be that or if you're going
into a room to audition for a role in
something and it and it has nothing to
do and a lot of the times it has nothing
to do with with your talent or or not
um this is off topic and this is a
little bit of add kicking in yeah sure I
don't have a problem with ADD cool I'm
I'm curious about when you're on stage
how present are you in your head with
because sometimes we go into autopilot
with our material you know are you do
you does your mind wander ever when
you're on stage my mind um will wander a
little on stage but uh mostly
if most of the time I have to say that
uh I it really is trying to figure stuff
either that why something didn't work
why it could work better what it is that
I should be doing down the line what the
but part of it is is and especially as
I've grown older what the [ __ ] is coming
next MH yeah you know it's like we got
through this and then we have what do we
[ __ ] have next right and then I'm
like doing two or three lines where I
basically I'm talking to them but my
brain is I do that too you yeah just
just the what's next yeah just want the
Q cards up there yeah really but I never
do the other thing you said which is
editing as it as you go yeah but that's
where I write on stage so that's a lot
of that has got to do with that did you
always do that or did you have to reach
a certain point of comfortability no I
just had always done it I always felt um
I always it was the way I I found I mean
I wrote stuff down initially I wrote
some of the stuff down I'd even read it
I didn't care I wasn't working in comedy
club so I didn't give a [ __ ] no there
was no rules I was just doing it for
friends and I was working out of
theaters that I can get my hands on and
invite people to come and not really
make any money and just do it for a kick
and uh so I could keep writing because
the playwriting you didn't get plays up
so this was a way I could write stuff
and and get it out there so uh and it
was but mostly uh it was then I just
pick topics I wanted to or have like um
like tonight uh it's um what did I read
today that uh uh you know they're doing
this um there's the uh you know Obama
finally apologizes today that you might
not be able to get your your shitty
policy I mean in seriously that's what
he you know it's like you know cu the
whole thing is is you're going to keep
your policy and he made that big you
know idiot makes the stupid statement
and it is and so but to me it was so
they come back with this stuff and to me
it was like well you know and so I
started thinking well now you you know
uh um who likes their
policy who the [ __ ] unless you've got a
you know a gold card policy who the [ __ ]
likes their policy it's a piece of [ __ ]
yeah I have what supposed to be a good
policy and in the end it's a shitty
policy so I start thinking about that
and then I'll kind of roll it out on
stage and I'll see where that goes and
um and it's a part of a thing I already
have that I've been talking about so
that's how it kind of works for me now
but then I would literally just go okay
here's an article in the paper and I
just start talking about it I was always
amazed like George Carlin said he he
wrote every single word was planned and
like nothing was improvised yeah I was
just I I can I can't imagine doing that
that's so precise it's such yeah and I
think Jerry does That Seinfeld there's a
number of people who do that and it's I
get it I mean I wish in a lot of ways I
wish I could do it that way um why cuz I
I like to write but but whoever is on
you know I I find it hard outside of
sitting around and thinking about it I
find it hard to write it down I find it
easier to write it on stage and I've
been reinfor part of it is is I've been
reinforced by audiences to to you know I
mean they seem to come to want to see me
yeah be spontaneous so yeah and it may
and it and a lot of it is you know the
other thing is is by the time I would do
a special 90% of what they're going to
see that night night I've worked on for
a year and a half it's written I might I
could write it down right right by the
time I get to the end of the line I
always wonder if I if I transcripted
everything that I already said and
looked through it would I would I find
further edits do you ever think about
that like um I mean not really I don't
because the audience edits
for me so I once uh interned at the coar
report and I and one of my jobs was to
write everything Steve said transcribe
all the tapes and I used to get so mad
at him for saying unnecessary things I'd
be sitting you don't need to say all
that to get to the point you know
because I didn't want to type it
all I often wonder how much of what we
say we don't even need to say maybe I
don't even need to say
this all right let me get focused again
back to our guy uh a little more
background on him then we'll jump into
the quotes and uh he was uh he lived
from January 11th I'll be specific 1842
to August 26th
1910 he was an American philosopher
psychologist he was trained physician
that's a lot it's a lot of peas yeah
yeah uh yeah but back then you to be a
trained physician you'd only had to use
a Band-Aid and
Stu you just let the guy he's he's got
you get the he gets what are those
things called the uh the the the the
things you uh where they they they suck
the blood out of you those uh leeches
leeches yeah you had leeches you had
stuff like
that took two weeks to get a degree yeah
all right I could have been a doctor
then too yeah um he was uh the first
educator to offer a psychology course in
the United
States wow James is one of the leading
thinkers of the late 19th century is
believed by many to be one of the most
influential philosophers the United
States has ever produced probably uh
While others have labeled him the father
of American
psychology along with Charles Sanders
Pierce and John Dewey he's considered to
be one of the greatest figures
associated with the philosophical School
known as pragmatism and is also cited as
one of the founders of the functional of
the functional psychology he is I wonder
if that's a typo of the functional
psychology or just functional probably I
I don't know it's functional psychology
one of those wasted
words he also developed the opposed to a
functional Psychology was different
movement this is like you know he want
he wanted to be known as the
the uh he also developed the
philosophical perspective known as
radical empiricism I don't know what
that is do you know what that is I just
know I've heard it before I don't it
would I would fail the test now but then
I got it right I'll I'll Google it later
yeah James is work has influenced
intellectual Giants I don't even know
who radical empir so empirical is
taking
uh empirical evidence I think it's I
don't [ __ ] know it's it would take my
brain too long to compute to a
guess it's
uh I don't know if I mean it sounds like
take a shot at it I'm looking at
something I'm going to take a guess but
I don't that's really what I've just
done what I've done is radical imperal
empiricism all right well well well done
then yeah really I just did it I I gave
you a demonstration of what I thought
might be radical
empirical radical imperialism I know
what that
is um so lastly on him on James James
wrote widely on many topics including
epistemology education emology is what
the woman has after she has a baby is it
no I really don't know what it actually
otomy but what is epistemology um I
think it's the origin of words I think
[ __ ] this is just showing my
ignorance it's good let's get through
this whole thing and then people stop
saying I'm so [ __ ] smart I believe
that's what it is in part and I probably
another part of the definition I believe
the joke you know so I I come off worse
if anything so um metaphysics psychology
religion and mysticism mysticism I guess
is the psychic connection there yeah I
think he felt you know and these guys
who start doing it I mean young was in a
sense partly I mean the difference
between Freud and young was just that
Freud was uh you know it's id liido id
ego liido that stuff you know you break
the thing down you know it's your mother
did this your father did that but your
young kind of believed in dreams and the
whole other thing that's that's kind of
where James was in part uh not so much
in the dream thing but that there
something else going on you think
there's anything to dreams more than
it's just uh because I've asked other
guests this I'm curious what your
opinion is is it just a bunch of junk
that you pick up during the day or do
you think there's more to dreams than
that no I think there's more to it I
think uh I think that
uh um your brain is trying to tell you
something you know I mean I've gotten
stuff from my dreams you know I I have a
shrink who's really good who's uh and uh
I wouldn't have thought it about dreams
but we've talked about some stuff and uh
and I don't dream a lot I of dreaming
more now I I was taking chantex the
anti-m smoking drug because it would
give you wild dreams I thought wow they
were all going oh you know it gives you
really bad dreams well yeah i' like
something at night cuz really I was not
having in and I've had a a number
recently and a lot of it has to do with
whatever you know um the reasoning
behind it but uh but I would talk to her
about it and I found found um and my and
my friends and I my brother
actually uh well what I found with her
was is that um you know there is some
sort of uh when oh
that's you know as opposed to uh [ __ ]
why am I doing this and I'm going
through the what I did during the day
and why did I make those choices and
then I go here's what I dreamt oh and
then she goes well because of this this
and this well that's why I [ __ ] did
that so there is this there is a I
believe a connection um my brother used
to uh my brother used to be able to
there people who can do this control
those dreams yeah I've heard about that
yeah I wish I could do that yeah no I
mean so do I but I'm not I have that
sense of I think everybody's got that
sense of um you're in the middle of the
dream you go really this is my piece of
[ __ ] dream and you wake
up um but I also had uh I have a friend
of mine who's really out further out I I
know a lot of people who kind of dabble
and crazier
[ __ ] um
and I have a friend of mine who's always
kind of been out there and he went to a
place called the Monroe
Institute and uh the guy there was
experiencing out of body
experiences and um he and you know look
you start sper you know I mean there's
enough people that happens to that you
can't say you can't dismiss it you know
and and before there was like okay
that's
crazy um he said [ __ ] you know he was he
had [ __ ] you money so he was a big
industrialist or he he did something he
was an
entrepreneur made a lot of money and he
said okay [ __ ] this I'm going to pursue
this and came up with a uh a kind of a
hum that would send you out of yourself
in a sense and uh and my friend has come
back with stories that are just
astonishing I mean [ __ ] unbelievable
that I would not and and
um uh and and they're not it's not
there's no reason not to uh you know
believe it I mean that you know you know
you don't kind of nobody nobody except
for someone you know there's of course
there people who like you know you want
to have quackery work on some levels you
know you want to you know you pursue
a a medicine that you know is nonsense
because you think it's you know it's
going to help or you know this is uh you
know but this was like but a lot of
people actually experience stuff it's
legitimate and uh and really hard to
dismiss a friend of one of the guys he
knew um W was walking down a street
somewhere in uh Berlin where he or
checkel law in Prague or somewhere and
saw friends of
his and waved and and the the uh he uh
he knew the street they were on he knew
everything and he called the next day
and that's where they had been that that
at the time he had done it and they had
seen him that's incredible yeah I mean
which is crazy yeah you know what what's
what hit me the hardest about all of
that because it was all fascinating but
just the idea of [ __ ] you money yeah cuz
I feel like I have pardoned me money I'm
so far for [ __ ] you money my money is
way too polite I have raised your finger
uh timidly excuse me money but I I had
you know up until recently I failed my
dreams always like uh it I even even
I've had many almost wet dreams you know
to get to get into I like I'm I'm about
to and then something goes wrong like
and it's also been that way in terms of
like career like my standup in my dreams
it goes bad or for the first time ever
recently I had not only a dream where it
went well but the most this week I had
the most incredible dream I've ever had
because it spanned months and it was so
vivid to every single like it was B I've
never had a dream that spanned months in
order sequentially I I auditioned for
Saturday Night Live in a dream it was a
real audition I every single detail leou
from the waiting room to uh uh
preliminary people before you get to
meet Lauren Michaels getting called back
the in between time at my apartment
going back auditioning for him several
times in the dream uh to to getting some
kind of weird tests uh uh put on me then
uh you know like not you know test
they're like testing my per make sure
that I'm not a psycho or something
before they bring me in uh then uh
getting in sitting with a bunch of Suits
around a table and they're like welcome
to the NBC family with wood panel walls
the whole thing happened and it spanned
months that's unbelievable in one night
it was it was so weird and and I got it
it worked out it worked out well yeah
right up until the first night that I
was about to go on stage and then I woke
up I didn't get on stage but I got as
that's pretty amazing yeah and then you
and then you lay there disappointed I I
had a couple of Dreams recently where I
did where it was uh this is if this
better be a dream you know or this is
really going to be shitty those are the
ones but you know I woke up from that
dream where that that the whole point of
this long story is that I woke up from
it feeling accomplished even though I
that's great though I felt so much
better about life that's good I'm like I
experienced all that now and and that
was good enough and you did experience
it yeah you know that's what I would do
I would go uh a lot of the times people
go well aren't you disciplined you
didn't get that and I go well cuz they
would say you know I mean they're really
early on when something would come up
and then I could make a money and it
would be great and da and uh I would
spend the money in my
head so by the time I didn't get it I'd
already spent the
money I like it find a way to make
ourselves feel better [ __ ] the system
we're going to do already SP money
anyway so [ __ ] it yeah what's what's
next I like it yeah what
what is there a point in life you see I
get to a point where I'm like I can't
believe it's Thanksgiving again it was
just Thanksgiving a minute ago yeah
right it's going to get worse you know
yeah I imagine like it's going to get
really worse tell me I want to know well
it was August and now it's Thanksgiving
I mean it that was 35 seconds for me 35
seconds yeah September didn't exist
uh-huh and uh October literally it was
like uh a blank and it'll be
Thanksgiving and literally but you
finish packing up and put the stuff in
there and go it'll be Thanksgiving it'll
be Thanksgiving yeah I'm serious what's
the point of it all what's the point of
life what do you think is the point yeah
what do you think is the point of us
doing this again and again and again
well I mean just to get it to do it
better I really think that's the deal
the idea is is you know this a you know
the last Christmas was shitty this this
will be the good Christmas oh this is
shitty too but you know next Christmas
is going to be great MH um I think but I
think really the point of going through
it again and again and again is to try
to get it right I mean that's the way I
open my act now I mean it's that uh that
I think that that's really I mean that's
not what I say and but that's really
what I think the point of it is that you
um that you wake up every day and you
try to learn a little more about
yourself and try to keep be a little a
little more open and try to become more
part of what the hell everything is and
uh and hope that uh you know and and
that you you know you I mean basically
you know you find ways to try to cope
with life because it
sucks um we got two quotes here I
usually ask the guests to read the
quotes and then we try and make heads or
tailes of them and wrap the show like
that okay the stronghold of the
determinist argument is the antipathy to
the idea of chance
this notion of alternative possibility
this admission that any one of several
things may come to pass is after all
only a roundabout name for
chance I can read it
backwards and it just as much chance for
name roundabout a only all after is Bast
to come May things several of one any
that admission this possibility
alternative of notion this chance of
ideas to the antiy is the argument
determinist the of stronghold the made
more sense that it makes it makes more
sense that way actually uh the um I have
noide
the list you know that thing you do on
stage uh I don't know why um what you
you're Blown Away by something that that
that's that internally is how I feel
when I hear this stuff yeah I mean all
it is and I don't quite understand it
because it's he says look the the the
fact that people believe in determinism
which is is that everything is already
played out for us is against the idea of
that it's the possibility of Randomness
and then I don't know why um uh that uh
you know and then that the fact that
that several things may come to pass as
opposed to one is what chance is so [ __ ]
it doesn't the psychic knowing these
things sort of prove determinism though
like no he just knows that uh you know
because it's you're going to you you
choose to do things that get you to
there but if he's saying don't worry
about your friend Lewis he's going to be
okay it almost implies you don't have a
choice in the matter you're going to be
okay whether you like it or not yeah
that's great that's bonus points but
where's the free choice that well here's
the free choice he didn't have to tell
me a b he tells me now I [ __ ] relax a
little and don't when I have to deal
with something don't [ __ ] worry about
it cuz is uh this guy I don't know is
that everything's going to be okay
that's good you're you you're in good
hands in other words yeah I you know he
knows you know it I mean in a lot of
ways you know I mean it's uh it
helps um to have that kind of
faith I mean you know there's the
psychotic faith that you know some you
know uh of the of certain Christians is
like beyond belief but the basic faith
that it's going to it's going to work
out as opposed to you know I'm a piece
of [ __ ] but you know why I don't I'm not
going to amount to nothing I'm a piece
of [ __ ] is you know I think whatever you
I don't think it's you know oprish but I
don't think it helps if you know you
don't really a you don't like sitting
down with people who think they're
pieces of [ __ ] right I mean it's just
exhausting at least pretend you're not a
piece of [ __ ] for the 20 minutes we
having
dinner that's
great for my have some self-esteem
really no it's true um all right here's
the second one I'll it's this one here I
think that yesterday was a crisis in my
life I could have said it myself I think
that yesterday was a crisis in my life I
finished the first part of ruier second
essays or essays and see no reason why
this definition of Free Will here's the
definition of Free Will according to Ren
ofier the sustaining of a thought
because I choose to when I might have
other thoughts need to be the definition
of
Illusion this definition need to be at
any rate I will assume for the president
till next year that it is no illusion My
First Act of Free Will shall be to
believe in Free
Will wow I don't know how he have you
write something like that and then I'd
have to take a nap unless he was unless
it was determined that he'd believe in
Free Will and he had no choice in the
matter well that's what they would say
that's but that's what how you make a
living you see you could be that's all
you got to do you take the Counterpoint
to that right you know and then he says
well the reason I know that I have free
will is because and then he'll have
whatever his argument you go well [ __ ]
you and he goes back cter that's what it
is I mean I I I've known a couple of I
knew actually someone who was going for
a doctor in philosophy and uh they were
uh it was like crazy bill I mean it is
it's it's
a ton of thought I mean if you really
want to read a great uh book in terms of
just simple philosophy is and it's goofy
but it's it's it's it's really kind of
puts philosophy in a
more it's a philosophical book that is
not a philosophical book is Zen In The
Art of Motorcycle Maintenance which is
just a
great uh sense of um it's a guy who
completely I think I as I remember it
who the [ __ ] knows but it's a guy who
really kind of has to makes it kind of
loses it a bit and then um comes back
and how it he puts it all together and
that in a sense is philosophy I mean
it's in in part m i mean because the end
of this amount of thought is the [ __ ]
nut
house I mean really I think a lot of
these guys were crazy you know yeah they
were I mean it's they think a lot you
know a lot of this would be called
obsessive compulsive Behavior or um the
I mean that's in part I think why I was
why playwriting was suited me in a sense
because it's this obsessive compulsive
kind of of a uh um of a craft and I mean
as as as as probably any art is to a
point um is opposed to stand up which is
not that it's not obsessive and
compulsive except for the fact that I've
got to get back there tomorrow and you
know and find out what the what will
make the joke work um uh there's not but
border by
bolar you know I'm sure that a lot of
these guys must have been or some of
them for sure must have been bipolar I
wonder if you see it in the book where
it starts getting really one way and
then the other it's like oh he seems
very positive about life the problem
yeah the problem no but it isn't bipolar
is mostly that they uh uh just kind of
laser in on something and then become
completely obsessed with it to the point
of and uh um I've I've been around
bipolar and it's
it comes in all sorts of forms I mean I
I knew this this novelist uh who was
writing four different books at one time
I mean it's like and bipolar I mean it's
just like you know go there go there go
there go there I mean it's yeah you know
it's crazy though I wonder if I guess
they're not aware most bipolar people
are not self-aware enough to know that
they're bipolar well it's good when they
find out because it takes a toll on
those around them I mean now it's more
known I mean literally I would say that
a lot of I'm not so sure of add I mean I
think that there's part in there's a
problem there but I also think that can
be you know it doesn't need to be it's
focusing okay so [ __ ] you know if the
if if if Indian philosophy can take us
to the point that you can meditate on
something that's internal then [ __ ] you
you you should be able to get somebody
to focus on something that's external
but I mean bipolar and um uh depressive
personalities and all of that I mean
there's just been more and more of an
understanding of that in in the course
of our lifetime but this guy didn't seem
to be depressed oh Bill not if you come
up not if you got 19 jobs and uh and
come up and can think that much it's
definitely productive and uh if you want
to find out more of his stuff uh he
wrote some books one of the most popular
of them was called principles of
psychology if you're looking for an 1846
psychologist it's if you're looking for
somebody who could help with the problem
in 1875 chapter one
electroshock shock the patient upon them
entering the you know um what else is
there what other books come on Dan he
helped these people out that [ __ ]
isn't going to help sorry it's a bottom
paragraph there leis essays in radical
empiricism so you can find out what the
[ __ ] that means yeah uh ah this is the
one this is the one Jesus come on they
his major book that you actually if
you're going to read one of his books
the word experience is the only thing
yeah is the varieties of religious
experience which investigated different
forms of haha religious experience
that's the book you want to read yeah
seriously that's well that's the one
really that makes uh is the one that he
I think he's as well known for as any
probably more well known for unless
you're majoring in
Psychology and want to go back and look
at the early influences but uh the VAR
of religious experience was uh was
something that was the the kind of the
the his his book in a way well go pick
it up yeah I'm sure you will yeah would
go I'm sure and I'm sure you can get at
any secondhand bookstore in the country
yeah half.com yeah or or Kindle yeah
Kindle it
[ __ ] this is a pleasure a lot of fun
thanks so much thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
all right thank you guys again for
tuning in to another episode of modern
day philosophers thank you again to my
guest Lewis Black thank you again to
Jesse PS and po aful pole.com Pol TV
Sunday nights 8:00 P.M Eastern Standard
Time is when you can check that out live
go to Modern mod day philosophers. net
it's got links to everything we're on
Stitcher we're on Soundcloud you can
email me at the comical yahoo.com tell
me uh what you think of the show say
hello go on iTunes leave five stars in a
nice rating a nice comment whatever it
is it helps the show's presents on
iTunes and I appreciate it
tremendously um I didn't get a chance to
tell you guys but I had a fantastic
Thanksgiving this past year and I've got
a really good story I'm dying to tell
you but I guess it'll wait for another
show maybe it'll come up in conversation
maybe I could sneak it into a
conversation I really want to tell you
the story but not
yet all right everybody that's it for
now and I'll see you next Monday have a
good week bye