hello and welcome to the season 2 finale
of modernday philosophers I'm your host
Danny LEL you're the listener that's
what you're doing anyway and the guest
today is Arty Lang one of my favorite
people to talk to and one of the
funniest people on the planet very
excited to have him on the show we
recorded this interview at his apartment
in Hoboken New Jersey Thanksgiving time
so I've been sitting on this one for a
while waiting to use it for the season
finale and I I thought it I think I
think you're really going to enjoy it
there's one question I I know I don't
have to point this out but I misspoke
when I asked it wasn't I said I was
wondering if addiction and desire were
the same thing of course that question
to me makes no sense but when I asked it
I said to myself I let already answer
and then I'll just cut it out but then
what he answered I thought was so
fascinating I just left the whole thing
in and I know I could have probably just
not said anything and maybe people
wouldn't have noticed but I just felt
like I as long as I put a question in
the doesn't make sense to me I have the
right to tell you so other than that I
think you know even including that I
think you're really going to enjoy this
but first let me tell you that this
episode is brought to you by a sponsor
very close to my heart it is the label
that put out my CD some kind of comedian
that's right standup records is proud to
announce the launch of their online
store standup crap.com where you can go
and buy downloads and soon CDs vinyl
records DVDs shirts and a wide variety
of other merchandise direct from one of
the best and most prolific comedy labels
out there so go visit
standup.on stress to you enough how
proud and flattered I am to be
presenting this sponsor Dan schle the
guy who runs it who started it is one of
the nicest kindest most supportive
organic true blue comedy guys out there
he really is and he started standup
records and he puts out the very best
comedy and he really stands by his
product and he believes in what he puts
out there and that's why everything you
hear on his label is set to such a high
standard go to
standup.on pick up something go buy some
go buy some downloads go buy my CD some
kind of comedian and buy other people's
CDs support comedy support
standup.on all right thank you to
everybody who throughout the season has
been praying and meditating and sending
Good Vibes to my friend ITA she's still
in the hospital she's been in and out of
Consciousness she's in the ICU and I
think it helps I think what you're doing
helps I appreciate it even if it doesn't
help it doesn't hurt so keep it up if
you will okay that's all I had to say up
front so now oh wait one more thing
sorry that was a tease there was a bit
of a
tease the tweaked audio you go to
tweaked audio.com pick up headphones
with the discount code mdp short for
modern day philosophers and it gets you
a third off free shipping and a lifetime
guarantee they're good little earbuds
and I'm supposed to get a kickback on
the back end if you do this so help me
out okay and now without further Ado
here it is the intro song and then my
talk with Arty Lang enjoy
hello and welcome to modern day
philosophers modern day philosophers
having failed to pay attention in school
Danny LEL now older and wiser will
attempt to learn basic philosophy 101
our young hero will be joined by today's
top comedians philosophers all their own
ladies and gentlemen here's Danny LEL
Mother Day
philosophers all right I'm here with the
great AR
I think uh that's an appropriate title
thanks Dan I I've been worse I've been
worse to a lot of people so I'll take
great that's fine oh you're great to me
sir thank you I'm grateful to be here
it's a beautiful view you got yeah it's
a lousy day we're sitting here on a day
of nor Easter supposed to hit or
something but uh yeah I got uh the whole
apartment's to view I'm wearing hobok
and in my place and I got a perfect view
of the so if you shut these Shades this
is like a $30,000 condo I think
Manhattan is I I've always felt this way
like the the city is is nicer the
farther away you get from it no I said
it to be I go you get to see New York
but you're not in it right I I live I
live in Hoboken but I work in New York I
think that's the best of both worlds you
know it really is when you're in New
York you really can't appreciate it cuz
you're in it you can't you can't see it
like the great pict you can see this is
like a postcard it is I really got lucky
with this I bought this place about 12
years ago and it it's uh right on the
water so I can't build in front of it I
love it it gets me up in the morning you
know we the depression I suffer from uh
a lot of times just gets me up and I'm
like all right let me get in the world
cuz it's not like I'm looking at St
Louis it's New York yeah it's like we're
the center of everything I'm inspired I
could live I would love to live like
this you know I my dream was always to
live in the Dakota you know oh okay like
since I was a kid I wanted to live in
cuz I figured cuz you heard about Lenin
or it's you know just cuz yeah and I I
always like to me like the Dakota has
got to be such a great like Yoko on a
watch her husband get murdered right in
front of her door there and she still
didn't move yeah it's
true it's good real estate that's how
great it is to live in the Dakota I
think if she saw her business manager
get killed right in front of the Dakota
she might have
moved she's like ah it's a shame but
yeah I mean I'm very cynical when it
comes to
Yoko yeah I don't know I me
guess I don't know I I guess I guess she
did love him I don't know I'm in the
other Camp I'm not I don't agree with
you there I've always well yeah that's a
better Camp to be in the Pro Yoko um Pro
Yoko yeah that's an odd Camp to be in
she was on the stern no he was on the
Stern Show uh he Paul mcar he was on the
Stern Show and uh Howard did this
hourlong interview with him right after
I got on the show in 2001 and he said
that he met Yoko first and he thought
she was just a crazy fan and as a joke
he sent her over to John Lenn flat as a
joke oh man and uh and uh 3 Days Later
Lennon called him up and said I met this
girl I'm in love with and it was
yok jokes on you Paul sounds like it cuz
now Paul is dealing every every time
they got to sell something to doal
business she wasn't there when he wrote
Hey Jude but he's got to deal with her
yeah her face is right there in the
office yeah that's funny you know you
I'll tell you why I really like Yoko I
think she brought the best out in John
artistically like The Beatles all those
songs are great and they're and they're
catchy and they're and they're really
wonderful but if you listen to like
Double Fantasy and all those you know
post Beatles Lenin albums I think that's
where you really that's where JN starts
to really you know be an artist his solo
stuff is better than McCartney's that
that that I will say uh and uh I don't
know what Yoko has to do with that but
you're right she was there for it so mhm
you think it would have happened either
way I don't know I don't know you're
right I mean it's actually excellent I
mean uh ex excellent uh theory that you
know she was there for it so therefore
uh she's responsible for but uh you
know ballot of John and Yoko all those
stuff I mean you know he would had to
find some other words that maybe rhyme
with Elaine if there was an Elaine
there but I I think he would have I
think he could have done that but also
the fact that she everybody hated her I
think fueled him into doing great stuff
like yeah the rebel in them was like
[ __ ] you I'm Gonna Keep dating her yeah
if if he would have had another girl
that everybody was like oh you guys are
adorable yeah the [ __ ] is that well
Ringo Ringo got the hottest chick out of
all of them with Barbara Bach and uh you
know he just kind of spends his money
yeah I love Ringo when yeah Ringo is uh
he knew how to live he knows how to live
he's even cleaned up at the right time
you know he seems happy I well that
brings me to I'm reading your book and
it's excellent it's really really I love
I love the way you write and uh it's
it's well you got to go and get it I'm
going to tell you this is an honest true
plug for people out there appreciate it
um Crash and Burn and it's really really
great and you're talking in the book
about davel telling you about money
being an addiction right now I've never
I haven't hit yet you know I've been had
this 11 years but uh I'm still I've
still never had money you know right
right so for me I think a lot about the
difference in like what's what is life
with money versus what what is life
now and
well I I must say that the I've been
lucky I'm 46 years old the last time I
did an honest days work I was
26 uh and that's when I started making a
living from Show Business and then I
started making really good money when I
was 27 because I got on Mad TV the
sketch show on a network and I started
making about 10 grand a week and about
400 Grand a year and I never look back
and uh I'm not you know wealthy wealthy
but I have I I've I've you know I'm I'm
technically a millionaire I guess and
it's just it certainly doesn't buy
happiness it doesn't come close to that
but what it does is it just it just
makes sure that the little things in
life aren't going to take you out
depression
uh you know if you have no money and you
drop a bottle of ketchup that becomes a
billion times worse than if you have
money and you drop a bottle of ketchup
you know like I got no money and this
[ __ ] ketchup on the floor you know
you can add I got no money to every
single problem you have I got no money
in this traffic I got no money in this
[ __ ] you know my I do my laundry I
got no money and my broad left me you
know but uh it just takes one more thing
out of the bitching session that um
helps you very practically you know so
that's how it helps it it certainly
doesn't ensure any sort of happiness I
found you know you're talking about yeah
sure it it helps in terms of like you
don't have to worry about things it it
helps you in that way right but what
about just in terms of how you relate to
the world is it different having money
do you see the world differently do you
see yes yes I do I I I I must say I I um
it's not an elitist attitude it's like
you just when I see
somebody even somebody I know really
well struggling when they tell me a
story about how they they had to take
two Subways and this or that the other
thing to get to a certain place and
everything I really go thank God that's
not me anymore and I don't say it out
loud cuz that would be terrible but I I
go thank God I don't have to do that
right uh and uh I I I've I haven't had
to do it long enough it's to the it's as
if I grew up rich right I didn't grow up
rich at all I I had you know when I
started I had no money uh completely
broke my family was practically on
welfare as a matter of fact and uh I my
mother was toiling along as a secretary
and um we had zero less than zero and uh
I don't really remember that it's been
so long it's 20 years removed so it's as
if I grew up rich and so when I [ __ ] at
Rich Kids I'm almost the same way I'm
just a 46y old rich
kid I'm not an 18-year-old rich kid I'm
a 46y old rich kid and I uh I don't
remember really what it was like to to
take to not have enough money to buy
another
CD but I talk about
CDs I'm old enough to where that's my
problem I don't talk about downloading I
still talk about CD does it change how
you relate to an audience
uh it can and you have to watch yourself
you know I mean I don't have the kind of
money where
uh you know it's totally
unrelatable uh like uh I'm sure Seinfeld
has to catch himself at times when he's
in front of a crowd in Ohio and he's
talking about the fact that you know
this gig they wouldn't pay for the gas
and his private jet and stuff like that
but at the same time people you know who
don't have a lot of money like hearing
about people with money like watching
people with money that's been proven
look at the [ __ ] Kardashians I guess
people like watching that show just cuz
they're they're in some way living
through them or jealous of them or
whatever so maybe you know if an
observation's funny enough maybe he
could get away with it I uh no matter
I'm one of those guys where I don't know
if this is lucky for comedy or not no
matter how rich I get I will never seem
Rich I just and I don't do that on
purpose I'm not proud of it like oh you
know you're a guy who stayed real it's I
have no other choice you're just a blue
color guy I just don't know anything
else I wouldn't know how
to I didn't go to college I had to go to
summer school to get out of high school
I I would not know how to do anything
else or act like anything else I'm
really like you know Rodney Dangerfield
and easy money you know less money but
you know same type of guy well you're
also in a way staying true to yourself
you're not pretending I swear but that's
not the
reason it's just I I I I just cuz you
know even pretending it would be so I
wouldn't know how to do it I literally
would not know how to do it it's like
Chopsticks I've never bothered learning
how to use chopsticks and I hate when I
see somebody I grew up with use them I
hate it I'm like when the [ __ ] did you
learn how to use chopsticks and why
would you use them instead like if we go
eat sushi or something to get mad I
always ask for a fork I don't care what
the waiter what the look waiter gives me
I don't give a [ __ ] what some [ __ ]
[ __ ] at the next table who's got a
Chanel bag what look she gives me and I
don't care I'm embarrassed to people I
i' I've had women probably stop dating
me because I I asked for a fork because
it's it's so much easier to use a
[ __ ] Fork it's a [ __ ] Fork over
Chopsticks and the only reason you use
those Chopsticks is to seem like okay
now I'm more cultured now I'm more
cultured and I'm not willing to give up
the convenience of a fork to seem more
cultured I'm not to me just learning how
to use them is you're being a [ __ ]
dick you're standing your ground though
you're not you're not backing down no
yeah I I I uh yeah I I I just I hate and
and I get mad and then I should be
getting mad at them they're getting mad
at me and that makes me Furious I'm like
how [ __ ] dare you I'm the one who's
biting my tongue when I see you not use
the convenience of a fork and you're
trying to figure that thing out it makes
me sick you know what I think it pisses
you off when people are pretending
around you yeah yeah well it's a yeah
it's it's it's right exactly exactly I
feel like I have to get off my chest at
this point that I use chopsticks cuz
otherwise I'm just a phony don't worry
about it but I've been using them since
I was a kid yeah that's if you learned
as a kid I learned but believe me the
neighborhood I'm from no one was using
Chopsticks okay everybody had a fork
yeah uh you know we
had our fathers didn't bother to figure
out how to you know get a job much l you
was up staks going back to the idea of
money and
wealth now that you've been wealthy for
so long is there still any fear in you
that you could go back or do you feel
pretty secure and set in all right I've
I'm a made man now no I'm not that's the
other thing there other thing that's
crazy about me and the other Edge I live
on or other Cliff I always feel I'm
going to fall off of is no I I don't
have enough money to to where I like to
spend and live because now I've gotten
used to a
a certain amount of cash uh and uh and a
certain lifestyle like uh especially the
weight I'm at now I can't fly anything
but first class if I flew coach right
now would be I'd want to sue somebody I
think it's uh offensive it's it's it's
oppressive uh so uh and I like nice
hotels I you know I don't know I just I
I just got used to nicer hotels like a
Four Seasons or a rich G and a and uh I
certainly was never like that any hotel
was cool to
me uh but uh I I don't have enough money
to where I could stop working and I
really want to stop working you know but
CH yeah in a way but show business tells
you when you're
done it's not the other way around so
I'm worried that that day will come
where it says you're done and and uh I
run out of cash that would be awful
awful it's like that that line in match
point you know where the guy once he
shoots Scarlett Johansson he goes I've
just become accustomed to a certain way
of life exactly's willing to suffer to
to not suffer right exactly you uh yeah
and and that's what's great about a
movie like that and you know Woody Allen
does that a lot in his movies where
someone does
something some uh you know usually
someone you never think would do
something like that goes to a certain
level to to to keep living the way
they're living that's like a common
theme and you go [ __ ] I don't know if I
could totally judge that person it's
right it's the old woman that get you
it's like scarl Johanson maybe she kind
of knew what she was getting into but
when the old woman goes it's like whoo
he's gone to the dark side yeah I wonder
if it sometimes I look at it like when
I'm being lazy sometimes I wind up doing
a lot more work to be lazy than if I
would just not be lazy right yeah no
exactly it's like you know organized
crime people you see the amount of work
like like if I was an organized crime
the first day I put in that seemed like
a [ __ ] I would go guys I I thinking I'm
going to get a job like in construct
like legit construction I'm going to
learn to actually build a deck you still
be working for him right cuz I wouldn't
have this [ __ ] piano hanging over my
head or to drop of getting arrested or
you killing me right and it's a same
amount of work like the first day in
organ if I was in the mafia that it was
like wow this was a [ __ ] today i' I'd
go this doesn't make any sense this
should be a this should not be at all
stressful you know and I feel like we
that it's the same thing as a comic we
work really hard to not work oh yeah
well I think we're willing to put
ourselves through a bunch of stress like
that hour on stage is stressful and you
you start looking at every crowd even if
you're doing it forever and and you
start to panic and look at one guy or
one girl she's going to hate me she's
going to hate me you yeah at times yeah
and I'm like uh because you just want to
get a check and get out of there and
you're worried they're going to hate
this material and will the guy pay me
and you know I don't know uh yeah I
still go through that and it's really a
lot of stress that builds up in your
stomach to where you're like yeah uh I
don't want nine hours of a little stress
and LA but I'll take the one hour of it
a day or one hour a week you know that's
one of the things I find like really
fascinating about you also reading the
book
that story about the Playboy Mansion
yeah is to me Arty and to a lot of
people you're one of the funniest people
on the planet like with that question
right but I feel like you're not
completely
convinced no I definitely am not
convinced really I I guess I don't know
there there's times where
I you know I'm definitely not someone
who rests on his lals i' I've I've I I I
you know I did for a long time I was on
the Stern Show four and a half hours a
day I was doing standup and specials a
book a movie writing I was trying
everything and now I work my ass off
still three hours doing a TV and radio
show I stand up I'm do another special
another book like like I put myself out
there I don't just like you know appear
once every month and say hey I'm funny
and leave like I try so the fact that I
do it so
much every every once in a while I have
a day where I go yeah today today I was
good today I was up there with the
Wittier people I know but uh normally
I'm disappointed in my performance as as
a funny person I don't know do you think
that's what makes you
great see I don't think I'm great so I
don't
know I don't know I mean true great do
you think it that's what makes great
artists in
general I I put it this way I've never
met one funny comic who thinks he's
funny M you know I think deep down you
know they know it but they don't they
don't really like ah that sucked this is
going to suck blah blah blah like if you
talk to dve tell you'd think he was like
uh an unfunny
dishwasher when he's really one of the
funniest guys who's ever lived you know
certainly of Our Generation but you know
he he hates himself and he hates what he
you know I was just talking to him last
night he feels like he hit a wall uh
Norm McDonald would get off stage I open
for Norm on the road Norm would get off
stage and say that suck this sucked and
I just watched them do you know an hour
and a half of some of the best standup I
ever saw you just don't I guess it
that's been a trait put it this way with
funny people I think I I you know I
think I'm the same way in a lot of ways
just I can't listen I put a CD out that
you were nice enough to let me promote
on your show and I can't listen to it I
just can't listen to it cuz it's too
painful I just keep thinking it it sucks
and then people write me and they say oh
I love it I love the CD and and I'm like
oh good yeah they love the good good but
if somebody else were to tell me oh this
suck then I'd be upset you know well
that's the problem with Twitter like the
your amount of like people that are on
there like some people even just to say
it are going to say something sucks and
that's why right for Comics that could
be deadly like that's all you're going
to focus on but uh uh yeah I'm the same
way I can't uh a matter of fact uh when
when my last Comedy Central special came
out uh I was in a a rehab that was also
mental institution it was like a
combination and there's a common area
where a TV is and Comedy Central was on
and I completely forgot and I had sold
it to Comedy Central so much had
happened in my life and we're watching
something on Comedy Central me and like
12 other people on the floor and it says
there's a picture of me doing standup a
clip and it goes coming up the world
premiere of Jack and Coke with Ry Lang
and they all looked at me like hey it's
your special I had no idea so I went to
my room and I said I can't watch watch
this especially in this situation I
can't watch it until I got up in that
robe that like your ass hangs out of and
I went I laid in my bed and you can't
lock your door and you got to be close
to the nurse station because they don't
want to make sure they want to make sure
you don't do anything and uh I overheard
like 15 lunatics laughing at my
special and I was happy they were
laughing but uh I would peek out every
once in a while and one guy was just
sitting there and shaking MH and I think
it was cuz he hadn't gotten his thorine
but but uh you know I'm like what's
what's that motherfucker's problem you
know and I I I couldn't bring myself to
watch and I said if I see even a second
of this just the clip they showed made
me want to throw up I never met Jerry
Seinfield but just from watching him in
interviews and stuff I feel like he's
the opposite of guys like you and me in
that way that he seems so confident in
his being funny and so yeah well when
you have that kind of success it's hard
not to seem that way you know uh
uh if uh you know if
you if if you're looking at a comedian
sitting there and he doesn't have a
smile on his face but he's wearing an
$8,000 sweater you go he seems confident
you know if they're dressed like me and
you were dressed like right now I think
they go oh wow that guy's depressed that
guy's suicidal this is no good no it
looks that's fine to me but I'm saying
other people might judge D I'm saying no
I don't judge but other people might I'm
not sensitive about it I'm not I figured
that but I uh yeah so I think he has his
dark times he just looks better you
know and when you go home and you see
the show that he helped create and is on
on for four straight hours it's hard to
think he's depressed yeah well you ready
to get into our philosopher here so Alex
picked out a guy for you also named Arty
I guess Arthur uh I have a hard time
pronouncing these names schopen Houser
Hower okay s c h o p n h a u e r and
Alex wrote Because of Art's new book
where he talks about attempting suicide
I picked an existential philosopher the
Arty Arty
combo so schopenhauer believes that life
is a blind striving meaning that the
only reason that it continues to exist
is because it feels it should human
morality is driven by desire desire is
directionless IR
and malignant and must therefore be
controlled with our duty to abstain from
Bad worldly pleasures and our duty to
our fellow
man I don't know if that's do you think
morality is driven by
desire
um
well it could me a couple of things you
know this is why philosophers to me
don't make any sense it's like listen to
a song it could mean something to them
and you have no idea what the [ __ ] it
mean like I list in a Moonlight Mile by
The Rolling Stones and that's a great
song but I don't know what the [ __ ] he's
talking about like you
know just another Moonlight Mile down
the road and you're sitting there going
I guess I know what that means but you
know I guess desire could be morality
could be driven by desire in the sense
that
um your desires could scare you so much
like what you really want deep down that
you uh you know they're bad and it's
it's the reason you you abstain from
them in a way I don't know uh or the
desire he's talking about might not be
like the dark desires we think of like
sexual or something but it could be the
desire to be good to be a good person
maybe that's what he means you know so
um I I think there's a couple angles
there I often wonder if desire and
addiction are the same
thing they're definitely related without
question you know I don't know if to
same thing no uh you could desire
something and even satisfy that desire
without being addicted to it happens all
the time uh but uh like they call people
sex addicts I don't know if that's real
like I have a desire to have sex a lot
and and I've at times even fulfilled
that desire but I don't think I'm
addicted to it I mean heroin is such a
physical addiction I mean the stuff I
was addicted to was such physically
addictive stuff that I mean there's no
one who
wouldn't I mean I think it's a small
percentage of people who if they tried
heroin for a couple straight days would
not become addicted to it you it's
almost impossible not
to that's why it's so scary you know
people ask about legalizing drugs like
uh they go I don't know we we should
legalize drugs the world would be the
same I'm like I don't know if I knew I
could go to CVS and pick up a marble
lights and some
heroin I don't know I wouldn't be here
right now probably it' be at CVS or
you'd be here but you wouldn't be here
or well exactly or if a guy uh is having
a shitty week guy who's never done
anything wrong in his life just having a
bad but have a glass of wine he's having
a bad week and he's at CBS he goes I
don't know a lot of anxiety this week uh
let me try heroin MH you know and couple
weeks later he's sucking dick for it you
know it's yeah do you think um your
perspective of reality is is changed
because you've been on drugs and you've
seen the world in a way that like I've
I've never seen I've never done heroin
or any of that cuz I'm too scared you
know no that's a good that's a good move
man if you have any addictive
personality at all if you've been
addicted to anything at all or think you
have do not try it
no yeah you'll you'll Chas it you'll
live with it you know but you know what
I watch like these uh Bill Hicks
documentary right where he's dropping
acid and it changes the way he sees the
world you know I'm so tempted as a comic
to be like man I want to I want to I
want to open my eyes to what they're
seeing like you know also like John
lennin and George Carlin these guys all
you know well Carlin has that famous
quote where he said the only drug that's
worth anything is weed he he did say he
used to write his act straight smoke
weed and then rewrite it it always got
funnier uh I don't know I would go with
the would sound like assd though I would
go with the odds you know most people
would drop assd even if they've been
creative at first it it it just makes
their lives worse worse I had a couple
of bad trips with it U at a Elton John
Eric Clapton concert at Chase stadium in
1992 I I dropped ass and I I was really
in bad shape like I was you know on the
top of of sha Stadium like looking down
thinking I could fly practically and
they had my buddies had to take me home
you know it didn't make me
funnier but you know you got those
stories like the Sid Barrett uh from the
the Pink Floyd you know getting badass
and and he was real creative it didn't
help him I don't know I guess it's it's
different for everybody but I think it
helps with music more than it would
comedy I think Hicks
uh Bill Hicks uh I I don't know I think
he would have been that funny anyway and
he would have had those thoughts anyway
you know I I do so you don't think drugs
opened your eyes up to a different kind
of world than the one I
see yes yes but I'm saying it's not
necessarily a better one and it's not
necessarily one that'll make you more
creative or funnier it's different
that's for sure but I don't know if it's
better what's the main
difference well uh why you think uh
creatively it might help his risk you're
you're willing to take a lot more risk
that's why you he these drummers talk
about being on smack that's why
musically it might be better uh like
Ginger Baker talks about heroin he's
like when you're on heroin you'll take
more risks Charlie Parker with jazz like
he he you know the only way to get
better was to risk something and
musically music has a better pace for
what you see when you're uh [ __ ] up
and uh and if you're on dope you don't
care so you'll risk something and in
that risk you might create something
amazing with the drums or the trumpet or
guitar you know uh but with
comedy uh it needs to be more
controlled you know it's it's it's fun
to take a risk but it can't be as as
crazy as
uh as music like like uh comedy is more
like baseball it's more like a baseball
skill it's more like you know all the
adrenaline in the world can't make
you better at baseball but it can help
you in basketball you like in basketball
you got a lot of you can win a game
through sheer adrenaline like I'm just
pumped up right now but baseball you got
to calm down and hit the ball and catch
the ball you got to it's more and that's
what comedy is and that's why I think
drugs could actually hurt it
um but I think with music it might help
comedians it can make you take risks and
make it way worse and make it just sound
stupid it's got to be more logical it's
more of a fine art you know well I'll
give you a little background on our guy
here he lived from 1788 to
1860 well that definitely is yeah you
know says a lot times are different yeah
Arthur
schopen was a German philosopher best
known for his book The World As will and
representation in which he claimed that
our world is driven by a continually
dissatisfied will well that's what
Carlin was always talking about sure
yeah yeah continually seeking
satisfaction and that's what you were
just saying a minute ago yeah you uh you
know it just never
happens it just it just never you never
get there you can never be satisfied you
could be temporarily satisfied now it
could yeah it could happen I like the
first time I tried ecstasy I'll never
forget that I I was like God they
perfected drugs every feeling you want
in one pill heroin coke and I walked
down the street I walked to Manhattan
like 40 blocks I hugged homeless guys I
was like hey buddy come here shake my
hand let's take a picture like you know
what and uh and I've been chasing that
High ever since never came back in a way
life's like that and if you've been
exposed to that once and you wake up
like if you've done heroin and you see
how high you can get from heroin how
great that feels waking up in the
morning and going oh my God this is
it I might feel a little better after a
shower but it's not going to be like I
was on heroin you know that's the same
thing as those
hotels exactly it's hard to go back
you're right it's hard that's the whole
thing it's hard to go back um he was
influenced by Eastern thought he
maintained that the truth was
recognized by the sages of India
consequently his solutions to suffering
were similar to those of verdic and
Buddhist thinkers his faith in
transcendental idealy I don't know what
that is I guess neither led him to
accept atheism and learn from Christian
philosophy what do you think do about
God and well you know I was brought up
Roman Catholic and I'm certainly at the
point where I think that's almost
complete
[ __ ] but
um uh I don't know I I I I think the
best argument for there being some sort
of higher power or something out there
that's bigger than us is you know how
the [ __ ] did we go from mud and sticks
to to the city I'm looking at right now
in New York I don't know how that
happened how does that happen without
some sort of guidance from a higher
being that we might even know is guiding
us
uh was there a Jesus maybe there was a
guy was he a Son of God I doubt
it what is God I have no idea but I just
know there might be something out
there that there's enough proof there
might be something out there to the
point where I'm scared [ __ ] of it put it
that way yeah yeah something scares me
do you ever
pray I have yeah
uh but only in horrible situations but I
have I to admit I have it and but in
really bad situations like you know
uh I was in jail I prayed every night in
jail I was in jail for a week uh you
know and uh I'm still uh I'm still an
ass virgin so that worked I guess I
don't know but I I I I don't know I it's
that that's a complicated question
obviously the people been trying to
figure out forever uh people far smarter
than me I don't know but I know there's
enough of proof here that I'm scared of
something else out there do you think we
have
souls yes absolutely but I believe they
could be taken
away I believe every kid has one that's
sort of pure for a while but I I believe
they can be taken away pretty
quickly most people have them taken away
you think you can get them
back not the whole thing
you can get a piece of it back not the
whole thing you're just never as you're
never as happy as you were when you were
8 years old just jumping around like an
idiot you know it's
like I think that's the original high
that we're all chasing oh God yeah yeah
I think Brian rean has a bit where he's
like you know you're six years old
you're jumping around the backyard
you're having fun then your mother goes
hey come here you got to stop doing that
you got to go to school and you go to
school and everything gets [ __ ] up and
like oh why don't can I just stand back
here and just keep jumping around like
an idiot oh you
can't it's so true right I always I
always said why don't you just let kids
be kids why do you have to let them work
later on or whatever it is and that goes
back to the money question eventually
everybody [ __ ] needs money that's why
you go to
school that's why you have to stop
jumping around because the backyard
you're jumping around didn't cost money
the clothes you're jumping around then
cost money when I keep jumping around
like an idiot you now some people can
like pish H never stopped jumping around
like an
idiot and everyone resents her for it
yeah I know it's like why be doing the
exact same [ __ ] thing maybe it's
jealousy maybe we of course it is of
course it is we all just want to jump
around like be way worse than her all
right at age 25 he published his
doctoral dissertation on the four-fold
root of the principle of sufficient
reason in which he exclaimed the four
distinct aspects of experience
in the phenomenal World consequently
he's been influential in the history of
phenomenology he has influenced many
thinkers including nii Wagner Ludwick
and then names a bunch of other ones and
that's it that's our that's our dude
yeah so uh do you want to read some
quotes from him and we'll see what we
make sure I think there's three here
that made me think of that Woody Allen
joke and crimes and misdemeanor nii this
nii who whose theory is we just going to
keep living the same life over and over
that's great that means you got to sit
through ice capades
again I love that that's true okay
here's a here's a quote from they tell
us that suicide is the greatest piece of
cowardice that suicide is wrong when it
is quite obvious that there is nothing
in the world to which Every Man Has a
more unsatiable title than to his own
life and
person I guess you know exactly right
it's your life to to live and to take
when you want though right yeah I guess
why do you think people uh get mad at
people for committing suicide or trying
to commit suicide you think it has to do
with taking risk because how it affects
the people they
love how it affects the people they love
they say well how could you do that to
the people you love it's a car I say
look what I'm doing to them while I'm
here my argument is it's going to be way
worse if I stay here as far as I'm
concerned I'm trying to help him out
but death is death really why do people
get more upset if you take it away than
if you know it comes another another way
because they the whole theory that life
is so precious life is a precious gift
you know talk to a crackhead [ __ ]
himself in Thompson Square Park at 4 in
the morning on a February night it's not
a precious gift to that guy it's gone
horribly wrong yeah you know do you
value life more since your suicide
attempt yeah sure but because I was was
able to bounce back and and and I'm so
lucky that my career came back and but
you know without
this ability to to make some money and
to to have a career and do stuff that I
like I don't know what I'd feel I don't
know what I'd feel if I was a TGI
Fridays right now waitering for being
forced to sing Happy Birthday to some
[ __ ] who just cuz he bought an extra
piece of cheesecake I'd be I don't know
what I'd be what what do you think is
the greatest part of life
I guess love I guess I guess the feeling
that I if you actually have a connection
with somebody and you feel my God I'm
not
alone the the rare feeling where you go
I'm truly not
alone and loneliness is a is a feeling
that's that that happens more but that
rare feeling where you go I have a
connection with somebody and you
know I'm not alone it doesn't have to be
sexually it doesn't have to be woman or
could be like a guy that you friends
with you
know usually abroad just connecting
connecting with somebody
MH uh all right man can do what he Wills
but he cannot will what he
Wills that's a tough
one you can't I think it's saying you
can't control your desire you can do
what you desire but you can't control
what you desire desire you desire what
you desire in a way but I don't know if
Will and desire are really the same yeah
well it can be seems
like I think you can't will something to
happen but if it happens to happen you
you're able to do it you're able to deal
with it I think that's what it means
that makes sense I have no
idea nice one here compassion is the
basis of morality that I completely
agree with
that I completely agree with if you have
a if you have a lack of compassion you
can't be a good person you have to have
compassion you have to have guilt you
have to
have uh you
know a feeling of
of not wanting something to happen to
[Music]
you so you don't do it to somebody else
and uh if you see it happening to
somebody else you know you want to help
them absolutely without compassion there
would be morality wouldn't exist I agree
with that you know what what do you
think how do you define
compassion like what makes someone very
having guilt over something like
um uh if
uh if you if you
see I don't know if you see a guy on the
street you know and most New Yorkers are
cynical if you see a guy begging for
money and he's got all his arms and legs
and he looks ample body like he could
get a
job I don't know if I'd be so fast to
give that guy money but if I see a guy
who's clearly has no
legs I I I I what I do is I instead of
giving a bunch of guys ones I save up
and I might give that guy a 50 yeah I
guess that's why Eddie Murphy did it in
uh in trading places yeah but I believe
me I checked there's no way they could
totally hide that I I know the scene
you're talking about yeah I I give it a
full I give it a go round I go I just
want to make sure lift up that one okay
you check you lift them up I us I
usually travel around with a the
orthopedist and he just I just have this
guy look at you real quick just to make
sure allel this guys aren't Bo quick
evaluation before I yeah I just got to
get I'm going get a quick physical I
travel with someone from the mail Clinic
to give a quick physical no but if I I
clearly have no legs I
mean you go I guy's got no legs I do I
have compassion for him so that's I
think some people have the ability to go
[ __ ] him yeah better better him than me
let's say you had I don't have that in
me better him than me I hate that let's
say you had Seinfeld money what then
would you keep producing the Way You Are
no probably not no I I I I'm I'm too
another terrible thing about my
character is the laziness I'm just too
lazy I'm too
lazy uh if I had that kind of money I I
don't know you're probably lazy based on
your potential but you're not
objectively lazy well I like I'm going
to Cleveland this weekend to do a gig
I'm doing a book signing I have an 8:
a.m. flight the day after Thanksgiving
to do a book signing for Friday that I'm
in Cleveland Friday night doing whatever
you do there with no gig and then
Saturday night I have a gig in Cleveland
come back Sunday basically giving up the
whole Thanksgiving weekend that's not
lazy you're working hard yeah but I
wouldn't do that if I had sign for money
right but you're still not lazy you're
just saying you'd become lazy or or it's
in you to be lazy you just don't have
the option yeah yeah right I should be
right that's true I should be walk the
next weekend but I'm not I wonder if you
cling on to like this quality of life
thing as an excuse like you could go
back you could scale it back and
probably be just as happy but I wonder
if you have to cling on to I must
maintain these nice hotels these first
class just to keep you motivated just to
keep you working maybe maybe that's
true so maybe if you had that money
you'd find something else you'd be like
oh I got to get to that Bill Gates level
or whatever whatever it is maybe that's
part of I guess I'm there now where I I
should want to I do want to get to the
next level but I just don't I don't know
how to do it I I guess something's got
to hit none of us know how to do I don't
know how to get to the next level the
that's the that's the tricky thing of it
I guess that's the challenge right you
know I always I thought about you know
since Geraldo passed away I've thought
about it a lot and I think the thing
that this is just my theory but I think
the thing that depressed him to the
point that he didn't want to be here
anymore was just the knowledge of his
own potential because I
think you think he committed suicide I
think he committed suicide you do I do
yeah from what I he from what I heard
about it I thought maybe it was was
actually an accident but you he could
have I you know I mean it it was an
accident a very avoidable accident for
someone who was hellbent on living you
know what I mean yeah if if he really
wanted to be here I don't think that
would have happened right well sometimes
when you get tolerance to pills and you
get the wrong
kind it's not you're not getting the
high you want from them and uh you keep
taking them I don't know you're right
but if you think him suicide I look I I
think he I'm just pissed off in someone
that funny doesn't leave a
note you know the only people leave know
are these awful unfunny
bores I I wish you were with me right
now
Sarah as I look out at at my backyard
the tractor don't
work and I don't have money for the
furnace no more and I wish you were here
sir you're you're in California pursuing
a music career and I wish you luck you
got so talented you really are but I
don't have any more money for the
furnace to work exactly and I can't go
to my job no more cuz they fired me you
I'd want to hear what Greg Geraldo would
saying his though you just feel deprived
man it'd be great if Greg dadoo like
somebody L her like just roasted
everybody in his life in the well we
should get some of the writers that
wrote his that helped him on the roast
jokes and have them like at least put it
together and say hey he wrote this that
would be great that would Bob Hope
committed suicide he didn't write the
note he didn't write the
note that's a great joke we just thought
of that's what happens when two
comedians get together about yeah Bob
Bob Bob Hope uh committed suicide his
not will be ready according to the
writers in four
weeks that's great I love it well thank
thank you so much Ary we should end on
that we should we should yeah it's not
going we that's what we figured out
that's what we figur that now we just
have to decide which one of us can put
that in his standup
act I love the view man I'm goingon to
I'm going to miss this going back to LA
I really thank God stop by if you want
thank you you could come by if you want
you're in LA but you know whenever if
you're in town stop by I appreciate it
we'll have a sandwich or something oh
I'm always down for a sandwich I think
being in La the view is even more
beautiful in away I think the farther
you get away from it the more like you
romanticize it and make it
absolutely no you'll miss New York here
if you live in New York you see that
view you'll see that in your sleep man
you know yeah I think you know Woody
Allen I'll quote him since you did but
uh in that documentary Wild Man Blues
yes he he was he was saying whenever
he's in Europe he misses New York
whenever he's in New York he misses
Europe and I I feel the same way about
wherever I am I want to be the other
place right she con state of
sadness that's what that's what seeing
both of those places achieved if I just
stayed here I'd be happy here I got to
go here and be find another place I got
to miss and you know it's like but it
won that it usually doesn't happen in La
most people most people living in New
York uh don't who lived in La at one
point you don't see them walking down 57
you're going God I miss Los Feliz but
you miss the weather you don't miss the
place you miss the you miss the warmth
you missed the weather but there's so
many [ __ ] are talking in that
weather about the weather and you know
that that's why whenever you talk to
someone about La you know how is they go
it's great the weather's great that's I
hate when a young person says that I'm
like buy a [ __ ]
jacket honestly the cost of a jacket is
all your is is is all between you and
being happy is the cost of a go let's
let's go to Old Navy I'll get you some
I'll get you thermal shirt like you know
congratulations here's La yeah exactly
yeah bye thanks s thanks
[Music]
[Applause]
Dad well I hope you enjoyed that as much
as I did thank you again to Arty Lang
for doing the show thank you to you guys
for listening please don't be afraid
during our little time off now between
Seasons to send me an email say hello
the comical yahoo.com let me know what
you think of the show let me know you
exist connect that's what Ry and I were
talking about not feeling alone in the
world he said it was one of the greatest
parts of life and I agree it's nice to
know you're out there say hello drop me
an email the comical
yahoo.com jump on the Facebook page I
don't know if you to jump on it but you
know you can go on it you can ease into
it
facebook.com/ modernday philosophers
that's the Facebook page we also have a
website modernday philosophers. net
where there is a PayPal donate button
and should you feel so inclined to
support a truly struggling artist that
is what I am you can make a donation and
hey you know what it would be a
lifechanging
thing even if it's a small donation it
would change my life technically in some
way but any donation would be very
appreciated and would go a long way so
please do that if you can go to standup
crap.com once again standup.on brought
us this beautiful episode today Dan
schle a wonderful man who runs it
standup records is the label standup
crap.com is the store go buy some
downloads support support the cause you
need some earbuds go to tweaked
audio.com and put in promo code mdp get
a third off and I'm supposed to get
something back on that all right I think
that's about it for this week I will see
you guys next week with the wrap-up show
the season wrap-up with Alex faella and
I and then a great guest is kicking off
season 3 so get excited for that all
that coming up and so much more right
here at modern day philosophers
headquarters my apartment it's just I
don't know if you can hear he my dog
snoring in the background if you can't
well then you'll just have to take my
word for it that my dog is snoring in
the
background only one of them is snoring
the other one's sleeping silently and
the Tortoise he doesn't snore too much
at all all right I'm rambling on have a
good week everybody and I'll see you
next Monday bye