hello everyone and welcome to another
exciting and jam-packed edition of
modern day philosophers I am your host I
am Danny LEL you are the listeners you
are whoever you are aren't you I think
you are and you're out there somewhere
listening to this show and I appreciate
you doing so please donate if you can to
modernday philosophers. there's a donate
button there and keep the show going it
is supported by listeners like you and
it is also supported by listeners who
are not like like you listeners who
sponsor the episodes like tent tent is
encounters with Jewish culture they
offer week-long residencies for Creative
20s something year olds they've got
programs in food fashion journalism
creative writing and a bunch of other
topics and the deadline for their comedy
program is coming up soon go to tent
site.org for more
details and by the way I'm a proud of
Lum of tent comedy myself I did it last
year even though I'm not usually a fan
of these kinds of things it was really
great fun even
enlightening they will feed you which
I'm always a fan of and they will put
you up which is also cool and it doesn't
cost you anything they cover your meals
your tickets to shows workshops classes
it's really cool if you're uh into the
history of Jews and comedy it doesn't
get better than this you just need to go
to La if you're not there already in the
program last year we did an improv
workshop at the Groundlings with
Michaela Watkins we did comedy writing
workshops with Yoni brener writes for
the New Yorker shouts and murmur section
we talked with Ken LaVine who was
written for mash and The Jeffersons and
The Simpsons and we saw performances by
Jeff Garland and Sarah Silverman tigero
Pete Holmes and many others we learned a
lot about history of Jews we learned
about the old Lowery side pretty cool
stuff and like I said it's not just
comedy they have programs for people
interested in food journalism ative
writing and many more things you don't
have to be obsessed with Jewish stuff to
do tent you can just be curious there's
no catch except for the fact that there
are only 20 spots in each program and
the deadlines are coming up soon so
check out tent site.org for more
details check that out and and I'm also
proud to tell you that this week's
episode is also brought to you by
standup records standup records present
standup crap.com standup crap.com is
where you can go you yeah you you yeah
you you you you can go to standup
crap.com and you can pick up fantastic
records from comedians like Mark Maron
Lewis Black Maria Bamford Brendan Burns
and well me Danny LEL you can go pick up
my album some kind of comedian I'm proud
to be on their label and I'm happy that
Mr Dan schle has kept this show going
yet another episode thank you very much
Dan schle go to standup crap.com pick up
CDs vinyls DVDs t-shirts and lots more
merchandise from the leading number one
most prolific comedy label out there
standup crap.com go there today and if
you can't do today tomorrow but come on
you got to be able to fit in either
today or tomorrow okay it's been quite a
week here's a good story I like to give
you a little tibbit from the from the
week went with my buddy Rick wood who's
a very funny comic I met out here in La
we go to garage sales sometimes on a
Sunday it's a fun thing to do well we
stopped off at a coffee bean and I
needed to use a bathroom and I noticed
there was a long line so I went next
door there was a bagel place I said can
you use the bathroom they said we don't
have a bathroom I was like oh I'm
getting desperate so I go to the other
side of the Coffee Bean and there's a
fancy brunch place and I noticed there's
a hostess at the greeting stand which is
generally where they stand at the
greeting stand and it's also where they
they stop people from going to the
bathroom in my experience who are not
customers or patrons of the restaurant
so I devised a plan very quickly in my
head I decided to pretend to make eye
contact with a table in the back of the
room so when I walked up to her I I
wasn't looking at her I was looking at
the table and I was fake waving to
nobody and she didn't think anything of
it so I just continued past her stand so
I get to the back area where there's a
line for the bathroom there's someone in
the bathroom and there's one guy ahead
of me online and me and the guy he's
like a real Jersey tough guy I don't I
don't even know who let him into La you
never see guys like this in La this is
like an East Coast guy I know them I
know them from being one and he's mad
and the guy he goes can you freaking
believe this can you freaking believe
this we got to wait for the bathroom in
a fancy restaurant like this can you
freaking believe I got to wait while
some my [ __ ] in there probably
didn't even pay to come into the
restaurant probably right off of the
street you know it's the problem with
these places he goes they just let and
by the way there's no way he could have
known that how I how I came to be in
that part of the restaurant just the way
it was set up he goes people you know I
bet they don't have good security here I
bet they're just letting any [ __ ] head
in off the street they need to use the
bathroom and they probably just let them
in while people like me and you have to
pay a ton of money and sit down and then
we don't we have to wait for these
people who aren't even part of the
restaurant to use a bathroom and I go
yes you're yes sir you're absolutely
right just start agreeing with him I go
you're right it's it's an outrage it's
shocking shocking they they bet you they
do have bad security he goes yeah thank
you thank you for saying so thank you
for agreeing with me because I am I am
outraged about this and nobody ever
nobody ever agrees with me about this
but I'm telling you this they should be
stopped they just let anybody in off the
street I go anybody anybody they
probably letting in just anyone oh I
just need to use a bathroom vers just go
ahead they're probably encouraging
people to come in they hey you need to
use a bathroom people are like I don't
even know maybe just come in and use it
you never know you might need to go he
goes the go he goes you're right you're
right something needs to be done I go
yeah you we should be we should be
talking to the upper management we
should be this is I we need to protest
this is an outrage and then we hear the
toilet flush the guy who's in the in the
bathroom is obviously done and he and he
gets out and I and the the guy says to
me he goes you get me man you get me he
goes hey do you need to go ahead of me I
go yeah absolutely and I go ahead
of I go ahead of him into the bathroom
I'm exactly the guy he's complaining
about it was like a small victory for me
cuz I I'm ABS I'm absolutely against
that everything that he was
saying he was just so damn intimidating
I decided to agree with him but I was AB
anybody who should use a bathroom in my
opinion should be allowed to use a
bathroom I think it's uh it's inhumane
to restrict people who need to use a
bathroom from using it and my friend
said when I told him the story he said
the only thing that would have been
funnier was if I used the of the toilet
paper in there and then he needed to use
it and he got
it oh my god well it was an absolute
pleasure getting to talk to Carl Riner
and you're going to get to hear that in
a second and the most amazing thing was
that after doing the interview he gave
me a call a few days later and invited
me for what was an incredible experience
where I got to spend an evening with him
and Mel Brooks and that's a whole
another story onto itself that maybe
I'll tell it some other time but it
there's a lot there's a lot for for me
to say about it and to be sitting with
these two Heroes of mine was uh well it
was it was more than just special I'll
tell you that it was it was incredibly
meaningful to me and we had a wonderful
time and we talked a lot and we talked
about music and at the end Carl gave me
some CDs that his late wife Estelle
Riner had recorded and I've been
listening to them all week and they're
just absolutely wonderful and they're
inspiring they're so inspiring
especially because of the fact that she
started her singing career in her 60s
and had a career for over 30
years and if that's not motivation for
anybody out there that if you have a
dream that you want to follow that it's
not too late you better go and do it
well nothing will be because I sometimes
get down about the fact that I'm 31 and
I see guys who are starting out in their
teens as Comedians and they're shooting
up to success and I feel old and I'm not
old I'm young and I've always dreamt of
being on Saturday Night Live and
sometimes I think well that dream can't
be anymore I'm 31 it's too late and I
and I got to tell you something this
really recharged my battery and it
really made me think you know what I'm
going to I'm going to go for it I'm
going to figure this out I'm in this
eating disorder program now I'm going to
lose some weight I'm going to sharpen up
my character showcase and I'm going to
audition for Saturday Night Live I'll do
it and I'll get on it and if I don't get
on it it I'll do something else some
I'll get on another sketch show of
course there's nothing like Saturday
Night Live but I will get on a sketch
show I'm going to make things happen I'm
only 31 years old I'm a kid for crying
out loud and I found Estelle riner's CDs
to be incredibly inspiring and I'm going
to play a song from one of her CDs for
you at the end of the show okay
everybody without further
Ado my
talk with Carl Riner well except for the
intro song that's a slight further Ado
but other than that coming up right now
my talk with Carl Riner
enjoy hello and welcome to Moder day
philosophers modern day philosophers
having failed to pay attention in school
Danny LEL now older and wiser will
attempt to learn basic philosophy 101
our young hero will be joined by today's
top comedians philosophers all their own
ladies and gentlemen here's Danny
LEL
[Applause]
philosophers it's an honor to be here
it's wonderful to meet you so say you
all right oh so so
arguing no I'm I'm happy to be any place
you know when you get to be 92 you're
just happy that your brain is is working
enough so that you make sense of words
that come into your head and your
impressions are so spoton they used to
be good I used to was it young every
young comedian uses Impressions to get
into the to put their foot in the door
everybody wants to hear about the great
stars and you give them a taste of it I
think more your generation than mine
were very big on Impressions the
comedian absolutely you don't hear them
now there there are only one or two
really good Impressionists around these
days do you think it became a taboo or
what do you think it is I have no idea
Governor really I have no idea I also
have no idea why people are so enamored
of these rappers and and they they don't
say very much but they say a lot they
use a lot of words to say
nothing and uh and I would rather
hear pencils I'd rather hear a song with
lyrics I guess that's why not too many
of them tweet you don't see too many
rappers on Twitter I I tweet a lot I
tweet every day I enjoy your tweets oh
you do that's good that's one of the
things that tweet teaches you a synness
yeah as a writer for so many years is
that a skill that You' already crafted
before Twitter I imagine I guess yes I I
realized that I'm I didn't even know I
was a writer until I the book started
coming out I mean I I think I became a
writer because in the Army I was
separated from my wife for three almost
two two and a half three years and we
wrote every day and I wrote four or five
page letters a day once I wrote her 17
letters of six pages in one day and that
be really I think that's how I thoughted
to become a writer do you think emails
nowadays have the same effect as letters
or no not at all so no they're not as
personal and not as long and there's not
you know this and it's not a phone call
is better see my girlfriend all the time
but I don't think we we have that strong
of uh written connection as I would if
we wrote actual letters try going to the
dinner together I'm working on it I've
been I have a savings fund about 3 years
from now I ought to be able to take her
to dinner I enjoyed the poem you wrote
In the book you wrote a poem OED to the
btics Bountiful yes yeah it reminded me
of Robbie Burns Ed to a mouse I don't
know that no no you you know Robert
Burns the I know you don't know oh we
Sleek it kurin timorous beasy oh what a
panic in thy breasy oh that's wonderful
y
we I would be kissed to come Andy that's
about as much as I can remember and
you're do it very well you're a good
performer oh thank you well going back
to the book being called I just
remembered the followup to I remember me
by the way I'm doing another book now
I'm about 40 pages into it it's called
um what I had
forgotten and I'm really 40 pages into
it and I have a at least a dozen more
chapters I've written seven CH eight
chap nine chapters I imagine you could
do many many more of these well you have
to hang around to do them right yes 92
it's I by the way I worked my you know
92 is a a long time but not long enough
so I've decided to find out how many Nan
seconds
I've lived in how many Nan seconds I
will live till 90 94 if I go at 94 how
many Nan seconds I have have a written
down it's very interesting and you
picked 94 because of Estelle Estelle
left at 94 yes and and she was 8 years
older than me so she's this year's her
hund would have been her 100th year
right I look at the every morning I wake
up and I watch I first thing I read is
the old bits to see what age people are
going so whether they're and they're
mostly younger than I am today there
were a couple hundred year olds that was
very heartening right do you think if
the ages just got higher and higher
you'd have more and more hope is that
what you're yes you do absolutely well
you know the the mean age during the
Middle Ages was 40 years old 42 43 and
we've got it up to now 70 or 80 now how
if you could live to be any age how old
would you want to live uh as long as I'm
functioning m mentally I think it'd be
all right once things start to hurt and
you and you have trouble maneuvering if
you fall down a lot you know what once
your while your brain is working it
seems you want to hang around and when
there are good programs to be seen still
on television to tonight there are a
couple I want to see so as long as TV is
good and the mind is working tonight um
I'm just taped it I just Toot It my
favorite performer of all one of my old
Time Performance order McDonald is on
Letterman tonight and I'm just hoping
she does a piece from a new thing about
Billy Holiday my wife was enamored of
Billy holiday and I have a piece in my
book about Billy I think it's in this
book oh yes yes yes you how do you know
I read the book oh you read the oh you
that's right you did yeah that's it it
is in this book you know what I liked uh
you you mentioned that you picked up a
Fascination for IR
music yes I'll sing a song for you if
you like oh I'd love it I going right
now when I was about eight or n years
old my father had a friend named Max
calus he was a German Jewish gentleman
and he had a brother called John Calvin
who sang on W radio in New York every
Saturday he had a 15minute show and he'd
say and here's a song me mother taught
me when I was in me Mother's KN and he'd
sing an Irish song and I love those song
and one of the first songs I remember
was tumbled down Shack and aone and I
said to my father I want to be an Irish
tenner he said well you can't you're
Jewish I said but he's an Irish T and he
he you can be an a Jewish singer singing
Irish songs so that's what I hope to
become someday I'm a long way from home
and it's there that i' roam to L A and
Far Over the Sea oh me heart is there
where the skies are so fair and all irin
is calling
me there are eyes that are sad as they
watch for the lad from the Tumbl down
sharing at loone and I pray for the day
I'll be sailing away to All In Me Mother
me
home oh I want to go back to that Tumbl
down Shack where the bright roses bloom
around the door just to pillow me head
on me old trundle bed just to hear me
dear mother once
more there's a bright Guiding Light
guiding Me Home Tonight Down The Long
Road of white
Cobblestone down the road that leads
back to that Tumbl down Shack to the
that Tumbl down
Shack in
a all right that's beautiful see that
you know that I brought it up cuz we
have this in common when I was a kid I
said the same thing to my dad I I'm not
kidding I I thought it was a very
interesting connection that we shared I
also wanted to be an Irish Tenor well
you know there was that particular song
by the way was sung by almost everybody
in the world starting with Dr kic way
back goinging to Bing Crosby everybody
recorded that song well you did a
beautiful rendition hey thank you yeah I
used to listen to the Clancy Brothers
and memorize the oh really do you want
to hear one yes all right there was
Johnny mled and McGee and me and a
couple two or three went to spree one
day we had a bu or two which we knew out
a blue and a beer and whiskey FLW and we
all felt gay we visited mcken M man
humty D we then went into swans our
stomachs were to pack we ordered out a
feed which indeed we did need and we
finished it with speed but we still felt
slack Johnny mled do turn a red white
and blue as a plate of Irish stew he
soon put out of sight he shouted out in
core with a roar for some more that he'd
never felt before such a keen appetite
he ordered eggs and ham bread and jam
what a cram him we couldn't CH though we
tried to love a best for no matter what
they brought cold or hot matter not went
down and like a shot and he Stills stood
the test swallow L by the yard we get
scarred we thought it m a hard when the
waiter brought the bill he told him to
give or but he swore he could L twice as
much again and more before he not his F
he nearly S A trough full of BR and mcra
he'll Dev the tablecloth if you own all
them in when the waiter brought the
charge mleo felt so large he began to
scge and Barge and his blood went in
fire he began to curse and swear tear
his hair in Despair and to finish the
affair called the shopman liar shopman
he threw out and a doubt he a cloud me
do he kicked about like an old football
tarted up his clothes broke his nose I
suppose he'd killed him in a few blows
no time at all M be to H and to grow but
he threw an empty ball at the
shopkeeper's head he hit po Micky fin
peeled the skin from his chin and the
ruptur to begin and we all fought and
bled the peelers did arrive man life for
a five and thus it made a dry for us all
to March away we paid for all the mate
that we ate stood a trait and went home
to remate on thee that day now that is
one beautiful rendition of a song I've
never heard before you win hands down
you win first prize and I got ninth you
know what I realized and appear and only
two of us are competing well no I think
you win first prize but I I'll tell you
what no that was brilliantly done
brilliantly done I realized that there's
no other use for me knowing that song in
my whole life it had to serve a purpose
that I'd remembered it and all these
years have gone by and it's never served
me any purpose until I realized Carl
Riner and I both share I had a chat with
Ferguson on the show and I was saying
that there was a whole thing about my
one of my favorite human beings that
ever lived was Pete Seager a great great
great man I met him in Hawaii once and
we were talking about folk songs he he
sang for a 100,000 people and he make he
got them all to sing along he gave gave
them the lyrics and they sang them back
and it was thrilling I've never seen
anything like it in my life and we're
talking about folk songs is you know mo
a lot of folk songs mainly the the ones
from the little towns he's guys used to
get together they're all boy he's
they're very bardy and he sang me one of
the borest songs I've ever heard the
ball of bellamore have you ever heard no
I told Ferguson about that and he say oh
you can't sing that on this show you oh
know you can't but he forced me to sing
it so he could say don't sing that don't
sing that and I sang it up to the the
the Rhymes but the Rhymes were so dirty
that you you don't have to say what the
rhyme was you knew what it was it's
going to be the dirtiest thing ever
right can I get a piece certainly I'll
give you a piece but I won't go to the
Rhymes here they're ladies
PR oh have you heard the story of the
ball of bellamore 4 and20 prostitutes
lying on the floor singing who do you
this time who will do you no the man who
did you last time he can of do you knew
the old fat Maiden she was there she was
in a state of fits swinging from the
chandelier and landing on
her anyway it goes like that there are
four more lyrics like that wor each get
worse and worse and worse there was
screwing there was [ __ ] in the paror
and [ __ ] In The Sticks you can hardly
hear the music for the swishing
of know it was and but he he forced me
to sing it and he kept saying don't do
that but it was I can't wait to see if
he puts that on the air or he just did
it for a studio audience how how many
late night show appearances do you think
you've done in your lifetime
91,4 wow you have it right
yes right down to the wait 65 I just
remembered I did one on Tavis Smiley
which is coming on this Friday what's
the trick to being great on these talk
shows be yourself don't try to be
anybody else or be a good
impersonator you know I have something
worth selling so you're there for a
purpose usually I remember going on
Carson a few times and having nothing to
sell just he needed somebody calling I
have nothing to sell come on anyway he
said do you get nerves when you go on TV
not really did you ever yeah the proper
proper amount of nerves yeah you just
worry that you you don't trip or
something but no when you when you go on
with people you who you trust you know
they're going to ask you to co it's when
you go on with some who doesn't how to
interview that it makes it tough then
you just take it over and go right you
never get self-conscious only if my fly
is open and they find out later yeah you
know I when I'm on stage I always get
paranoid my fly is open at some point
when I'm on stage I'm not kidding you
almost every time I've done a show where
it's like an hourong show at some point
in the show I'm thinking I hope my fly
is not
open that's why why why is it going so
well
yeah well you see where they the look at
the people's eyes see if their eyes are
on your forehead or they're on your
crotch it's a good trick yes what if if
they're moving around then you you got
to be more interesting than the fly you
know if I'm more interesting than an
open fly then I'm really good I think
that's the trick maybe to being the best
comedian yes you got to go up with an
open fly every time till you get so
strong that the people can only focus on
you and not the fly yeah that's right if
you're if you have an open fly and you
can keep them looking at your face
you're really a great comedian that's
got to be the secret to it all
absolutely
yeah uh you brought up the the song on
Ferguson reminded me of a great story in
your book which was the girl who
couldn't tell couldn't pronounce her own
name yes true story uh I I met her at a
a
Uso gathering in Washington DC I just
was
going to Georgetown I learned to be a
French interpreter so I met her and she
was the first one at the dance and I was
one of the first guys there she came
over to me and she said her name she
said hi she said my name is Joyce Van so
she had a middle name George Jessica
[ __ ] she said and I said just she
repeated it what's yours and I said call
Riner and she says Kyle Ry she's BR such
a thick a beautiful girl wearing a
beautiful dress long blonde hair and
very very sweet and you could see she
was a naive naive person and I said I
said how are you spelling that name she
says how it's
pronounced k u n TZ I says Ah I says I'm
German extraction my father spoke German
I says that's in Germany that's
pronounced Kun she that's silly is that
no which was a very very soft way of
telling her I thought that was very yeah
and I and but I was really serious about
it I wasn't trying to fool as you know
something and I I was serious I said if
you pronounce the way you're you're
pronouncing it most of the people are
going to take it to mean the female
sexual female the female sex organ and
she said oh that's silliest thing I ever
heard you know and she wouldn't and my
friend came over sa pomerans came over
to say hello and she introduced herself
as Joyce come and he said he he punched
me you know he thought I put her up to
it and we the two of us really for the
rest of the afternoon or for a good part
of it we convinced her to we and we
taught her how to say Kun we said you're
going to get a lot of people giggling at
you and then and the reason they're
giggling is they think you're saying
vagina you definitely have a part of you
that you want to help you you really I
see it in a lot of your stories is that
you do really truly want to help people
the guy with the combover was another
good story well two guys Neil Simon I
thought that was fantastic that you cut
off his combover that's right no that
was that
was for those who don't know what we're
talking about uh I have a picture in the
book of uh General MacArthur who had the
best combover combover means you part
the you part your hair near near your
ear and if you have hair that really
should be cut off you comb it over to
make it look like you're covering the
bow spot right and I this young writer
was I was doing the Van Dyke Show at the
time and looking for writers to help me
and this young writer submitted one of
was and I said I can't read your script
he say why not I said because I don't
trust you said why don't you trust me
right you don't know me he's me I but
I'm looking at your hair that your hair
is you combed over it's a fake you know
you're probably you're trying to hide
your boldness and instead of looking at
your face I'm looking at your hairline
can't look at you so he what are you
talk and I
I I had a got a scissor from ma the
Harry C was my agent the mors office I
had had a comb and I cut his hair and I
and he he he looked he looked everybody
said you look much better all of them
and he looked at himself hey this isn't
bad and I listened to the script was no
good but his hair was better he did read
the a couple of years later at
the S Caesar we got two writers the the
Simon Brothers doc Simon which is Neil
Simon was doing a coover he was very
young but he was had sparse hair and I
did the same thing for him in Max lean's
office I gave him a comb over and his
wife said oh this is so much nice you
don't have the same thing and I cont I
say I contributed to his to his uh
successes uh one of the probably the
greatest writer in in our in our country
of plays play right could be because of
the haircut maybe would I no question he
would have been dismissed otherwise no
question about it they looked at his
plays instead of his hair you mention in
your first book your relationship with
the tup pays that you used to have the
toupe so it's like an ongoing theme the
hair yes I well I never actually uh I
always wore didn't I never wore a toue
when I went normal living and I remember
meeting Frederick Murray who wore a toue
all the time and he says you're not
wearing a pay how do you decide when to
wear it I said well it's a it's like a
tuxedo you you want to get dressed up if
you want to be fully dressed and make an
impression of handsomeness or to I said
I never wear it if there's less than a
thousand people I said if I go to an
event and there if you want to be I
won't wear it and I always made a big
point of where when I wore it I would
say I'm wearing my two pain tonight it's
an important event you know cuz I was
never wanted people to look at my head
and I said it in the book people say is
that a toe you're wearing you'd say yes
and they say you know you can you can
never tell you can't know right it is
unfair to make people stand there and
wonder it's the same maybe the combover
is more honest than the person with a
toupe that doesn't let you know that's
right you know it's it's interesting CU
My Generation you don't see Tays and and
you never see coover so I think there
were definitely people like you that
made a stand at some point in in history
and said we're going to bald and and
that's and that's cool I put Larry David
in the group oh yes absolutely Fighters
for the bald
Community yes be honest because now
people are are happy to be bald so I
think I think you changed the world
maybe that maybe we're talking to one
last hold out who's still has his hand
right on his head right now as we're
talking not me
no it's so funny uh so many of your
memories
are in my head now with the transfer of
you know through the books I feel like
I've gotten to also live your life I
feel like I really know you you don't
know me it's unfair you know Mel who
sits there every night almost right
there he says you know I've written like
five or six I I don't know how many
books I written five six seven I wrote
only one novel which was called
um all kinds of love and I've written
but they're all bi biographical I've
written I write a and I realize it's the
easiest thing to write about you don't
have to research it it's there and
things pop in your head why is it so
important to you to preserve these
memories it's not important it's just
fun it's just for fun yeah yeah fun I
don't think it's important no it it's
important it is important in the sense
that I once discovered not too long ago
that I'm a really the world's M the
world's MC I'm a master ceremonies at
heart I've been able to do it since I'm
18 17 18 years old when I went away to
the mountains I was able to do game
shows and introduce people without even
with no script I would just get out
there and be funny and I get I never
have anything prepared I just get up and
it's a gift that I have and it's being
an MC is pointing to people and saying
here look at this guy you're going to
really enjoy it Steve Allen was the
biggest one for that he loved getting to
point to people and say look at this guy
look what he does I've done that all my
life and I've done it very comfortably
without ever I never have to prepare I
never do prepare if I prepare it's going
to come out stilted so having read both
of your books and I try to figure out as
any young comedian would what what makes
somebody successful what makes somebody
successful in life not just in comedy
and what struck me from your books is
your ability to think very quickly on
your your feet it helps yes it helps uh
and you and and the same thing happens
in front of the typewriter you're
thinking on your keyboard very quickly
and you're changing all the time it's
you never somebody says you never finish
a an art project you you stop right
that's right and I today I was ready to
type I wait this and I fix and I really
improved it there's no question about
making improvements but you can keep
improving forever
the thing that strikes me as the best
example is in your first book when you
talked about the FBI interrogating you
oh yes as a communist yes yes and how
quick and sharp you were with your
responses well I decided right away I
was they were charming and I said I'm
going to out charm them and going to
going if they you if they have nothing
to lean against if they're pushing
against and you're pushing back they'll
push hard it so you wor you fall over
together so I I was reading that and I
was thinking what if I was in that
situation IM I would be there would be
fear it there was definitely fear but
there's also the a very good actor I was
acting feess you were acting FS but you
were fear fearful course of course in
the back of my head I said my God
everything can go down it was the
McCarthy era they were looking for
Communists and there was all started
with a a grosser up in New York Ryan New
York is a place looking for Communists
everywhere I hear people talk about how
now with the NSA listening in on phone
calls and and everything it's becoming
like that again as somebody who's been
through it do you think that's true well
unless they use
it everybody knows what everybody's
doing with my God your
phones it's unless somebody uses it
nefariously it doesn't matter I don't
care if they know what they know about
me you don't think we're heading to
another time like that I don't think so
I think it's so open that it's going to
be yeah
they will use pieces of information
badly you know the right-wing has been
doing it all the time they got a piece
of almost
information John Stewart God bless him
he puts it right out there so perfectly
and Co the two guys for for and Rachel M
there are certain people who know how to
tell you what the truth is the Fox
network makes up facts and then they
they act on them they continue to act on
facts they've made up that's why I love
Mark Twain he put it all out there for
everybody he was the best ever what
about him specifically well he covered
every subject in the world that was
worth covering and uh as a matter of
fact
he 50 years after he died they published
a thing called letters from the earth
that was not allowed to be published
that night because it was Blasphemous
and his wife or somebody kept they said
was no it won't be published till 50
years later they published it and
somebody asked me to read it you know
tape it and I it one of the proudest
things I've ever done it doesn't sound
like me it doesn't it was nothing it was
the best acting I've ever done it was
because I really Mor to Mark Twain I was
on this is your life once and they
wanted to know what they they asked my
wife what did she give me what kind of
car she said he has a car what's he like
she says Mark Twain so they gave me a
sign copy one of the books actually has
his original manuscript pasted into the
book wonderful and 100 you know 50 books
so he's he's the the guy what sets him
apart for you about from all the other
writers what's he doing that they didn't
do such honesty and such humor my gosh I
mean if you're going to read one book in
your life read Huckleberry Finn somebody
once said and the other one is
a um King Author
yank and
kinging oh yes I've read that one yeah
that one has everything in it if you
want to know about what makes societies
and governments tick that's in it I mean
for all time it's brilliant it's
absolutely
brilliant and he wrote a thing called
what is man A little short book what is
man and he this I never even thought he
says what is
selflessness what is selfishness and
what is
selflessness he he everybody fixing
they're selfless he says everybody is
selfish there's very little selflessness
he said well what about
the selfless act he says like uh if
somebody saw a little F fall in the
water and you jump in to save somebody's
life isn't that selfless no is that
selfish you would not be able to live
with yourself if you not didn't do that
there are certain things you do because
you know you can't live with yourself if
you didn't do them if you didn't help a
a person in need and selfishness really
exists so there is no truly selfless
person actor person he that's what he's
saying you know I it's it's a small book
what ises man is worth three man he told
man he talks to man you know man God God
man is God man or whatever it seems this
seems like a perfect transition into
philosophy since that's basically what
we're talking about anyway so the
philosopher that I have chosen for you
is somebody I'm sure you're familiar
with I'm not okay well then because I
haven't read many philosop books on
philosophy well do you know about Moses
myones I've heard of him he's the the
the big Guru of the of the of our sect
right yes what did he say the ROM bomb
ROM bom he said a lot of things I that I
knew I knew about the ROM bom I I don't
know what he said maybe I'll know the
quote you're going to get um well I'll
tell you why we chose him for you okay
uh we we chose him because of your
famous record with Mel Brooks the
2,000-year old man right right and uh
figured you're half the record all right
my Mones is a thousand years old that's
a thousand each so I'll give you a
thousand- year old philosopher okay half
a 2,000 year old man my Mones was born
in 1135 and lived to 1204 69 years and
he lived in Cairo Egypt my monties
thinks that our minds are the tool to
find truth but we must accept that they
are flawed tools
for example let's examine proving the
existence of God myones is a proponent
of negative theory meaning we describe
God based on what he isn't he never dies
he is not confined to one form if we
attempt to describe God by what he is
eternal we are putting our finite Vision
on an infinite thing and hence doing it
in Justice well first of all I'll
discuss with you your thoughts on God
cuz I well you know I think I've got my
monties beat I got to figure it out oh
yeah yes a long time ago I'm under
confirmed died in the wo atheist I know
I'm an atheist and and when people say
how can you be an atheist I says well
let's take God I said you are God man is
God human beings have invented God
because they needed him I says every
thought ever done is done by man
nobody put the thought in your head you
had the thought very a long long time
ago I said when Moses went up the side
of the mountain and there was always
smart men in society one smart guy a
little smarter than everybody else and
and somebody gave this example once and
I never forgot it they said during the
um the methal days human beings did not
know from whence came children where did
children come from how did they come how
did they get it took a very smart
Neanderthal to put together the sex act
and the birth act they were months apart
nine months apart nobody ever said if
you do that this happens they didn't
know it one smart guy said hey this guy
never did that and he never had that so
maybe that's and one it's always one man
who figured out something there's always
one brighter person it has been
throughout centuries you know we have U
you know Freud and Marx and Christ and
people who thought Moses went up on the
hill and I'm I'm sure this is absolutely
true the synchronistic thing of a
lightning striking when he's getting
these ideas I really think there was a
thunderbolt when he was writing down
these things but those were his ideas
Thou shalt not you know cover thy
neighbor's wife thou sh and and I said
those things were put down and when he
came down he said look at the ideas I
came down with they said who are you
he's look at the ideas that came down
that God has given me to give you
because the Flesh of lightning came and
I said so man needed God because he
there were things happening they had
nothing to know you know they used to
pray to rocks they pray to a con cell
they they picked before they had a the
monotheism they prayed to many gods they
had you know crazy looking statues they
were praying to do you think that means
there's a need for prayer it's a need to
know and they don't know how to who will
answer their their really profound
questions where did I come from how did
I get here what are we doing here and I
said men is God he has figured it out my
God the things he's figured out how we
are now living to 80 90 years old
because we know how to kill diseases
that used to kill you like this in the
desert my God you know and people got
smart very very early on I said you know
that my father used to tell me about the
one of the
traditions in Jewish uh culture is when
you cut your fingernails you burn them
you put them in a thing and burn them I
said where did that come from he says in
the desert you know he said um a lot of
dirt on the fingernails the and they
they said mikum devils are on in in dirt
under the fingernails so they got to get
rid of them otherwise you'll get sick
and they knew about figured out there
was an unseen thing called mikum germs
man very way early back man is smart
then they figured out they got
telescopes they invented microscopes and
telescopes and all those things so man
is very very smart and he needed God and
I say those who who use God who doesn't
exist as for Comfort I said it's all
well and good I whatever gives you
comfort you you pray to something that's
not fair but that's all right what do
you use for
comfort the fact that I know there's no
God and I have to do it myself you do it
yourself you go you you have something
bothering you with your foot you go to a
foot doctor your brain can't figure
something out there's a guy thing called
Freud who invented Psychiatry who has
now been proven that it's way he was way
off Bas and some things they other
improvements on him including a guy
named beon who came lately and I have a
daughter who just aote a Beyond beon she
wrote a book she's a psychoanalyst and
she has written
about what how the mind works and what
what it does to the body and it's an
extraordinary piece of work so but it's
a person it's I know she's a person
she's my daughter have you ever prayed
no never oh yeah sure but you pray to
yourself you know oh come on let's this
yeah sure of course I don't it's not I'm
not praying to anything you're hoping
that's what it is you're hope you're
hoping that this works out what what
going back to the idea with the Jews I
always think about this as a Jew what
why why do you think we've been
persecuted so so much I have no idea uh
well you know something uh people who
don't have
much sometimes Elevate themselves by
making somebody lower than them making
somebody a scapegoat for your in in in
inabilities saying they they they're
Terri I think that's it and because they
were they were literate I think they
were very UPS said that they were
illiterate and did things a lot that the
pagans couldn't do but they but they
weren't weren't Waring they weren't
warlike at one point at one point they
were you know they were they did do
conquering battle and what was it the
Philistines and sure the King David
times yeah we had a we had a few good
War years yes
absolutely having fought in World War I
you must have thought about this quite a
bit over the years right oh my God that
was the fact that that a a a whole
billions millions of people could accept
them a maniac that goals or guring GBL
figured out a way to get all the people
in the country together United by hating
something and they pick on the Jews who
were rif for rating at the time because
uh they were different you know anybody
anyway so that was the thing I will
never ever understand why all those
people went along with it and I never
forgive them for that for and and and I
I praised those people there was a book
who just came out I just ordered it
about a guy who was writing about
against Hitler for years in years in
Germany a new book it's been one of the
biggest books in Europe for hundreds the
dozens of years just came here I just
ordered it I forgot the name of it
anyway I I think it's interesting I mean
I I grew up was sent to Yeshiva so I
grew up very religious and moved away
from it now I moved back towards it I
think I believe that belief in God is
something that's either instilled in you
when you're young or not it's true my
father didn't go to sh or synagogue he
believed in God but he didn't go to
synagogue and my friends all went to
synagogue and the only reason I went is
to not be alone on the high holidays I
went with them that we didn't have to
pay in those days but I I never took it
seriously do you think there's any value
to any of it the Traditions or anything
oh Traditions are always if the
Traditions have good things in them sure
they're good you know the the tradition
of getting together for dinner for for
for family to get to dinner forc them to
get to get dinner during SATA that's
lovely yeah but to pray to somebody who
doesn't exist is you know is pray look
unto yourself look until I own self be
true and you'll be okay
organized religion and my first thing
that comes to my mind is the Catholic
Church which they really not how to
organize my wife and I went to Mexico
City one day and we went to guadalahara
to saw that absolutely magnificent
Temple we were on the day of Ascension
when people are crawling on their hands
and knees to give arms to the church
these poor people be dragged people in
tatters with their knees bleeding
crawling the Last Mile to the church
with an with a little token of money
which they laid on the the church's
step and I'm saying and I'm looking at
this gold door and I'm saying there it
is there's what you that's ridiculous
the pope is walking around with with
these gold shoes and a gold hat and
millions of people are praying to him
and what do they get back they get back
peace right we'll give you peace Eternal
peace so you never believed in your
whole life no even as a kid and a kid I
probably did I mean I my course I went
to show my I know I probably
didn't no I my father said he did so I
guess I did well I'm going to keep
reading the myi stuff we can keep we can
okay keep analyzing it there is one
disease which is widespread and from
which men rarely escape the disease
varies in degree in different men I
refer to this that every person thinks
his mind more clever and more learned
than it is I have found that this
disease has attacked many an intelligent
person they express themselves not only
upon the science with which they're
familiar but upon other Sciences about
which they know nothing if met with
Applause so does this disease itself
become
aggravated just because somebody thinks
they're they're smart it doesn't mean
they're smart I mean you're can be
educated but not inventive smart and
those people kid themselves when they
think that they because they have
learned all the things they were taught
to learn they they had they had a a way
of digesting stuff that was invented by
somebody else and they and they learned
it and they became doctors they became
lawyers judges but people who think
clearly about things innovatively MH
those are those are those those are the
real thinkers those are the real and
most people ordinary people can have
that and never be um never be lorded as
doctors you know right I think there's a
difference Common Sense between being
clever and being intelligent and being
being educated You Can Be You Can Be
Clever and you don't you can be educated
and be very dumb
too give me an example well learning
things by
roote really understanding what makes
people tick what makes things tick it's
a rare it's a rare gift and some some
people some people who have degrees have
that but most people don't I don't think
do you think the older you get the more
you understand if you understood it a
little at the beginning you will and
continue on that path if you never
understood you will never understand and
you will think you understand and make
fun of people who think they understand
right so so you have to have something
to build on
are you still as young in your mind as
you were I think so I think so because
I'm able to come up with things that uh
are new for me and so at 92 if if I can
do that I will stay around as long as
that keeps going what about marriage in
this business of Comedy so many fail
and how do you balance a a brilliant
career in Show Business like you did and
a and a good relationship is there a
trick to that yeah sure there is a trick
my wife he once said it somebody asked
of her right there sitting
there what makes a a good
marriage she says how do you how do you
live so long she said she says marry
someone who can stand
you now you can stand who can stand you
if you can stand all the little
picadillos you don't leave you well if
it's your right and you hang in there
because you marry that person for a
reason in the first place and you forget
it sometimes because so many things come
come into the
mix positive and negative things but uh
where are you going if you if you get
divorce you'll only do it again you make
the same mistake twice now we were
married for 65 years and and uh it was
they were great great re to this day I I
say I made a little adage in one of the
books you noticed the new adage which is
70 is the new 65 when people ask me how
long have I've been married I say 65 and
one day it occurred to me he right my
wife was married 65 years but I'm still
married she's still within me I think of
her all the time so I'm married 70 years
so I'm saying that's the new ad 70 is
new 65 and sadly you can apply you can
change it to 50 is the new 45 or sadly
12 is the new seven you know depending
on how long right you stay married
before one passes on
as I get older I feel like time moves
faster it does no question about it so
at 92 does it continue to I think it's
slowing down no it doesn't oh it doesn't
I I don't think it moves faster I'm
moving slower that's what it is yeah I
really move slower and I'm very aware of
it when I walk around a block very aware
of it I I found it fascinating in your
book how you talked so much about how
you think about your own mortality one
one line in your book that that made me
laugh out loud was the idea that the
mortician would admire your
toenails yeah long time ago I was when I
used to run around the track at Beverly
Hill so I was running a mile a day for
every day and I had fine looking
toenails and all of a sudden they got I
got ingrown and they were had to go to
dietr and and he says wait a second he I
said what happened he says I said I'm
wearing is you wearing the wrong
size shoe I said I'm wearing a 10 which
is my size he 10 and a half is your size
you're banging up against the shoe when
you run so I got a bigger shoe and he
gave me something to to put on the nail
it took years till they straighten out
again so both nails look good and I put
this little stuff on it but I have shoes
that so I said they look perfect and I
took pictures of it I said when someday
mortici is going to say look at the a
92y old man or 95 whatever yeah he's got
very young Nails hopefully he's as
attentive to detail as you are I says
well if he reads this if he gets the
chance to read the book he'll find out
how he can have a young nail yeah I
think anytime if if I was a mortician
anytime I had someone die who had a book
out about their life I'd want I want to
read it
before but also you're a comedian you
pick apart the little things I don't
know that most people do that I don't
know that most people would pay
attention to the toenails yeah if a
comedian was was taking care of the body
almost 100% they would say that yeah
yeah you you think about everything why
do you think we do that as comedians why
do we observe that's that's why we're
ComEd that's why people um enjoy
comedians because they do notice the
things that people would have noticed
did notice but didn't take note of you
know they been passing by but they and
you you pointed and they start thinking
about oh my God I have the same thing
and I and they laugh they laugh in
recognition you're talking about them
talking about their relation to their
wife their relation to their kids what
if we were just called noticers instead
of comedians yeah notices right well
this next noticer he notices a lot
you're going to love this guy nothing
gets past
him well what talking about the big
questions that you say people invent God
to answer these big questions what do
you make of them what do you think is
the purpose of life what do you
think that's the point the purpose of
life uh as far as I'm concerned is not
to foul not to foul uh the atmosphere or
to send nourishing people into the world
bring children into the world with a
good sense of values that do not impress
oppress other
people just a good people and by by
example make make for a better world for
the sake of discussion I I'll ask you
why why is it important important to
have a good
World
well the we are we are we have only we
have one planet and way we don't think
I'm thinking about the guy who reads
about says the the the planet is doomed
to doomed to to die within 9 million
years 9 billion whatever 9 billion years
right and he says did he what did he say
he said 9 billion Oh I thought he said 9
million yeah
I don't know why we
think yeah uh what do you make of death
what do you think death is it's it's
going into the the best sound sleep
you've ever had where you really sleep
and you wake up in the morning you don't
have a you've had no dreams and just
come from you fall asleep and that's it
there's nothing I really think there's a
part of you that's very poetic not just
the the one about Lois but there there's
definitely a a poetry to the way you
write one line from your book that that
stuck with me that I thought was
particularly poetic was I'm happy every
day that I have a
shadow Yeah well yeah I was leaning on
the wall and I saw my shadow and I said
oh if you have a shadow you're alive you
know you always look for signs of of
life in in in your aging body yeah the
uh the um yeah I have a whole slew of uh
uh indications you're on your way out
yeah you're checking out you yeah
checking out yeah I like that one I
we've talked on the show before about uh
Carlin and the euphemisms the passing
away checking out's a good one yeah
checking out I I have not chapter I love
the title of checkups of lay checkouts
mhm CU one day I found out I had just
accidentally I had uh point with three
or four four or five doctors all
accidental one was a hearing doctor one
was a foot doctor one was a for my ear
something but there was uh just
accidentally I saw in my book I said how
did they all come on one day so and I
realized but the more times you checkup
your check out you're probably putting
years onto your life so checkups laay
checkouts that was a good title chapter
yeah I like that one and how you got n
nine in in two days and the interesting
thing is I could never think of the word
La after that I was saying what the
hell's the name of that chapter I can't
I never use the word la la
right the words come to you is you need
them they store in a place that is cold
storage until you for some reason your
your brain starts heating up melts the
cold storage and words flop down out of
the cold stores that you never knew you
knew that's an always a thing that
surprises me I didn't know I knew that
word word yeah it's it's all up there I
even know how to spell it
yeah I I felt good as an overweight guy
when I read about the shadow I thought
hey I got a lot of Shadow by the way I'm
going to talk to you about your
overweight before you leave every time I
read about it you're cutting years off
your life and it's and it when you find
out there is a way to do it that makes
sense it's unbelievable I mean I'm
watching I just happened to see Maria
Osman she was like this she
and there are so many ways to do it but
you got to do it because you're cutting
out years of your life and you you
obviously got a lot of work to do yet I
know I do do you think about I try all
the time I just enrolled in another
eating disorder program it's it's a
constant battle for me well keep at it
and and think in terms of smaller
portions and fish and chicken instead of
and forget about this Steaks and Chops
just throw them out and and and no
butter you know all throw them and there
were things that are satisfying you know
sherbets instead of ice cream you know
and things like that I knew you were
going to bring this up when I came in
here because you fix the guy's hair and
uh yeah no no this is right yeah but you
and I'm so you're a fixer up gu and I
wouldn't say it to anybody but you
really have a a purpose a really purpose
a purpose on Earth that I and I'm very
uh I applaud I think it's wonderful what
you're doing the stuff you're doing and
I I'd like you to continue to do it
longer than you want to do it longer
than you no longer than you're Prime to
do it all right better better than
longer than you want to do it then I'm
just going to be doing it for a bunch of
years I appreciate that thank you I'm
not kidding and and and I'm I've learned
it by the way accidentally I learned
that if you cut down a portions because
I have to cut down a portion because I
had this osty with it I had something in
my stomach that was almost did me in
uh it's it I it's very satisfying eating
portions small portions eating it slowly
and have two or three four or five times
a day but small portions like this
instead of this maybe we'll do a
follow-up interview and I'll be in
better shape okay maybe I could be the
next Neil Simon yes yes yes I feel like
uh there's a magic to to when you save
people right um I wanted to ask you
about work ethic because even when it
comes to Twitter you talk about how you
set aside 10 minutes before you go to
sleep to write tweets yeah so how did
you develop such a good work ethic I
don't know it's it's just it it's
pleasurable I these are things that
please me I sit down at the computer I
look at the email I look at the Twitter
to see if I have to I do a couple
of games of
solitire and I get to work or in in
rever sometimes reverse I work and then
do that after but before I go to bed I
always play a couple games of solitire
do you think that's just to keep your
mind sharp but and I re didn't realize
it but it does keep your mind sharp
keeps your eyes and mind coordinated you
have to oh look at that boom boom I love
when you have move things around before
I go to bed every night I play this game
called Rubik's race where you have to
solve a Rubik's Cube very quickly too
much but it's the same thing it's just
it is that's just something to keep
absolutely but it it's also mind handle
coordination because you're on a you're
on a keyboard and you're looking at yeah
that and I figured out when I play the
game before I go to sleep I have much
more vivid dreams do you do you get
strong dreams when you sometimes yeah
yeah not all not every time and I wish I
did because I go to a psychas once a
week and last week I didn't have any
dream do you do you remember your dreams
I put them down if I don't you write
them down yeah if you don't write them
down you know I forget them I have three
quotes here from my monties and that's
the end of the show okay yeah
do not consider it proof just because it
is written in books for a liar who will
deceive with his tongue will not
hesitate to do the same with his pen so
he's saying in other words oh yeah well
that's absolutely true and and today
mades would have to say about television
and soon as you read that I'm I'm
reading I'm seeing the Fox network yeah
they come up with things and they tell
you they're true and they're not sure
they can they they can present the same
idea in different mediums and you'll
believe it more or less based on how you
see it so mes would be very very very
active today if he were on television I
think if he if he was around now you'd
probably go see him if only for the
medical he was a doctor as well you know
ROM I love that name ROM I like I told
Kylie I'd love to name a kid ROM it's
it's a good strong name it's giving him
a giving him a big a
responsibility yeah I think uh on on his
on his grave site it said from Moses to
Moses there was no one like Moses so uh
from Mo so I was just watching the
what's the name of the Moses picture
that Ten Commandments Ten Commandments
Mel and I will finish watching it last
night what a piece of extraordinary work
as far as the technical things in it
yeah the artwork and the unbelievable
but the story you know is just Sil I'm
surprised nobody's remade it you can't
not you can never redo it like that oh
my God the
uh it's the it's the most elaborately
structured piece of uh film making ever
I mean the the sets alone and the uh the
props I've never seen anything like it
it's worth looking at What attracted you
to directing films I wrote a couple of
films couple films that were directed by
people and I watched the film and I said
oh why do he do that why did he do that
why did he why do he go close up on the
head it's a two shot you want to see the
guy reacting you don't want to cut to
the reaction you want the audience to
look and laugh you cut to the reaction
you're saying laugh they won't laugh if
you do that right I was I so was
somebody directed a couple of the first
films I wrote and I said I better direct
so when I wrote the the U screenplay of
a of a book uh ental laughing mhm I
decided I would I would direct it just
so I would be able to protect protect
the script that's why I edit the show
myself this show yeah absolutely exactly
right and editing is the I think editing
is is almost as perform as important if
not more than the writing or the
performance you do it in your writing
you edit all the time you're right and
no that editing is the the final polish
that nobody can I think a bad editor can
destroy a great film there's no such
thing bad at it you got rid of that
guy is there a secret to show business
I'm sure you've been asked before but is
the to me tell the truth it's very
abstract the whole I mean the business I
don't you know I come out I just moved
out from New York not long ago and so
Hollywood to me it's just this big
monster that I don't understand but
you've known it for your whole
life what what is it what do you well
show business yeah oh it's uh I love it
it's first of all the some of the nicest
wonderful people here you laugh you have
a good your product is you enjoy it as
you make your product you know what
other product do you make over and over
again that you enjoy because you never
make it over and over again you're
making Su something new each time you're
on a belt line making automobiles you're
making fenders you're making fenders
same thing but in in Show Business
you're making new things all the time do
you think you'll Direct another movie no
you get of an age it's directing a movie
is of two things it's social directing
it's keeping everybody happy on the set
and being
there 12 hours a day and then going into
the editing room no I Tes it I think I
stopped directing him when I was in my
80s or something it's too taxing oh it
is taxing I don't think there's any
90-year old directors you talk about in
this book all the character actors that
are forgotten and then you find out that
they died and it makes you happy that
they had a family and yeah well yeah
like for instance little known for I
just happen to read the your bits and
I'm reading about a a a little known you
know and I read the movies in a lot of
movies cuz some of these actors little
small parts in a lot of movies and then
at the end you see he had a good life he
had a wife and children with it would
never made it as a star but he obviously
had a star life as a husband and father
but it doesn't tell tell you in the
obituary how many days he walked around
the house full of anxiety and fear no
that everybody has that do you anxiety I
have sure really well at this AG you
wonder how and when you're going to go
you you don't want you don't want to go
hitting your head on the ground why why
what does it matter it it doesn't matter
but oh you don't want to go in a
hospital that's what I would I said
don't if I have to go to the hospital
give me a so what what what's the trick
to stay young and keep going is it just
something you get up for I get up for
and I say I have my if I didn't have the
computer to go to I don't know what I
would get up for watch television
Jeopardy is fun you know MH but uh not
enough I was so excited to wake up today
I love days when I when I can't wait to
wake up just because I got to do this
today oh that's nice to you this makes
it a a special day it it was marked on
my calendar and well I had two things I
I did today I got new hearing aids
wonderful without them I oh that's
another thing you take your hearing age
out at night and it's so quiet mhm it's
very quiet well that's good at least you
get sound sleep men's hearing goes
earlier than women's for some reason I
don't know why say
[Laughter]
again at times the truth shines so
brilliantly that we perceive it as clear
as day our nature and habit then draw a
veil over our perception and we return
to a Darkness almost as dense as before
what do you make that's people who are
so involved with themselves that they
can't accept the pleasures that are
happening to them on the from the
outside like a clear day a beer day yeah
when your when your burdens are
heavy clear day doesn't seem to do much
except make them seem heavier well that
goes back to the anxiety what we were
talking about yeah right how do you
alleviate the anxiety what what's what
works best to clear your mind zitan I
don't know
I don't know well that's one of my
that's one of my things that I laugh at
so much when they give these new drugs
is do not
take if do not take this drug if you are
prone to sleep eight hours a day eat
food go to the toilet and breathe air
and drink water when you're thirsty if
you have any of those symptoms this will
kill you right yeah here's here's the
last quote from my Mones he says You
must accept the truth
from whatever Source it comes you must
accept the of course why not yeah I
don't think you need to tell me now yeah
sometimes the truth will come from a a
child who doesn't know he's he's come up
with something sometimes they have a
clearer perception of the world than
because uh they haven't they haven't
been fed enough lies yeah or they do you
think that's what it is could be or they
may be forc to taste the water that is
brackish and say this water brackish
I have some lines that I'll I'll close
on about memories go to plug the books I
remember me and I just remembered and
the new one I I what I what I had
forgotten what I had almost
forgotten here's a few from a bunch of
different philosophers we each need to
make peace with our own memories we have
all done things that make us Flinch and
that's suya
Das memory is a child walking along a SE
sure you never can tell what small
pebble it will pick up and store away
amongst its treasured things and that's
Pierce
Harris everybody needs his memories they
keep the wolf of insignificance from the
door that's Sal Bellow he was nice he
was good memory itself is an internal
rumor that's George
sanana sanana S Tiana Every Man's memory
is his private literature that's Aldis
Huxley that's beautiful uh that that is
absolutely perfect for me Isn't it I
better put that down Jesus because if
that isn't what I'm doing
yeah Mel was pointing out that I'm all I
write about is uh is my own life boy is
that I'm you know I may use that in the
in the front of my book I Ed my own I
quote myself yeah and from a book I the
first my anecdotal life I quoted myself
from my anecdotal life I wrote it in the
book and I said I'm looking for a quote
like this couldn't find one so I used
Isaiah's a good quote on page 37 so I
quoted myself which nobody's ever
done so but this one now now memory is
his private jeez that's great and it's
really true I think we're just a
compilation of our memories and how we
perceive them anyway you know private
literacy Bible all this a l d us huh
yeah a l d o us o us Huxley
xux you know I did an audition for a
Comedy Festival and they asked me this
is a few years ago they didn't get a
sense of who I was from my act in my old
act oh and they said uh well we we
thought you were very funny but we
didn't really get a sense of who you are
and I realized now I should have told
them I'm a compilation of all my
memories and how I perceived
them it's who we all are right that's
what makes you you and me me absolutely
no question about it and and because you
can do that people say oh that's just
like me and you know something now that
I have all your memories in my memory
yes it's your memory now now in some way
you and I are alike exactly that's
interesting and then the last one here
is the past is never dead it is not even
past that's William fauler fauler he's
good too yeah best is never dead if
somebody remembers it that's the show
Carl thank you so much for doing it and
I appreciate you having me here and
taking the time this is it you mean
we're finished I haven't even started to
tell you things that I've been thinking
all week oh dear can you come back
tomorrow I oh this is so disappointing
did did I sing you my uh my Scottish I
didn't even sing you my Scottish song
well you give me an Irish song all right
forget it forget it I'm very
disappointed very
disappointed thanks so much Carl I bet
you never got one of those no that was a
great sign off a Master of Ceremonies
and sign
offs yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
all right that's our show everybody I
want to thank Alex faella as always for
picking out some fantastic philosophers
I want to thank our wonderful guest Mr
Carl Riner the great Carl Riner and I
want to thank you guys for tuning in I
want to thank our sponsors you know what
I'm going to stop saying I want to
thinkk and I'm going to start thanking
so I thank our sponsors tent encounters
with Jewish culture remember if you're
interested in thinking more about why so
many Jews have been involved in comedy
go and check out
www.ent.com it enough and please go
check out standup crap.com and pick up
some wonderful comedy albums pick up my
album some kind of comedian support Dan
schle support
standup.on wonderful standup stuff you
want to hear more car Riner I know that
you do he's on my buddy Mark Mal's
podcast this week also the Carson
podcast which I've talked about a little
bit before on this program Mark malov
talks to people whose lives were changed
by their experience being on the old
Tonight Show with Johnny Carson and some
fantastic stories come out of that so go
and check out the Carson podcast and
Mark malov is a phenomenal host and I
think you're going to love it you can
email me at the comical yahoo.com I love
hearing from you please be in touch and
if you are in touch stay in touch and if
you have a little bit of time on your
hands this week it would mean a lot to
me if you could jump on iTunes and leave
five stars in a nice review that would
help the show and it would help me so
please do that make a donation at moday
philosophers. net if you send me $20 or
more I'll send you some complimentary
tweaked audio earbuds which you can also
find at tweaked aio.com and if you want
to buy them there use promo code mdp for
oneir off in free shipping can't go
wrong okay everybody that is about it I
want to leave you now with a beautiful
song from the late great Estelle Riner
off her album hurry home the track is
called the more I see you the lyrics are
by Mark Gordon and the music is by Harry
Warren so enjoy that and I'll see you
guys next week thanks for tuning in
[Music]
bye-bye the more I see you more I want
you somehow this
feeling just grows and
grows with every sigh I become more mad
about you
more lost without you and so it goes can
you IM
imagine how much I love you the more I
see you as years go by I know the only
one for me can ever be you and my arms
won't free you and my heart won't dry
[Music]
the more I see you the more I want you
somehow this
feeling just grows and
grows with every side I become more mad
about you more lost without you and so
it
goes can you
imagine how much I'm going to love you
the more I see you as years go by
I know the only one for me can only be
you and my arms won't free you the more
I see you these arm W free you and my
heart
[Music]