yeah hello and welcome to modern day
philosophers modern day philosophers
having failed to pay attention in school
Danny LEL now older and wiser will
attempt to learn basic philosophy 101
our young hero will be joined by today's
top comedians philosophers all their own
ladies and gentlemen here's Danny
LEL day philosophers
we are in the unoccupied during the day
Comedy Club the stand in New York that's
a conversation for another day as we had
off Mike about why the Sacred Space is
not used during CU I'll tell you that
the briefing is my theory is Club must
remain untainted by anything but comedy
until the night until it gets tainted by
comedy at night Alex picked for us today
a guy this is the first guy who's still
alive that we're studying on the show he
was born in 1938 which makes him about
75 I'm terrible with math but uh my dad
was born around then and I believe he's
around that age so his name is Tom rean
have you heard of Tom rean I have not me
neither and the reason Alex picked him
is because he said he knows about you
that you're very into animal rights mhm
and uh Tom wrote All About animal rights
so he thought this would be a good guy
for us to talk about okay I'm also very
into animal rights I didn't know that
about you well it's not like I I walk
around saying I am into animal I I just
believe that animals should be treated
with respect and dignity as as one would
hope humans are treated with respect and
unless of course the human or the animal
is undeserving of but animals are
innocent you know I mean like they uh
they even when they do things we
perceive as bad it's usually uh out of
provocation or a threat of some kind
it's not a a malicious thing that is
premeditated whereas there are some
humans who are sociopathic and or
cultural criminals who do not deserve a
lot of respect so you don't think that
um there are any animals sitting around
plotting well if there are I'm not aware
of them they they they're I'm not saying
there's not a thinking process there is
and some animals are unbelievably
intelligent and and thoughtful and
compassionate and all that I don't know
that they premeditate m
you know or uh you know collecting the
insurance money by disposing of a spouse
or a Don Draper like
reinvention after the Korean War things
of that nature cool well um well what
about what do you think constitutes an
evil person well I don't like the word
evil because it's reductive and it's the
type of thing that that uh you know when
George Bush among others evildoer it's
just like talking to a child and it and
uh it since the political discourse gets
lower and lower a lot of times that's
considered a legitimate question in a in
a debate what I think you mean is
somebody that that does things that they
could be uh incarcerated for or they
could be considered outside or you know
there are crimes committed Against
Humanity and against the environment and
against animals that um are are just
nefarious unkind unconscious selfish
things but I don't consider it evil in
the sense of that there is a there is a
just universe and a just deity somewhere
and then this satanic one elsewhere I
don't I don't believe in those things so
the distinction between animals being
innocent and humans not being innocent
well humans there are certainly many
innocent hum especially little ones and
babies and and things of that nature who
who have no malicious intent I'm talking
about a a thinking conscious adult Endor
te or cogn I mean adult enough child
that they understand consequences they
understand what it is to
harm and they do it anyway and their
life is not in threat and they're not
for any moral reason defending something
how much of it can you say could just be
attributed to mental illness or
upbringing well that's a whole different
thing okay so that if there is a mental
illness involved that is a different
thing that that again is not something
that isn't is particular nefarious or a
person who's thinking about how to harm
if there is uh neurological or brain
chemistry issues that's a whole another
factor that we should we should be
sympathetic to and take into account
whenever there's a crime committed or
something like that what about if
somebody was a victim of abuse
themselves to the point where that's
another thing I I understand is sympath
uh sympathize with I don't say I
understand it because I've been abused
what I'm saying is is a a person and an
animal are made like a pitbulls get a
bad rap I I am a huge fan of pitbull
dogs they are I have one as do I and and
over the years I've had a number of of
pites and fostered pit bues they are
they used to be called the family
companion for very good reason they
they're a wonderful dog they
unfortunately have been used by many
people for uh nefarious I keep saying
nefarious I'm trying not to say evil but
uh the if you punish and
abuse a dog any dog you know the most uh
aggressive dog is the jack russell
terrier but because it's so small and
cute uh people you know that pit are
actually uh rarely involved in in
attacks in the aggregate in a year it's
just we only hear about pitbull attacks
because it's news and also probably
somebody gets attacked by a Jack Russell
ter it's not as bad but it it's
certainly bad to be
you know if a child's attacked by sure a
Jack Russell teror it's still going to
be bad but uh pimples have a biological
imperative that makes their jaw lock
whether they want it to or not that's
another problem when they get involved
in a fight or if they're made to fight
they lock on and they can't disengage
their jaw very easily unless you pull on
their back legs or unfortunately stick a
finger up their rectum oh yeah which I
know it it it shocks them into their jaw
unlocking but it's very hard during a
fight or a dog you know someone had to
figure that out yeah to to do that and
also people think you're insane when
you're when you're trying to do it but
um it the the pitbull or any dog that
becomes aggressive and nasty has been
very mistreated because dogs are pure
heart they really are coming from
unconditional love they want to please
person so you really have to work at UH
making a dog but do you a bad dog you
don't think that's the same for humans
yes yes it's just that we were on the
Pitbull right uh to what extent can you
really say okay this guy is at fault
more than just he's a victim of his
upbringing or mental health or mental
illness whatever it is MH um well there
if if there is mental illness and abuse
that all has to be taken into account
and that's why I don't like reductive
words like evil and then there but then
there's a point where if this person
does seem to recognize even with the
abuse I'm not talking about the mental
illness cuz that really affects your
brain chemistry and your and and the
ways that you think and see things I'm
talking about a person that does not
have a a mental illness caveat we can
put into this but as a person who has
been abused and damaged that is all
something that should be people should
be compassionate about but there could
be a point where they see see this is
terrible you know I I I hated how I was
abused and treated but I'm going to do
it anyway not seek therapy not seek ways
around it um I'm not saying in every
case I'm just saying if if if there's a
way that's you have to have a certain
degree of mental health to do that right
even to just get yourself to the point
where you're like I could you know I
should seek therapy or just even to lack
so much empathy you know for for a
victim well that's another thing again
lack of EMP victim yourself yeah yeah
well there's things that that I can't
understand cuz I haven't been right
systematically abused so it's difficult
to speak with any eloquence on these
things when I have I have no firsthand
knowledge with no backhand with or or or
backhand oh that's terrible you made a
joke about abuse get the blogs going get
the letters coming for this guy but that
I I feel so I canot even pretend to
understand the depths of despair of of
somebody who since childhood has
suffered like that um and then again I
think there's a difference between
neurological uh brain chemical mental
illness and the Fallout from abuse there
may be two separate categories I'm not
sure MH uh does that make sense yeah um
and then there's people who have not
been either abused or don't suffer from
mental illness as far as we know who
lack empathy AB attribute that to who
knows personality type it's just it's
just hardwiring so there's some people
that just uh and they tend to to be in
powerful positions and they're Risk
Takers and they are impervious to others
emotions and that's how they become CEOs
or political Titans or do you know what
I mean like real Achievers in certain
Fields because they do not seem to be
bothered by the consequences of their
actions okay so um did that answer
anything that you asked me I don't even
remember what maybe it was interesting
either way I think yeah it answered
something especially that last bit that
you just said would you know that's a
certain type of person that you're
talking about that maybe is um just has
a mellian type of you know approach to
life and just trying to take over as
much as they can and in that case maybe
maybe that person wouldn't be I guess
the word in isn't evil we decided but
maybe that's the again I don't well look
at just say Wall Street for example just
the financial misdeeds of of the of a
hedge fun fund human who has no or the
Enron guys who work there and there was
the tapes of their phone calls when they
were laughing about artificially
destroying the electricity uh the flow
of electricity in in certain markets
and they uh there's something about that
culture right of of corporate culture
with that's deregulated and it and it
attracts a certain type of person as
does sometimes law enforcement politics
entertainment MH there are certain
personality types that
gravitate towards those fields for good
reasons and for bad reasons do you think
people have a moral uh do you think
there's such a thing as morality or a
moral
code uh I I would I guess there's
whatever society says it is and then
you're indoctrinated into that um it
seems to be fairly basic among almost
all
societies at least in modern you know or
but whatever you consider modern times
about killing would be bad although we
have
state well yes and no well everybody has
their interpretation of the origin myths
everybody has their interpretation of
deities and everybody has their
interpretation of what is a legal and
just way to run your Society so it it
just depends on where you were born and
in what era so do you think it's good
that Society dictates
morality well I don't know that Society
does dictate morality per se or I
thought you were saying basically it's
whatever society says is moral oh oh
what I'm saying is is that's what you
accept and that's what you grow up with
and I think I very confusingly was
trying to say that there seems to be
basic impulses of what is right and
wrong that I think predate are created
myths of of Good and Evil and uh you
know I even prates uh Egyptian and
Abyssinian myths which a lot of our
origin myths are based upon as concerns
religion uh I think that even in going
back to hunter gatherer times or or uh
you know
neander time whatever you know
Paleolithic I don't know I'm not very
smart but I don't know I don't know
exactly which I I think the hominids
were the
link between prehistoric and what was
considered modern I'm not about that
than you your smart friend would know
that's your smart friend but I think
even back then there was a sense of that
harming if you weren't if it wasn't for
self-preservation or or what have you
was wrong I'm I'm not positive about
that but it seems like people thrived in
communities of some sort and get and
traveled together and raise their young
and do you think it's based on just
human instinct like animal Instinct in
that way or is there anything innate in
us
that you know dictates well I would say
that when most children are born and
most most animals are born for the most
part unless there's neurological damage
in both the animal and human they seem
very very innocent and and uh have no
interest in in harming they they can be
quite selfish because they're little and
they're babies and they don't you know
they they're not thinking in terms of
what's good for the group or I shouldn't
make so much noise because people are
talking but I don't think there's a
sense of no devil babies well well again
you have to believe in in a devil well
no I was just using the term devil sure
that there is but it wouldn't be because
they are
cognitively diabolical it would be that
perhaps they're wired in a way that that
affects them negatively in their
behaviors what if the majority of people
started to be born wired that way well
that would be a problem for society
wouldn't it or or it would just change
what we consider more look at what we
can what we accept I mean it's it's un
it's unbelievable and shocking what
societies do accept whether it be State
sanctioned killing or illegal Wars or uh
rigged Financial systems uh the racism
the the uh misogyny all these things are
tolerated on a daily basis in quote
unquote democracies and so uh we do
tolerate quite a lot that that seems on
the face of it unacceptable yeah all the
while bragging about how we're the best
and the more and whenever on the news
when they say we're in danger of losing
our standing in the world we're in
danger of losing our moral High Ground
when do you think that our
self-described moral High our self
described moral High Ground now even if
it wasn't destroyed by
Vietnam uh which Vietnam certainly
helped destroy quote unquote our beacon
on the hill Divine Providence idea of
ourselves there was many other
atrocities committed before that that
that certainly did and since Vietnam
that the rest of the world doesn't share
you know our political platitudes I've
often wondered if if America were to
take on an
attitude not only that we weren't the
best because because that bothers me a
lot that whole the best country thing
because especially lot of countries do
it traveling yeah I was going to say
traveling around the world everybody's
got this best country thing and it's so
funny that some more than others
everybody thinks they have the best
country you know right well isn't that
again another Community thing uh that
you sort of do for for your so that's
what I was going to say like do we need
that I don't think we do and I think
it's actually quite dangerous you know
whether it's Rome the British Empire uh
Japan what if there's just one country
that held their head down low and
they're like we uh well there are some
countries that keep out of it you know
they keep you know the worst country no
no nobody would say the worst and like I
said America's not the only offender in
this area many countries declare
themselves the best because for whatever
reason they they calculate that the
masses are not mature enough to handle
they need the moral Bo boost the Boost
of or they probably don't need it it's
just well they think they need it anyway
or we're who knows though cuz it's not
been tested you know what I mean because
people seem to respond really well when
other social critics point it whether it
be George car the late George Carlin or
uh Bill Mah or or any other mainstream
you know social critics who say things
similar to what we're talking about it
seems very eagerly accepted and enjoyed
by a lot of people it's a it's
mainstream politics and mainstream
entertainment that doesn't indulge more
nuanced thinking since you brought up
George Carlin I'm going to bring up and
I've brought this up on the show once
before but I think about it a lot when
he talked about people own this country
we have owners M and I think if people
own the country that makes the citizens
a product that's own vassels vassels
well there's I think what he may mean by
that and certainly the ownership changes
over time in in many ways we are owned
by among other other people's CH China
you know they support us and we owe them
a great deal of money
and if they were to ever call in their
chips if you will right there there it
would be impossible to pay them back at
the interest rate and things like that
but that's you know we're not the only
country like that there's many countries
and then there's the international
monetary fund which rigs it so the
countries are constantly indebted to the
IMF and that's just human nothing's
going to change until human nature
changes this is fundamentally like all
political systems about the people that
that are the key players in those
systems and human nature is what it is
until it evolves somewhat so where does
power to the people come
in you know just isn't power to the
people overtaking the people that own us
well there is uh certainly a great uh
deal of organ you know organizations at
the Civic level is that what you're
talking about like people who get
together to do things and they make
changes that's also historically true in
in a lot of eras in a lot of countries
but do you don't think that there are
people who
actually um view the citizens of America
as a product that they own well there in
their interest to keep us thinking
there's no reason to ever leave America
this is the greatest country in the
world oh I don't know if that's the
thought process but I think that there's
definitely people who see it as their
right to own and to make the rules again
that's politics a lot of politics and
that has been true since there was the
ability to set up systems where powerful
people dominate that's that's human
nature that's what I'm talking about
this is this we could go back to the
Scottish Highlands if you want to when
there was Clans sure uh and then there
was a more powerful Clan than others and
then there were people that proclaimed
themselves Kings of those particular
regions and then there was the but you
don't think that there's some kind of an
effort that's made to keep the people
from Ever wanting to go anywhere else
just keep the people here I don't think
you have to make an effort there's
plenty of people who have no interest in
having a passport or going anywhere else
yeah but don't you think that they're
they are basically a product of a system
that's made them that way I don't know
if it's a system they're a product of uh
and you know there's plenty of people
that have ever have had every advantage
and privilege who have no interests um
and again they're just you know for
whatever reason they just uh don't have
a lot of interest but more and more and
more as time goes on people do have an
interest and they also get the ability
to connect globally through the new
mediums of Technology uh it's quite
common now for young people to be very
globally plugged in from their bedroom
you know what I mean and and friends
with people around the world and all
that uh so those things are changing now
there's certainly no doubt that there
are some
people that are we're number one I'll
kick your ass
blah blah blah where does that culture
come from it's trickling down from the
top well there there's always been
people at the top that have an interest
in fostering keeping the worker and
here of course that's again the nature
of power how does power Thrive unless it
yeah consolidates its power um but I
don't know that it's about having an
interest in
keeping these people in this country
there's always more people to dominate
who will come in there's always you know
what I mean it's I don't think it's it's
it bothers someone if they if they are
going to be an expat or if they're going
to travel what I think is in the
interest of some powerful people is uh
like Rupert Murdoch for buying up papers
and news stations dumbing it down
cooning and dumbing down Society that's
very useful to powerful people what does
Tom ran say about this I was just
wondering strictly about animals I was
wondering how to transition back into
that well I would assume animals don't
have don't have these systems although
there is a certain um it's not the
bonobo monkey which I believe is is
peaceful some strains of chimpanzee
which I believe that in the animal
kingdom we share like 96% of our DNA
with which is generous which is and also
I believe with pumpkins too we have a
great deal in common genetically with
pumpkins interestingly um with our DNA I
read that once it could be false but it
always stuck with me somebody Google
that
but any whoel um there is certain
aggressive
domineering groups of animals that
dominate the other animals by
force but there are
also other animals where the animal in
their animal communities they do the
exact opposite and it's about communally
raising children and it's about uh
caring for the elderly you know that
that's that's just and unfortunately the
animals that are indoctrinate ated into
the into the dominionist breed of animal
they pick it up as kids even into like
where there's a in some animals uh
communities they
kill baby boy animals male animals the
dominant males because of a
threat and then uh what kind of animals
do you Dolphins sometimes do it oddly
and certain chimpanzees do it and then I
was watching on animal King like certain
Lions sometimes do it if they want to be
the alpha male I went right to lions in
my when you I think that sometimes yeah
especially if they see a mate they like
and there's another get rid of the you
get rid of the competition or the
competition's child um it's it's tragic
and when you watch National Geographic
challeng stuff it's just as painful to
look at that that as it is to human
Carnage and tragedy you know I'm
thinking I'd love to think that I got
this information from National
Geographic but it's far more likely it
came from The Lion King you know See
Lion King but you know what many truths
are revealed in The Lion King that's why
it's so popular although I haven't seen
it I assume that or life of pie life of
pie didn't see it with the sound on I
saw it with the sound down and cried
like a baby at life of pie cuz those CGI
animals look so real to me and when they
were suffering I I was on a plane and I
was crying and there was a b a
businessman and I say businessman
because of how he was talking on his
cell phone when he was supposed to turn
it off he was using business speak like
at the end of the day you know
branding so he was in business but he
was watching life of pie with the sound
on and he had ner and emotion and he
kept looking at me like I was insane but
it it's like that's i p the silent movie
Life of Pi which I I'm sure is brilliant
more brilliant even with the sound on oh
you got to check it out with the sound
it's so beautiful and onle is a is a
great director but did you see Life of
pie so like the understand watching it
you know it's so visually stunning that
you know but did you feel oh no leave
the zebra alone like the little on the
boat and when he wouldn't let the tiger
back in the boat when the tiger was I
kept rooting for the different animals
to make it well at least that one you
know the tiger made it but he he was he
made the tiger seasick at one point
which made me feel sad or when he had
when he learned that lesson life lesson
with the with the goat being slain by
the tiger when his uncle or whatever
tied M the Little Goat to the yeah the
bars that and the orangutang the
orangutang is what I was rooting for the
most like just let the orang Tang I know
that's how I feel and and cuz it looks
so real and also cuz you know these
things happen in life and it wasn't a
real orang Tang no no no I believe
they're all CGI I mean they may use okay
they were filming them individually and
then putting them all together but I'm
might imag that the that that some of it
was they couldn't have done some of that
I so real yeah I because there were
certain scenes there's no way you could
get those takes the tiger I would I
would think would be I thought it was
all CGI but certain things happen
there's no way that could have been a
live tiger if you cried that much
thinking they were CGI I almost don't
want to tell you if they were well then
I don't want to know if they were real I
mean I can understand using real animals
for certain shots but you couldn't have
used them I wanted to protect you from
this information also the way that
animals would look at at him it C
there's no way you're going to get the
camera ankle for some of these animals I
would assume I don't know but then again
I am no expert in CGI in the life of pie
the making of yeah but um yeah I don't
want to know that they were really but
then then again the real ones wouldn't
have been eaten by them right right the
little Tasmanian Devil yeah Jackal
wasn't it hyena hyena whatever I think
of it I think of it like the um
Tasmanian devil in the cartoons yeah
just the way storm around and again he
was just trying to survive too and then
somebody told me after the fact that
those were metaphorical those were
humans yeah well it's I don't want to
ruin the movie but it's oh that's okay I
will never look at it again because it
was oh so you're never going to
no it was to up it's left at the end
maybe it is a metaphor maybe it isn't
you know okay cuz I I could tell also it
seemed he lost his family in the storm
is that accurate yeah okay they drowned
they drowned all right but they so there
wasn't I should animals representing
just to just as a favor do you want
maybe I'll I'll edit the movie for you
and take out all I can't honestly it was
so painful really um such a good movie
though oh it's beautiful it it was
beautiful but then uh just from
the scenes it's so emotionally brilliant
that that it's would you read the book
no because there's going to be Peril
right cuz then you could put the words
they'll be that'll be even deeper
resonance cuz sometimes books really sck
to your ribs I mean at least for me
anyway like the pain of the characters
or whatever if there's things it just
haunts me for days and days so there's
an element of fear there to to to doing
that element of fear yes I'm I'm
frightened to read the life of pie and
now I can't go buy it because it'll be
with the movie picture cover on it and
you always feel like a douche getting a
book with the movie with the movie
poster on it when you should have read
that book years ago or like The Great
Gatsby I'm not buying it with Leo
DiCaprio on the cover it rarely ever
happens the other way I think it might
have at one or two two I'm trying to
think where like the movie would take on
the books cover with its uh mhm the
poster oh well I was supposed to have
read the Gatsby many years ago and
didn't and then I read it after the
movie came out but I went to a used
bookstore and got you didn't watch like
the Leonardo DiCaprio I didn't see the
movie I didn't see that either I'm just
saying um I I see the Robert Redford
movie of The Great Gatsby I would
imagine the Leonardo DiCaprio one
wouldn't be anything like the real Great
Gatsby book well the I didn't see it but
the the book The Great Gatsby which is
quite short was very very very good that
was one of my favorite books really good
when I read that I was in high school
and I I related so much to that part
where he would throw a party and watch
the party from the balcony but not
partake so I tried to do it at at home
and and I threw a party in high school
and I just stood in my parents bedroom
overlooking the backyard at the window
and everyone thought I was just such a
creep and did you feel a kind of uh Jay
Gatsby esque I was trying I wanted to be
the Gatsby but also I could only I kept
seeing M Pharaoh in the in the charact
in the feem daisy I think your name da
um because I had seen when I was younger
the the Robert Redford version but just
the trailers for The the big bold great
gadsby didn't appeal to me and the
soundtrack I don't need a s you know
what I mean I I think it's corny to Pump
It Up with a modern soundtrack cuz it
it's it's like it's saying you you won't
this is it's not enough on its own when
it's when it's clearly a great story
it's an arrogant thing to do be like
look this Great Gatsby it's not not so
great actually I know so we're going to
make it better with a modern soundtrack
called it Greater Gatsby yeah it's going
to it it would be you know the the
original not the original The Great
Gatsby movie I saw many years ago
certainly didn't do that if they had
done I guess of the time they would have
soundtracked by America the Rolling
Stones Bachman Turner overdrive it would
be the same thing because I think it
came out in that era Grand Funk Railroad
and then just as the years go by people
keep trying to top The Great Gatsby with
greater and greater greater greatest
gadsby this is the greatest gadsby yet
get a better Gatsby than this Gatsby
come Skrillex is going doing the entire
soundtrack there's going to be glow
sticks in the theater all right I'm
going to try to jump into this Tom rean
guy and find out a little bit about him
Tom rean uh born November 28th 1938 is
an American philosopher who specializes
in animal rights theory he is a
professor emirus of philosophy it's I
see that written a lot too ameritus
ameritus I think that's how you know I I
don't know well no I'm I'm just guessing
but I feel like I'm so far away from
being that level of academic that I
can't even pronounce it I don't I don't
know that that's a litmus test of a you
know it's not like you hear that word
every single day yeah but you can't be a
professor and not know the word ameritus
ameritus I think I think I could be
wrong he's a professor ameritus of
philosophy at North Carolina State
University where he taught from 1967
until his retirement in 2001 he's the
author of numer books on philosophy of
animal rights including the case for
animal rights
1983 uh one of a handful of studies that
have significantly influence the modern
animal rights movement in these he
argues that non-human animals are what
he calls the subject of life just as
animal just as humans are and that if we
want to ascribe value to all human
beings regardless of their ability to be
rational agents then to be consistent we
must similarly have scrub
it to
nonhumans so he's arguing that that
actually makes a lot of sense if he's
saying if you give the right the rights
of of humanity and all that that implies
to people who are clearly not acting
rationally then shouldn't we apply to
animals apply to animals who actually
are acting rationally much more so than
a lot of humans so what he's saying is
and this it's funny I go back again to
thinking about George Carlin when he
said we have no rights you remember that
in one of his last special you don't
have rights rights are made up he said
oh he goes there is no such thing as
rights I oh I guess that's that's sort
of true but then there are some people
that I guess that would say that there
are rights that just that you exist that
you should have but I I think I
understand what he's saying is you are
told what your rights are rights are I
mean right to silent with any rights who
knows that you have you don't even know
that you do have a right to exist you do
exist do you have a right to exist
that's uh that's true I I would say that
once you're here out of the
womb it seems like people should help
you stay especially if you're a helpless
little baby or a helpless little animal
but is that a right I I yeah I I I I I I
don't recall him saying that that's a
very interesting yeah idea but I and
again I do take that point you are told
what your rights are right or but it
always did also bother me when people
say driving is a privilege whenever you
get a traffic ticket or something it's
not a a privilege it's a a Act of life
you I have to drive you know what I mean
in a modern society uh in order to get
to work or what have you so then what
isn't a privilege that then you could
yeah walking is a privilege or uh
everything's a privilege air airplane
travel is a priv air itself is a
privilege right yeah it's not a
privilege who are you to say what a
privilege is it's a strange thing when
people say driving is a privilege but
they would say that in driver's ed class
to in high school all the time remember
kids driving is a privilege it doesn't
seem like a privilege so much as
something that has to happen because in
order to survive in modern society in
most cases uh one needs to be able to
drive it's a better situation I don't
know if it's a privilege it's a better
situation than not being able it enables
you to live more fully right I guess cuz
and that's why they deny that right what
is a priv women drive like I wonder what
a privilege actually is what is a
privilege um a privilege I guess would
be a privileged person a person who was
born with Financial Security was born
with a roof over their head and and no
dangers put in front of them that and
then also had the ability to go to the
finest schools and right go on summer
vacations and all these things those
seem like a privileged lifestyle no
they're they're just entitled to a
better not entitled to but they were
just hand they were lucky enough to be
born into a situation so luck
luck luck luck luck luck some people uh
make their luck where through sheer will
intelligence hard work they become right
so then maybe driving is privileged
because you'd be lucky enough to drive
mhm but I mean it shouldn't be something
single that out as the privilege well
I'm I'm just saying it's something I
remember from driver's ed and there are
also some countries that deny women the
right to drive because they know that it
it empowers people to drive so so they
don't have the right so there there
again as a as a man created right you
know they they should uh in a just
Society be able to drive humans should
be able to do what other humans are able
to do in a just Society in the same way
that here that in this country and many
other countries in the year 2013 we
should not be having discussions about
gay rights they should just be there
they're human rights right but going
back to what you were just saying humans
should be able to do what other humans
should be able to can do is where's the
line like could I say oh because I know
a human who has a a private jet and gets
to fly in a private jet I should
therefore no that's different I I
believe that is different and here's for
why I'm talking about the basic rights
to exist without apologizing or
defending
yourself women animals the LGBT
community uh very poor people things of
that nature uh these people should not
have to defend every political season or
every every year against some right-wing
or ignorant group their right to be MH
that's different than a private jet
which who cares uh you know when when it
comes down to it if you can ride a dve
if you can ride on a private jet that's
nice I mean I don't disagree at all with
what you're saying I'm just trying to
figure out at what point do you define
what a right is and in terms of as we
perceive them well I think I think in my
opinion the word right is we're kind of
stuck that's The American or the English
in our lexicon that we've used entitled
to right right means I should be
entitled to right or no because
entitlement carries its own baggage
people use it in a pejorative way I
feel that if if a like I said say a
newborn baby or
animal it shouldn't be snuffed out just
on on a precarious whim or because
somebody doesn't care that that seems
unkind and it seems wron that this this
thing new life doesn't have a chance um
that
there is it's not a privilege that it
gets to not be killed right it's a it's
it it
luckily has survived and somebody's
caring for it you just again there's
luckily right next to privileged because
luck and privilege might be the same but
I'm not using luck in that's that uh you
are you are granted luck I'm saying just
I should have said randomly happen
stance it didn't get snuffed out this
animal or this baby before it even had a
chance to
participate now having said that there
are um others that would say there is no
special you know I mean it doesn't
matter if if but I feel like in the case
of helpless things or things that do
need protection for survival it seems
very unjust to deny them that then when
it comes to adults though
who
um behave in a way that is endangers
others or is incendiary like say uh uh
that that guy who um a few years ago
deliberately was I guess burning krans
just to incite violence that seems
absolutely wrong now the person who was
burning the cran or verely any other
place in the world provoking or doing
anything that Pro that I don't care
actually if they are put In Harm's Way a
person doing that how do we know I mean
in this case it seems fairly obvious but
how do we know when somebody is acting
in a way that endangers us but
ultimately will help us like a
revolutionary say you're in you're in
Syria um and now but maybe not right now
but maybe let's go back a year or
whatever before things got or at least
to my knowledge got really bad so things
are really bad but you're like you know
what this is tolerable I think uh or
Egypt's a better example um this is this
is they're like oh it's bad and people
are like no we need to revolt they're
like don't Revolt that's just going to
incite the powers of being what are you
doing you know what are you nuts uh and
then they do things that could be
perceived to those people again bad
example with the guy burning the Quran
but just just to have one they could
perceive that as oh what are you doing
this guy is just you know trying to you
know and ultimately what they're doing
is for the greater good of society I
don't live there I can't I can't weigh
in very effectively on the motivations
or intentions of of anything and
unfortunately a lot of the news that I
get even though I try very hard to get
multiple sources and and to to to figure
out what's going on I can never know
what's going on and also when people say
oppressed societies and democracy those
are all very relative terms there is no
such thing as an actual real democracy
because the human condition won't allow
it um and you think it never will I
don't know I don't know uh you know
certainly things are better in that we
don't live in the in the streets and
squalor you know elderly you know that
that's changing back in some ways but
then as right-wing pendulums swing and
and funds get cut from things and
threats to take away Social Security it
could be the way it was back in the old
days uh where the elderly just died in
the streets who knows what can happen
I'm often amazed and I I wonder if it's
attributed to order in the universe of
just how few bullets are flying by at
any given moment when you walk depends
on where you live down the street well
well why does even depend on where you
live people could jump on a subway and
and just start shooting anywhere right
they could they could um and and
sometimes they do and then there's some
soci some uh blighted urban areas and
even rural areas where it is like that
people get shot constantly the amount of
homicides and uh gun injuries and gun
deaths in this country on a daily basis
is insane but I wonder what keeps the
people from doing like I'll give you
another
example you're on the subway you always
see these ad Suicide Hotline yeah uh
depression all kinds of pills for
depression clearly a huge a large
segment of just local people here in New
York that are suicidal
and well that's not necessarily true the
pharmaceutical industry has like a huge
investment in putting those signs
up you don't think that there's a lot of
suicidal people all around oh there
could be and there there always has been
the probably the same amount I mean
there's the level of
suicides uh in
society has probably always been fair
you know people used to do it just out
of sheer Bleak despair on the Prairie um
again you know depression is a very real
thing uh but certainly the
pharmaceutical industry will medic and
diagnose everyone there's no way every
kid has ADD and ADHD there's just no way
that the amount of kids who are
medicated have these receed they're
selling products they're selling
products to a willing a willing uh you
know consumer base in the same way that
there's if you ever watch uh certain
cable news channels every other
commercial is for restless leg syndrome
low tea all these manufactured things
that are just a a a byproduct of aging
process they give you enough Sy symptoms
that you're like at least I have one of
them you know it could be anything you
know what I mean so ask your doctor and
then the side effects will kill you of
these medications I wonder if they're
just sitting there like can we come up
with a few more symptoms for this just
so we could grab another absolutely in
the same way that if you look at the
charts that diagnose children with
various things you see it is the widest
net possible the ad ADHD for kids thing
is literally
every any child my D I'm like but I
really have it Janine but that you might
and you might not uh but if you were
born when I was born you would have
never heard of it and there I didn't
even know anyone that knew anyone I
started kindergarten around 6869
graduated college in ' 86 there was no
such thing that I had ever heard of
called a nut allergy there was honestly
there was peanut butter was fine um the
food allergy thing there was always a
bumblebee kid you heard about it I never
met him but there was a like a Suburban
legend about there was a kid stung by a
bee and he died uh that you would hear
about that other than that uh I wonder I
wonder if it if it's what you're saying
which is that it's manufactured by a
pharmaceutical company no no there
definitely was going on diagnosed we as
a as a race as a species sure there's
there's many contingencies first of all
there was many things not understood and
and not diagnosed right that's how he's
been true in history but to go from
none in in the average public school
body right to in the last 10 12 Years to
all that you can't bring peanut butter
within 25t of a school yard a gun you
can but not peanut butter not be
symptomatic of the drugs that they gave
people in your generation that their
kids wound up with all these or it could
be power of
suggestion uh it's just it's just it
just seems that how could in one go
round of a
generation their chromosomes and
genetics are all mixing together and
every kid now has whatever the flavor of
the month allergy is or whatever the
pharmaceutical industry will tell you
that you have but if you look at most
children can't sit still doesn't want to
pay atten that is the nature of being a
child what we what a lot of it is is is
these children exhibiting behaviors that
we as adults find annoying especially
overstressed teachers who have an
enormous amount of kids in their
classroom
underfunded uh you know and they would
prefer that these kids be quieter be
funny if doctors just diagnosed well I'm
sorry well you just have an annoying
child well isn't that what a lot of it
is like your kid has a lot of energy
yeah you know I mean like your kid talks
when I'm talking that's what's he got
doctor well according to these charts
he's very he very annoying so let's
medicate him but you know ADD and ADHD
which I I actually am fascinated by uh
can't it also be just a personality type
can it also be just the product of the
way your mind works why is it a a thing
that now is codified as perhaps negative
and you need to take medication um in
the same way there's a new thing called
fibromyalgia for the last few years
which again is another catchall thing
you have pain vaguely in any joint take
this pill ask you talk about
fibromyalgia or restless leg or they
just come up new names all the time they
Rebrand it rename it they'll Trot out
some other medicine medication that
didn't take off in another Market it
sounds like a word you've never heard
you're like oh it's got to be LCA right
now they medicate your fibromyalgia
which is nonsense with lria used to be
an anti a present uh they just switched
it over
to uh for your for your fibromyalgia
your restless leg uh just one of those
things and that low tea thing is
hilarious to me that is uh has your
testosterone lowered after the age of 40
yes if you're a man that's after the age
of 25 it starts to go down supposed to
but they say you may be just you like
the you know the commercial play into
your insecurities playing into your
insecurities ask your doctor you may be
suffering from low tea as if it's a
thing people say they should just say
maybe you're not so much of a man I know
ex that's exactly right and and for
women they do it in other ways uh that
their femininity is in question their
sexuality is in question just by
refusing to say this is what happens
after the age of 30 this is what you
know what I mean it's these things are
going to change and also now that people
live to about 100 there's going to be
even way more and we're going to
medicate those even the elderly are like
well why don't I have an erection I know
exactly they can take pills to do in the
same way that you took Aderall and
sometimes I take Aderall cuz I do like
that too it it makes me really zero in
on something but it doesn't mean I have
a problem and again I'm not I'm not
absolutely saying don't I'm not taking
it away from my high definition AD yeah
yeah it's it's I it's perhaps the way
your mind worked and uh you obviously
went into a type of line of work that
interest you that is similar to what you
were doing as a kid right right in your
notebook or in your world or in your
head where you were that's where you are
now so before we wrap it up uh would you
do the honors of reading one or two
paragraphs of I would indeed which
philosopher here you can pick and choose
I always there's a few pages and you can
always let people hang on Grandma's got
to take her glasses off to read I
actually have uh bifocals and they're
not working do you have the inability to
read after the age of toxicity tests of
cosmetics ftis oh I'm talking about the
animals here stop if you cared at all
about the animals apologize toxicity
tests of Cosmetics on animals violates
their rights but important medical
research cancer research for example
does not the clubbing of babies he's
using that's not what Tom rean is saying
he's actually uh saying that that's
people's logic so it I didn't want it to
sound like he's saying it doesn't
violate their rights to to do medical
research he he believes that it does um
medical research for example does not
the clubbing of baby seals is aor but
not the harvesting of adult seals again
he's not advocating he's saying that's
how people think um you don't change
unjust institutions by tidying them up I
guess what he means is by putting it in
convenience acceptable not again what's
wrong fundamentally wrong with the way
animals are treated isn't the details
that vary from case toase is the whole
system the forlornness of the V calf is
pathetic heart-wrenching the pulsing
pain of the chimp with electrod actually
I can't even go on because I know when
you see those I'm so sorry but uh
corporate farming and the medical tests
on on on animals if you've seen
documentaries about it and you see what
exactly what he's saying the forlorn
sadness and depressed it's I'm life of
ping right now I can't continue to read
sorry that's okay uh it's uh I I
absolutely in theoretically would agree
with everything he's saying here because
I assume he's on the same on the same
track as me but now I am thinking about
those documentaries where they show the
monkey
suffering terribly so that's an
interesting question though um let's say
they could find a cure for cancer but
the only way right but that's that's a
false opposition false I'm just saying
in in theory just for the sake of
argument right the only way to do it
would be to and I'm I'm sure there is
another way mhm but the only way to do
it would be to experiment on an animal
in that case do we well I don't know
because again it's a hypothetical so
what's the point uh never we've first of
all at this point if they haven't cured
cancer I also feel like how much more
money and time does uh collectively the
world need to to seem to get its arms
around this thing it I feel like there's
monetary reasons uh it's a business it's
a huge business I don't know this for
sure it just feels odd to me that with
so much energy time and money for years
and years and years having been put
towards cancer research that many of the
treatments are still very similar to
when I was my mom passed away of cancer
like many people's parents and relatives
almost everyone gets cancer seemingly
I'm not I'm not downplaying it I'm I'm
bringing this up merely to uh to make a
larger point that in 20 30 years ago
when my mom passed away many of the same
treatments are still in play today all
so little progress has been made I'm not
saying that uh progress hasn't been made
it has but to be used using some of the
very same things that I'm seeing now on
other relatives that literally a feels
like a lifetime ago were being used on
my mother who of course uh did not in
any way benefit from any of these
grueling procedures as most people don't
uh some people do if you catch it early
enough obviously there are many success
stories but for the most part uh I don't
really see the logic in putting people
through what they go through especially
when the cancer is not particularly
found early enough it's it's a very
expensive very physically grueling
painful process for the patient and um
the the to to continually test not just
for medical reasons but uh cosmetics and
other things that is absolutely not
necessary to use animals for and to
continue to farm in such an inhumane way
where the life of these animals is
misery just abject misery they in their
entire lives never move an inch some of
the cattle with Twisted necks literally
from growing up in in a
crowd uh and the despair raising and
owning chickens by the way which I did
in Brooklyn changed the way I eat meat
forever I I won't eat anything that's
not free range uh kosher me or may well
sometimes it's not free range but I try
to get well even with that cuz I I take
your point but I even feel badly about
that because it it feels wrong to that
the whole job seemingly of these animals
is to feed us uh it even if they're
human Heritage uh locally sourced Farm
to Table uh the chicken so you're still
killing it for someone to eat that's its
whole it what and I feel like a lot of
these animals and and I have eaten meat
I I do eat meat on occasion uh not very
much but I I and unfortunately you know
obviously we have worn uh leather uh
things like that uh so I'm not saying
I'm this
innocent right moral person but I try
very much to stay away from me as as
much as I can and to stay away from
products that animals have been harmed
in in in these products coming to me um
I almost I mean that the corporate
farming thing or even puppy mills to
provide certain breeds of dogs for the
consumer um the life of or uh the the uh
animals that are done for medical and
psychological research where they put
animals in deliberately perilous
situations to study their
behavior uh I find abhorent and the
conditions these animals live in and
then they are just either killed or are
sent to an even worse situation to just
die on their own in a field right um
it's it is indicative of a society of
how it treats its children it animals
its elderly and the environment when I
was younger I S try and think okay maybe
this animal that's suffering terribly
was in a past life a oppressor of some
kind that made others lives miserable
and and if there was Justice in the
universe then it came back as this but I
thought but it doesn't know right that
so there's not just plus I don't believe
in a just I don't believe there's a that
the Universe tilts towards Justice
you're you're creating reincarnation I
was I was trying to find a way around
some of the suffering when I was younger
I've thought about that and I know I
Kylie and I watched a documentary about
this guy who beat these dogs like
brutally beat these dogs it was very
hard to watch um and uh I was thinking
to myself if there if there's a hell I
hope it's that he comes back as those
dogs and with the knowledge of what he
did to them the knowledge has to be
there though has to then face himself in
human form
as the dog and and and know but but it
won't be worth it if he doesn't know if
if the knowledge isn't retained through
the Journey to reincarnation then it's
just another dog suffering right I got
to go to the I grandma has to use the
restroom for my overactive bladder
syndrome ask your doctor take toz Janine
thanks so much for being on the show
thank you um can we actually do one more
outro real quick Janine thanks so much
for being on the show thank you all
right thank you maybe I'll leave it in
with both that'd be
[Music]
fun well thank you everybody for
listening to another edition of modern
day philosophers thanks again to Janine
garoo for doing the Show and The Stand
Comedy Club for hosting the recording
you guys if you want to help support me
support the show there's only one way
right now and that is to go and pick up
my CD which is called some kind of
comedian available on iTunes and Amazon
and standup records.com so please do
that and help me survive uh the other
way I survive is at the kindness of
Ralphie and Lana turna who employ me to
produce the perfect 10 podcast also
available on iTunes so go check that out
and you can always email at the comical
yahoo.com I'd love to hear from you and
another way you could help the show is
to leave five stars and a nice comment
on the iTunes because that will help
other people find out about the show and
if you have nothing nice to say either
email me or just don't say anything well
thanks everybody and hope you have a
great week see you next week on Monday
bye