it's the season
seven
finale of modern
day
philosophers that's right the season
seven finale what's up everybody we made
it it's the season s finale of modern
day philosophers I'm excited I'm Danny
LEL I host this show and today's episode
is with special guest Bobcat gold the
incredible Bobcat gold weight who
according to Logan who Masters the audio
since episode one Logan heftel the very
best at AT Audio if you ever need
anything look him up and he's also an
incredibly talented musician uh Logan
said that he's heard a lot of interviews
with bobcat and nothing is quite like
this one he said we really have
something special and I believe him I
also felt that it was very special and
I'm very grateful to bobc for doing it
we have some SP sponsors some incredible
sponsors today's episode is brought to
you by standup records here's a word
from them warning last year over 40,000
Americans died in car related accidents
not a pleasant thought is it in fact as
thoughts go it's downright depressing
well that's where we can help cheer you
up we're standup records.com and we
offer the finest in CDs DVDs downloads
and merchandise from the best comedians
on Earth artists like Mark Marin Maria
Bamford Eddie peperone and Doug stanh
hope available at fine record stores
amazon.com and the the iTunes music
store that's standup records.com come on
listen to us while you're driving live
dangerously standup records the very
best the very very best in comedy CDs
albums vinyls digital downloads check
out standup records.com my new album
should be out shortly it's now uh got a
title it's called Danny Lael the nicest
boy in Barcelona and we recorded it in
Barcelona and God willing that will be
out
within a month so by uh the beginning of
season 8 I should be able to direct you
to a link so that would be good and I
look forward to hopefully you guys
supporting it and picking up the new
album but in the meantime go pick up
some great stuff from standup records
and today's episode is also brought to
you by renovo Enterprises do you have
bad credit well guess what they fixed my
credit and they can fix yours as well
there is no cost no obligation analysis
to determine exactly what is holding
your scores down other than $250 deposit
you don't pay for anything until the
negative item or items get removed and
they will get you over a 700 credit
score in as little as 30 days they can
get you qualified for a new credit card
or an unsecured personal loan you go to
renovo enterprises.com that's re ovov
AO enterprises.com or call them at 888
2908 888 443 298 renovo enterprises.com
they will fix your credit they did
incredible incredible work for me I
guarantee you I promise you they're
awesome check them out all right
everybody without further Ado except for
the intro song I bring you my talk with
the wonderful Bobcat gold enjoy
hello and welcome to modern day
philosophers modern day philosophers
having failed to pay attention in school
Danny LEL now older and wiser will
attempt to learn basic philosophy 101
our young hero will be joined by today's
top comedians philosophers all their own
ladies and gentlemen here's Danny lope
mod day philosophers
got bobcat in the studio that's fun it's
exciting to have you here I'm in the
house I'm actually in the house you're
in the house I'm in I'm in the apartment
I can keep showing you the the yeah you
got a lot of stuff here I had a comedy
magazine in in the early 2000s and that
was that was the magazine I'm looking at
the picture of Marin and we spelled his
name wrong on the cover which I think we
put it with a K yeah but I think we
might have been like the first ones to
put him on a a cover of a magazine too
so it was bittersweet yeah he never he
never brought it up in fact it took
years till till he blew up and then I
started realized that his name was
misspelled yeah I remember the Boston
Comedy Festival gave me a really hard
time about putting him on there and I'm
like but he's a Boston guy they're like
nobody knows who he is nobody's going to
pick up this magazine we're sponsoring
this thing I'm like but he's really
funny they're like it's not about that
who do they want on the cover it's
anyone more famous they didn't care
they're like just want Lenny Clark they
would have gone for probably Lenny Clark
they I remember they said to me like I'm
trying to think of who was more famous
in Boston then the guy was cool from the
Boston Comedy Festival uh but he was
like listen I get it I'm into comedy too
but nobody knows who this guy is I get
it just pick somebody else for a com I'm
like I already told Mark well first time
I met uh Eugene Merman was he was he
interviewed me for a something a paper
or something or maybe school he went to
am I mean went to uh uh uh Hampshire
college and so yeah so he was a cub
reporter when I met him he had a Fedor
on and it said press
no now I remember I I did the interview
already I was there was no way I was
going back to Mark Marin and saying I'm
sorry I'm not putting you on the cover
after I said that I just had to fight
for it well that's good now does he how
about where's your relationship now with
him we'll do this interview as if it is
a
WTF I did WTF so we all good we're good
we're good we're good all right so uh I
know absolutely nothing about uh
philosophy outside of um anything that
could be boiled down to a bumper sticker
so right whoever wrote um ask grass or
gas No One Rides For Free might be my
biggest
philosophy inspiration I'm I'm trying to
be as shallow as possible in life this
is not uh I think I do actually have
philosophies in my life I I I often uh
you know I I truly believe that um it's
important to quit a lot in life you know
I think I think you should quit until
you end up someplace where you don't
want to leave you know and and I've done
that in my career I've quit uh a lot
actually and it's funny I didn't realize
until recently that I keep quitting I
didn't realize that it was pointed out
by my roommates you know and I I always
jokingly say you know 53 with roommates
it's really coming together so do you
really want to listen to this guy's
philosophies on life but I will say um
I'm way happier than I ever have been in
life and I don't know if it's because of
any um ways I've decided to live my life
at this age or if it's simply just
testosterone fleeing my body but I do
know that I'm way less angry I do know
that I'm never been more productive as
as somebody who who tells stories
so sometimes I'm on stage on the road
and I'm doing my AC and I'm like going
well I'm doing a lot of old bits and and
then I think of like when I ego surf on
the internet and someone will say
something snarky about that maybe I did
some stories before old old material and
then I thought but you know I've also
written a few screenplays and made a few
movies in between the last time I was in
your town so so the true granted I
probably don't have the freshest
nightclub act but I do I I do I am a
little more productive I think than um
than people would think I am yeah and
the people who write the comments are
probably not doing anything yeah which
is really it's not even like you could
say oh who are these people stuff but
but sometimes when you go down a rabbit
hole and you look at somebody who who
writes really
well character assassinations like a lot
of the guys who write comments like on
on the AV Squad they're very funny and
they're sharp and some of them are very
articulate and they're very well-crafted
and you just want to go well maybe
that's how that is their form maybe that
is their Outlet creatively because part
of me wants to go I don't have that kind
of time to write that kind of thesis on
um on a television program that I watch
why not you know you could you could
write a television program in that same
same amount of time and energy yeah I
always wonder about that like the they
they like dig through all these old TV
shows and and I can't even get through
the article like I I like to like think
that I'm I'm like oh I can this is excit
this speaks to me in like one paragraph
into it I'm like I just remember I liked
it
yeah I remember I laughed you know I
don't know uh the Advent of the digital
age has changed the way comedy is
perceived where it used to be there's a
handful of Gatekeepers you know people
you get on The Tonight Show and that
would change your career or young
comedians on HBO or maybe Letterman or
evening at The Improv or whatever but
there wasn't very many Gatekeepers and
now with podcasts and and YouTube and
things like that folks can make their
own products and get their own audience
but the the weird part is is that one of
the things that came up and I'm all for
that I love the idea that that people
don't have to be mainstream anymore to
have
success um as a comedian but this this
new thing that cropped up
is H there's a lot of people that treat
comedy like it's Sports now so now
there's like people who top 10 funniest
guys ever or or you know and it's like
what are you doing this is it's it's
allegedly an art form don't don't
diminish it and and make it you know D
you know or that guy's a professional
like that's the most insulting thing
anyone I think could ever say to me
about any job I do as a director a
writer as a comedian is that you're a
professional yeah yeah that's insulting
to me cuz that means that there is
absolutely no craft art
inspiration or anything to your act
outside of just trying to please and uh
to you know you're good at your
profession you're good at to be a
professional
comedian I mean I'm already getting paid
jokes yeah yeah he's a professional he
did so great he didn't you know he
didn't he didn't read from notes on
stage
you know I've saw Carlin a bunch over
the years and I don't remember ever
seeing George Carlin without notes on
stage M so what you guys say George
Carlin's not professional because he
read he read notes very unprofessional
George Carlin was very unprofessional I
remember he talked about the comics he
didn't like as suit and tie nice guys I
always thought that was like such a nice
ring to that like yeah suit and tie nice
guys yeah yeah or yeah when I I was a
little past that so when I was a kid it
was sweater comedians you know that was
what we rebelled against sweater
comedians guys who went up in sweaters
and uh talked about datings and and
things that not only did it not interest
me I I I I you know it was by the I was
such a comedy nerd when I was a little
boy it's funny that I find I find adult
comedy nerds frustrating I was such a
comedy nerd when I was a boy that by the
time I became an adult I no longer
wanted to be a standup comedian I kind
of wanted to make fun of The Craft M
yeah which you did I did and then later
on in life I became the very thing I was
making fun of cuz you know now I'm a
Storyteller when I tell do standup well
do you still want to go back to that guy
sometimes no you know I think I get to
to Tom Kenny was saying my friend Tom
Kenny um you know he he said that I used
to people didn't know what they were
going to see when they saw me because I
was new or they had no expectations so I
could flip them out by by doing weird
things and whatever I wanted to do on
stage and then once there was an
expectation that that was what was going
to happen I guess for me now the biggest
way to freak people out is going up as
myself but but that's why I make movies
because because then the expectation
every time you make a movie is is is
Limitless you know so so so that's why I
really enjoy making movies he said it
made sense that I went on to to go on
and make movies it's just curveballs you
like throwing these curveballs pretty
much I do but I don't I don't really
think of the audience as much as myself
I I like to see if I can tell these
stories that's and of course part of
telling a story is you have to connect
with an audience but I don't really
connect with a major audience I I
connect with
um tiny audience and and in film
festivals that's that's that's where I
see my movies with people my movies make
hundreds of dollars well that's good
it's it's more than a lot of them yeah
and it doesn't bother me I you know I
have such disdain for so much things
that are popular in pop culture that
that I would rather not be right but
that's the position you've always taken
that seems like yeah I think I've spent
too much of my time making stuff and
doing what I was interested in and not a
lot of time really being too concerned
with how I was perceived by people is
that a
mistake I think in history I won't be
remembered as anybody that
you know I mean and and that's okay but
I mean sadly there's been so
many deaths
lately and show business I I do realize
that I'll be remembered for the guy who
was in Police Academy even no matter how
many more movies I make you know and and
that's okay cuz I know my friends and
family will reme remember me hopefully
in the way I'd like to be remembered
yeah how important is it to you that you
be remembered still I mean it's it's
it's not because I know it's not un un
unachievable that that there's nothing I
can do that's going to
erase uh being in three Police Academy
movies from from everybody's mind yeah
do you do you wish you could not be in
them do you no because everything I did
ended up making me who I am so so so I
don't regret them well let's say you
could still be who you were who you are
now but I could be a guy making small
movies and and doing standup to pay my
rent uh yeah I would not do
them really yeah yeah but what about
other people but I mean Bill Murray says
it's the same thing actually you know he
says that if you want to be rich and
famous try to figure out a way just to
be rich you know so I mean so so you
know um and his body of work is way less
embarrassing than mine I'm I'm surprised
that you're embarrassed by it really
well I'm not embarrassed as much as um I
spent so much in my life and time
discussing it that it it
becomes
uh a lot like especially on the road
it's a lot like Groundhog Day you know
so so I go out and do press and it's
people asking me and talking to me all
about these movies I made 30 years ago
and and um and I get it I understand
that's how they know me and stuff but
it's probably healthy it's kind of funny
you know the last movie I'm made um well
won nine Awards I just you know at
various film festivals I just got one
this morning oh in the mail but so it
it's very nice but um you know my
ex-wife used to say when I would talk
like this she would say that my diamond
shoes were too tight you know these are
really great problems to have
um I'm I'm fortunate enough that I I've
I've had a second career you know most
people don't get the opportunity to um
to go on and and make movies and direct
television and do all that you know they
just they just um you know think about
show business they don't they
don't it would be nice if you just got
fired it'd be much cleaner if they just
said you're fired no we're done with you
but they don't they say they just go
you're you're not going to make as much
money and you're not going to be as well
known but we're going to put you on um
this year we're going to put you on
Hollywood Squares and you're going to do
the voice of a talking puppet sometimes
I get the feeling I was never hired I
don't know if that's worse yeah that's
what I'm saying so that's why my diamond
shoes a te you were never fired and I
was never hired it probably feels about
the same it's probably the same but you
know often when I'm on the road there'll
be young comedians in the dressing room
and they'll they'll ask me they go you
know do you have any advice I go we're
on the same show
man we're both sitting backstage at
Morty's uh in a Mexican restaurant you
know I you know uh what do I have do I
have any advice don't do any talking
horse movies no
um actually it's funny I do find myself
doing out advice now and I don't know if
people take it serious because I'm old
or it's funny that they'll actually they
pretend to be listening I don't know if
they listen to it but they they do
pretend they listening do you ever hit
him with advice that you're like oh man
I you tell him something you didn't even
realize you knew no but sometimes you
know what's funny I just got advice from
from Old Friends uh Tim kazarinski oddly
enough who was in Police Academy so I
would do those movies because I'm glad I
met Tim
but I I currently have like a a few
different things that I can possibly do
which is new for me it's usually I make
a movie and I go scramble to go make the
next one and um he was really smart he
said if you could only do one which one
would you do and then it made it really
clear on which one I should spend my
energy trying to get going I feel like
so many times I I talk to comics and
I've done it myself where you just kind
of almost you're living for the memory
that you want to leave
almost well I don't know if that's true
in most Comics but I I know that um
there's a you know Barry kremens I made
the documentary about call me lucky you
know he always says play for the ages
not for the time um but you know I mean
that that it is absurd to want to be
remembered uh because because you are
powerless over the the way you will be
remembered so so to try to control that
would be ridiculous I think I disagree
with them nowadays I think play it for
the time I think now is only thing that
matters yeah basically you know you're
in that room and if you can make make a
dent um or you know it's not like you
have to go up
there and blow people away with with
uh some sort of scathing take on society
or politics or or or personal
relationships it's basically if you can
go up
there and connect with people by by by
giving them a something private
something unique something personal you
know that's pretty exciting yeah and
also just because it doesn't matter if
you're remembered you're dead there is
that too do I care what a bunch of
people who are now dead would think
about me probably not no because those
people are dead and they're they're done
with yeah so why do I care about people
who are around when I'm dead well it's
it's the the part of our brain that when
we're a kid you you when you realize
that you're not going to live forever
you bum out and then when you realize
and the next thing is you realize your
parents are going to die you bum out
about that so there's the god part of
our brain where some folks say that's
God has created in this part of our
brain where we are trying to
justify things we can't answer or
Justify where we go when we die MH so uh
the god part of a comedian or an artist
brain
is trying to might say well there's no
heaven but I'll live in on Forever by my
work uhhuh which is absurd it's just a
chasing of immortality one way one way
or another you ever really care about
what what nine-year-olds think of you
like well I I do because that's who I'm
speaking to every night when I play a
comedy club I'm I'm talking to people
who have their 9-year-old memory of me
right so I talk to the n years old every
night cuz they always show me how tall
they were they always go I was this big
when I watched you I don't know why they
always have to tell me how tall they
were but they do you ever act really
impressed by how they've grown how tall
wow you really shot up that's you must
have eating your vegetables you're
kidding you were that short wait wait
cuz
usually you know when you forget about
me you're going to be about 3 in shorter
cuz when the dementia hits you're going
to lose m yeah that's another thing by
the way you create the perfect memory of
yourself in these people's heads and
then they all get to Mena anyway yeah
that's true best case best case if they
don't just drop dead it does sound um we
sound very fatalistic but creating in
that moment on stage or that new
painting or screenplay or song you're
you're giving the middle finger to death
you know even if you're making neol
listic art you're still
showing up you're still trying to
connect so I guess at the end of the day
you know for me I don't I don't know if
I believe in a God or a higher power but
I do believe in the the the the power of
Storytelling which you know there's
these certain formulas and if I get them
right someone across the world can look
at the story I made and it can affect
them in their brain in a way where they
feel things so I mean that's that's a
pretty that's huge that's crazy if you
think about it the people in Japan will
watch God Bless America and laugh is is
insane that's I can't even wrap my brain
around that or when I go to Europe with
my my my movies um you know
it's it's funny I mean it's easy it is
funny that like my my movies are are are
better received in in other
countries so I'm I'm the that makes you
a real artist yeah I'm the new Jerry
Lewis or or Sam Fuller I'm going to go
I'm going to go live in Paris or
something but yeah but yeah that's that
that's not me bragging that's that means
you're doing art you know if they don't
like I guess yeah they don't like me
here but uh yeah you ever look at an
audience and try and single out people
and say who in this audience might
trying to impress well yeah you know I
try not to because um you know there's I
just did a video with a a man who's very
beautiful and he dresses as a woman I
don't know how he identifies he just
identifies as a gay man he doesn't
identify as a drag queen or trans but I
did I put him in a video with a pop star
uh not pop star but a a valid singer and
the
video was shocking in the fact that I
just played that character as a normal
person with a normal relationship so it
the result was some people found it
shocking and it's not but I ran into a
guy this weekend who I would have
dismissed if I judged him from the stage
M he had like a he had like a uh he had
a Cubby's baseball hat on and all this
and then he came up to me and he said
that was really great video like he
liked that so so you can never tell who
who you're going to connect with you
know it's surprising it you can't you
can't you can't you never know you know
you can't you it just it'll always
backfire I I think it's interesting that
for a long time your act kind of like
hid who you were yeah and then you got
ultimately frustrated that people didn't
know who you were and uh you ound up
being misrepresented but the weird part
is I don't promote the new
me which is strange like I don't promote
like I don't go on talk shows I don't do
a podcast I don't do the things even
though I've changed who I am on stage
it's still kind of a secret I I I I mean
I really think in a weird way if it was
up to me at this point in my career I
would not be in front of the mic I would
not be only well it is up to you I mean
I would well I mean I I'm up I'm I'm up
on stage sometimes for fun so that's not
true I do enjoy that like when I host
crab apples with Caitlyn Gil my friend
but when I when I'm on the road I I do a
lot of standup
to pay my bills so I can keep making
movies you know I I make a I make a
living so I can make movies I don't make
a living making movies I thought it was
really interesting When I Was preparing
for this interview I'm like oh I love
bobcat and then I realized I don't even
know who Bobcat
is that's and then I thought well I
guess the most I know about him is from
the crab apple show that talking about
that you do at the Improv uh and you did
my show bookshelf at The
Improv and then I I watched a bunch of
interviews with you and most of them
were about you talking about Robin
Williams passing away right I mean that
was what's defined me in the past few
years um initially when he died I didn't
discuss it at
all and now I find myself talking about
it partially because he died from Louis
body dementia which was misdiagnosed as
Parkinson's uh which was something even
that he kept secret but um and I like to
talk about I don't enjoy talking about
it but I like it to be out there so
people don't think he died from
depression or drugs or you're protecting
his memory yeah I am protecting his
memory because he he was a fighter you
know and he he he fought with this
dementia uh you know and and and and I
don't mean to
diminish um you know people die from
depression and it's a very serious thing
but I I just want people to know that
that that that's not he had a disease
that that's very fatal anyways um
despite him taking his own life but he
was getting misinformation from his own
head you know towards the end he got
very
quiet and I was talking to his widow and
I said do you think he
was you know what do you think that was
about and we both kind of thought that
it it was because he was was getting
facts that weren't right and and he knew
they weren't right so he kind of stopped
even talking too much you know that's
that's what she and I believe but you
know now I'm just still processing all
of it to to have someone pass away have
someone pass away who connected with so
many people and and and perpetuated a a
a personality that
was part of him but wasn't you know
wasn't wasn't the the Rob and I my
relationship with you guys were like two
two real people in hiding and and the
whole world knew these like fake
versions of you guys yeah that's pretty
accurate and if you heard us talking you
would go those are the most boring guys
of what that is really true and maybe
that's why we clicked and we're such
good friends you know we both had these
personas that we perpetuated to protect
ourselves from from from people knowing
who we really were so it one thing that
strikes me talking to you about all this
is is that you seem like a very
vulnerable guy and I'm not surprised by
it but your your act that everybody very
aggressive so aggressive and it's so
like and even now sometimes like last
week when I was at crab apples I was
really nasty I must have been feeling
scared or something but yeah it's it's
how I kept people away and and I and I
think Robin was even more vulnerable
than myself um so he always seemed like
a very sweet sensitive guy he was really
sweet and really sensitive and you know
he was very uh uh he's he he was good at
keep keeping a distance with people by
by by giving them what they wanted which
might
be to perform or or or whatever but but
but yeah we we both did a really good
job of of of kind of hiding who we are
you ever think about
why um I can't speak for him I mean
because I'm insecure you know like all
people you know I think I think the idea
of and I think that's part of why I was
destructive for so long because you know
as a younger man I was given
opportunities to probably really put
myself out there and I didn't have the
tools so it would be it's easier to to
tell the president of a network or
Studio to go cram it than it is to
create and and say well this is me this
is how I see the world so you know
that's the phase I'm at now and and the
movies that I make are
are well they're all different kinds but
often they're they're simple in some
ways they're very like fables they're
not accurate slices of life
um but
but but that's I mean that's that's
that's kind of how I see the world I'm
always trying to figure out at the end
of the day there's so many
under there's so
many uh preconceived truths that we live
in and I'm I'm always interested in in
exploring there's always an exception to
all these rules yeah and that's why
that's what interests me in making
movies all my movies at the end of the
day are usually about trying to find
some sort of Truth and
um I think that's kind of weird because
uh I'll look at other filmmakers and
that's not what their body work is about
I'm not saying mine's better or worse
but it's interesting you know why is it
weird to
you I I don't know why that's what I'm
obsessed with as a
Storyteller you know I think when you
were a kid and you found out that the
there is no Santa Claus or whatever you
know I was I took that really
hard basically
that's what my whole body of work is
based on I'm still mad that everybody
was lying well it seems like you're more
Fearless now than you were when you
seemed Fearless yeah that's true it's
funny because it's different that before
it was like f you I don't care and
destruction and now it's it's it's it's
the
um it's
me
really making these movies and things
that are challenging for
people but I'm not trying to piss them
off I'm just you know looking for the
other Starbelly snitches the other
people that see the world the way I do I
like that star belly
sne man that's cool that's really cool
um yeah when when you came in I was
after watching going back to my original
thing I was watching all these things
where you talk about Robin I'm like okay
but he's not talking about himself he's
talking about Robin and then I was
watching a lot of you and I'm like well
he's not really talking about about
himself there uh he's he's just
something else and then I'm like he's
not even really Bobcat he's Robbie like
in I want to talk to
Robbie like you know but you're Bobcat
but you're rob you know yeah yeah I it's
very uh yeah I get very squirely you
know for
um yeah you know I tell I'm fairly
decent at telling stories but uh only
sometimes I get to where I'll let people
all the way in yeah scary well it's good
you're taking steps towards it I'm
excited to see like what kind of art is
g to come out what Happ well yeah
or or I'll get hit by a
bus and then we'll remember you as a
police academy yeah the police academy
dude it's come full circle all right
should we get into the philosopher yes
we should all right the guy that Alex
picked out for you I wonder if it's
pronounced Jorge or George it's j o RJ e
I'm going to go Jorge you're going to go
Jorge with by the way I don't know if I
told you I don't look at any of this
until you do cuz otherwise I come in
with an upper hand so it's Jorge
Francisco
isidoro Lis
Borges I've heard of Borges I think I
think this is like a way longer way of
just saying
Borges have you heard of Borges no I'm
I've heard the name but I I don't know
the context all right let's hear um so
Alex writes Bobcat lit the tonight's
show on fire so I picked a philosopher
who talks about
hell
good but by the way what where were you
in your head at that point which part of
hell I was uh very destructive and uh
running on fear and uh I got really
frustrated with the fact that I could go
on a talk show and I would do very well
but it wasn't changing where I was and I
kind of got to the point where I was
like well I don't want to be on these
shows anymore and I was slightly
influenced by Kaufman and oddly enough
Prince I remember Prince setting a
guitar on fire I mean I know Hendrick
did it but I saw Prince Set uh not a
guitar I think he set his contracts on
fire on a talk show uhuh yeah so so I
thought oh maybe I'll start a fire so
nobody knew you were going to do it when
no no they were really upset they were
they were really upset but I did tell my
buddy I said stand by the fire
extinguisher in case this thing gos out
of hand so so there was some prep that's
great uh bores says that hell is an
illogical mess of an idea used mostly
for
propaganda its main logical problem is
this because a human life is finite
there are a finite number of sins one
can commit because a human's power is
finite there is a finite power to the
evil that he can perform therefore an
Infinity long and Powerful punishment is
always disproportionate it because man
can never earn it if God is truly all
loving and all knowing he would not
commit such a mathematical error I
like hell only works if you don't think
about it too much well you know when I
was a kid I was raised Catholic so you
know you could go to hell for not
actually doing a sin but just thinking
about it and then dying before you had a
chance to be absolved from that sin wow
so you just a tiny child basically
pretty sure you're going to go to hell
maybe Purgatory because human nature
every thought runs through your head at
one point you know um so it's it's the
it's acting on these things that
separates us
from from being animals but uh yeah so
it's a really great place the Catholic
church is a great place to make
comedians cuz you're just racked with
guilt
and you're obsessed with exposing truth
mhm yeah I like the idea about the the
finite and the infinite being
disproportional yeah also um is he
suggesting that there is an afterlife I
mean that just seems well I I think he's
saying that if there is an afterlife
that there is no hell it's it's always
fascinating to me the differences in
when I talk to to Catholics cuz I was
raised religious Jewish and and like we
didn't have a concept of Hell there
we have something that's that's like a
cleansing process that can only take 12
months so it's not
infinite that's why when when the Jew
dies uh people say cottage for him you
know yes and they only say it for 11
months because 12 months would be for
Hitler like the very worst person in the
world could would take 12 months to
cleanse sure so for a regular person
we're like for sure 11 months covers it
is a good guy he may me knock off at 6
months
for 11 months we're basically saying
spare this guy after that we know he's
okay yeah so there is no infinite hell
uh and even what we have as hell is only
just a discomfort a cleansing process of
the Soul so are you are you burning in a
fire or um I like to think of it like an
acid
wash all right so so where do you go
though after to the acid wash is there
the you go Florida of course is there um
is there like purgatory and heaven or
it's just Heaven no there's just this
this atonement for it's just another
world it's just another world it's just
another world there's an idea that
there's seven
worlds and uh there are different levels
of impurity in the different worlds and
we're on the lowest world then you move
up to the next World which is a little
more pure okay and uh where is this
world uh it's it's a different realm
it's a different Universe it's a
different everything this actually holds
more water to me than than living in the
Earth with Devils right there's no devil
in in the sky I like this idea that
there's this this there are different
planes there's different Realms that
that that could actually exist and you
could get bumped down to this one again
if you didn't do it right yeah so it's
reincarnation there's a lot of
reincarnation yeah oh I didn't realize
that yeah I remember learning that most
people that are here right now are on
their second or third time around oh
really
yeah so so they're just not good at it
yeah this is uh this is all new to me
see um 53 so yeah I mean it's what's the
last one though it sounds like a pyramid
scheme what's the last one Does Elon
hover take you out on the yacht or where
do you go uh well then there's just
different higher levels of of closeness
to together to God so then towards the
end it's just you're just but then
there's also the understanding that
there is no real separation between us
and God right it's just
one energy but that's another thought
that's that's a pretty good thought that
that you're connected that's not a bad I
oh no I like it I like that too my
higher power is
reality because when I'm spinning out
I'm not in reality like describe what
spinning out is for you well when I'm
living in fear when I'm thinking that
I'm not enough or this is going to
horrible things are going to happen or
that I'm a failure or I I'm
disappointing people or all these things
when I can stop and go oh you know the
equivalent of praying or whatever I said
well let me look at reality that's my
equivalent let me talk to God let me let
me look at reality reality is it's like
people aren't going to hate you yeah you
you actually showed up and and sometimes
there's so much uh things that I
perceive as as
Injustice you know when someone dies
early or there's a tragedy or all that
kind of stuff I can go well what's
reality and the reality of it is is yeah
it is it's really uneven and again then
then it shifts back and I have gratitude
in my life I know practice is all the
time but reality is enough of a higher
power for me and I'm not I used to
identify as an atheist but now I
identify as an agnostic because you know
Science is based on hypothesis proving
hypothesis correct so I'm not going to
rule out that there might not be a
higher being or meaning or cuz that
flies in the face of s you're sliding
towards the god side I'm going to say
agnostic I I I I guess yeah I guess I am
which is which is weird
um but I think it's because there's so
much zealots in The Atheist movement
that really remind me of Christian
zealots that I don't like right so I'd
rather just go say I'm agnostic it's
less of a movement but but as more
people become agnostic I feel like it's
really catching on then it'll be a big
agnostic movement a big agnostic
movement but that's that's at least your
brain's open you know right right right
yeah I just did uh one of these with
Brian rean also said he recently became
agnostic from from the other side he
went from being more of a god believer
to being more agnostic and uh I was
telling him like we we had a pretty good
back and forth about agnostic dating
sites for people just can't
commit well he uh you know he's a super
talented guy and you would see our acts
they're on the opposite side of the
world but I I have uh I have nothing but
respect for him I think he's just such a
a decent good man you know oh I I
thought there was more to that I no he's
just he's just done a few things that
I'll keep uh I'll I'll let them remain
anonymous that I CU he asked for that
but I just thought I just think he's a
real standup guy I didn't even know when
I brought him up no no I just really
admire him yeah cool all right well uh
he just got a weird shout out yeah I
like the the not knowing part of it all
I I I tend to be I'm a God believer yeah
so I don't know if it's like if there's
agnostic God Believers and there's
agnostic atheists and if there's just
agnostic agnostics right but uh I like I
like the constant questioning I like the
constantly and your brain can play so
many tricks on you it's amazing like you
were talking about like the spiraling
out and how you think um everybody hates
you or everybody's mad at you and I just
know that so many times I'm like
completely off the mark from reality
yeah and I was thinking about it today I
was just like
man I wonder if I if I could go back to
like all those younger mes and just kind
of be like no no no this is what's
really going on like where would I be
now you know well last night I witnessed
something that was So Meta it was uh it
was it was uh you know it was beautiful
do you know Daniel Johnston the singer
right
songwriter um so Daniel was sitting in a
theater we were watching clips of him
from 25 years ago and he hadn't seen the
clips and his mic was on and there's
Daniel and he's talking about how how
the devil's winning the war that rages
with him there's Daniel saying that it's
the end of times and that you have to
get right with God and saying all this
stuff and he's certainly meant and he's
very passionate while he's saying these
things on this thing that we're watching
on screen and Daniel's got his mic and
he goes
Daniel uh it's this is the future
everything's okay the world didn't
end it's a great moment yeah cuz I was
watching it and in in this clip he
clearly was having a manic episode M and
I was like I was like well this is
somewhat dangerous to be presenting a
person
with footage that he hadn't seen and it
ended up being really beautiful it was
really so sweet it was great it was it
was genius and the the the thing about
Daniel Johnson that I really love is
that um you know there's certainly
obviously this real naive uh approach to
how he makes his art or his music but at
the end of the day there's also uh he is
aware you know to an extent obviously
what he said then was aware so it's not
and I do believe his art is valid I
don't think it's it's it's I don't
consider his music or art the ramblings
of somebody who's not stable I there's a
there's a hurt in him that comes out in
his song writing and in his paintings
that that um I connect with you know
even if he was rambling on unstable I'd
still consider it valid I mean yeah but
I but but the difference I think between
him and someone who's actually lost
disconnect with reality is is is Daniel
is forming thoughts and saying this is
how I see the world you know and
sometimes he would have flights where he
clearly was like I said in a manic state
but then he'd have these flights where H
they're not flights they're very thought
out ideas and tunes and Melodies and and
I don't know I just I see what you mean
you know it's I question and then I
stopped I was sitting in the audience
and I was
questioning like a little part of me was
going man you don't get it looking at
the people in the audience and then I
said you know what you're what that's
stop that that you're not here with an
open heart you know you're judging and
that's ridiculous so so it was a really
wonderful thing what you know if there's
a hell it would have to be
finite um that's what uh Jorge is saying
here that's what Jorge saying or is
saying if there's if there's a
hell it couldn't be Limitless cuz we're
we're not Limitless yeah so
we well but you know I think when I when
I was a kid I used to think hell would
be becoming heaven and hell would be
becoming fully aware
of of how you your actions really did
affect other people
if you really were suddenly attuned to
all that and if you had lived a decent
life you would you would be comfortable
but if you hadn't you you would be in a
lot of pain it's like um Adam croll
remember him talking about if if you
could leave a a mini recorder on a table
that let's say you're at a a restaurant
having lunch and then you got up and
walked away and left a mini pen recorder
and then you could hear what people said
you would you would want to kill
yourself it doesn't matter who you are
when you left the table people would be
you know and uh so I guess that was my
perception you know what would be on
that mini recorder yeah I've thought
about that a lot and I also when I was
telling you earlier today I was thinking
about going back to the younger me and
pointing out like how off the mark from
reality I was here and there and there
then I thought maybe I'm off the mark
right now yeah of course how do I know
I'm even well I think I think of of of
how Robin's Remembered in the way I
remember him and how that's
just and then I also triy to not make
his memories in my life just be
stories to to kind of
constantly unearth new memories that I
remember of him in my effort to keep him
alive on a personal level you know uh
one that I just had was cuz my
birthday's coming up I remember when I
turned 50 he lives in San Francisco he
calls me up he wishes me happy
birthday and then I walk into my house
and he's on the phone in my living room
he let me think that he was up in San
Francisco and he had flown down and
surprised me wow so those are the
memories that I'll always you know I try
to keep them alive and not stories but
the feelings yeah
that's incredible you had that
friendship that's just like a kind of
people don't have friendships like that
yeah and that's the other thing you know
it's like I often felt like I was never
going to recover from his loss like I
thought um it was like losing an arm and
i' just learn how to live without having
an arm but I've I've I've definitely
come through the other side and now I'm
starting to process it all and um um I'm
trying trying to process it through the
things I I
make do you remember the first time you
met Robin sure sure of course I mean he
was a huge star then I was 19 I was in a
comedy club I was at where uh the comedy
connection was uh
originally and the guy who ran the club
was like Robin Williams is coming he
goes go in the kitchen I don't want him
to see you and because I was like I had
all this mascara on
and and I was in a leisure suit and so I
just stood in this kitchen and then all
of a sudden he walks into the kitchen
and I wouldn't even look at him and he's
like what are you what are you doing in
the kitchen and I was like well they
told me you were coming I didn't want to
why didn't they want you to meet me I go
I I don't
know it was really
weird so then maybe nine 10 months after
that I was out in San Francisco opening
for Paula Poundstone and he would start
coming to my shows he's still and the
character was full bore you know it was
full bore rage and and and I was in that
Persona and uh and he I think he thought
I was going to be mean or something
because I'd hear him laughing in the
back of the club and then he wouldn't
say Hi and then oddly
enough uh I remember the night we first
started talking and hanging out all
night we were watching
um we were watching that 25th mtown
special where Michael Jackson moon
walked my God is that 30 years ago it
would have to be and um yeah we were
just watching this and and that that was
weird that that was one of the things we
that's how we first started talking yeah
what what were your reactions I don't
remember what we were thinking but we
were like yeah we thought it was crazy
you know nobody had seen that you know
and uh yeah yeah it was all weird all
right well let's uh we'll go back to
Jorge I'll tell you a little more about
him Jorge Francisco isidoro Lewis bores
was an Argentine short story writer he
was an essayist he was a poet and a
translator he was a key figure in
Spanish language literature his best
known books are Fones which is fictions
and L Al the elf he wrote Elf he wrote
Elf Oh I thought that was Jerry stall no
that was just a spin-off on on Borges it
was published in the 1940s they are
compilations of short stories
interconnected by common themes
including dreams labyrinths libraries
mirrors fictional writers philosophy and
religion borges's Works have contributed
to philosophical literature and the
fantasy genre critique Angel
Flores the first to use the term magical
realism to define a genre that reacted
against the dominant realism and
naturalism of the 19th century considers
the beginning of the movement to be the
release of borges's a universal history
of infamy however some critics would
consider Borges to be a predecessor and
not actually a magical
realist his late poems dialogue with
such cultural figures as Spinosa cameos
and I'm probably saying that wrong
camelos and
Vergil enough what you got out of that I
uh well
[Laughter]
uh all what did I get out of that they
they said that he was he created the
term and then they tried to take it away
or he created the the the form I think
they're saying he created the genre ah
by having well no used the term the term
magical real well I first to use it I'm
drawn to magical realism you know I
think that's that's that's what uh
interests me I think all storytelling
has it outside of doing a documentary
but because you're always
saying what if these things happened you
know and and uh you're not saying well
this is the truth and and even when you
go back and you make a movie that's
that's supposed to be based on reality
you're still changing the truth but if
he he he was it the fact that he was M
mixing genres and having folks that were
from different time periods talking to
each other that they thought that um
well I don't know anything more than
what I've read so far I could keep going
if you want sure in 1914 borges's family
moved to Switzerland where he studied at
Le College deiv the family traveled
widly in Europe including stays in Spain
on his return to Argentina in 1921
Borges began publishing his poems and
essays in surrealist literary journals
he also worked as a librarian and public
lecturer in 1955 he was appointed to
director of the national public library
and professor of English literature at
the University of Buenos Ares he became
completely blind by the age of 55 as he
never learned Braille he became unable
to read wow that's that's harsh for a
writer for a writer yeah yeah well you
didn't have to read other people's
things and there was an audible back
then yeah but he could just keep writing
yeah Scholars have suggested that his
Progressive BL helped him create
Innovative literary symbols through
imagination in 1961 he came to
International attention when he received
his first formentor prize uh which he
shared with Samuel Becket in 1971 he won
the Jerusalem prize his work was
translated and published widely in the
United States and in Europe bores
himself was fluent in several languages
he dedicated his final work the
conspirators to the city of Geneva
Switzerland
uh I started reading that like it was
going to be a Spanish word but it was
just the conspir the
conspirators uh his International
reputation was Consolidated in the 1960s
aided by his Works being available in
English by the Latin American boom and
by the success of Garcia marquez's 100
Years of Solitude writer and essayist JM
goet or Ki said of him
he more than anyone renovated the
language of fiction and thus opened the
way to a remarkable generation of
Spanish American novelists that's all
I've got well so clearly he was a bit of
a surrealist if he was up there compared
to Beckett and uh that he dabbled in
magical realism or this is the guy For
Better or Worse who gave us
ComicCon that's that's what I've learned
today
um I have a paragraph uh from him would
you mind uh reading it sure I now
consider hell the dictionary tells us
that hell is dogma and the Christian
Church did not invent these brutalities
it implies that Christianity attracts
all the truths it finds in false
religions I'm not referring to the
simplistic mythology of dung Roasters
fire and tongs I'm speaking Eternal
punishment for the wicked Gibbon writes
that the two vulgar ingredients of fire
and darkness are suff ient to create a
sensation of pain that can be
exaggerated infinitely by the idea of
duration Without End this proves that
the creation of infernos is easy the
attribute of Eternity is horrifying
continuity the fact that the Divine
persecution lacks intervals that in Hell
there is no rest is even more horrifying
but imagining it is impossible writers
who expound on Hell dishonor their
imagination and their
decency I like the dis dishonoring of
the imagination wow I think so what he's
saying is that there can't be hell if
you're not given coffee
breaks and the coffee breaks themselves
might be a hell in themselves but here's
the thing that is true like if you're
in uh this infinite torture and you just
is constant without a break where you go
oh and then they go back yeah it's just
you're just it's just a different it's
just reality yeah yeah it's just
constant pain that would just uh I guess
I don't know if you get even if you
don't get used to it it' just be where
what what what life is you know it
wouldn't be anything other than just
this thing I mean maybe maybe that's
what modern life is yeah I was I was
thinking about how like it seems like
you're having a breather now from from
like the tortured Bobcat of of the ' 80s
and 90s that's true I mean that's and
that's storytelling you know if if you
if you pack the 90 minutes only with uh
it has to ebb and flow there's there
it's the the rhythm of telling a story
the rhythm of of a punchline the rhythm
of of making people laugh or cry or or
any feel anything you know you there has
to be the absence of in the story so
people can fill it in with their head
and once they fill it in then they're
engag engaged and if you don't if you're
not asking them to engage and and try to
second guess what's going on and try to
figure it out they're not that's why I
think like I go to movies now and and it
sounds like an old guy saying get off my
lawn but there's this assault of imagery
that doesn't give my brain I think if
you were raised in video games and
things that doesn't doesn't give me a
chance
to comprehend what I'm watching it comes
at such an Assa all that I don't know if
I I think other people are assimilating
it and it's working for them it just
doesn't for me I'm just questioning if
there's storytelling going on well are
do you go see them often are you going
there I no I don't go there to be mad
like what will happen is someone say you
should see it it's not that bad and then
I'll see it and I go oh I didn't get
this right you know yeah I think there
it's just a lot of flashy flashing
lights and and and explosions more or
less yeah there's it makes sense that
why it does well uh all around the
world it makes perfect nobody has the
attention fan anymore it's like you know
it's like a Snapchat world now so it's
like you see things and they're gone and
and that's kind of like you know
going going back to the memory I don't
think anybody's going to be remembered
no no not
unless not unless I get blown up even
then like people will forget everything
I don't think this like the next gener
generation's memory is just going to be
like you
know TR ourselves to not have a memory
yeah we don't I don't need to Ian I can
look it up on my iPhone right yeah but
it's it's really just like creating
things and they evaporate and like I was
thinking about that with Snapchat like
Snapchat and and a movie are kind of the
same thing look at how much money and
time and work and people go into a movie
and then there's like a billion movies
on Netflix that don't even like I don't
even get to scroll past them right I
like that's like that's years and hopes
and dreams of people's lives right it
may as well just be a Snapchat photo
that that dissolved a few seconds later
well it's interesting because there was
an anxiety that we used to have we go
into u a video store and couldn't and I
wouldn't walk out with a title because
it was so
overwhelming I don't think on the way I
watch stuff now when I go to Netflix
I I guess I do eventually pick out
something that's the difference I guess
before I I would actually
get I would flip out and not
go I don't watch a lot of stuff um and
it's not because I'm a snob it's um
partially I I
just you know I get it like I'll watch a
couple episodes or something and I go oh
this is really well done but I just
won't get hooked in MH I don't think I'm
going to lead this it's just uh once I
see how it's done I go oh this is cool
and and you already know the trick yeah
or just like it's like oh I get it and
then there's shows that aren't made for
me you know right it' would be weird if
I couldn't wait for the next Broad City
as a 53y old
dude I'm laughing and at the same time
thinking man I like Broad City but oh
really like I watch it and I and I
laughed and everything but I also felt
like it's a little creepy that I'm
watching this like like I felt like this
old dude
it was too it wasn't offensive it was
more like oh this is really personal and
uh and um and I don't I don't think
Grandpa should be watching
it w see theot it's so funny that you
see yourself as this old man and well I
do and then I I I joke about it and then
I see myself and I go wow you're old but
but the people I work with and my
friends are a lot of them are much
younger than me and the ideas that
interest me yeah it's weird but I didn't
think of you as an old person until you
kept insisting that you were one yeah I
was like oh yeah I guess he is old well
I'm just kind of pissed about that you
know I've kind of dialed in what I want
to do and now I'm going ah there's a
finite amount of time left but you know
what else though I think you were so
huge at one point yeah that it almost
feels like you lived a whole life that I
think there are guys your age who have
kind of had an even kill existence up
until now they feel a lot younger yeah
but you true and then there are guys who
blew up huge and they're still like
riding high on top but you've lived like
three realities well you know it's it's
interesting I I was directing you know I
work on Mark Maron show I direct a lot
of the episodes and and I did one with
um uh Ray Romano and
uh you know there was a time in my life
I'd look at ry's life and what he had
and thought well why you know I should
have done a sick or I should have
figured it out or I or I wonder if I
could have ever done that and you know
all those kind of things but we were
sitting there in between setups in this
garage just him and I and I was talking
to him and and we were talking about the
same kind of things that
and and it was just like in in a good
way and not that his life is not a good
life but it was like oh I didn't miss
anything it was kind of cool cuz he was
just going you know what are you up to
now I go well I make these movies oh you
know and he was talking to me about my
movies and it was just funny it was like
um matter it didn't matter at all NE
neither of us were any happier and both
of us were interesting making stuff you
know I I you know I was really hoping he
would be a jerk you
know because everybody just says nice
things about the guy and then and then
he I was like oh come on and then and
then he was he was a really good guy
so let's take a look at quotes okay
let's do it to make punishment Eternal
is to make evil Eternal God cannot will
that Eternity for his
Universe I think it's kind of what we
were saying before like without good
there is no bad so if there's no end to
evil God canot will that Eternity for
his universe so God will not say there
will be evil for the rest of
time you know the and I'm not trying to
be cynical I'm just having a hard time
wrapping my brain around his he it seems
like he's wrestling with God he wants
there to be a God he just doesn't want
there to be a hell that I think he wants
there to be more
consistency he wants hell to be but I
think the argument against him from a
god believer's point of view is that God
controls time so whatever is infinite
and whatever is finite would be up to
God so just because you can't understand
it doesn't mean God can't do it cuz if
God is God then why can't God do that
you just have a limited understanding of
of time right and if God created time
then he can bend it like Silly Putty
however he wants and it wouldn't make a
difference Eternal punishment proves
that there is no venial sin all Faults
Are
unpardonable so a venial and mortal sin
do you know those terms I only know
mortal what's a venial venial uh is one
that you can um you can
erase you can say oh I'm sorry but IM
mortal that that's that's that's in yeah
yeah you can't you're locked in yeah you
can't you're going to hell so there's
nothing like that in Judaism either you
can't they're different there's no JV
Varsity sin no I mean as long as you
exist you can repent that's not bad
otherwise you wouldn't be here the only
point to be to be here is is because you
can you can improve is because you can
grow and you wouldn't be here if it was
too getting a whole new idea on on on
the on the faith of you know I I
always
assumed that it was there it was more
Dooms Day it seems like Christianity is
a little more doomsday than uh than
Judaism Judaism yeah you know I always
wind up talking about Judaism I guess
it's cuz it's a big part that's who you
are I me yeah yeah but I I remember you
know every time I go into one of these
I'm like I don't need to bring up
Judi yeah but you know it's it's how you
perceive the world you know no matter
how what you take away from it now or or
you know but that's that's uh uh yeah I
guess Christianity is just is more
Droopy Dog you know it's like it'll
never work you
know that's why it get it's a little
nerve-wracking when when when people
believe in the ends of times get close
to the button you know when elected
official believes that the we're in the
end days that's terrifying it's also
pretty cool that with all the crazy
different beliefs out there that the
world is still yeah like there's some
weird balance be you know everybody has
all these such extreme different ways of
seeing the world and every now and then
somebody gets to navigate the ship with
a different belief and somehow we're
still we're still we haven't yeah I
think it is kind of uh it's it's
dangerous when people believe they're
God is mad at an entire you know uh
Faith ideology government group of
people that's not only dangerous that's
really well it's beyond danger you know
that that's that's a um projection I
think yeah it's just people projecting
God into well we don't like you so God
doesn't like it yeah and also it's just
you know it's most human interactions
are you know based on some sort of fear
you know am I going to be liked am I
going to get hurt am I going to get
killed yeah you know and when you're on
stage and you get to that point where
you're genuinely ad living and you there
is no you're not even sure where the end
of the thoughts going and it and it and
it and it lands that's there's nothing
that can that's the that's and I don't
you know that doesn't happen every time
I go on stage but when that does happen
there there's nothing like that you know
to be talking out of your ass and all of
a sudden it not only does it not only
does it get a laugh but it actually
makes sense you know that's that's so so
for someone who says he's
an agnostic agnostic I I I think that
sometimes when those ideas happen I I
feel like they almost already exist and
I'm just grabbing them and and pulling
them down you're tapping into the cosmos
or maybe it was already even in my head
yeah on how religion is used for
political manipulation there is the
concept that there is the destroyer of
all others I speak not of evil whose
limit is that of Ethics I speak of the
infinite and we were just talking about
that yeah we beat him to the punch
yeah yeah
I'd be interested to see what his what
his
um what his essays are because it seems
like as a philosopher he's mostly
remembered because he questioned the
existence of
hell I think I don't know if this is the
only thing he's remembered for if this
is just the piece that this this is what
his okay yeah that's that's the other
thing when I when I did goes through the
Alex filter it goes through the Alex
filter this could just be like one of
many different things he could just he
could had a couple beers in him yeah he
just might have picked this piece cuz it
worked with the
fire did you ever go back on a Tonight
Show after that yeah actually I was back
on then the following week I did a skit
for them but it's interesting like in
the zygus you know when I'm ego suring
on the internet it'll say that I was
banned from The Tonight Show I like no I
I wasn't I think you want me to be maybe
it's just a better story like that yeah
it is it's just kind of interesting
though it's just you know if the
internet's had me married to people I
haven't been married to and I mean it's
nice to be gossiped about I guess versus
not being but again it it we went full
circle on how you're going to be
remembered and you're powerless over
that so you should have a good time yeah
it's amazing I I mean just I I don't
know what it's like to be at that level
of Fame where people are like you know
what he's married to this woman they
just put it together for you it's
you know Tom Kenny say you have all the
um all the pits of success and not a lot
of the
benefits which is not true but it was
just it's just sometimes you know it's
it's it's a funny line anyway but it's
true to an extent but but it but I'm but
I'm very
happy um creating stuff working stuff
paying my bills and um connecting with a
new audience you know not just the the
I'm connecting you know when I play Rock
clubs it's much younger folks that come
out and they you know a lot of them
weren't even born when I was a big deal
so so I do see things turning and it's
not as uh it's not as depressing as I
make it sound I think what'll happen is
you'll get more and more vulnerable and
open with people and and the and they'll
get to know the real you and as soon as
they expect that you'll come back out
screaming yeah I think so they the other
night I did that at crab apples I was
just like I never do the voice and I was
like I yeah I'm going to do the voice
cuz I'll hide behind
it it's been a pleasure having you here
thank you so much and thanks for having
on your show yeah thanks for doing it
cool
[Music]
[Applause]
all right everybody that's our show
that's our season thank you so much for
being with us thanks again to Bobcat
gold way for being on the show thanks of
course again to Logan heftel for
mastering the audio and Alex felo for
getting us the philosophers please write
into the comical yahoo.com and say hello
it's the end of the season it's the best
time to say hi let me know what's going
on check in if you've already written WR
in and if you've never written in
introduce yourself please make a
donation go to modernday philosophers.
net and there's a donate button there
that keeps this ship fueled this train
rolling this boat from being doc you get
it please make a donation and uh and of
course uh spread the word tell everyone
you know tell everyone you don't know
talk to your mailman talk to the guy at
the pharmacy tell them about the show
please spread the word don't be stingy
with the show share it with everybody
just you know walk down the street and
stop everybody like I used to flyer for
shows in Time Square where you hand out
flyers to everybody and it's not
comfortable but you you got to get the
the stage time so you know you walk down
this the street and whoever you pass you
say hey uh have you ever heard of the
modern day philosophers podcast we're
really trying to grow this thing come on
so please do that and be well take care
yourselves it can be crazy out there be
good to
yourselves I'll uh look forward to you
guys tuning into to the wrap-up show oh
I've got some goodies in the wrapup show
somebody sent in audio of Patrice O'Neal
and I from back in the day on comical
radio when I defend aluel if you heard
the alubel episode I talk about it
somebody sent me that clip I'm going to
put a little piece of that into the
wrapup show I haven't heard it in years
uh but if you heard the the alabel so
you know what I'm talking about should
be should be interesting and I'm going
to read some fan emails that were sent
in recently some real nice ones and if
you send in some now yours could get R
um also you know iTunes go on the iTunes
and leave a nice comment five stars that
keeps this thing visible leave a nice
comment it's the end of the season say
hey what a great season something like
that be well and you'll be hearing from
me and Alex faella with the wrap-up show
in just a little while bye-bye