sir all right well you guys know about
that awful fashion trend skinny jeans
anybody oh man I can't stand it h this
so I want to sing sing a song about that
I just and it's a tight pant it's a
tight pen it's hindering the growth of
cellulite I'm trying to cultivate on the
backs of my legs okay what what if
somebody comes by and they just shank
you right so like you're walking walking
and they're like Shank and then they're
like oh son of a [ __ ] I hit a air
pocket so it could save your
life it's good to be a hearty woman you
don't want to be a wisp of a woman so
anyway this is a a song that uh maybe
skinny jeans could actually save your
life and that's what this song is about
what whoever who didn't think about
tuning
oh I got it oh I try to make I try to
have as many things go
wrong I used to teach
band that was a job from Hell
guys okay I mean it like I think
somebody went down to Hell scooped up
some of that molten material down there
and then um brought it back up and said
behold flutes and
recorders did you ever have kids play
recorder oh God you thought it was
plastic but it's genuine Hellfire
[Music]
Brimstone and when you play the recorder
it calls the
[Music]
devil and then the devil's like a crap I
got to go up there and hear Hot Cross
Buns
again it's horri
it's
horrible all
right all right I save my skinny jeans
oh you got a part in this song you'll
hear it when we do it I save my skinny
jeans for a skinny gen occasion like if
I were riding a bicycle really fast like
away from a predator and I didn't want
my pant cff to get stuck in the chain
see that's smart right that's makes
sense well I save my skinny jeans for
Times Like These Times Like These well I
save my skinny jeans well I save my
skinny yeah you got it okay here we go
save my skinny jeans I save my skinny if
it's too high for
you wherever you're comfortable just put
it in there it doesn't even have to be
this song okay I say my skinny jeans
well I say my skinny nice well I save my
skinny jeans well I save my skinny jeans
while I save my skinny jeans for
desperate means
wo I save my skinny jeans for Times Like
These Times Like These well I save my
skinny jeans for a skinny jean occasion
like if I were on a passenger train and
there were another passenger train
headed directly at us and then we
crashed head on even though the engineer
tried to prevent this whole ORD deal
except there was two trains and only one
engineer so maybe that was the whole
problem there was a lot of sharp
protruding objects in that train and
everybody had on baggy clothing but not
me I had on my skinny jeans so I was
like all right I guess I'll just slip
out so you guys later then I save my
skinny jeans for Times Like These here
we go I save my skinny jeans well I save
my skin nice well I save my skinny jeans
well I save
well I save my skinny jeans for
desperate
means I save my skinny jeans for Times
Like These now hold on give me one
second cuz the instrumental solo is
coming and I'm super stoked
[Music]
[Applause]
save my skinny jeans for Times Like
These thank you very much see you at
laita guys there's another show right
now we really appreciate you being here
thanks a