the priorities in this country are all
wrong you ever feel that way I feel like
the only two things we care about
anymore are recycling and celebrities
and we've even gone as far as to recycle
our celebrities don't believe me take a
look at Who's Back Billy Ray Cyrus New
Kids on the Block Brett Michaels I was
unimpressed with these [ __ ] first
brush with Fame why the [ __ ] are we
giving them a redo oh come on Stanley
Nostalgia can be fun really even when it
comes to something that sucks look I've
been kicked in the balls before I'm in
no hurry to have it done again just for
the sake of nostalgia but they're back
and they're performing and they're
selling out crowds you know what this
tells me the learning curve never kicked
in you see people would rather resort to
something they know because it's
familiar rather than go out and
experience something new no matter how
God awful it is it's kind of like the
girl who sleeps with her ex-boyfriend
knowing that he's a fan of the donkey
punch sure she hates it but there's
comfort and familiar it and by the way
what a bunch of unimpressive uninspiring
talentless Apes they are and that's what
they are overpaid overmarking talentless
Apes period if it were a matter of
talent Brett Michaels would be playing
an open mic night in a dive bar in
Hollywood after working a long shift at
a car wash would you like Turtle Wax and
some Armor All on your dash touch my
dick we get it you know the chords D and
G you're a musical genius is you want to
impress me see if you can make a noose
out of fake hair but women love him they
do Rock of Love those chicks are skanky
too they are I found out they were
coming to Chicago I immediately threw on
a rubber and took some penicillin
there's nothing Rock about him you think
Jack White's ever gone tanning I don't
think so marketing that's not true
Stanley we give new performers a chance
all the time what about American Idol
those are people we don't know and we
give them a shot at Fame true but you
notice they only Sing cover songs so
basically we create new stars out of the
shitty soundtrack of our past what is
this obsession with making everyone an
overnight success in this country
America loves an underdog but only when
it comes in the form of a sports team or
an Entertainer never when it comes down
to things that actually matter like our
policies or your right as an individual
and that's another thing somewhere along
the lines this country became one big
mediocre talent show American Idol
America's Got Talent America's Next Top
Model Project Runway Toddlers and Tiaras
Dancing with the Stars what a [ __ ]
joke every lunatic with CA teeth and a
dream thinks they're somehow entitled to
fame and fortune in this country but we
do it we make them famous then we make
them Infamous which is my favorite part
did you hear what Miss California said
about gay marriage no you know why
wasn't listening sorry but I don't take
my social cues from someone just just
because they look pretty and a
convertible on Thanksgiving remember
this intellectual
Juggernaut and I believe that our
education like such as in South Africa
and Iraq everywhere like such as Iraq
everywhere like such as yeah she placed
in the top three in a similar contest
top three weren't you the bell of the
ball I don't listen to beauty pageant
contestants just like I don't call the
prom queen from my senior years and ask
her which way I should lean when it
comes to abortion Miss California holy
[ __ ] that controversy cranked out more
right-wing nut jobs than Elizabeth
hasselbacks vagina and [ __ ] liberals too
while I'm at it seriously I don't litter
and I'm not racist that's all you're
getting out of me whose side is this guy
on no one's I've read Animal Farm I have
a pretty good idea of how it all works
out you see the media pumps out these
stories cuz they're bored and they know
you'll buy into it their whole business
is predicated on shitty parents all over
the country believe that anyone who gets
a modom of airtime is somehow
responsible for being a role model for
their children eat [ __ ] Fame and
morality aren't mutually exclusive if
you're willing to accept someone at the
drop of a hat to be a role model for you
and your stupid kids don't get your
panties in a l when they do or say
something you don't agree with you Dopey
[ __ ] my point is aggressive marketing
and media hoopla are just going to keep
shoving nonsense down your throat until
you have the gag reflex of Sasha Gray
eventually stupid people will swallow
anything controversial as a significant
issue because in the end all they're
worried about is taking a side people
love to take sides in this country
you're the problem that's the problem
let me tell you what the problem is it
makes them feel important when they
regurgitate unoriginal opinions between
the water cooler and keeping up with the
Joneses they have no real social
aptitude so they put moral stock in
celebrities because they believe that
success is measured by how much money
you have or how often you make an
appearance on television and they want
so desperately to be identified in that
very same way so strong opinions about
nonsense issues fills that void for them
everybody wants a mansion and an iPhone
and a hard dick and a lollipop they want
a pat on the back they want spinner rims
and a bedazzled Ed hearty t-shirt they
want a cool haircut and fake tits and a
dog in their purse they don't give a
[ __ ] they want courtside seats in Paul
Walker movies and they apparently want
all of that to the sound of the guy that
broke their Achy Breaky
Heart what do I
want I want to be inspired I want a cup
of coffee and I want to be left the [ __ ]
alone
[Music]