[Applause]
how you doing
man I'm going to uh I'm going to the
lake shore the
theat
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
ladies and gentlemen it's my great
pleasure to present to you Mike
Stanley come
[Music]
[Applause]
on how you guys
doing Chicago we sold it out it's sold
out this is amazing right everybody here
is really good-looking you got dressed
up you look good I I don't look good I
know you guys are looking at me right
now like is that that guy from the movie
Powder he looks like
[ __ ] I do look like [ __ ] man I do I look
like I should be in a wheelchair with a
quilt covering my
legs outside the Ronald McDonald
House Ronald McDonald House they
shouldn't call it that that tricks
children right kids love McDonald's
they're like yay Happy Meals nope
chemo chemo here's your M wig
chemo enjoy it chemo
saby I love being here man I live here I
live here in Chicago you know yeah it's
[ __ ] great man cuz sometimes I have
to drive long distances to perform you
know what I mean like I have drive to
Canada recently was 5 hours but thanks
to Map Quest it was 8 so that was
fun you don't understand 8 hours in a
car alone for me that's an entire pack
of cigarettes and three serious rounds
of masturbation right
there right off the top yeah I'm
stopping at drive-throughs I'm not even
hungry I'm just out of napkins you know
what I mean buddy
pulling up to the window with my t-shirt
and my teeth
[Applause]
hello I love being here man I'm happy to
perform anywhere where I don't have to
drive through [ __ ] Indiana
basically
yeah you ever do that you ever you ever
drive through Indiana
anybody yeah that's the best way to do
it drive right through it don't even
[ __ ]
stop seriously unless you have a green
belt in Taekwondo or rape whistle get
the [ __ ] out of
there that's melon Camp country you got
no business being
there I'm driving through Gary it just
reeks like [ __ ] and despair I'm like
oh oh Michael ma Memorial you guys
should build a nose plug Factory around
this
[ __ ]
[ __ ] and if you're from Indiana or Gary
I apologize all right I'm sorry I don't
want to walk out of here and get dips
bit in my eye
okay cuz the people are [ __ ] crazy
man they're just like [ __ ] nuts in
Indiana and you could tell they're nuts
just look at the Billboards when you
drive drive through Indiana every
Billboard's like strip club adult
bookstore fireworks cheap
cigarettes strip club an old bookstore
fireworks cheap cigarettes it's like
what does that say about Indiana really
it's like hey man if you're looking for
a state where you just want to stop by
get drunk watch a woman get completely
naked then light a Roman Candle off a
cheap Winston then [ __ ] Indiana's the
place for
[Music]
you come on down you can pick up a copy
of Hustler on your way to the burn
center you're like
what and I have friends from Indiana you
know and I ask them I'm like why is
everybody out of their [ __ ] mind and
they all say the same thing they all go
cuz it's full of white
trash it's full of white trash it's like
maybe but there's white trash everywhere
right there's white trash in your own
family you don't get that pissed off
about it right applaud if if you avoid
trash in your own
family and if you didn't applaud guess
who it
[Applause]
is so I'm driving through Indiana right
I'm driving through it with another
comic right and I see this billboard and
it's for Planned
Parenthood and I'm like what's Planned
Parenthood My Buddy goes oh uh that's
the abortion clinic and I was like oh
but then I was like wait a minute it's
called Planned Parenthood shouldn't that
be called unplanned
Parenthood or just
oops with three O's just to make it fun
for everyone just a big neon sign like o
o o PS exclamation point But the dot on
the exclamation point would be a baby's
face with a line drawn through
[Applause]
it
guys you got to look at a white trash
area optimistically like come on how
often you get to [ __ ] a girl in a
wheelbarrow never not since I've been
fired from Home Depot can I make that
[Applause]
happen you know what's getting
progressively more white trash I've
noticed you guys gas
stations yeah I was in a gas station not
that long ago and a from selling gas and
glow-in-the-dark
ashtrays they also sold fish yes fish
from a gas station oo I bet that's
delicious hot off the George Foreman and
under your Dale Earnhart commemorative
plate
huh that's a good family meal hey maybe
while you're eating you can explain to
your kids why your house has a flat
tire or how to make bathtub
Jin or or maybe or maybe you can explain
why whenever new mommy comes home from
work her mascara's running but she's
always got a fist full of
cash those ain't herpes around here we
calls them love freckles
what
what herpes does anybody in here have
[Applause]
it herpes you know what those are God's
Little stop signs that's what are think
before you drink you
guys so I live here I live here in
Chicago I didn't always live here I was
actually born and raised in the
beautiful Detroit
Michigan which is a nice area it's a
nice area if you're like losing your job
and getting
carjacked I used to live like a really
dangerous area of Detroit like a really
seedy dangerous area in Detroit but now
we live in the gayest neighborhood in
Chicago Boys Town yeah that's where I
live and I had no idea my girlfriend
moved out here a month before I did she
was like Mike I found the perfect place
that's in boy toown and I'm like what is
boy toown she goes it's the number one
gay male hotspot outside of San
Francisco you're going to love it and
I'm like
what and then I moved here and I didn't
realize how gay it was until I was at
the laundry mat one day and I put three
quarters in the dryer and I pushed that
lever in and it played an Elton John
song All My Shirts came out all sparkly
and
[ __ ] but I feel bad for gay males in
America though I do cuz they get the
shitty end of the stick a lot you
guys
everybody in my neighborhood's gay but
they're all like really friendly and
helpful and nice like when I first moved
here I didn't know my way around the
city but there was always somebody I
could ask for directions like there was
always a cop or a construction worker or
an
Indian or two bikers blowing each
other here's something I just found out
America did you know you can get a DUI
and a bicycle did you know that that
[ __ ] I
do what's the worst thing I'm going to
do drunk on a bike seriously break my
waffle cone come
on and I can't go to jail are you
[ __ ] me look at
me I look like a [ __ ] Sears mannequin
without the
wig they would tear my ass apart you
might as well throw me in there with a
feather hanging out of my ass in a tube
toop that just says [ __ ] in
rhinestones because I am rapable you
guys that's all I'm
saying I am rapable and I know this
because that's what they used to tell me
all the time in
church bam writing the Pope's nuts on
that one
huh I don't mean to be a dick but I
don't like this new
pope
[ __ ] him
right he's a showof isn't he the new
pope he's always standing up and using
both of his
arms showing off the full rotation of
his neck I'm like you cocky
[ __ ] last Pope didn't do that
[ __ ] and people loved
him I had to get some fast food the
other day I had to to cuz I was hungry
and I was out of napkin
so two
birds I don't know if you guys are like
me I don't like eating fast food I just
don't trust it I don't because every
year we get some [ __ ] up story where
something horrible ends up into the food
right like that time of guy got a finger
in his food remember that a guy got a
finger in his food and there was another
one too where a guy got an ice cream
cone or some yogurt or some frogurt or
some [ __ ] and there was a finger in it
did it end up in anybody's mouth does
anybody know
a I would never go public with
that you know what I would do if I found
a finger in my food I would take it home
and I would clean it really
well yeah I would trim the
nail and then I'd carry it with me and
use it to touch stuff that I don't want
to like I'd push an elevator button or
flush a public
toilet I'd finger a fat chick you know
what I'm
[Applause]
saying it's your finger you can do
whatever you want with
it boy some Hogs got moist on that one
huh
fellas listen I don't care if you're fat
I don't if you're overweight it doesn't
matter as long as you're a good person
in here
okay and I don't tell a lot of fat jokes
in my act I don't I used to when I first
started doing standup comedy and one
time I told this fat joke and I was in
Ohio where there's a shitload of fatties
and
uh there big fat lady stood up after I
told the joke and she was like how dare
you make fun of fat people you're an
[ __ ] and I was just like
whoa lighten
up
and as soon as I got out of the
hospital stop telling that
joke Summer's Here everyone's excited
right yeah we go ape [ __ ] in the summer
here right don't we CU we're [ __ ]
locked in all winter because it's just
[ __ ] [ __ ] cold
here it is it gets [ __ ] cold you know
[ __ ] cold [ __ ] cold is when you
walk outside and as soon as the wind
hits your face you make a face like you
just sniffed an [ __ ] you're just
like and then your face freezes into
that face and then you walk into the bar
and everyone's like Jesus Stanley what
were you sniffing [ __ ] before you
got here I'm like no it's [ __ ] cold
check the temp
dick everybody pars it up in the summer
here you know I got invited to a house
party recently I didn't want to go but
then I remembered it's been a while
since I've seen someone regret inviting
people over
so isn't that great I love that isn't it
like you just see the [ __ ] mood of
the host change throughout the course of
the evening they're like why the [ __ ]
did I invite these people
here you know cuz you show up at like
10:30 and they're just happy as a clam
they're like oh yeah they're [ __ ]
dancing come on in [ __ ] party sweet
have some spinach dip it's a good time
[ __ ] beers in the fridge thanks for
hanging out and then cuts at 4:30 in the
morning and they're [ __ ] crying and
they're like we're all out of toilet
paper and the cat smells like [ __ ] you
guys are dicks everybody
out fair enough I bid you a
do but I can't drink like I used to I
can't man it gets harder as you get
older right the hangovers
crippling yeah you ever you ever drink
so much you wake up
sore maybe it's because I live in boy
town I don't know I'm just saying you
guys I think someone tried to Lance my
bass hole you know what I
[Applause]
mean but why not you know go out party
it up I don't have kids you know what I
mean [ __ ] it I don't have any
responsibility I couldn't imagine being
a parent in this day and age you guys
have kids a lot of
you couple of you yeah it's got to be
difficult man cuz shit's like so
different than the way all of us were
raised you know what I mean like there
might be an age differentiation here
between most of us but for the most part
I think we're all raised old school you
know what I mean like the technology is
just everywhere right now and I think
parents are using it inappropriately on
their kids for instance I saw this
commercial the other day 99-year-old kid
had a cell phone in the commercial what
the [ __ ] does a 9-year-old kid need a
cell phone for hey Tommy yeah I just ate
the brown
cray what's that nope tastes just like
the pink one snap like
what have you seen that commercial
9-year-old kid has a cell phone and he's
bragging about it to all of his friends
he's like yeah it has movies and music
and an iPod and video games and and his
friends are like oh your mom bought that
for you she's the coolest but then it
shows his mom and she's sitting in the
front of the computer with all her Dopey
friends and she goes yeah with a click
of this button I can see exactly where
little Jimmy is because the phone has
GPS GPS what we didn't have that [ __ ] gr
up right our parents had no idea where
we were when we were growing
up listen I don't know if you guys are
like me but in the summertime at my
house we weren't even allowed in the
[ __ ] house do you remember that
[ __ ] not being allowed in the house in
the summertime we got kicked out in the
morning and when we're allowed back
until the street lights came
on we didn't have cell phones my dad
would whistle and we come running like
sheep
dog and they put GPS on a kid it's a kid
it's not a school of migrating Dolphins
you're tracking for the Discovery
Channel leave him the [ __ ] alone let him
figure out life a little bit on his own
that's what our parents did and what did
we do we hopped fences and we ran from
the cops we threw rocks at windows we
learned what real danger was
all
[Music]
right I guarantee you I guarantee you
those same parents that are using all
this [ __ ] technology to watch over
their children like big brother are the
exact same ones that wind up on super
nning like my kid's such an [ __ ] I
don't have the
problem I'm gonna have four or five more
[Music]
though [ __ ] you get a grip I always
thought my dad was an [ __ ] growing up
who wanted nothing to do with me turns
out he was just busting his ass to put
food on the table you know what I mean
and he had a great motto too he said
Mike you go and do whatever you want
with your life but if you get your ass
in trouble don't call me to bail you out
some of you might have heard that and
that's true too because if I did go to
jail and I had to call my dad I would
have heard this you're rapable click
that's
it tough luck chump that's a waste of a
phone call right
there
cuz that's all it took for us that's it
that's all it took just the fear of your
father to keep your ass out of trouble
right that's all it took and my dad's a
big dude too he's scary of [ __ ] he's a
surly [ __ ] you know he's like a
gorilla with table etiquette you know
what I
mean if my dad had to bail me out from
jail holy [ __ ] this is how that little
scenario would go down I'd be sitting in
the cell right the cop would walk up
he'd Slide the bars open he'd be like Mr
Stanley uh someone posted your bail I'd
be like oh sweet who was it it was your
father you know what [ __ ] slide that
thing shut I'm going to hang out in here
is that all right what do we have in
baloney again bring it on I'm not going
anywhere near that
man I just traded three cigarettes for a
teardrop tattoo I'm sticking
around I couldn't imagine being a dad
you know it's got to be tough you've got
to learn to drink and drive
and pay child support [ __ ] that
plus you look [ __ ] in
shorts yeah I said it all Dads look
[ __ ] in shorts and you're giggling
right now because you're picturing your
own father in
shorts and he looks [ __ ]
[ __ ] so I'm bald it's true it's not
a cap I'm not [ __ ] with you you guys
anybody else any other bald gu shave her
head anybody Yeah couple there you go
Shine On You Crazy
Diamond I would never get hair
transplants or plugs or any of that [ __ ]
it seems like whatever your downfall is
whatever your shortcomings are they
always come up with a pill or a [ __ ]
infomercial that's always on late at
night when you're drunk trying to make
you feel horrible about yourself you
know what I mean you ever see those hair
restoration ads like they're all the
same watch them every time I swear to
God there's one real curring theme on
all of them and that is as soon as those
guys in the commercial get the new hair
as soon as they get the plugs for some
reason all of them immediately bam hop
on a jet ski
woo jet ski time everybody I got new
hair they make it seem like you need
hair to ride a jet
ski like if you were balding and on
vacation and you tried to rent a Jet Ski
the guy behind the counter would just be
like
no why don't you take your comb over and
what's left to your dignity down to the
paddleboats
douchebag and don't drink from our
fountains so we'll spray you with the
fire
hose and yes Miss the carpet does match
the drapes okay keep them up here keep
them up here I'm trying to work right
now all
right I lost all my hair in the middle
that's where you lose it young guys
right in the middle so we lose it first
isn't that weird and then right after
that even Stranger than that I lost all
of my chest hair right down the middle
all of it fell out gone even Stranger
than that right after that all of my
pubes right down the middle all of them
fell out gone but the sides are long and
thick and
flowing just
gorgeous it looks like a bastad Hound's
ears on each side of my
dick some sometimes I'll take my
girlfriend's curling iron and I'll curl
him down the
sides then I'll put a little black hat
on him like he's a hidic
[Applause]
Jew I don't pretend I'm a skin head
who's choking him until he
[Music]
pukes pretending is fun isn't
it
I'm not very good-looking and I'm okay
with it a lot of people get to be famous
just based on the fact they're
good-looking and I like to call these
people Paul
Walker so I'm broke anybody
else it's fun isn't it go going to Coin
Star to buy mouse traps that's a good
time
I've been broke too I've been broke for
so long when I found out the market
crashed I was just like sweet now we're
all
leaving but we have Barack right Barack
I like Barack you
know I feel like he's trying you know I
like him he seems to be a very
intelligent man you know he seems to
have a plan to fix everything the market
the war some people are still skeptical
some people are like don't get too ahead
of yourself there still are a lot of
hurdles I'm like hurdles he's part
Kenyon those won't be a problem
[Applause]
either I can't even afford to go out
anymore I just stay home I don't do [ __ ]
you know I stay home and I watch
television with my girlfriend that's the
best way to save money I found but it
sucks cuz I have to watch whatever she's
watching watching and she likes the
worst television on the planet like I
had to watch Oprah the other day I had
to because she was watching Oprah and
she was making me a sandwich and that's
called
compromise so I'm watching this show
right and I don't want to watch it to
begin with and the story is this
13-year-old girl fell in love and had an
affair with her 45-year-old softball
coach which is disgusting I know but the
cool thing was at the end of the episode
Oprah gave everybody a 45-year-old
softball
[Applause]
coach I like Oprah though because she
always has stories of hope you know we
never hear stories of Hope anymore like
I'll tell you the last story of hope I
read took place in an area called Paw
Paw Michigan all right here's the story
you've heard of it all
right here's the story 15-year-old kid
in a wheelchair got stuck on the front
of a
semi
true story 15-year-old kid in a
wheelchair was at a truck stop somehow
got stuck on the front of a semi TR
here's where it gets fun kids truck
driver drove 5 and 1 12 miles at 60 M an
hour before he realized the kid was
there and I thought to myself wow that's
probably the most fun you could have
being
[Applause]
crippled it's probably the most fun you
could have being a truck driver
too I'm going to get the [ __ ] kicked out
of me with naked lady mud flaps when I
walk out of
here so I have a girlfriend I love her
she's great she's fantastic she's smart
she's got her [ __ ] together she's got a
great sense of humor plus you guys she's
got huge tits and a drinking problem and
I'm like
[Applause]
yes
finally because I used to have to lie to
girls all the time and young guys if
you're in here and you're going to lie
to girls be careful cuz it will backfire
on you it will and you're like how tell
me Mike Stanley you bald Whimsical
huster I
will there one time I was in this bar
right and I'm talking to this girl and
I'm trying to get her to come back to
the love dojo for a spank and tickle
contest but sometimes I'll say
ridiculous [ __ ] to people just to test
their sense of humor right I look at
this girl and I rattle off the worst
pickup line anyone's ever said I go you
should come back to my place I've got
leather
sheets but she looked at me dead serious
and she was like is that even
comfortable and as soon as she said
comfortable my brain immediately went
into safety mode where it was like Mike
listen if by some stroke of bad luck you
get this girl pregnant you were going to
have the dumbest kid on the planet
and I'm like yes so I snap back to
reality right I look this girl right in
the face and I go you know what it was
very nice to meet you I've got to get
out of here and then I high-fived her on
the forehead and I got the [ __ ] out of
there that's not true I actually ate her
out on the hood of a snowmobile later
that
night why because I'm a gentleman that's
why you notice she wasn't blowing me in
the joke I was going down on her cuz
someone still cares
ladies
[Applause]
all right well here's where the show
gets dirty kids are you ready for
it all right all right cuz this next bit
contains salty
language but it's peppered with
morals this is more of a public service
announcement all right here's the deal I
hang out with a lot of single guys who
Lie To Girls At Last Call cuz they're
trying to pull a piece of skirt steak
their words not
mine
and they lie to girls but they don't lie
about what kind of car they drive or how
much money they make I have single guy
friends that lie about the size of their
penis I don't know why as a guy you
would ever think that that's a good idea
to lie about the size of your penis cuz
let's say you talking up all night she
believes you you go back to her place
things heat up she pulls down your pants
then what Casanova you've got a lot of
explaining to
do and I don't have a big penis I don't
I don't give a [ __ ] I don't you people
I'll tell
you I wouldn't even want a big penis I
wouldn't I've seen porno we've all seen
the guys in porno holy
[ __ ] those guys are slamming [ __ ]
with [ __ ] the size of duralogs
which makes for a great show but then
you figure they have to walk around with
that giant dick in their everyday life I
have a hard enough time trying to find a
pair of jeans that fit I don't want the
added aggravation of bringing a tail
into the mix like yes sir do you think
you could let out the crotch of these
Wranglers just a tad I seem to have been
blessed with an enormous
tallywhacker somewhat of a hindrance
when I buy slacks you've got to roll it
up like a cinnamon bun and stick it with
bobby pins just to keep it from flopping
out of the bottom of your shorts at the
family volleyball
game cuz that's an awkward topic of
discussion no matter how great your
aunt's potato salad
is
I did that joke last show right I'm
standing out front this girl walks out
to me and she goes you know that joke
you do Mike Stanley about big penises
it's funny but I only date guys with big
penises and I was like really and I'm
trying to talk to her and she's just not
getting it I'm like listen sweetie
here's the deal let's say you are dating
a guy and he's toting a staunch mules
[ __ ] and it's everything that you want
but then four months down the road like
most Rel relationships right you guys
break up [ __ ] goes pear-shaped he takes
off and leaves you then what are you
left with just a total crotch and a
shello
ideology yeah just a Haggard saggy
lipped beef hole rendered useless to
every other average man on the
planet and she might wise up one day she
might wise up and go you know what I
don't need that to make me happy too
late honey cuz the damage is already
done you might meet the man of your
dreams he might be average like me then
what's he got to do to please you he's
going to take your 15-in great American
challenge dildo and Saran WP and under
his 6-in nub like the fuel tank on a
rocket ship just to hear you breathe
heavy I'm standing up for the little guy
for Christ's sake can I get an
[Applause]
nameen that's my mom's favorite
joke but ladies you lie too to though
you lie too you're not off the hook
what's the number one thing every woman
says she looks for in a
man what is it according to every study
what is it sense of humor
[ __ ] you're [ __ ] lying I'm a
standup comic I've been doing standup
comedy for 5 years living out of my car
flinging around not only this country
but Canada as well I think I'm a pretty
funny chap but at no point after any
show have I walked towards the exit and
seen two girls go you know what Tammy he
was pretty funny we should stick around
and blow him
seriously you take the tip I'll work the
shaft and balls that guy was [ __ ]
hilarious not
once tonight could be the
night single ladies are you here are
there Single Ladies
here Single Ladies I'm going to give you
a piece of advice here's something
Beyond say won't tell you all
right Single Ladies if you meet a guy in
a bar and he takes you back to his place
and he walks you into his bedroom and he
has track lighting on the ceiling and a
box of wine on the night stand right
next to his water
bed don't even wait for him to take the
rubber band out of his ponytail get the
[ __ ] out of
there cuz his friends are in the closet
with a
camcorder and you're going to end up on
the internet and I won't be the only one
to watch
it so will all of your
co-workers I love internet porn I don't
know if anybody else does I'm like huge
advocate of internet porn I do I love it
I love every type of porn I do except
one and that's outdoor porn when people
are [ __ ] outdoors I hate that and I
don't know if it's because the sound of
passing traffic throws off my jerk speed
or I'm jealous that they have a gazebo
and I
don't but I watch outdoor porn I watch
it and I watch it for one reason and one
reason only and here it is kids flies
you ever see a guy with a 10-in [ __ ]
shoe a fly off a woman's ass that's a
whole new type of funny right
there they don't even yell
cut I've been dating my girlfriend for 5
years every time I tell people that
they're like you guys been dating for 5
years why don't you guys get married uh
because I don't want her to get
fat
well I'm concerned about her health you
guys she's always like you don't really
care if I get fat do you Mike I'm like
no as long as you don't care if I buy a
tuba just so I have something to play
while I follow you around the plus-size
section at
Kohl's while you pick out a
moomoo I'm just saying you pack on the p
pounds I'll Play the
soundtrack she can't get fat I can't get
fat we have Ikea
furniture can't be packing on the lbs
with Ikea furniture that [ __ ] is cheap
do you have Ikea furniture don't buy it
it's [ __ ] horrible seriously unless
you're decorating a treehouse for your
kids or all your friends are horse
jockeys don't [ __ ] buy
it
anybody married in here anybody been
married a ridiculously long time been
married a real long time to the point
where you're just [ __ ]
miserable you guys are married who's
married you guys married yeah how long
you guys been married years eight years
nice do you remember the first time you
uh hurt or fart that's
all grow up okay it's weird isn't it the
first time hear your girlfriend or your
wife fart right it is cuz guys when we
fart we fart with
Force we fart with conviction we have no
shame we'll LIF the leg loud as hell we
don't [ __ ]
care but ladies the first time you do it
the first time you do it it's always a
little
elusive it's always a little
confusing it's always just like
[Applause]
a
I'm like did I just hear a
clarinet I think you sat on a
clarinet I'm just saying it's one of
those things that throws you off right
it does it throws you off like the same
way it does the first time you see a
black clown you're like
what
I can't wait for the day that I do that
joke and there's a whole table of
off-duty black
clowns right in the front row twisting
up balloon animal weapons like no it was
funny
[ __ ] we'll see your ass in the
parking lot
honky we take sex for granted though we
really do you don't even realize it man
you do cuz you can have it whenever you
want now right you're old enough you've
got your own place you can have sex
pretty much whenever you want or
whenever she'll let you right remember
when you first started having sex though
remember when you like sneak around and
[ __ ] you're always like like back in
high school you always like [ __ ] you
know you always worried about getting
caught I almost got caught one time it
was like one of the first times I ever
had sex right me and this girl just
finished right her dad pulls up into the
driveway he comes running into the house
he runs into the bedroom he looks at me
dead in the eye and he goes you guys
have better not have been doing what I
think you guys were just doing and I'm
quick wited right so I step right up to
the plate and I'm like sir listen this
was all very innocent okay we were just
in here listening to some Bell Biv
devau I lit a few salmon scented
[Applause]
candles we were discussing plans for
college and he believed me he was like
why are you just wearing a t-shirt and a
condom and I was
like you never do laundry old man what
the
[ __ ] you got to be romantic you know I'm
very romantic I am every year I take my
girlfriend to someplace exotic someplace
where there's an ocean every night I
walk her down to that ocean I blindfold
her and then we play a game called
saltwater or
seen oh she's good you guys she's good
amazing pallet thanks wine
country you know want to take her where
she's never been is Vegas you ever been
to anybody ever been to
Vegas yeah it's amazing we told my mom
we were going she's like what happens in
Vegas stays in Vegas and I was like yeah
that's where we're going to have our
first
kid Vegas is great though it is man if
you've never been like they they
literally have everything you could
possibly want to do like if you've never
been the only way that I could explain
it to you is if Google were a
place thank you for getting that I
didn't in Indiana they were like what
the [ __ ] is
Google he's like put down the baby and
pick up a laptop and join the rest of
us I used to go all the time when I was
single and one time I went to Vegas and
it's always nuts when you go cuz there's
always like weird convention and [ __ ]
going on like you'll go into one hotel
and it'll be like the juggling
bartenders convention or you'll go into
another one they'll be like the [ __ ]
NASCAR driver convention right in my
hotel there was a championship female
Bowlers convention going on so there
were all these Championship Championship
female Bowers everywhere right and I'm
sitting at the bar one night minding my
own goddamn business and this
Championship female bowler sits down
right next to me and she's into me which
is rare for any woman to be into me for
[ __ ] obvious reasons mostly because
when I drink I look like popey's
[ __ ] nephew I'm just
like yeah more whiskey
B I look like a testicle with eyes I'm
not pulling ass
people Championship female bowler is
into me right and we're talking and I'm
making her laugh and at one point she
looks at me and she goes would you like
to go up to my hotel room and I was like
[ __ ]
yeah and she gave me a hand job and she
gave me the most incredible hand job I
have ever had in my life you guys she
did it UPR right she put on her bowling
brace she put her hand on the air
conditioning vent for a second she was
like she threw a rosin bag back and
forth a few times and I was amazed at
her grip but I was more amazed at her
form cuz she came in just
like
three times I got a turkey it was
incredible I got to get out of
here we're all going to go to the bar
after this right all of us we'll all go
together just [ __ ] storm into some
douchy bar down the
street it's weird man my only goal right
now in life is just to be successful
enough to not have to move mooved back
in with my parents that's it that's my
have you ever you ever done that you
ever moved out and then moved back home
oh yeah maybe you want to Wi a college
or maybe you were squatting in a meth
Shack to avoid Jesus Camp I don't
know it sucks though right when you move
back home because you still have those
live on your own Tendencies you know and
I would go out to the bar and do the
same [ __ ] I would always do IID just get
shitfaced drunk and then I'd forget that
I live with my mom and dad and then I'd
come home and do the same thing I would
always I get home all wasted and I kick
open the door like let Zeppelin just
like and my mom would wake up all
disheveled like what's going on there's
a bird in the house and I'm like you
need cool
in 10 minutes later I'm throwing up into
my hamper like oh
oh she's like what's wrong with you
Michael you have a problem and I'm like
just Ramble
On ramble along hey I'm Mike Stanley
thank you guys so much thanks for coming
out all right
[Applause]
[Music]
thanks
yeah
[Music]
oh