[Music]
drink with the
end get drunk have
fun how's everybody doing tonight oh
it's so great to see a crowd that's so
DED up we've got a great show for you
here tonight we have our very special
guest Mark mothers ball and musical
guest is dvo and now the one the only
Puppet Master in town Mr
Ian man this is spectacular let me tell
you this is great this is going to be a
good show but first I want to rousse a
round of applause for our friend
[Applause]
Neil and nothing would be anything in
this big world without drinks put your
hands together for the partender of the
Stars Mr Ali
stench hey how's everyone doing tonight
you ready for another
shot all right well a lot of you people
think that you know me some of you
really know me and those of you that
really know me know that I am the king
of the sixth grade
jokes you know deeper that's one of them
uh all those kind of like stupid booby
jokes and like that but there's even one
joke that's too stupid and too base for
me to repeat so you're going to have to
Google the setup but it's about P it's
about pinoc
and uh the punchline to that joke is the
name of tonight's shot and it's called
tell a lie tell the truth and to make
tell a lie tell the truth you take three
fingers of Philips
vodka you take two fingers of your
favorite flavor of vermouth
ver and you take a shot of root beer
schnaps add a splash of cream cream
shake it all up add in some ice ice
strain it out stra and enjoy in
moderation tell a lie tell the truth
shots on the
house that saber you know I think you
need to make a saving throw versus suck
really I hear your mother [ __ ] off
Vader oh yeah you want a piece of the
calm down run you through dude seriously
I'm going to call the MPS
all right anyway uh here's a short film
that was sent to us by a team Courtney
Branch Keith Allen and Seth Gordon Take
a
Look y
[Music]
drip drip drip went the rain rain rain
and Billy and Sally thought they would
go insane with nothing to do and nowhere
to go they had to think of some fun that
didn't
blow so they went to the kitchen and
looked under the sink When Sally said
Billy I'd like to order a
drink with Billy as bartender and
Sally's hooker they mixed cookie
cocktails and began to get
snooker with a shot of glass cleaner and
drain unclogged Chaser they toasted
their old friend Freddy Crystal free
baser the fun was beginning the room
started to swirl but it all had end when
Sally started to
hurl with the kitchen a mess they had
move on and look for some more fun that
was the bomb they snuck into dad's room
just to explore Sally checked closets
while Billy checked drawers and under a
magazine of fat tited [ __ ] they found
a revolver engraved with up
yours they shot at the
dog they shot at the kitty they shot
holes in the magazine of [ __ ] with big
titties they took target practice on
fluff fluff the bear Sally started to
fire like she hadn't a care she shot at
the window she splintered a chair but it
paid off when Geral exploded mid
a Sally turned kind of blue and she
started to pout when she aimed at Bill's
head and no ammo came out a gun with no
bullets well that is no fun what to do
now look here comes the
sun they scurried outside to greet the
new day and see what fun games they
could think of to play they skipped down
the alley on their sweet merry way when
Billy said Sally hip hip hooray we could
play homeless for just pennies a day
they dove into dumpsters looking for
treats they found a dead baby in rotting
lunch meats Sally said Billy my new
Dolly's bitching Billy said Sally this
meat Pi like
chcken Then They begged for some chains
from some passer by folks and got just
enough to buy themselves smokes and in
an old Warehouse in the bad part of town
they lit up their sigs and matches threw
down Billy said Sally let's see what can
burn and striking their fire they each
took a turn Billy lit door frames and
Sally torched Rags whoops it's really
wio passed out with his bag his liquor
soaked jacket just look how it burns
watch how he's spinning the finess of
his turns that clapped right along with
his fiery jig laughing and singing the
Flames growing big his skin turned extra
crispy as the fire took toll he should
have remembered a stop drop and
roll they poked him with the stick to
look for his soul but the stick had
found none and it made a big hole as
their dance Partners smouldered Sirens
started to whail chees it the cops and
the Tikes ran like hell their adrenaline
pumping they were catching a buzz and
searched for a spot they could hide from
the fuzz they scaled the link fence was
embed wire topping their feet hit the
ground and they ran without stopping and
into the junkyard they searched high and
low to find a swell spot where the pigs
wouldn't go we could hide in that Barrel
or that car over there that rusted out
loln that smells like burnt
hair then off in the distance it loomed
from afar a shiny Frost freeze with its
front door a
jar and Sally said Billy I think this is
it they had to scrunch close it was a
tight fit little arms were entangled
tiny feet were
inwin almost as Twisted as his sweet
little
mindes and Billy said Sally it's the
best place to hide and they closed the
door
tight to see if the light went out
[Music]
inside when you are sleeping
hey everybody Billy and Sally's big
refrigerator Adventure Round of
Applause all right everybody to
introduce our guest tonight let me take
you back to those thrilling days of the
1980s new way had been co-opted cocaine
was still cool and Saddam Hussein was
our
Ally yeah but dvo dvo was a standout
though they made stuff unlike anything
we'd heard in the mainstream and damn it
they did it better than anyone but the
front man of this group didn't stop
there though he kept making music as a
solo career and now he's touring all
over showing his visual art and
galleries across the United States of
America here he is in living flesh the
one and only Mark mothers
B um here hold on uh let me just get
this excuse me for a
second hey you uh you smell that it's
it's something stinks and oh wait it's
the
episode hello oh oh hey Mark how you
doing um well I know we were hoping to
have you on live and stuff but I know
you're busy scoring Wes Anderson's
latest moment I just had this weird
thing I was writing something and I was
right in the middle of it you never know
an inspiration is going to going to
strike and yeah speaking of uh scoring I
mean do directors just kind of set you
loose now I mean do you actually they
give you ideas are they giving you moods
or they because those guys you know you
figure a director might have been on the
film God maybe five years by the time I
get I get a copy of it they've already
pretty much they're pretty far into the
editing so it's like all the all the
really painful stuff is over um and how
has uh how has scoring changed your
outlook on instrumentation it's changed
a lot in the last uh 10 or 15 I think
it's more interesting that said my
favorite movies are black
I tend to watch a lot of AMC Turner
Classic Movies oh yeah yeah yeah one of
the directors worked with is a big
dealer out here you know Chuck Statler
how did how' you meet him how'd that
come to be we were just starting you
know we we we were in this Amic
protozoic stage of dvo where we were you
I think we were even called the de
Evolution B we just decided we weren't
the de evolutionary Army anymore we were
dvo we cut all the letters off at the
end contracted it down to Doo and with
Chuck came and said he wanted to make a
film it really just clicked we knew
that's what we wanted to do films and
there was no such thing as MTV it wasn't
even talked about since he kind of
predicted the uh the birth of MTV did
you have any uh you know idea of how
horrible was going to become no it was
shocking how fast it became bad uh but
you guys did provide basically a
blueprint for MTV back in those early
days did you guys shoot anything that
you never used is there are there any
videos in the vaults uh one of the guys
that worked with us in the early these
two guys um Marty Raymond and Ed barter
and he shot maybe 30 hours maybe 30
different shows maybe more has odd
things on film like
uh dead boys jumping on to while we're
playing and getting in a fist fight with
us I think he has David Bowie coming on
stage in maxas Kansas City and
introducing the band and going this is
the band of the
future I'm going to produce dvo in Japan
in this winter we're like looking at
each other like well we're sleeping in a
van tonight so you know that sounds
great to us you know we'd make like 75
bucks that would just pay
for one room at the Chelsea and gas
money there and back yeah and we'd all
just like you know crash on the floor in
this one hideous you know like a crack
hotel room but at the same time our
guest list would have like all of the
Rolling Stones you know uh brand Jones
uh The Beetles which I remember one
night uh early when we played John
Lennon I I had lifted a piece of um I
Want to Hold Your Hand um for the
beginning of uncontrollable urge the
opening cords on uncontrollable urge are
the same as on oh wow I never yeah I
never picked that
up and he he was at least one person in
the audience that noticed that because
he probably wrote that and he but but I
was sitting in the the van we were going
to be sleeping in that night and he
stuck his head in the window in a
drunken kind of sloppy voice say half of
uncontrollable urge to me from about
four inches away from my face and uh it
just it was a totally different thing
well yeah when you have a drunken John
lennin you know yelling your song back
at you yeah that that doesn't happen in
akaran yeah and then then Brian you know
and Brian youo came with Robert FR to
the show and we went to Robert fr's
house and they were both fighting over
who would produce dvo it was it was a
different and we were like wait a minute
you guys should have been there last
week when we got our asses kicked at the
Eagle Street Saloon in in in Cleveland
but pretty soon you know you can tell
those people the Eagle Street to go
themselves CU Divo just got really
really damn big who selling a lot of
albums and you know that breeds a lot of
copycats uh what do you think about all
those dvo clones that came out I like
the good ones and I don't like the bad
ones you know in a way we didn't really
own what we did we were just you know
come on bands music bands even
dvo uh are incredibly eclectic I mean it
it's it said it's most boring when when
somebody creates some new genre like
heavy metal or rap and yeah you know
like five years later you know the the
in the increments of innovation are
become smaller and smaller I remember
you know like at one point the the the
things that differentiated the bands
were so
minimal unimportant yeah and I don't
know it's it's it's a whole different
you have to think about the world of
music
and art and public art all differently
now because of the internet yeah because
it just I think uh nowadays it's just
harder work to find good stuff that's
the thing there's there's probably more
good stuff than there ever was but more
great music it's just really hard to
find because there's more crap in this
big cess pool called the internet
looking for it and you know it's like
you can have Nostalgia for the old days
but they're gone yeah well let's end
that NP note that's kind of
huh well there you go uh let's see if
there's anybody left left first
avue hey everybody Mark mother's ball
isn't that pretty damn cool I think so
too well as you know every episode of
drinking with the in is comes equipped
with its own ha coup everybody round of
applause for Hau
[Music]
Jim hey thanks everybody Hau Jim here I
do have some syllables for you tonight
why don't we just get
started I met a hot chick she's French
quiet alluring sweet
marionette here's another one for you
he's a war
hero but GI Joe's got
Secrets Don't Ask and don't tell very
nice everybody hiu Jim CU see this is
weird how well the show is going I i'
I've read in the papers I've read in the
dailies that you have beef with a royal
family is that true yeah that's a fact
you know I I pretty much feel he's not
even worth the syllables that I that I
utter be honest okay Jim come on I mean
I know you you had to write something
about it let's hear it all right okay
here I got one for you he's the Emperor
Palpatine lacks star power checked under
the
hood no
[Music]
[Applause]
um well that's kind of shows you what
happens when o the power of Hau is a
dangerous thing it makes him dangerous
enemies uh BR FL for hu gym
everybody uh screw it let's uh look at
this uh short film
peanut butter and jelly can't be friends
because no peanut butter can be friends
with the Jelly he finds delicious he
always wants to make a sandwich so
you're saying that a peanut butter can
be friends with a jelly that he doesn't
find delicious no you pretty much want
to spread them
[Music]
too a mason jar rips off your lid and
that's the sex fantasy you've been
having since you were on the vine
exactly the same well sometimes I vary
it a little which part what's on my leg
so you tell her about other jellies yeah
like a couple of lunches ago I tapped
this Bo and Berry Sprout and it was so
incredible I took her to a place that
wasn't even human she actually meowed
what meowed no the human thing you said
you took her to a place that wasn't
human right she totally your peanut
butter right I'm difficult I'm too
structured and I'm completely closed off
but in a good way and I'm going to
expire
when
someday in 14 months
[Music]
ah
take your light off man fighting never
solved anything
[Music]
all right everybody a show like this
can't happen without some friends we'll
be back in a couple
seconds come on let's get in the
character why you so interested in big
man's wife well he's going in a town of
sor and he asked me if I take care of
her while he's gone take care of no man
just show her a good time make sure she
don't get
[Music]
long you see this is a moral test of
oneself I do believe Mar my husband your
boss told you to take me out and do
whatever I
wanted you can maintain loyalty night of
the fight you may feel a slight sting
Pride only hurts it never helps
in the fifth your ass goes down I have
to say play with matches you get
burn we should have shotguns with this
kind of deal we're in a lot of danger
aren't we I'm prepared to scout Earth
[Music]
for oh I'm sorry did I break your
concentration you got a corpse in a car
mine is a head in the garage take me to
it
[Music]
[Applause]
don't you hate that hate what
uncomfortable
silences kmit the frog fzy bear Miss
Piggy bunson honey gono Camila Janice Dr
T Eric stes animal Sam the eagle and be
looking at something fr my friend cler
die you
mother a new film directed poly by Jim
Hansen oh mu she really thinking about
quit most definitely what she going to
do that basically I'm just going to walk
the earth what you mean walk the earth
you know like Kane and kung fu
[Music]
you'll save money and time you'll get
the best of merchandise and service when
you patronize these good neighbors no
beer in the midwest has a grander
brewing tradition than Grain Belt for
over 100 years Grain Belt has been the
beer that fathers have passed on to sons
and friends have passed amongst each
other at local bars and watering holes
it is a beer with tradition that spans
Generations which is why it has become
legendary both here and across the
country next time you go out ask for a
premium shamay is France's most exciting
new brand of wine uniting the colors
flavors and Aromas of France's most
celebrated wine making regions shamur is
delightfully and deliciously original
our wide pallet of wines contains a
treat for every taste bud offer yourself
a glass of shamur and see what the
flutter is all about to find out more
say bonjour to
share.com if there's one thing we like
better than booze it's cheap foods and
that's why we chose Merwin Liquors as
the official drinking withian liquor
store great deals a huge elction they
even have a contest where customers can
win free drinks for a year Merwin Liquor
is hard to beat yeah it's a bit ghetto
but up your street cred and Save A Buck
or two stop in at Merwin lickers at
Lindale and West Broadway in North
Minneapolis just two blocks west of 94
or visit Merwin lick.com
[Applause]
drinking with the end is proud to be
sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV Vodka
no matter if it's UV blue raspberry UV
red cherry UV green apple UV Ivory
vanilla or UV orange vodka UV flavored
vodka offer a premium product without
the high price tag please visit UV
vodka.com for additional information and
recipes a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest news source and the AV club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and entertainment scene
available at news stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at theonion.com
and avclub.com pizza luche proudly
supports drinking with and free delivery
until 2:30 a.m. weekdays and 3:30 a.m.
weekends download our menu at
www.pal.com drinking with Ian is nothing
without our sponsors please support them
hey hey how's it going guys hey remember
us we're Crystal Warriors yeah christar
you don't remember us totally Crystal
Warriors you guys don't remember us yeah
you want to buy us some drinks yeah we
could use a few drinks we're Crystal
Warriors oh man we were huge we protect
the crystals 8s oh man screw it you want
to make out yeah all right let's go all
right I've been asking this band to play
on our show since day one tonight we
finally had an open slot and you know
dvo
[Applause]
[Music]
way the
gates the way that
TST
and all we know we
[Music]
human a man is real that is
we
[Music]
human the beginning was the end for
everything now
on
[Music]
itat made
nothing is all we know to play the human
way a man is real not
[Music]
[Applause]
ladies and gentlemen boys and girls
dvo I know that's pretty amazing isn't
it well that's with the end this week
we'll see you next time