sometimes your kids do racist [ __ ] it's
not your
fault you ever see like a little racist
and you're like oh my God they learned
it from somewhere and you look like a
monster and like no sometimes they
accidentally do something stupid and you
look like a racist
[ __ ] my little one he had bad ear
infections last summer little you know
ear infection he was in a lot of pain
felt really bad we had to go to the
pediatrician you know make him feel
better about it he brought his little
toys brought his little toys and at the
time he was really into the little green
army men you guys know the green AR you
know the oldfashioned Toy Story right
green army man so he's getting checked
out by the pedi old pediatrician it's
like oh so are these your eima guys are
these does he know eima does he know you
like no he's two all right
um I'm trying to get him to say his
name letters
numbers we'll we'll get to eima I
promise we
[Music]
the thing is at the time he couldn't
really say he could say elevator he was
excited about being in an elevator cuz
it's like a ride so we're on the fourth
floor doctor's office we're going down
second floor doors open nice guy gets on
with us he looks down he's like oh he's
cute and then I watch in horror as my
2-year-old shoves his hand up at a nice
elderly Japanese man iima
and that is some racist stuff that is
some racist like it'd be less racist if
he held up a Godzilla because at least
that remake just came out you know what
I mean but eima is a hell of a reference
for a 2-year-old to pull out of nowhere
and I can't tell him the whole so he's
got an old pediatrician over there like
I just look like a racist [ __ ] it
looks like I've been coaching him it
looks like we're at home like all right
that's enough s street today we're
watching History
Channel now remember you see one of them
you say
something it's so funny