is that it yep that'll be
1565 there you
are that's just a
10 oh my
God it's okay nobody's perfect no you
don't understand I used to be what do
you mean you used to be perfect I was
perfect up until I gave you this wrong
bill bull no it's true all started when
my mom was in labor with me for 9
minutes I helped her out on that one
when I turned one years old I baked a
little cake to put my face in so that
everybody could have non-face cake when
I turned five I fell and skinn my
knee
perfect in high school I made the
football team with
determination after the games in the
shower room the players would all point
and laugh at themselves if you're
perfect why are you
bald that just
happened what you came in here like that
I came in here perfect I've never had to
change my bong water I'm drug- free I
know nine different ways to kill a man
with my bare hands and 10 ways to save
him I've only ever had sex with two
women at once unless there were more
okay that's too much it's true they're
all still climaxing and we're all still
friends shouldn't I have heard of you if
you're perfect I've always been fairly
humble no desire desire for
fame no one who's perfect would refer to
themselves as humble never told a lie
I've never had to I only eat organic
foods and I've never had to wipe I've
only ever heard Music Live or on vinyl
records I have no Tan Lines my blood can
theoretically cure
AIDS you can't cure AIDS you can't cure
AIDS you're not perfect neither am I
anymore ow just got a hangnail see
everybody gets hang nails they do now
you're starting to piss me off I'm sorry
I've never upset anybody before hold on
it's my
phone
hello
yeah
okay I
see all
right who is that it's my girlfriends
they're pregnant and itchy oh my god did
you tell those women you were perfect I
didn't have to they knew it the moment
we met it was perfect no it was
fate come to think of it maybe I haven't
always been perfect did always take me
two times to remember someone's name
birthday blood type eye color I uh could
get two packs of
M1 what's the matter man look a little
down I used to be perfect now I'm bald
that's not a big deal I'm I'm bald
look what the hell I got
hair my my phone's
ringing
hello oh hey
what really yeah no no no no I'll be
right there that yeah
bye that was my girlfriend she's not
pregnant and she's finally ready to have
that
threeome I'm sorry what what do I owe
you that's $855
okay see
here perfect change what do you
know
thanks take it easy
man what an [ __ ] yep