here's what my jackass friend did he had
one of these uh
children here's what he does he takes
his kid in for an Autism test I guess
the kid test negative so he decided to
post it on Facebook I guess he's happy
and relieved like hooray my kid tested
negative for autism I'm like why are you
happy now you just deal with
oldfashioned dumb right now now you
don't even have an official word to
apply his behavior people still come to
your house like hey what the [ __ ]
wrong with your kid
staring at its feet for 17
hours cuz now you can't say autistic now
you just got to look at people and go
evidently my sperm is not as much a
reproductive seed as it is a booya base
that produces dead-eyed swamp
creatures this child has been staring
through a clock for about 12 years
so I know parents hate hearing that and
I heard them ask earlier whose parents
so that I I guess that's the resistance
on this [ __ ] parents hate that you
realize are you aware of this there're
actually people who would rather have a
better life for their children than what
they had for themselves [ __ ] that why
would you ever do that how about living
a life so incredible your kid couldn't
possibly W up it you know follow that
you little dirt bag
yeah get used to answering questions
about daddy did some great
work by the way I'm an only child I
don't know if you're picking up on this
thank you youu there's the release I'm
38-year-old man saying that with no
shame you know I realize an only child
you know I'm the last boy in the Hooper
family can spread this
seed whatever you're supposed to feel
naturally compelled to do that I have no
desire to do I've decided I'm ending my
family and I tell them I tell them I'm
like you guys have had hundreds of years
to do something decent with this name
you haven't done anything better than
mediocre I am pulling the [ __ ] plug
on this program all right let's wrap it
up
huh domestic violence is not a legacy
right grandpa It's The End Of The
Bloodline End Of The Bloodline no more
hoopers for the planet Earth that's
awfully nice of me to do something like
that what does that make me a martyr
some [ __ ] I don't even know if I'm using
that word correctly I don't care I'm an
only child get myself fancy titles all
day a lot of times I call myself the
Archangel Paul Hooper yeah if you want
my signature that's what I'm giving you
the Archangel Paul Hooper people like
that's not a legal signature I'm like
well I'm not changing it you could
process that the Archangel Paul Hooper
would like his driver's license
renewed who are you to question the
chosen one that's the way I live my life
thank you and I am left-handed that
little shitty act out that's accurate
I'm left-handed like a [ __ ] artist
should be thank you like Michelangelo Da
Vinci rbrand you three left-handed
people good creative types seven of us
in
here seven everybody else right-handed
so I assume I don't know I guess you
just dabble with
blocks thank you for building the walls
we get to paint you [ __ ]
barbarians that's good glad you went to
masonry
class but push more people away
push I always say yo she loves it you
love the anger God damn it you cheer me
up being right here thank you anyway it
does here I can put myself in a more
Elite group you know I was born June
25th do anyone like understand how
significant that date is it's an
important dat June 25th six months a day
after Jesus Christ's birthday huh that
means something I don't know what it
means I assume he does the first half of
the year and I do the last half I don't
know what it means I am determined to
prove I'm special that's what all this
means that's what a child psychologist
told my mom Paul thinks he's special and
he really really needs to see his father
but I do feel like I could be the Holy
Ghost
someday I know