I really I feel good about this one
because you feel loose you know I don't
know how to greet people so sometimes
crowds lock up on me you start talking
about big cats in the woods and then it
veers off
sometimes but I refuse to come up here
and do this stereotypical opening I just
can't I can't take corny greetings in
life it bugs the [ __ ] out of me every
day life I don't know I got on an
airport shuttle bus a few weeks ago I
get on with a cup of coffee I get on bus
driver looks at me he's got to do this
he's like you didn't bring me a cup of
[Music]
coffee I'm like you didn't bring a
[ __ ] limo all right yeah yeah how
about we sit quietly until we learn to
greet one another
then I I was on a plane of course I
was guy across the aisle is a bigger guy
so he's having trouble getting in his
seat between the armrests of course he's
got to make his humorous quip about the
situation directed at me he looks at me
he's like oh you know what I should have
brought a vet Crisco to put on my hips
to Help Me ease into the seat
H and I'm like you can't bring more than
3 o on a plane so yeah that's right your
shitty joke won't make it past security
all right yeah thank you
yeah how about sitting your fat ass down
and saving that crowd work for your next
flight not into it you obese [ __ ]
extrovert I'm trying to sleep get
between point A to point B I don't need
your goddamn internet jokes
interrupting I don't connect to people
like that it's disingenuous they're
corny as [ __ ] and it makes my blood boy
I see people who I connect with it's not
that I hate everyone I saw a guy in a
diner in Oklahoma I never even went up
and talked to guy he just had his table
of friends around this all I heard him
saying he goes he goes I hate pinto
beans I hate green beans I hate
blackeyed peas I'm like I like this son
of a [ __ ] now we're talking right and
[ __ ] a lima bean [ __ ] lima beans you
know what I mean those are people I like
people who complain loudly for
decades until the stroke takes their
beautiful soul from us those are genuine
people not I should have put a v Crisco
on my hips ha [ __ ] you you're a piece of
[ __ ] see I'm smiling now because I like
this crowd but I'm telling you lock up a
lot of times if you're mean to me