[Music]
all right now I have a short film for
you here drink with even we've been
throwing together an anthology for you
it's called the anthology of lesser
known mythical creatures let's watch the
big screen if you've ever been a parent
then you'll know this character he's The
Lovable stor delivering swaddling
infants to often joyful couples St
working is one of the great professions
out there most people are delighted when
I show up uh I always bring cigars with
me cuz sometimes the dad wants a little
extra
celebration sometimes it can be a little
uncomfortable and there and I'm just
sort of like hey doing my job take this
thing I'll be on my
way that's that's part of the job what
can you tell us about your younger
brother Bill uh
not really at Liberty to talk about my
brother Phil uh so this is the st's
younger brother Phillip hey I get that a
lot actually but uh you know it's cool I
I'm okay with it uh not everybody wants
to talk about the abortion
stor you know I didn't start off
thinking this was going to be my career
it's not like I chose this you know I
went to start college I dropped out was
a little tough followed fish around for
a while that was pretty cool this is the
family business
so yeah I kind of fell into it
again I really I'm not very popular my
brother he gets all the joy and the
happy and
whatnot I get a lot of
crying uh it's hard cuz I I want to do
something about it but I'm just kind of
there to do it job I do get relief
though sometimes from certain people
it's an emotionally demanding job but
it's also pretty physically demanding
you know mostly I get
beaten I've been shot fatally seven
times uh I've been stabbed I get set on
fire did you just say you were shot
fatally it shouldn't you be dead oh well
you know I'm mythical you know I can't
be killed well that doesn't mean it
doesn't hurt it hurts a
lot I try as much as possible to be
there for the woman people say I'm funny
so I like to you know try to make them
laugh I joke around a lot doesn't always
really
work but you do meet some pretty cool
chicks though you know chicks that let
you bear back I suppose I probably
should go back to school or something
you know like get the degree in
Gynecology but I guess you know this
works out for now it's not like I have
to think a lot I can even do it when I'm
drunk you can edit that part out right
no no oh all
right I realize it's a crappy job but uh
you know I try to keep things positive
you know I'm fulfilling a certain
purpose
here it's it's like I always say God
doesn't flush a toilet without turning
on a faucet
[Applause]