I just like to say that there is a
jaguar in this [ __ ] Resort Village
and No One Believes Me and I don't know
if it's because you people are drinking
too much but I have a lucid mind and
Clear Eyes there is a jaguar panther in
this [ __ ] jungle she's nodding yes
you've seen this cat no one's concerned
no one is concerned about this wild cat
as we ride around on golf carts that's
open air and then all the restaurants
are open air so you can just turn your
back to the [ __ ] jungle and eat eggs
and hope that your head's not taken off
at 2:00 p.m. well I'm sorry I'm not
comfortable doing that so someone catch
this cat or put a net Jamie put a net
over this so I can eat a [ __ ] burrito
in
peace goddamn
nervous and then the um the the raccoon
with the long nose the [ __ ]
arvar and our house is open to a lagoon
it's none of it's making me good there's
a gas leak on the island in the
peninsula thing the Riviera Maya I'm not
doing that for comedic effect someone
catch that [ __ ] Jaguar it's
serious also on top of this like
everyone's been drinking like all my
friends there's tons of us in the house
so they're drinking I see a Jaguar that
makes me skittish I've been smoking two
packs of cigarettes every day so if I'm
horse tonight you got to deal with that
and I was really hoping the sun would
help the bags under my eyes but no luck
yet can you see my bags in this Tiki
Bar four days into this trip the Tan's
not even helping by the way I prefer not
to hear the home
remedies after this show when I get off
stage where women will do this women are
like men are not even aware it exist
well women to come up after this thing
go here's what you do you put cucumber
slices on your eyes you wake up tomorrow
it's all better it's [ __ ] yes tried
it 20 years ago it doesn't work and the
one you get giggly about is preparation
AG that's what you
do you put Preparation H in your eyes
and and I guess they're giggling cuz
that's hemorrhoid medication that you
apply to your eyes and that's silly and
a normal person 's World somehow I'm
like it why are you giggling it's just
chemicals that reduce swelling it's not
prepackaged with [ __ ] in it do you
understand unless you tell me like
listen you have to apply this to
someone's hemorrhoid then smear their
rectum on your ocular cavity I'm like
God damn it your home remedies are a tad
bit extreme if there is a plastic
surgeon that works pro bono I will take
that otherwise I'll just have a mean sad
tired head