[Applause]
[Music]
little here you ready yeah
almost
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah I'm
ready let's do
it
[Music]
W Mr Porter what's up buddy any thoughts
brother we're rolling um I'd like to
thank
Jesus and small puppies and kids who
have cancer because there would give me
the and in
beer ladies and Gentlemen please welcome
[Applause]
Chris what's up Kansas City how you
doing
sit down have a
seat uh it's good to be back I just got
back from Southern Florida hell yeah
holy [ __ ] the old
people [ __ ] everywhere old people in
Southern Florida are like Mexicans are
everywhere else you know what I'm
saying there's a lot of them
but you know how Mexicans are cool and
funny and sometimes they can get you
weed
yeah old people are the exact
opposite they are mean and rude they
don't give a [ __ ] about you or your
crosswalk and I'm thinking hey old
people if you're that close to death
maybe you should be on your best
behavior you know what I'm saying like a
little kid right before Christmas your
big days are
coming maybe you should finish strong
you
know maybe let me out of the elevator
before you clip me in the ankles with
your [ __ ]
[Applause]
scooter spent most of the day watching
my new favorite show on MTV it's called
engaged and underaged have you seen
it's hysterical it's kids under the age
of 21 and they're getting
married they should rename it to hey
look we're [ __ ] up our
lives no one seems to give a
[ __ ] in fact mom and dad are financing
it why do you want to get married under
the age of 21 what the [ __ ] is wrong
with
you the government doesn't even trust
you with beer
yet maybe that's a sign you're not ready
for a life
decision you don't know [ __ ] about
yourself at the age of 20 cuz you know
you're growing up you hit plateaus in
life where you change you know you hit
bigger ones when you get older like when
you're 50 the day shows up where you're
a dude you're like hey [ __ ] shorts and
loafers do that that's a good
look or if you're an 80e old woman
apparently the day shows up where you're
like yeah [ __ ] you I've got a
beard
it's white and it's
wispy call me Santa I don't give a [ __ ]
I
Ean I'm just happy you're talking to
me you had a lot of those plateaus
between the ages of 20 and
35 I recently hit one I don't talk to
stupid people
anymore I don't I know even if I wanted
to [ __ ]
you remember those days there was a day
when I was 25 ladies you could have said
the dumbest [ __ ] in the world and I
would have agreed with you i' been like
[ __ ] yeah Cold Play is
awesome they're the
best now I can't do it something
happened 26 years old my ears and my
dick got
connected
now if you say some stupid [ __ ] it quits
working it does if you ask me who lead
Zeppelin is I can't pee for like an
hour you drink Red Bull with your liquor
I don't even approach you anymore I
don't I don't [ __ ] stop it for all of
you guys girls stop it stop mixing the
Red Bull with the liquor there's a
reason that your body body shuts down
when you've had too much to drink it's
cuz you need to shut the [ __ ] up
[Applause]
okay your body has taken a vote decided
your face needs to quit
it that's why when you pass out your
arms are like this cuz you [ __ ]
tackled yourself you're like shut up
shut up shut
up it's 3: in the morning shut up okay I
don't want to talk anymore it's 3
there's two things to do at 3: in the
morning
sleep [ __ ] and that's it right guess
what second one's not going to be very
good you know why cuz it's 300 in the
morning that's
why you want to talk to me one I'd have
rocked your
[Applause]
world it's three now I'm tired and
grumpy I'm dead [ __ ]
today do you live in an apartment
complex you know the people that drink
Red Bull cuz they don't park their cars
they just slam them into
[ __ ]
lock
[Music]
it you know why these kids are getting
married cuz these girls won't [ __ ] them
till they get
married which is fine ladies if you want
to hold back to poon God bless
you but let me tell you something shit's
going to happen okay if you put an
obstacle in front of a 20-year-old
virgin and tell him that [ __ ] is on the
other side shit's going to get done okay
marriage what's that a trip to the mall
that's easy he was going there
anyway you know why don't you think
about the rest of us Ladies If you wield
that kind of power why don't you think
about Society for a change how about hey
I'm not [ __ ] anybody till they cure
cancer
it'll be two
weeks some 20-year-old be like I got it
I got it it's right here it's right
[Applause]
here there's carrots and mustard who
knew no one have never mixed them cuz
they're gross
but I'll work on a next week but right
now I need a blow job
okay L cure your
brother so I flew back from Florida I
stopped in Atlanta I didn't want to it's
Delta's
fault I was at an airport I was at a
McDonald's and the gentleman in front of
me got his order and it was in Incorrect
and he was pissed he was [ __ ] pissed
like someone had dinged his
Prius he was
angry and I just looked at him like
what's your level of expectation at
McDonald's like how angry can you get
cuz yeah yeah he [ __ ] up your order he
did that yeah he [ __ ] up his life
three years ago okay he's got enough
problems he worked at the airport
McDonald's he can't even lie and say
it's close to his house cuz it's not
it's at the
airport just saying give the guy a break
you know he's having a bad enough day he
was going to shoot himself in the face
but they took his gun away at the
checkpoint I just don't know why people
get angry over stupid [ __ ] people get
mad and traffic I understand if it's
like a Saturday and you're on the Plaza
and some [ __ ] won't turn left
I get that but Tuesday at 8:30 in the
morning you can't get pissed people act
like it's a first time the [ __ ] ever
happened you know it's Tuesday at 8:30
in the morning what are all these cars
doing
here so they honked their horns has that
ever worked have you ever been in
gridlock and like honk honk and everyone
started doing 70
again like there are 15 Stoners up at
the front go going oh [ __ ] sorry sorry
my
bad my
bad I was [ __ ] with my
iPod but I realized something it's
always the same people that honk their
horns in traffic it's always people in
shitty
cars not trying to be mean but think
about it everyone in this room knows
what a shitty car sounds like you'll be
sitting at home meet me [ __ ] fat Diva
where is
it where is
it it's got a spoiler it's a
[Laughter]
96 what kind of sound does a Rolls-Royce
horn
make I don't know
either no one knows not even people on a
Rolls-Royce they're not even driving the
thing they're sitting in back smoking
weed listening to Zeppelin
W that's what I would do I had a
rose the people who honk their horns in
traffic are the people whove run out of
options and it hits them they're just
like I got a shitty car shitty job
shitty
life meet me
[ __ ] meet
me look at me look at me Meep look at me
I am covered in ax body
spray I am listening to
Nickelback [ __ ] has taken a turn for the
[Applause]
worst nickel
back whoever thought there a band come
out that made Creed look
awesome
see sir there was this band called Creed
and they came out and they were like
really whiny Rock and um everyone's like
get them out of here then they left and
Nickelback showed up and everyone was
like call
Creed someone needs to take me higher
than
[Laughter]
nickel Axe Body Spray I've said it
before
[ __ ] stop
it stop it all of you cuz girls you're
part to blame cuz you're [ __ ] these
dudes you are you are cuz if you weren't
the [ __ ] wouldn't sell would it but it's
selling like hot cakes and ladies you
deserve better you deserve better than
some douchebag that spent four bucks at
Walgreens Axe body sprays prove positive
that we as Americans will buy whatever
the [ __ ] comes on television okay
they've got us now they know it you know
what's coming out next poop in a box
that's what's next you're going to be
watching TV there's going to be a
closeup of poop in a box then they're
going to pull back and there's going to
be a hot girl dancing next to poop in a
box and every single pop collar
douchebag in the country is going to go
holy
[ __ ] maybe if I have poop in a box a
pretty girl dance next to
me but they're going to run out they're
going to jump in their sigh
on and halfway to Walgreens common sense
is going to kick in they're going to go
wait a minute I have a
[Applause]
box ax body spray is a regret
as a society okay every time someone
uses it we all take a step backwards cuz
I want you to think about it up until
this moment in human history even the
shittiest colog in the world did not
come in an aerosol can they didn't they
didn't they
didn't Old Spice Aqua Velva hi
karate they all still had enough balls
to have a
spritzer and now we've got the Aquanet
of
colong and everyone knows somebody that
uses it you do right before you walked
in here tonight they're like hold
[Music]
on I'm
ready but no one had left the car yet so
now all your friends smell like date
rape I asked my friend why he did it I
go why do you do that why do you cover
yourself in that [ __ ] he said I don't
want to smell like pot and
beer why
not you know we've got pot and beer
let's
advertise cuz I'm going to tell you
something the girl does not like pot and
beer she's not going to like us at
all so I'm
single shocker what up the fact Mr
picky sucks being single and a guy
it's fun for girls it's nothing but free
drinks and
attention yeah for dudes it's having a
penis and nowhere to put
it girls don't know what that's like
they have a vagina yeah walk the earth
long it up someone's going to [ __ ]
you it's just a matter of time if you
lowering your standards a little
bit but if you got a penis there's no
guarantees anymore you got to have
something else to accentuate your penis
like a
car or a
job
$40 something you
know penis needs an ad campaign like
penis it's what's for
dinner have it your
way is it in you
cuz we're going up against a superior
product you got to look at it from a
marketing standpoint the vagina's
perfect it's symmetrical it's like a
little
pocket I'm going to lick it I'm going to
put things in
there like my penis or my tongue or the
title to my
truck only should have care about only
should have
care I'd ask her first you know can't
just go shoving [ __ ] up there they hate
that they hate
that that's rape in a lot of
counties who needs that on your record
you know what I'm saying got to start
telling people when you move and
[Laughter]
[ __ ] I'm just going to say you got to
feel like a douche on that day you know
hey I touched a little girls sorry kind
of like the day you buy a yellow Hummer
you
know yeah I said it [ __ ] are you
serious are you do you need a yellow
Hummer really really how small is your
dick really is it that small is it that
small I understand buy a Hummer I love
rap music I love it why a yellow one
it's not even attractive it's like hey
look I'm driving in the
Sun and I got a small
penis so this is all new to me being
single I dated a girl for three years
and I learned some [ __ ] like if you're
going to do that she should like
you like as a
person this girl would yell at me cuz
she ran out of [ __ ] to do not like it
was my fault we'd be going to bed she'd
be like oh there's nothing on TV let's
[ __ ] with you for a while
oh damn you Nick at
[Laughter]
night I woke up in the middle of an
argument how does that happen ladies
ever I've been asleep 6 hours you listen
to me you [ __ ]
[ __ ] I didn't know what the hell was
going on I thought she was on her cell
phone I started
laughing I was like listen to this poor
son of a
[ __ ] it was
me so I broke up with her a
lot cuz I'm an
idiot I did I am I'm like I'll call her
be like you're [ __ ] crazy don't call
me we're over bye she call me the next
day I'm not crazy oh my
bad
see in
20 so I finally got away from it right
then it took me like a year just to talk
to women I was scared I was scarred it's
more like it women would come up to me
after shows and they'd be like hey how
you doing I be like I don't want to
argue but I moved on and I started
dating again and I was terrible at it
cuz everything had changed the scene had
changed you got to go to a club now
which is [ __ ] cuz clubs are dark and
loud you end up walking out like oh [ __ ]
all right sorry
sorry no we're cool we're cool we're
going to to stop by a liquor store but
I'm
cool can't talk to him it's music's so
loud it's like hey how are you what I
said what's your name what you want to
[ __ ] what what here I want to do this
later this is what I want to do later
that's what you do at a club you just
rub your dick on chicks to one sticks
around this is what I want to do rubby
rubby rub
rub girls go they [ __ ] love it
they're like I had eight diicks rubbed
on me tonight this is my lucky outfit
you
know
apparently if you want to date a girl
now before you even talk to one you got
to call your cell phone company and get
a text messaging
plan holy [ __ ]
ladies what the
[ __ ] it's a phone it's a phone it's a
[ __ ]
phone press talk how about it huh if you
want to talk press the button that says
the [ __ ] that you want to do I'm not
anti- text message me and my buddies
text message each other all the time but
it's a message it's one line that needs
no answer [ __ ] like meet me here or I'm
running late or that girl you're talking
to is [ __ ] nasty [ __ ]
[Applause]
like don't look at me like that cuz
girls do it
too doesn't matter what sex you are
doesn't even matter what your sexual
orientation is if you've ever been
hitting on somebody and [ __ ] was going
well and then they looked at their phone
looked at
you and walked
away somebody has just reached out and
[ __ ] blocked you what
[Applause]
happened you know what [ __ ] blocking is
Sir don't pick on me no I'm just asking
I I'm not picking on you I was just
asking you're not really in My Demo you
know what I'm saying I'm just making
sure I'm crossing
over if you don't know what [ __ ]
blocking is I'll explain it to you
because it's a funny joke you should not
get it just cuz you're unfamiliar with
the
verbiage say me and this guy right here
were friends we're going to go out for a
night on the town try to score some Tail
cuz it's 1942 and people still talk like
that so Jimmy and I hop out of the
DeLorean
and mosy into the Speak
Easy Jimmy sees this girl here he goes
I'm going to go hit on that girl I go
sweet I'm going to go to the bar check
out the rest of the talent awesome I go
to the bar get my beer turn around
realize that Jimmy's hitting on the
hottest chick in the place and I can't
let that happen cuz I'm number one he's
number two that's just how it works I
got to get Jimmy out of the way how do I
do it I go hey Jimmy how's the her piece
you flaring is it
B
that's how dudes do it girls are a lot
better at it you never see these [ __ ]
coming you'll have a friend posted up
right she's totally into it she's like
I'm going to take you home I'm going to
suck on every inch of your body and
bring you to a level of ecstasy you have
never achieved awesome out of nowhere
friends like Hey we're leaving she's
like see you and they're
gone the [ __ ] was that
did you see that some sort of [ __ ]
blocky
ninja she came out of
nowhere girls want to conversate via the
text message you ever gotten a text
message from a girl holy [ __ ] nothing
but questions hey how are you what are
you doing what are you doing later what
are you thinking
beep I'm fine kind of wishing you didn't
have thumbs right
now
then maybe we can
talk cuz girls are so officient with the
phones you ever seen a girl with a 10
button phone she like a goddamn Court
stenographer H stud I go to the
beach every text message I send takes
seven
minutes
F
seven I don't need a
seven meanwhile she's freaking out why
are you texting me back are you seen
somebody else what's going on no I'm
[ __ ] [ __ ] shut
up shut
up he end up calling her give me five
minutes just give me five [ __ ]
minutes okay hey hey I'm on the phone
just tell me what you were going to type
was it JK was it LOL was it semicolon
closed parenthesis what the the [ __ ] was
it I'm not as good at this as you
[Laughter]
are cuz you don't know how unfair it is
ladies you don't know what it's like to
talk to you talk to each other that's
different cuz you're women you got the
pheromones and the estrogen and the
vaginas and
whatever I don't even think you need to
talk to each other I think you're doing
it just to [ __ ] with us to be honest
with you
see look they're all looking at each
other aren't they yeah yeah I'm on to
something you're going to find me gagged
out and a dump to a
tampons yeah the woman Mafia got me it's
what happened
there I'm be hopping this
[ __ ] it's hard it's hard to talk to you
you cuz you're all unique you're all
individual you all have your own little
[ __ ] that makes you [ __ ]
crazy you do you do that's why your
Gate's not laughing yeah cuz if it
wasn't true you'd laugh you'd laugh this
stuff's crazy I don't know what he's
talking about but no he's like hey
[ __ ] it's Saturday let's not [ __ ]
block
okay let's not bring up the crazy she's
doing
good cuz you do and it's always
something weird it's always crazy like
don't say toast I hate that
word like what when I was younger I had
a bad experience with toast and I am
just not comfortable enough with you and
I to tell you the toast story yet but if
you could just do me a favor and and
just say baked bread that'd be
super we got to figure this [ __ ] out
it's not just one thing it's not just a
dozen things it's a million things and
they're always changing we never figure
them all out I know this cuz my dad has
been married to my mom for 30 years and
that man can still talk to that woman
face to face piss her off and have no
idea how the [ __ ] it happened at
all dad's still trying to learn you'll
see him in another room like 20 minutes
later reworking the whole scenario
trying to figure out where he [ __ ]
up
dad what happened I don't know I don't
know I got home from the store [ __ ]
all hell broke
CL did you get everything on the list I
got everything on the list man
apparently there was a list I was
unaware
of and it was in her
face dad was smart dad realized mom was
pissed and got the [ __ ]
out because that's what you're supposed
to do he walked home he was like honey
I'm home she's like hey he's like
[ __ ] see
you cuz my father knows what most older
men know that when a woman's mad for the
first 20 minutes doesn't matter why
doesn't it doesn't you just get away
from it it's like right before a
tsunami you don't ask questions you just
walk out to the the beach you're like oh
[ __ ] all the water's gone [ __ ] run
run cuz you don't want to be the dude
standing on the beach going hey where'd
all the water
go something's wrong we need to figure
this out we need to stick around here
figure out where all the water
went hey is that a
starfish oh
[ __ ]
you know now you want us to text you
kind of [ __ ] aren't
we you know cuz there's no sarcasm font
that's a problem I'm trying to be funny
and T-Mobile makes me look like a
[ __ ] I'm like no I me your sister
was a [ __ ] like Walka Walka Walka
right nothing all
right
are you guys
drinking [ __ ] yeah it's Saturday we're
in a mall [ __ ] it
[Applause]
right let's get shitfaced and go break
into Black House White
Market I don't know what I would get
from
there maybe some
gifts well drink up drive home real fast
it'll be sweet uh see if the lord loves
you that's
funny do y'all go to
church some of you some of you like [ __ ]
you dude trying to have fun here
okay there's no g o d and Fu n you know
what I'm
saying I'm not saying that but
grammatically that's correct you know
what I'm saying atically means
words basically what I'm saying is
there's not a g or an o or a D in the
word
fun I was raised Catholic any Catholics
here surprised that many of them clapped
usually they don't want to put their
beards
down sorry I said this here go right
here cool don't spit it in right
now Catholicism is great especially if
you do drink cuz uh we have noon
masses yeah that's the latest in the
industry some Churches have a 5:00 cuz
they have like a cokehead contingency or
something I don't know but
like cuz Catholics like to drink we love
it that's why Catholic masses are so
boring a lot of people think we lack
Soul that's incorrect we're just [ __ ]
hung
over cuz you go to a lot of churches
start having a blast man they're like
Yay
Jesus Catholics we're like cut that [ __ ]
off just shut up okay I got a
headache let's just sit here and let
this dude talk
okay it's not even the priest priest
done knew [ __ ] for the first 20 minutes
he's as hung over as anybody else
did
[Applause]
if you've never been to a Catholic mass
it's about an hour
long sometimes you can get out in
45 there's this variable in the middle
called the
homy where the priest can just talk
about whatever he feels is relevant and
sometimes he's really succinct and gets
to the point and gets out you're out
there in 45 other days he goes [ __ ]
Almond Brothers on it you know what I'm
saying takes him 20 minutes to bring it
back to whipping
post first half an hour of any Catholic
Mass is like anybody else's Church where
they talk to you they sing to you you
know touching
yourself Jesus doesn't love you when
you're touching yourself right I'm
paraphrasing but that's a gist of and
uh the second half an hour is like a
cooking show with
Jesus cuz they take crackers and turn
them into the body of Christ then they
take a $4 bottle of wine and turn it
into the blood of Christ yeah super cool
the first couple times but two or three
years into it you're kind of like hey
Padre what else can you make you
know is there lasag something cuz I love
a Cheesy
Jesus you be
[Laughter]
delicious I quit going to church and
it's not cuz I got lazy it's cuz one
week I showed up and no one at my church
would drink the wine cuz the flu was
going
around where's the
faith you know if I had the flu I'd be
Bogart in the blood of Christ you I be
like [ __ ] you [ __ ] I got the FL CL
cluck clu CL it's the blood of Christ
according to all your stories that saved
us from sin I think it's going to do
something for a
snipple just saying if you're going to
go to a building every Saturday or
Sunday or Wednesday or whenever the hell
you go you should believe what these
people are telling you otherwise what
are you doing missing kickoff
[Applause]
basically and I don't care what religion
you are I don't care just believe
whatever you want to believe we're all
[Laughter]
wrong that's okay religions aren't there
to be correct they're there to be there
they're there to give you something to
believe in so believe in it that's why
of all the religions the people I
respect the most are the people down in
Texas that dance around with
rattlesnakes on their heads those people
are [ __ ]
crazy they believe you got to got a
[ __ ] rattlesnake on your head dancing
around with it asking it questions Lord
Jesus should I buy a
Honda no no I shouldn't oh
[ __ ]
[ __ ] Z come here [ __ ]
Z go tell everybody Jesus said bye
American that's what he
[Applause]
said don't let my death
be got to kind of hope that the
rattlesnake people aren't
right cuz that means there's
rattlesnakes in heaven if there's snakes
in heaven you know what's in
Hell
llamas right two Ls in hell
two L's and
[Laughter]
LL I smoke
[Music]
pot I do it a
lot that's what I was doing when I wrote
the llama
joke I thought it was brilliant I was
like who does a two L joke [ __ ]
nobody
yeah I'm lwis and Clark and this
[ __ ] they were
[Laughter]
Pioneers pot's My Favorite Drug it's the
only drug I do besides Xanax and
mushrooms I love Xanax man that shit's
like the reset
button it is if you're having a shitty
day take a Xanax next thing you know
it's
tomorrow what the hell happened yet
yesterday I don't
know I don't know it was shitty to a
point and then apparently I went to Taco
Bell
yeah by the way don't get stoned and eat
his annx holy [ __ ] that's an $18 Run for
the
Border you're a little too [ __ ] up for
choices you just kind of pull up to the
drive-thru I'll take the left side no
tomatoes thank
you
we will sort it out at the
house I need to get this vehicle off the
road
[Music]
[Applause]
ASAP take that oh cool I've been dating
again and uh there I got this thing I've
been getting them and then I put a stop
to them I don't if you start doing it I
tell you no and I'm here to put a stop
to them publicly and they're called hand
jobs yeah ladies we don't need
them we don't need them I don't need I
don't want to speak for everybody maybe
you're into it I am not okay I don't
ladies if we hook up later uh and you
were going to do that rub my
back you know give me a back rub cuz uh
I can't reach my back
yeah I can do that a lot better than you
can I might add
ladies holy [ __ ] fellas you ever gotten
a hand job there's 15 minutes you'll
never get
back just laying there staring at each
other
[Applause]
what's that
baby what's that no no it doesn't
usually take this long no
it you look
tired I'm just saying ladies if that's
what you want to do you're just kind of
doing some [ __ ] that we haven't gotten
to
today that's what you want to do go iron
my
shirt I'm not trying to be mean I'm not
trying to be sexist I'd go iron my shirt
while you're doing this but I can't I
got to be here for
this so let me do this you go do let's
be productive that's what I'm
[Laughter]
saying that's a weird
joke cuz not everyone can laugh at it
and the people the groups that can't are
very divided like the younger kids can't
laugh at it cuz they'd settle for
that they be like yeah she's touching it
I'm not complaining at all and older
dudes are the same way you're like she
hasn't seen it in three months so if she
would just touch it it'll probably go
off really she doesn't even need to put
a full wrap around
it are you like is hearing this [ __ ]
it's [ __ ] hysterical and you're just
staring at
me and you're the only one so I'm
starting to think it's you
guys something happened today your dog
died you got to take a
poop that happens to me sometimes is
that right like you had to poop but he
had [ __ ] to do so he held it cuz you're
an
adult and then you pooped and then
you're like [ __ ] I've been a dick for
the last
hour got call people sorry sorry yeah I
had to poop and I didn't know
it totally forgot about the fact that I
had to
poop well I'm going to get out of here
we're going to go get stone and listen
to The Black Crows cuz they're my most
favorite band in the world I don't know
if you've heard of them yeah I just went
and saw them again that's like 17 times
in the last two years which kind of
makes me a dork but [ __ ] you okay I lead
the life anyway they were broken up for
2 years so I didn't really get to see so
I try to get to see him whenever I can
and um cuz for the two years they were
broken up the only way we could watch
him was to watch their Behind the Music
which I have on
tape one weekend me and my buddies got
really [ __ ] shitfaced like strip club
[ __ ] face you know that when it finally
sounds like a good idea that's when
you've had too much it's like strip club
[ __ ] yeah let's go give me your
keys
cuz silver I'm like strip club no [ __ ]
that let's go to the casino we might get
it
back I might get to [ __ ] the
dealer I bet she doesn't have a Coke
problem
either you can laugh they're not here
this is their money night they're making
[Applause]
money so one night we got really [ __ ]
up up and couldn't find the remote so we
had to watch the commercials it's an
older tape it's got older commercials
it's got that old OB commercial on there
I went with the lady she walks out of
the laboratory and up to the camera
she's like did you know that the first
tampon was
developed by a
man what the
hell is she asking me
for why would I know I don't know
probably you know probably the first guy
tired of waking up in the middle of a
crime
scene what what what don't look at me
like you don't know what the hell I'm
talking
about yeah you call it spotting yeah I
got news for you ladies that's [ __ ]
leaking spotting is what you do with the
UFO that makes me the spotter I'm the
one waking up in the middle of the night
I don't know what the hell's going on I
wake up I look over I'm like oh my God
you've been
shot why' they shoot you there of all
places were they mad at
me cuz that was my favorite
place
why wouldn't they shoot you in the mouth
or
something what no for efficiency that's
all you're a hit man your Target's
asleep you don't go shooting her in the
vagge that's
mean and
unprofessional that is bad hit man
etiquette you guys are cool man I did
that joke last week this dude got pissed
she was
angry stood up started yelling [ __ ] out
at me why would you shoot her in the
mou I don't
know maybe cuz questions answer
themselves child out was funny but she
was drunk and didn't get it she kept
coming at me you don't go shooting her
in the mouth mouth can be just as good
as a
vagina
what I mean I've had some great [ __ ]
but I have yet to walk by an open vagina
I wish would shut the [ __ ]
up Kanas City you guys been a lot of fun
man thank you so
much
[Music]
w
la
[Music]
[Applause]
w
[Music]
poop