[Applause]
oh let's talk about
it let's talk about
it after it happened I had some friends
try to cheer me up they were like put
things in perspective Robert I mean yeah
Trump won but we've had presidents that
have owned people
before
okay true but I feel like we should set
a higher bar
than
slavery especially since no one's
allowed to do that
anymore right like you might have an
argument if slavery were still legal
then you could say well look at Trump
more money than God hasn't bought a
single fella I respect that you know he
could he chooses not to that's why he's
my candidate
no also say things like well Robert
Donald Trump winning proves anyone could
become president no it doesn't he was a
billionaire it's not like before running
Trump was assistant managing a Staples
and was like try to stop me and then
just beat
everybody with wits and open-mindedness
and tolerance and weal AO policies no
it's not inspiring that a billionaire
became president the only people
inspired by Trump are the uncles that
could shush to
Thanksgiving you know I'm not the only
one at work that doesn't trust Puerto
Ricans
sh I will not shush I killed that turkey
myself damn it you're going to hear what
I have to say about those Ricky Martin
what what did you call them sh
shush I don't know if you guys caught
this but apparently Trump has promised
to repeal Obamacare and replace it with
Trump care which is just a series of
unsolicited papsmear
and yeah don't even have to ask for it
it'll just happen you just have to wait
for
it won't cost you anything no co-pay all
lady
covered you see where he talked about
how bangable his own daughter was in
those interviews too a bangable his own
I mean it worked he won the southern
states you got to give that to him he
definitely knew what it took to get
elected I heard some people tell me that
Trump's victory was a backlash against
PC culture I don't know if that's true
or not I think in some cases it it might
be a little extreme though for instance
I don't know if you guys know this but
in schools now kids aren't even allowed
to celebrate Halloween anymore because
that's offensive Halloween is too
offensive so they can't call it
Halloween anymore they have to call it a
Harvest
Festival which makes sense right cuz
what do kids love crops
oh once they start talking about corn
you can't get him to shut up about it
it's like move on with your
lives but we can't throw any Stones
right cuz who amongst us growing up
didn't have many a blast playing those
classic childhood games like t a field
and sort the grains the time did
fly I don't know I think it's kind of
ironic that the people most offended by
Halloween are the same people that spend
a lot of their time in church you know
that building where people go to dress
up and pretend to be someone they're not
for a treat you know those um those
places I uh
all right could have used you on the
orange as the new Christ stuff but thank
you for
that
could and why isn't Halloween the
holiday we should be forced to spend
with our family right wouldn't that make
the most sense for our family's scariest
day of the year forget ghosts wait till
you find out what your aunt really
thinks of Black lives matter oh God
[Music]
a