for
NE
[Music]
make we got uh yeah
[Applause]
yep
we
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
a
[Music]
he
[Applause]
[Music]
W wo
[Applause]
I'm in New
Orleans I just said a fact that
everybody got [ __ ] super stoked about
it I'm in a place and you're like we're
here too and I like that I like what
we're all doing we're in the same place
together I'm from I'm okay that's good I
uh I'm originally from Seattle and I
[ __ ] hate that place and uh cuz it is
dark 9 months out of the year and when I
landed in New Orleans 3 days ago I
stopped taking my
anti-depressants cuz why do I need them
it's beautiful out
here I live in a place that is just
crushingly dark and shitty and love
crafty and it just rains passive
aggressiveness and oh I got to take it
cuz I said here's what I said last year
I had a doctor's appointment and I said
something when you are depressed you say
[ __ ]
under your breath that you think you're
being funny but it's really like a
suicidal threat you just do it and I
said this to my doctor he's like well
your blood sugar looks real good and uh
anything else you want me to check out
I'm like no no no I just got to remember
to stop eating cookie dough every now
after the barrel of my gun super bad for
my diabetes and uh now I'm on 40
milligrams of caloan which is amazing
because uh it uh gives you like an uh it
two of the side effects are increased
Suicidal Thoughts occasionally yeah
awesome bring it you want to come at me
[ __ ] come at me suicide I don't give
a [ __ ] I was at my 11-year-old nephew's
birthday party and he asked me like
what's it like being 45 I'm 11 and I was
like let me tell you you get to eat
whatever you want you get to stay up as
late as you want you can [ __ ] watch
any movies you want you everything is at
your command you get to do anything you
want sometimes you think about that girl
from high school that you just couldn't
follow through with and you look her up
on Facebook and she's doing great
and you kind of think oh man you know
what maybe I'll just go out to the car
for a little while and just think about
all the shots I didn't take and all the
chances I missed all the times I said no
and if you're lucky you'll open that
garage door and let all the exhaust out
am I not allowed to hang out with him
anymore so I'm on an I'm on an an
depress that uh also side side effect
number two uh 100% flaccid
impotency I don't give a
[ __ ] do you know how amazing it is to
not be able to feel anything but bliss
even if you don't want
to it's like you're trapped inside
yourself have you ever laugh cried have
you ever been like you but you're happy
but you don't want to be happy cuz
you're sad so you start crying but
you're like God damnn it I can't do
anything other than cry but I want to
laugh oh [ __ ] why is it my dick it's the
most amazing thing I have such creative
control and uh I it doesn't matter I
don't care this doesn't
work men you don't realize this but when
this is shut off completely I've
regained like eight gigs of hard drive
space in my
head oh [ __ ] yeah oh man I remembered a
kid's number from Elementary School my
dick's been blocking that stuff I want
it
back um I don't like the term drink the
Kool-Aid by the way I worked long enough
in Corporate America that I [ __ ] hate
that term drink the Kool-Aid Dean drank
the Kool-Aid at the sales do you guys
get how offensive that is drink the
Kool-Aid people say that all the time uh
drank the cool no that's not [ __ ]
cool first off you get where it came
from right
that comes directly from it D it comes
directly from Guyana from Jim Jones from
the [ __ ] Jim Jones massacre where he
convinced all of his followers to drink
poison
liquid and the media was like Kool-Aid
man they all drank the Kool-Aid and we
use that at like Best Buys for sales
meetings I hope Dean drank the coolant
on that 4K TV roll out that is so
insensitive also it pisses me off cuz it
wasn't [ __ ] Kool-Aid okay it was
[ __ ] flavorade Kool-Aid had nothing
to do with that okay [ __ ] flavorade
got away with murder Kool-Aid [ __ ] got
saddled with a death cult and they were
like what the [ __ ] did we ever do oh you
know flavorade America's seventh
flavored [ __ ] favorite powder drink
got away with
murder I can't even imagine I can't even
imagine like the Kool-Aid guy just
bursting through the wall of the
Jonestown
compound just dumping a box of rat
poison in his stupid Jug Head and
stirring it with a wooden spoon and then
trying to convince his flock to follow
him to the [ __ ] Crystal Skies of
whatever [ __ ] Messianic fever dream
he had and then he even drinks some
himself and then his legs buckle and he
shatters into a million reflective
pieces on the ground and then his soul
just sort of discc corporates and then
goes into that weird afterlife spiral
where it's shot into a hell of his own
making where he's just forced to burst
through wall after wall after wall after
wall after wall after wall after wall
after wall I can't picture that all I'm
saying is from now on when people are
like did you drink the Kool-Aid you go
[ __ ] you flavorade look it up it's
[ __ ] it's the same godamn drink for
people who can't afford regular cereal
okay you know that cereal when you're
like h can we get Captain Crunch and
your mom's like we can't afford Captain
Crunch but we can afford this clear bag
of cereal that's like Captain dinguses
[ __ ] sprinkled donnut holes we can
get that for you that's what we can
afford [ __ ]
flavored I'll take it new
things is anyone hear a health
goth can I get a woo uh if you guys
don't know what that is Health goth is a
story that came out on Facebook months
ago Facebook is the news now by the way
that's happening there's this the story
in the [ __ ] New York Times about a
bunch of goth kids that are like just
getting healthy together they're going
to the gym and
[ __ ] goth
style wearing little black headbands and
[ __ ] throwing those styrofoam weights
around you know listening to New Order
it's [ __ ]
adorable but it's not very goth if you
think about it because goth the concept
of goth right is all about looking like
a dead person like you fell out of Tim
Burton's hat you
know like going to look morose and going
to the gym and getting healthy is all
about life it's about being alive and
like being flush and having color in
your skin and [ __ ] so it's it would be
way more goth to just get really [ __ ]
fat right like guier goth should be a
thing I want to get so many rolls of fat
that when I take off my Joy Division
shirt I still look like I'm wearing a
Joy Division
shirt if your friend laughed at that
they were not cool in high school and we
all sat at the same lunch table all
right uh let's get into this
[ __ ] God I [ __ ] hate comedy all right
[Laughter]
uh I'm bipolar I think I don't know
because when you don't have you don't
get health insurance for doing this like
just have to self diagnose things but I
runs in my family and [ __ ] and I have
you know manic streaks and then
depressive streaks streaks and there's I
just just just days in my life where I
just can't get out of bed I watch a lot
of Netflix and eat junk food my favorite
depression junk food is bugles because
bugles are like little trumpets you use
to announce that you're not [ __ ]
going to work that
day you're
like I wonder what Moulder and Skully
are getting into from eight goddamn
[Music]
hours my life is falling apart
I'm just living a Bruce Springsteen song
right now
just [ __ ] wife dumped me my dog
killed me I three of my wh cruxes have
been destroyed I'm
just uh when you wear the same clothes
two days in a row everyone thinks that
you got
laid but on the third
day that's when they know that you're
just
disgusting and no one could ever love
you that's where I'm at I
work I work I work in in [ __ ]
there's a thing there's a thing like
when you are a comic or a musician or an
actor or whatever there's a thing where
you're kind of supposed to lie and tell
people you don't have a day job because
then they'll think you're a real comic
and then they'll hire you more and [ __ ]
and I don't like doing it I think it's a
[ __ ] really gross phony thing to do
cuz I do this [ __ ] but I also just have
to work at a shitty bar and stuff and
it's [ __ ] it's annoying to me cuz
everyone the economy is just [ __ ] it's
impossible to have a dream in America
anymore it's just over everyone is lying
there all everyone who comes up here is
just [ __ ] lying Louis C K works at a
Foot
Locker they make him wear the little
referee shirt and [ __ ] it's [ __ ]
degrading right L he's a Foot Locker
Janine garao manages a gap you know just
at the mall aiz ansari's just a hologram
they just made him up it's all [ __ ]
lies man and I'm a goddamn bartender I
work in
restaurants it sucks I know like God
restaurants man I know some of you guys
are like oh I worked in a restaurant
when I was in college before I became a
bazillionaire you know you you don't
[ __ ] know man you weren't there you
weren't there I'm in the [ __ ] you
haven't worked in a restaurant until
you've seen a Korean guy lose his [ __ ]
on someone in Spanish it's jarring it's
weird he's having flashbacks to a war
that ever happened between Korea and
Mexico you know he's like didy m didy m
pin bjo [ __ ] Bak guo round ey and
it's it's jarring all right I work in a
I work in bars I bartend to pay for for
all this
[ __ ] and uh it's it's making me
crazy it's making me hate people I hate
fictional characters now I hate James
Bond all right here's
why James Bond is supposed to be like a
cool like Suave person right he's like
he's British he's got a gun right he's a
he's a spy right and then there's this
other thing where he goes into casinos
and he goes up to the bartender and he
goes excuse me I'll have a
martini shaken not
stirred all
right are we supposed to think that it's
cool that he's annoying in
restaurants that's not a cool quality in
a person at all what are you talking
about oh can I have a little extra thing
in the side to dip my lemon shut the
[ __ ] up James Bond drink a [ __ ] beer
that tastes like cigarette butts like a
man pretend like it doesn't taste like
cigarette butts drink it cuz you're
addicted to it you [ __ ] man you old
lady you want a little [ __ ] thing to
sachche around the casino with you
[ __ ] lose it's like you know his
friends are all embarrassed they're like
we can't take this dick anywhere he
always has to I need a little shicken
Martin like he's a [ __ ] weird thing
you know what they don't show you is the
end of that scene where he's like and
I'll also need to spread that over three
different credit
cards cuz I'm a a [ __ ] [ __ ]
privileged Rich dick doesn't know how
life Works never ever been outside of
his own goddamn house you
know but I don't hate him cuz he's not
real I hate like people that imitate him
and then come into my job and do that
and they're like I need a [ __ ] white
russian but black and Mexican just shut
up just can't person ize your [ __ ]
like that it's not cool dude you just
[ __ ] drink beer man like thing it's
on the screenwriters right because
screenwriters write these movies and
these movies take place in just a
ridiculous fictional reality where
there's just no social rules right like
in a movie you can just you can order a
dumb drink and everyone's like cool you
know you can get into a cab and just say
like
Drive the guy just drivve you know he
doesn't get kick you the [ __ ] out of the
cab and call your friend on the phone
and say some [ __ ] and just hang up right
it's [ __ ] right so like we need to
stop writing movies like that so people
stop imitating them in real life like I
want the next James Bond movie to be a
movie where James Bond just goes up to
the bar and then he just orders
something off the menu and sits the [ __ ]
down right and then he's just looking at
his phone for 15 minutes of a movie
that's just you just stare at the movie
while he just plays Candy Crush then it
goes on as some other [ __ ] I want the
next doeki commercial to be a commercial
where the guy's like I don't always
drink beer but when I do I order off the
menu and sit the [ __ ] down I sometimes I
have to drink Corona which is the
leading competitor brand of my own thing
that I work for but it doesn't [ __ ]
matter cuz I'm a madeup construct of
capitalism in this Mad Men era of
marketing that is designed to take you
out of the moment and make you forget
about reality and things that actually
matter your kids are growing up in front
of you and you're thinking about [ __ ]
dois man what are you doing with just
shoots himself in the [ __ ]
face the blood just comes down and just
says drink whatever you
want it doesn't matter we all die
[Music]
alone
anyways um I I would say that on average
I whisper to myself now it's my
CH at least once or twice a
day bus is pulling up now's my
chance but they open the door to the bus
now's my
chance and everyone gets on the bus I'm
missing my
chance what I'm saying is I'm too
nervous to ride the
bus welcome
[Laughter]
I'm too nervous for anything in this
[ __ ] town I'll tell you that much
holy [ __ ] I had to walk to a friend's
house and it was like seven minute walk
and I was like s Minutes in
Hell don't look just smile don't look
just
smile I'm from Austin where ethnicities
don't
exist but I was raised in San Antonio
where I just wanted to be
Mexican
anyways do you guys like pop country
music yeah that's a it's a mixed review
it always is when I ask that question
some people say yes some people say no I
say if you say no that's okay I used to
be a hater too um I love pop country for
three reasons uh I listen to it every
day on the radio um I love it because
number one it's it's written by the
greatest songwriters of all time there's
at least 10 to 12 on every song um it's
played by the greatest players in the
world they're called Nashville cats been
playing since they
babies
and number three it's dumb as [ __ ] I
listen to it every day it's what keeps
the gun in the drawer and
[Laughter]
um you laugh at My Pain that's fine um I
was listening to pop country radio and I
heard a fell named Blandy bravis I know
what you're saying Blandy bravis that
sounds a lot like Randy Travis well yeah
that's a comparison I'm making
um he he ruined his career with drugs
and alcohol and not the typical route
not a broken bottle of Evan Williams and
a mound of cocaine he did a lot of LSD
and he fried his brain so much so the
last time they saw him in public he was
covered in blood and beaver nuggets
outside of a bues and um he's recorded a
new album and I heard the single on
Mexico ind. net the other day and I'd
like
to you guys don't like
music whatever um but I'd like to sing
it for you if you would
mine
okay uh this is called dirt road
obviously um um by Blandy
bravis fun intro
Avery he chilling on the dirt
road you got a beer in the
console you got your jeans painted on
and your hair in the wind you got a
sidekick named Fred and he is a frog and
you're riding down down the dirt
road you got a beer in the
console and the sky opens up and hey
it's God he says son you're the second
coming of Christ
CH you say Okay God I'm going to start a
war I'm going to kill everyone not
deserving of Your Love cuz you riding
down a dirt
road you got a beer in the console
and you head up the hill and you look
out the window and man when I looked out
the window I saw some commotion going on
so I turn to my girl my friend Fred I
say hey why don't you slide those sweet
asses off those spinal bucket sleeps
let's go check it out so we lock we hop
out the truck lock it up head up the
hill turns out we've stumbled upon an
archaeological dick I found the fell in
charge his name is Doctor Lee he says
hey what we have done is uncovered a
Bible printed on Papyrus that predates
all other Christian text and I was
like he points out this one passage you
know how 666 is commonly referred to as
the mark of the beast you guys know what
I'm talking about rock and roll
baby
yeah well in this version of the Bible
it's
616 like Grand Rapids
Michigan cuz he riding down a dirt
roll you got a beer in the
console God is my dad and I am his son
you're all Sinners I'm on to [ __ ]
kill
everyone cuz you riding down a dirt
road thank you so much don't tell anyone
you heard that
byebye drinking is my favorite
holiday you can do you can do that [ __ ]
seven days a week you ever drink so much
you break into an orphanage and try to
set the kids
free you ever drink so much you still
think there's
orphanages those aren't a thing anymore
turns out I was just kicking in the
doors of children's hospitals you're
free now
go why is your head
shaved turns out she was a fan so
oh um pretty excited my mom quit calling
her flip-flops thongs this
year there's just come something quite
disturbing about waking up to The
Whispers of your mom's voice on a
hungover holiday morning and hearing
Joe Joseph I'm like yeah Mom he's like
have you seen my thongs
anywhere I'm like why would you say this
to your son and I start to yell and
about halfway through my rant I realized
oh she's talking about those things she
wears on her feet and I'm like I'm sorry
Mom you just got to realize I've been
drinking for the past 24 hours to forget
that I'm part of this
family like you don't understand when I
go home from the holidays I have to go
home to Waco
Texas yeah home with Dr Pepper in Jesus
Christ real Dr Pepper fake Jesus it
turns
out uh for this next joke you have to
believe I have a
[Applause]
girlfriend the other day I got out of
the shower and I remembered how
hilarious the movie Silence of the Lambs
was so so I tuck it between my legs and
I go walking out in the living room
while she's watching TV I'm like do you
want to [ __ ]
me I [ __ ]
me and that's creepy as [ __ ] right but I
realize it's way creepier if your
girlfriend's never seen Silence of the
lamps thanks
guys hey what's up all
right okay
cool I uh I like to married a lot
um three up three down retire the side
in order I uh I do like a good party I
guess I uh I went on a date with a girl
though and uh I was excited to hear what
she has to say and you know I went to
Coffee that's a good date right you know
you can hear what they you know there's
no distractions and so she sits down and
uh I'm like uh hey how's it going and
she says uh she says something that
blows my [ __ ] mind she sits down and
she says it feels really good to be
out I'm like where the [ __ ] were you
just prior to this and no mention of
that on Tinder and then uh and she says
no it feels good to be on a date silly
and I was like yeah it feels good for me
too then she says well uh I went through
a rough stretch recently it's like okay
well maybe explain she says well I was
drinking quite a bit and one thing led
to another and I ended up doing Crystal
math with my
son it's like oh no
uh it's really [ __ ] gross uh you have
a
kid
uh gross um it's like you don't have a
problem with me doing Crystal math and I
was just like YOLO you know I mean you
do what you got to do and she's like
well I don't do much crystal meth
anymore and I was like yeah I know you
don't she's like well how do you know
and I was like well you're splitting
half of it with your kid
um hard to stretch your crystal meth
that way I've
heard yeah I like to thank people I'm a
thanker as before I go on with the rest
of my set I want to thank you guys for
coming out I want to thank all the
comics you've seen tonight and uh I also
want to thank Affliction
Clothing I do uh I want to thank
Affliction Clothing for making people I
never want to hang out with way easier
to
spot in a crowd you used have to guess
who you want to hang out with now you
see one of those shirts you're like well
it's not that [ __ ] guy I know that
for shies I
uh I was hanging out after a show one
night just hanging out in front of the
venue and I see a guy approaching me
directly and I think to myself uh this
guy's going to compliment me on my set
and as he gets closer I see as an ition
t-shirt on has a big sequence cross on
it and I think to myself uh this guy is
probably not going to compliment me on
my set and he gets uh and he doesn't he
gets this close to my face and he says
that t-shirt joke I [ __ ] hated it
bro and what I said to him was totally
different than what I said to myself
what I said to him was uh I'm sorry man
I didn't mean to be hurtful it's just a
joke thanks for coming out to the show
but what I said to myself was I'm about
to give my ass kicked by a guy in a
sequin man
blouse it's a pretty humbling Facebook
update oh hey everybody I did my set and
then I got the [ __ ] kicked out of me by
a guy in a bedazzled baby
T please don't like this
post spins around starts walking the
other way he has a yamaka on his head
which I thought was the weirdest fashion
Choice had a yamaka and a sequin cross
it was like he was wardrobe by
coexist starts walking the other
direction and uh my friend seen
everything and he's like dude what the
[ __ ] was that and I was like I don't
know man like a
hebro juice bag I don't know what
they're calling
them this
point yeah anybody here have
anxiety that's a weird way to say you
have anxiety uh oh wo wo I barely get
out of the house y'all
um I've had anxiety since I was a small
child uh five or 6 years old is when I
first realized that I had it it would be
bedtime I would just stare into the
darkness of my ceiling my heart would
start pounding I would start sweating
really bad and I would have the same
thought over and over again and the
thought is what am I going to do when my
parents die that's going to be the worst
day of my life how am I going to handle
my parents dying they're the only thing
I know they're everything to me what am
I going to do when my parents die and
this would happen night after night
after night and uh now my parents are
both dead so needless to say that's a
huge weight that's been lifted off my
shoulders finally catch some [ __ ]
Z's I have evil inside me I have D I
have darkness in me uh I learned it in a
weird way I just uh started shopping it
Safeway do you guys have Safeways out
here in New Orleans no do you have
grocery
stores I started shopping at grocery
stores here's the weird thing about some
grocery stores is that they make you
feel like you're evil even though you're
not because they're the only place on
the planet Earth that requires you a
check out to say no I don't want to help
kids with muscular distrophy
they make you say it too you think you
can politely Decline and didn't know on
the ATM but then the clerk looks at you
and they're like don't you want to help
the kids and then you have to be like uh
[ __ ] I guess I don't that's
weird I don't even know myself
anymore and then they might say
something like this I might be like uh
you know it's only a dollar and you
bought 30 pieces of string
cheese you try to save it you're like
uh do they like string chees
give him a couple thanks I'm Johnny have
a good
[Music]
night I became a
doctor thank
you which I did by checking off the
doctor option on the American Express
credit card
application it's the quickest way to
become a doctor it worked I got a card
that said Dr Danny Lobel on
it which was fantastic
and I did with that card what I've done
with every credit card I ever got I
maxed it out and didn't pay the bills at
all started getting calls from the
Creditor but it was different than any
other time because every time this woman
would call me she was asking for Dr
Danny LEL I felt really accomplished it
was like the best thing I ever she hi
this is Christine from American Express
is Dr LEL available please so I started
answering the phone as my own
receptionist I go no I'm sorry Dr LEL is
not in right now uh he's with a patient
can I take a message and she go oh no
I'm sorry this is a private business
matter I go oh okay so do you need to
speak to him yeah that would be best oh
all right let me see what he's got
available I
start flipping through a fake
appointment book looks like he's got
nothing open
until Tuesday at 10:00 a.m. can I fit
you in for the Tuesday at 10: a.m.
Christine and she go uh yeah that
that'll work for me and then she called
10:00 a.m. on Tuesday it
worked so hi I have an appointment with
Dr LEL I said ah
Christine I'm so sorry to break this to
you but Dr LEL got called into an
emergency surgery right
now ah it's awful she goes okay well uh
when when can I talk to him I go let me
look at the
books then I said hold on let me place
you on a brief hold and I just play some
music from
YouTube oh
hello yes I'm looking here I see he's
got nothing available for two weeks I
can fit you in on Thursday at 4 p.m. two
weeks from now you want to take that
she's like yeah all right I'll I'll take
that and then she calls two weeks later
right at her appointment time I'm like I
can't let this end so I just kept doing
it I said she he's been calling to
another emergency surgery and I rebooked
her and she called I said emergency
surgery and she called I said another
emergency surgery and she goes finally
she got impatient and she goes when will
Dr Lobel not be in surgery I said when
people's hearts stop failing and I slam
the phone
down you will not disparage Dr lel's
good name taking that tone with me the
man's a miracle worker
[Laughter]
people always tell me uh I should lose
weight which is fine they're really
telling me I should live
longer which is stupid because I worked
in an old age home and I know how that
ends there's no trophy at the end of
that
race but one people give me different
advice one person said every time you
eat a burger it takes 6 minutes off your
life and uh I heard that and I I went
home and I threw away all my
socks because I calculated I eat about
four Burgers a
month I went to Costco I got a 60 pack
of socks where they all had the same
matching patterns cuz I figured out it
takes me about 30 minutes a month to
pair my
socks so I gained six minutes a month on
my
life without giving up any
Burgers I'm living like an
immortal I'm married now I got married
which is exciting thank you it's very
good because I wasn't the kind of guy
who was like uh picking up women very
easily before this you know I locked one
down and I'm happy with that but before
this I did anything to pick up girls I
this one girl I liked was in AA so I
used to pretend to be an alcoholic and
go to the AA meetings to try and pick
her
up but then everybody there had these
crazy stories they'd be like going
around like hey yeah I uh lost my uh
everything to alcohol I had a
boat I had a house I had two kids and
drinking took all that away from me and
I just be sitting there like man I
haven't lived you
know I wish I had a
boat I don't have a boat or a house I
got nothing to lose I got to start
drinking and every time it come to me
I'd have to make up a fake story and my
stories were terrible and everybody
could tell and be like like oh one time
I I
drank quite a bit and
[Applause]
uh wasn't
good they be like what happened
oh
vomiting there was
some
vomiting anyway let's go on to the next
guy huh I could tell people were getting
suspicious of me that I wasn't a real
alcoholic so every week in between
meetings I just get wasted as much as I
could so I could have something you know
for the week coming
up I remember one night I got so
plastered I'm walking through Times
Square in New York City there's a uh hot
dog stand that one of those carts the
guy who's Manning it must have walked
away from the cart he was doing
something else and I was so hammered
that I just staggered and fell into the
cart and the cart fell on top of me and
all this nasty hot dog water that had
been sitting there all day this slimy
disgusting smelly water got all over me
and I kept trying to get up but I was
too drunk and I kept slipping on the
greasy water then I started vomiting all
over myself because of the smell and
then just for a second I remember
smiling thinking this is going to kill
at AA next
[Applause]
week I uh I got on
Obamacare I had to go to the Social
Services office which is the most
depressing place in in the world it's
the same office for food stamps and
Obamacare and I've been to these offices
before and they always depress me and I
get into the elevator and there's this
woman uh who uh has four kids single mom
and she's she's got the kids in the
elevator and she's yelling at them uh
one of them keeps taking her flip-flop
off in the elevator and putting her foot
down on the floor said put your damn
flipflop back on what the hell you doing
put your damn flipflop back on you want
people to think I got dirty nasty ghetto
kids is that what you want people to
think put your flip and she kept doing
it she said put your flip up then she
turns to me she goes excuse me sir when
you see my daughter doing that don't you
think that I got dirty nasty ghetto kids
and then she opened her eyes and looked
at me like real wide like you better
agree with me right
now so I'm like yeah that's what I think
she goes you see what white people think
of
you so then I got upset cuz I'm like I'm
not one of those white people you know I
always felt like if I had more ambition
I'd be into civil rights I'd be a civil
rights activist I'm just lazy I'm a
civil rights inactivist I haven't done
anything but I was like I want I want to
I got to change these kids' opinion
about white people I don't want this to
happen so I'm like I'm going to really
win win this lady over so we the
elevator gets to the floor we're both on
the the same floor on the third floor
and I'm positioned to get out of the
elevator first but I say no ma'am you go
ahead you go in front of me you got all
those kids go ahead and she goes thank
you that's very nice of you and she
leaves and then I leave but then I get
to the line before her cuz the kid's
still taking the flipflops off and she's
yelling at the kid slowed her down so
I'm like all right I'm going to do it
again she gets behind me I go ma'am you
got all those kids you go ahead of me
with with your kids ma'am it's fine and
she goes that's very nice of you thank
you and I'm thinking oh I'm really doing
it you know go in for the kill L Bell
I'm like and might I add ma'am you have
very cute kids
and then she goes what the hell is that
got to do with anything you got cute
kids don't help you in life what the
hell's wrong with you bringing up the
fact I got cute kids what's wrong I'm
like all right I lose I lose it's over I
tried and we're sitting in the waiting
room there's about 50 people and uh
everybody looks just miserable miserable
and I get very depressed from this and I
start I want to tell this story
specifically here because I I'm very
into jazz and and uh I start always
going into these like jazz Melodies when
I get depressed I start playing them
sometimes unconsciously that I'm doing
it so I'm going
[Applause]
[Music]
and this woman from the line starts
yelling she like what what excuse me and
I'm like oh crap I didn't even realize I
was doing it I S I'm like oh I'm so
sorry she goes you know I was watching
Bethany the other day and they had
people like you on I'm
like okay she goes people with what she
called a special talent do you know
that's what you got a special
[Music]
talent I was like oh thank
you she goes this is my favorite part
she goes I don't know how hard it's
going to be for you son but you need to
find yourself in
[Applause]
Internet I didn't imagine myself walking
around please does anyone know where I
can find an
internet there used to be one up at the
Old
Tavern don't know if it's still
there see he said you got to get
yourself an internet and get on the
YouTube you don't need to be here with
the rest of us you got a special talent
then she gets up in front of 50 people
in this room and she goes excuse me but
doesn't this man sound exactly 99% like
a
trumpet and nobody had heard me but her
cuz she was sitting right next to me so
now everybody's like do it do it and
part of me didn't want to but a part of
me was like you know this is the closest
I've had to representation in La I got
to really go for it
so I
start and I'm really doing
it and people were loving it more than
you and
uh people were loving it I'm telling you
some somebody was filming with an iPhone
somebody was like going like this and
then I saw this old black man in the
corner with a hat on and his eyes were
closed and he was smiling he was just
swaying his head slowly back and forth
going
[Music]
mhm that's jazz
mhm that's
Jess like I was just imagining that he
was asking himself different questions
in his head but they all had the same
answer is it that music that started in
New Orleans
mhm that's
jazz is that that basketball play game
that the team that now plays in
Utah mhm that's
jazz is that that shock that ain't all
those people on the beach that
time M that's
Jaws all right been Daniel Bell thank
you very
much thank you
[Music]