31 with a
baby ranting out of my ass at
strangers did not expect
this this was not part of the
responsibilities that I signed up for I
used to have three responsibilities in
my life three that was it when I was 21
10 years ago three responsibilities
where are we getting [ __ ] up
who are we getting [ __ ] up with and
what are we getting [ __ ] up on those
were the three and that's not even in a
particular order you can move those
around right now I have so many
responsibil I was talking to a friend of
mine the other day it was earlier it was
right before the show uh he asked me oh
now that you have a son now that you
have a baby you're a father are you
going to get life
insurance
no no I always thought life insurance
was like sad Lottery
right right like oh Uncle Pete died but
I paid off my car so thank you Uncle
Pete I appreciate that now I'm Uncle
Pete in that scenario that's terrible
right not to mention life insurance this
is my full-time job this is what I do
for a living there's nothing to
ensure this is it right if I die my wife
is sad that is the end of the
story right she's the one with like a
like a steady income she's got the
regular day job job the check comes we
get the benefits right everything's
great if she dies I am [ __ ] I'm in a
lot of trouble right just calling the
insurance company every is somebody
going to pay these
bills they come every
month and cuz somebody teach me use the
stove it's gas I get nervous