this is lovely I'm feeling great tonight
very very good I hope you're feeling as
good as I am uh the reason I'm feeling
so good is uh I'm wearing
pants right now and that has not been
able to happen the entire time I've been
here I've had to wear like one pair of
shorts the whole time very quiet
everybody knows exactly what I'm talking
about it's very difficult this is a
beautiful place and it's a beautiful
place to come ruin clothes it really is
I've been looking at everything going
nope that's not going to that's not
going to work that's going to go away
very quickly that'll
deteriorate rapidly I will look like a
ghost pirate walking around the
beaches I don't know uh I'm worried that
some of you have seen me on a golf cart
driving around casting judging eyes at
me as I go by I feel like some of you I
might have seen you I try not to make
eye contact while I'm doing
it mainly because I'm worried that my
shorts will catch a breeze and then you
see stuff you don't want to see as I
drive by that's a very interesting kind
of driveby to
happen I will say uh if I come back
again one more important thing that I
need to pack is an entire suitcase of
Gold Bond uh body
powder that needs to be a
sponsor of the show is Gold
Bond if you go into my my bathroom right
now it looks like two people had what is
referred to as a cocaine fight to the
death my entire bathroom is just covered
in a thin layer of white powder with
Footprints leading away from the
scene I've I've given up on soap and
showering I just sort of rinse off one
layer of powder and then put on another
coat when I go home I'm going to have to
explain that to my wife the first time
she sees me I'm going to go look honey
I'm coming to
bed just understand I had a lot of Gold
Bond happening my balls are not haunted
okay they just look like ghost balls
right now they are not
haunted I don't know what I'm talking
about this is this is good though I feel
good I feel like I can wear these
clothes for a little while and then I'm
going to have to do cut offs that's not
going to look good six seven big fat
dude in C offs that doesn't look good at
all oh look he dressed himself today
that's adorable I didn't know safety
scissors could cut through
cloth this is beautiful I love this
venue this is a very cool venue I like
this a lot the stage is amazing uh this
is like a I think this is the most
exotic place I've ever performed uh I
love it this is the most exotic comedy
show you can see or the most beautiful
gay wedding in the
world there are plan there are wedding
planners that are fighting to the death
right now to have this happen
again maybe a little less Gold Bond
but I like this and uh before I came on
the stage I saw in the backstage they
have a there's a fire
extinguisher attached to the well to the
stone that the whole thing is made out
of there's a fire extinguisher when you
you're you're chuckling now when you
leave and you walk by it and you see it
you will be laughing very very hard this
entire thing is made of
stone if there is a fire on this stage
leave it it is meant to be it is meant
to be someone wanted that fire very
badly this is the only place I've ever
performed where the Green Room is the
well it's just the street
and and this is the first time before I
came on stage a guy tried to sell me a
kitten
that just happened that's not a bit that
is not a bit I've worked on for a long
time in my comedy career going can't
wait to go to aqual that kitten selling
bit is really going to kill tried to
sell me a what am I going to do with a
kitten on stage hi everybody this is
whiskers I bought them oh no there's a
dog in the audience what is happening
here what is happening
somebody's sing me kidss there's dogs in
the
audience have I died and is this is this
a place where is this Valhalla is this
the end of the world for
me does the dog like this show so far
excellent excellent he looks happy he or
she she she she looks happy you're kind
of rubbing her chest weird
though if it was a he that would be fine
but it's a it's a lady dog
I'm sorry I don't have real good dog
jokes to give
you but it's a rarity that I have to do
crowd work with a
pet should bring that cat out maybe he
knows some good
jokes this is great I like this all
right I'll tell a joke because I didn't
do that yet I apologize I apologize I
didn't do that yet I just talked about
the things that I've seen