all right I know this is late what the
do you guys do uh New Year's resolutions
is that to uh [ __ ] white people
for the listening audience of this I
don't usually uh although this year I
don't know I always say I'm gonna do
something I join a gym how's that for uh
corny white people's
[ __ ] um CU I'm too stationary I need to
[ __ ] move a little bit or my heart is
going to collapse in on itself
uh so I did join a gym We'll see if that
sticks so far so good
um but every year I kind of say I'm not
going to make a big resolution but I'm
going to do something kind of this I
decree to myself you know some sort of
[ __ ] old timey [ __ ] and so this year
I said I'm going to scale back a little
bit across the board uh meaning 130 to
150 dates on the road each year is
unsustainable when you're looking down
the barrel of 41 as I I am love doing
shows love being on the road but I need
to to scale back a little bit otherwise
uh I won't see 45 and so that's what I'm
doing for 2017 scaling back a little bit
which means across the board
so uh the road podcast is going to be
weekly instead of twice a week when I
first started this podcast people said
how often are you doing it h every
Tuesday and every Thursday and my
podcast pal said you are out of your
[ __ ]
gourd I was said no that seems feasible
uh it's not two podcasts a week is is
too much to just Wrangle and I don't
want the quality to start to
affect uh and also it's it's like I said
scaling back a slight bit and giving my
ever trusty uh producer Ryan Miller from
bleeding heart a little bit of a
breather as well Ryan's very
busy so as of this week it's going to be
every Tuesday instead of every Tuesday
and Thursday still plenty of content
still free so uh yeah not much room to
complain for free [ __ ] um but thank you
all for tuning in each and every week
and I I think one episode per week is
doable and uh reasonable and it will uh
give me a little bit more breathing
space so that's what we're
doing today's episode is a doozy uh
sorry no episode last week last week I
had three giant shows within the span of
5 days thank you to everybody who came
out to the road stories show the
altercation Road stories first gig of
20167 check that sweet Jesus what a show
amazing cheetah Chrome from The Dead
Boys Kyle from The
Sword those of you who were there saw uh
Scott Reynolds from all bust out a
guitar which is kind of cheating
Scott cheetah said what the [ __ ] he gets
to bring a guitar I didn't know that was
allow us and it's not but uh who am I
going to tell Scott Reynolds from all
not to play a song no he played a song
um and thank you all for packing that
show out it was packed to the walls on a
bitterly cold for
Austin 12 Dee night amazing show at
kickb Coffee thanks to everybody who
made it out the gig a few days later
with David Hy was a blast the Lord of
Darkness David hety just recorded his
brand new 1H hour
special up in uh Canadian land
a David H is a Canuck which sounds
racist is that
racist no daughter M's going to date a
kuck I fought them in the war what
is that what uh that'll be the next
Target in Trump's America Canucks they
bleed syrup um that show was [ __ ]
super
fun and especially for me CU I only had
to do like 15 minutes and then I got to
sit back and watch David Hy make people
very uncomfortable Love David Hedy and
then on Friday the
13th at the lost well in downtown Austin
was the altercation uh Frost Giants ball
which is the Heavy Music Festival mini
Festival that I curate each and every
winter amazing time had by all thanks to
everybody who showed up I know we're up
against free week Austin has a thing
called free week where bands play for
free and they pack out the venues after
the holidays and free week has quickly
become free half a month so we were up
against a free Riverboat gamblers Pander
Z show amongst many other giant things
the Bowmont were playing for free that
night a kickb coffee and uh yeah people
still came out and paid 10 bucks ahead
so thank you for packing out the joint
thank thanks to all the bands who played
uh lots of bands from out of town too
TSS from Victoria Texas killed
it as did from Parts Unknown their name
is a lie they're from
Dallas Ben and the boys bringing it uh
Sabbath Crow everybody else
ass just a great uh show all across the
board so thanks to everybody who came
out that's what was up last week I just
got too much stuff going on man too many
whiskey shots but we are back with a
vengeance this week at the road podcast
uh sitting down at long last with the
Divine Londa Lester winner of funniest
person in Austin 2016 Lea is a comedic
force of Nature and a wonderful person
love Lea you may have caught her at the
altercation Comedy Festival this past
September and we have been trying to sit
down since about
then our schedu is both being
nutty uh I had a bail once or twice she
had a bail once or twice and
finally we got it together we sat down
an hour before she was uh taping her
brand new 1hour day special for standup
records
hooray of course she killed it uh
looking forward to that coming out I
don't know when but uh I have no doubt
it'll be on many best of year lists when
it does hit so keep an eye and an ear
peeled for that uh Lea hailing
originally from Detroit we had I had
heard all sorts of stories about Lea we
talk about that in in the the interview
this one took place in downtown Austin
at a bar called mug shots which is the
pretty much the comedians bar it's where
all the comics go to hang out and drink
away their neurosis and uh
neurosises neur what's theur plural of
neurotic go with
neurosises and I was like oh they have a
great outdoor patio it'll be perfect we
won't have to deal with music we can
chill in the corner and then it's
[ __ ] 8 degrees and high wind so we're
not not sitting out there so we're in a
in a little corner of uh mug shot so
apologies again for the music I know you
all dealt with it when I interviewed
Brett Brock in Nashville artist
extraordinaire uh for the last episode
so apologies for for the background
sound on this but uh deal with it pal
it's uh more than manageable I think and
Lea is goddamn hilarious so thank you to
her for taking time out of her very busy
schedule right before recording a
special no l she went she literally left
this conversation to go tape a special
I'm going to go kill a special now okay
bye uh so check out Londa and we're
going to tag uh a set from her at the
end of the episode so I hope you dig it
thanks for tuning in we'll see you again
next Tuesday see you next
Tuesday Trump cheers
[Music]
all right so long last Shonda Lester how
are you oh my God I'm so good I'm I'm
feeling better good Cedar fever kind of
got me messed up so I apologize if I'm
all nasly and snorty I'm going to sound
just as gross it's 20° in Austin Texas
which is as winter as it gets here and
we still have allergies and it's going
to be 70 in 3 days from now so oh man
I'm going stab the [ __ ] out of me a
cedar tree I'm going to [ __ ] up a tree
I'm going just be out one day jogging
and be like [ __ ] I got
you so we've literally been trying to
sit down together I think since August
more or less
yes it's been a minute yeah and just
various schedules and last minute stuff
on either one of our ends always kind of
foiled it but tonight I I real I
actually feel really bad cuz you're cool
enough to sit down with me before you're
getting ready to to film uh tapa special
tonight yeah I'm getting ready to do my
first album for stand up records yay I
am excited like we recorded some stuff
in April but I wanted to get some more
so we're going to do this one as well
and then kind of compile all this stuff
together and make one badass album nice
and when I say tonight I mean in like 45
minutes from now right yeah about 45
minutes was the stuff you recorded in
April also at the Vita room or was it a
different room okay yeah Vita room so
it'll probably hopefully sound the same
yeah yeah we got good people uh is
Dustin working with it yeah okay yeah
Dustin's done a lot of stuff with the
aamal Comedy Festival and uh an
associate of stand up records I guess is
the best way to to dub him um no nerves
you seem cool common collected I'm good
you know I know all the material works
even the new stuff I wrote so I'm not
really worried well here's a question
cuz when I I filmed last summer and
there was like I'd say 20% of it that
was new and I was excited about and I
wanted to get it out there which may
have in retrospect been a dumb idea cuz
it may have been like 80% you know and
not all the way there are you how do you
juggle that are you like is there newer
stuff that you want to put on it cuz
like it might be a while before you film
again or well yeah cuz I I wrote two new
bits and I tried them out and I was like
you know what they're going on the album
like I like them I like having new stuff
it feels good in my mouth when I get to
say it like old stuff after a while
you're like uh yucky yeah for sure you
get uh I don't know it it just becomes a
Through the Motions type thing a little
bit yeah um so you are the reigning
Champion or goddess I don't know what
the term is for Austin's funniest person
yes that is me congrats um that's a huge
deal uh how has that has that affected
you at all in terms of obviously a
higher profile in the city but on a
larger scale I know you've done a lot of
like fly out stuff to New York and some
comedy festivals in Montana and stuff
yeah so um I I got named one of Comedy
centrals to 10 comics to watch um and I
got to go do the New York Comedy
Festival at Carol lines which is a big
deal yeah it was so good and to be able
to go out there and kill it you know cuz
them New York New York [ __ ]
they is hard that's where I started
that's so to go up there you know with
my brand of humor and just like kill it
like that I was real happy about it
that's awesome how much time did they
give you um I think we all did like 7
minutes okay yeah like standard showcase
it right yeah and uh so so have you seen
kind of industry bumps I guess for lack
of a better term from winning um I mean
I got a lot more friend
requests that's right yeah cashing those
Twitter followers right you know I'm
sure some of these people could be
industry I don't know right um but yeah
it's been it's been good you know I
haven't let it go to my head like I
don't just like slam the door in people
faces no [ __ ] yeah you've never been
like that anyway yeah yeah you know I
ain't one of them I'm not throwing on
Mariah Carey
fit not going to lip sync your set
tonight at all no um
so when I first heard of you you you
were in town what's what year did you
move to Austin uh I moved here March 1st
2004 okay so you beat me by about a year
I got here 2005 okay and I guess the
first time I didn't really start to it
stand up to 2008 but I was aware of you
yeah that was when I started here okay
yeah so that that must be why then uh it
feels around the same time and somebody
I remember I know it was Joe stats or
somebody said oh that's leanda she's
super funny and she she's a pimp from
Detroit
which was
intriguing uh and you you referenced
that a little bit I know when you did at
the altercation Comedy Festival thank
you for doing that you killed it and you
referenced some Detroit stuff um car to
care to comment on that a little bit or
just um well it was it was like 20 years
ago I was young and you know it was the
'90s man all my friends was making money
and it was like yo I want to make money
too I want to be out here flossing uhhuh
and then I just kind of fell into the
pimp position you know I was a phone
girl for a couple of years and then the
lady that I was working for retired and
just turned everything over to me and so
you know I had learned everything I knew
all the girls and [ __ ] so you know it
just was what it was it was like you
know I'm like I'm a girl but I'm a pimp
[ __ ] you weren't Corner hustling you
were like you said working for phones
and uh yeah so it was to me it was a job
you know it unfortunately you know the
product was nothing that I could just
give people but uh yeah it was a job so
what did that entail was it like
scheduling and just like what it was
like scheduling so you get weirdos that
would call that be like hi I'm calling
for my sexy
message and it was like massage
[ __ ] it's a sexy
massage and you said being from Detroit
a lot of Auto industry yeah it was a lot
our clientele was mainly the big three
so they were weird and they would just
call every day at lunch they would call
during the Dream Cruise which is like
the big the the Woodward Dream Cruise is
like all these old cars that uh are on
display these people that have taken
care of all their Chevys and stuff and
they would call during the [ __ ] Dream
Cruise like yeah you got anything around
this area like 15 minutes wow that's
quick service that's man go on with your
family go on enjoy the
dream sketchy we'll be here tomorrow
we'll be here tomorrow for you but
profitable at of imagine and kind of fun
like neat that's a you know yeah and the
thing I never met anybody nobody ever
saw me other than the lady that own the
place cuz I never picked up money huh I
was just the voice on the phone the
voice on the phone so when they all
right so this is also the '90s you think
about now like internet like was it back
page how did they get the number What
would did you advertise like what yeah
you pay for ads so like the regular
newspaper used to have those tiny little
classified you know you'd be surprised a
tiny little classified and some
suggested word will had your phone
ringing off the hook and uh this is way
before the internet right you know so it
was all like ads but a clientele hungry
for the service like going to search it
yeah you know and so on the phone cuz
there were tons of services so you know
on the phone you really have to get a
good person personality and convince
these [ __ ] hey you should spend
$60 with this
[ __ ] did you ever have any police sting
type things or sketchy like no because
like I said it was the 90s there was so
much other [ __ ] going on in the D like
like the height of the dope crack
epidemic East Coast West Coast Rap
Battles C Tupac was getting shot at so
it was they wern't thinking about me
right right so how did you get out of it
like what was the Catalyst for like it's
enough well it start the business
started getting slower um really we got
a bunch of
casinos and so the internet was also
coming into play and these girls were
like well I can do it for myself and you
know it was just like well I'm not going
to keep spending money on this [ __ ] I
ain't in it for the lifestyle yeah right
you know I'm starting to lose money so I
just shut the phones off and was like
next
hustle how did did the girls come to you
how did you recruit or whatever like how
so you would have I'm telling you these
people they would call and they'd be
like hi I'm so and so forth I'm in town
looking for a job okay what you look
like right and then they'll tell you a
description cuz they couldn't even text
you a photo they could send a photo so
they would give you a description and
you're like okay well I'll send you one
right and we'll see how that works and
then the person that will get the money
and be like girl her teeth [ __ ] up or
you know oh yeah girl you know go ahead
and keep her
around so so so somebody how did you get
the money somebody would go there and
get you like yeah it was somebody who
would just pick up in the area uh you
know just hold on somebody will be there
to get that for
fascinating so how did you uh parlay
into comedy then uh what made you move
from Detroit to Austin uh there was no
opportunities in Detroit at the time I
knew the city was going down after the
hip-hop mayor got caught up in some
[ __ ] then spent all the money on
hoes and fur coats and I was like I
gotta go and I had been looking at
Austin for two years actually and I was
like no time like the present broke up
with my high school sweetheart and then
like two months later I was here just
bounced I just bounced that's kind of
how we did it too my wife got a job
offer here and we're just like we want
to go somewhere that's warm and not New
York State as far as taxes and just
expense let's go there and we just moved
like we didn't know anybody here either
yeah yeah so it was just like I've been
here almost 13 years yeah yeah so so
what uh a lot of comics especially well
I guess in any City but I was going to
say especially in Austin like a lot of
the the most known ones have very
distinct personality kind of on and off
stage I think you know um what led you
to did you start hitting mics or like
what was the I think I want to try
comedy cuz you're obviously funny and
you're obviously a personality for lack
of a better term you know so I had moved
on to the next Hustle and I had a
magazine and nobody and Austin knew who
I was and I was like well I always kind
of wanted to try comedy maybe I could do
comedy and promote the magazine what
kind of magazine was it so it was called
it was a couple of them there was
virtual politics and then there was
Austin after dark which was about stuff
to do in Austin strictly after dark I
didn't know that was you I remember that
and yeah so it was fun it was a cool
concept that was why I moved here but I
couldn't get any businesses to take me
serious cuz I didn't have anything on
the internet I didn't have an internet
presence so I was like well I'll try
comedy for a bit and then I can meet
people that way and then I'll go ahead
and get with the magazine and then
comedy took off faster than the magazine
did so I got a bunch of equipment in my
house and
[ __ ] that's funny it's funny cuz I ran a
magazine also that's where the
altercation brand was altercation
magazine that's what it started as
that's um yeah magazines are tough all
around um where you remember the first
place you got up in town uh Kick Butt
Coffee oh really like a month after they
opened wild all right cuz I didn't even
I did I did a a benefit of kick butt
earlier last year and that was the first
time I'd ever been there I didn't I was
like this place is [ __ ]
great I am still officially the reigning
kickb comedy Champion oh yeah was from
2008 there a contest there there was a
contest really yeah and like I won like
$500 wor a [ __ ] nice like a bunch of
gift cards and like food and drinks was
it a one night battle or was there like
a round robin it was like a couple of
weeks really yeah it's pretty great so
yeah after that I was like oh yeah I'm
good and and then I thought I was done
with comedy that was it it so what's
kept you kept you
going um it's almost like that mob [ __ ]
where it's like you know you want to get
out and then they give you a little bit
of something dangling in your face and
you like
a I can't turn that down it's a weird
mistress like that cuz there's certainly
times where it's like [ __ ] this and then
there's other exactly that where it's
like well you take a break and then it's
like I've got to get back up right so
that's what been happening every time
I'm like I'm going move on and it's been
[ __ ] eight
years is there a uh I I know a lot of
comics that have won the contest there's
suddenly a thing like well you need to
go to LA or New York now did you get any
of that kind of pting with a stick um
they know not to come to me with that
[ __ ] uh I'm not going nowhere don't
it took me a long time to get to Austin
[ __ ] so no I'm not going to do that I'm
going to stay here plus the industry
comes here exactly that's what I always
tell people are like you need to go to
New York or LA or maybe Chicago I'm like
no you just need to be in in a city that
people have heard of at all right and
maybe tore a bit and like do some
high-profile [ __ ] you don't need to live
in LA unless you want to sitcom but yeah
see and I'm not interested in none of
that me either yeah I like being a comic
um I'll do a couple of like movie
projects every now and again but I love
being a comedian I don't want to write
for anybody else I like writing for me
yeah y so um you're filming all weekend
tonight and tomorrow or uh yeah tonight
and tomorrow night at the Vita room
right yes where uh Louis CK did a drop
in last night yeah I was going to say
something real shady but I'm not oh
please do if he shows up tonight tell
that [ __ ] you get no time oh My
Lou CK better not show up in my show
tonight I would clown the [ __ ] out of
him I don't give a [ __ ] if you got a
show on
Fox I hear jerking off on people
feet yeah I've heard uh I've heard an
interesting backstory about that I'm
just playing louk let me open for you
for
real he's playing I think he sold out I
don't know he's playing the the Moody
Theater which solds I think 2,000 people
I think he so yeah he's there four shows
and he sold at 8,000 tickets in an hour
I think was wow yeah they were like20
and something dollars I want to say well
yeah they they were flipping them I know
uh he's pretty good about keeping the
ticket prices fairly low though his
website I think got for like 45 or
something like that okay yeah that was
somebody probably scalping and [ __ ] that
happens but uh so how did you get hooked
up with Dan and stand up records cuz uh
well see it was dur South by a couple
years ago Lucas mandes um had got me a
spot on uh the stand up record showcase
and he was like I want you to meet Dan
cuz at the time I was real real
frustrated with comedy I was like this
[ __ ] ain't working out wasting my time
and so I got on the Showcase and I
killed it and then Dan was like hey
let's keep in touch we just kind of kept
in touch you know over the the course of
a year year and a half and um yeah just
kind of talked back and forth and then
you know he asked me to come on the
label and I was like yeah I can do that
nice that's awesome so you're doing a
full hour yeah awesome you have a title
in mind are you waiting to yeah I I I
would like to be called imported from
the D what is it imported from the D
imported from the D that's red is there
a uh well like I said when I first heard
of you the pimp thing was the first
thing I heard and also there's a my
buddy Mike Stanley lives out in Detroit
I did Detroit for the first time uh over
the summer and uh to be honest I was a
little intimidated to go there I'm like
I don't know it's got such a tough
exterior but everybody there was red
like it was really fun I don't know I it
is you know they were salty but it's you
know there's the element that's
everywhere um and it just really depends
on where you at you know if you could be
in a there's some parts parts of the D
that's real cool there the parts you
know I don't [ __ ] with yeah you know
especially after dark so it just really
depends yeah I uh I was impressed by
how they they were cuz the show was
packed and great but they were
definitely like all right prove it
[ __ ] like there was a degree of which
as a New Yorker I I respected like that
was pretty pretty rad and actually
remember you posting uh on Facebook I
put a photo up or something like oh it's
right by my uh my uncle but but
seriously don't go to this
neighborhood don't get shot right oh I
posted the Eight Mile sign that's what
it was yeah yeah have you gone back
there to do comedy cuz that's always a
weird thing um I went to do comedy one
time at a mega church what yeah I did a
mega church show with Ricky Smiley who's
Ricky Smiley Ricky Smiley he used to be
one of the hosts I think on Comic View
for a minute and uh he's got a he's got
a morning radio show syndicated he's he
does like a lot of church stuff all
right and uh Ricky and my uncle were
good friends in college they were both
Church musicians so I got to do this
show and yeah my granddad was there and
I was like oh [ __ ] he was sitting up
front he had got a new battery for his
hearing a and everything he was like I'm
hear these jokes well you got to all
right doing a HomeTown show is always G
cuz like I did one in New York about a
year and a half ago and like my entire
extended family showed up and like
people from high school and all that
weird [ __ ] and that's weird enough but
you had to do it in a church like a mega
church what did you do could you do your
act like did um I did a couple like I
got some stuff that's like squeaky clean
and it was just like they laughed you
know they were like oh it's so good and
I was like oh you've never seen my club
at that sounds like the toughest gig in
the world it was but I got up there I
was like O Lord please don't let me drop
no F bombs in the middle of this [ __ ]
Church please steep collapse right so
you haven't gotone back to just do a gig
I don't you know when I go back to
Detroit I don't even I don't even talk
about comedy it's just like it's almost
it's a totally different person you know
I'm just Shonda and I'm just hanging out
with all my people and comedy is like
the ass thing that's where I go to get
away from it yeah that's pretty great
they don't they don't harp on it cuz I
mean comedy for better for worse is a
unique kind of oh that's an interesting
job that you know hey my cousin's a
comic I'm going to bother you about it
at the family reunion you know like yeah
you know we just it's just it's just one
of those things like that's what Shonda
does and she she also pimp people how
refreshing and healthy that's awesome
not that I'm bothered by it but you know
it's going to you know the aunt you
haven't seen in a long time is like so
how's Hollywood and like the perception
that they have of what comedy is yeah my
one Auntie should be like oh you still
doing that little comedy stuff right
like your sketches your little your
little
skits when are you going to be on TV
yeah yeah so you also ran uh for a long
time the um the True Hollywood Story
yeah wear true Tales yeah that was a
really impressive show you did explain a
little bit the concept behind it is I
yeah okay so we're True Hollywood Tales
is a lecture biography series presented
by standup comics about 20th century pop
culture icons that died under tragic or
mysterious circumstances and Comics tell
their story like from the start from the
beginning of childhood on up to how they
ended up dead in the bathtub right and
what what happened along the way why did
he end up Dad in the
bathtub yeah and segmented out like you
did well the one I was involved in was
punk rock stuff so I got to do the story
of GG Allen so thank you for the invite
to that that was red but you've done
like Playboy Centerfolds and boxers
we've done pro wrestlers uh We've also
done country music stars we did Mo we
did a mtown show called it's so cold in
the D and it was we had Jimmy Hof on
that one really yeah can't talk about
Detroit without Jimmy
H have you ever done one focusing on
comedians or is that two inside baseball
yeah we did that one um so it it's so
many of these stories it's really like
we're telling the same story every
show died young yeah it's like they
worked super hard to get to the point
where they finally excelled with their
career and then some they just got out
of control and then just ended up you
know just [ __ ] up burned out such a
unique interesting show cuz you combine
slides and you would really present it
like the work showed a lot uh and what
what kind of gave you the uh the spark
to to decide to do that show I did an
encyclopedia show I want to say in maybe
2010 and it was about uh serial killers
and I had to do the servant girl
Annihilator the what the servant girl
Annihilator murderer it was a it was a
dude in Austin in the 1800s who was like
murdering servant girls oh yeah he's the
the moon Towery guy right or was that I
confusing uh he would like come out with
an ax and Shop people in half so I had
to do that story and it was dark as hell
and they were expecting me to make that
[ __ ] funny
Jesus that's a tough nut to yeah and so
I was able to to take the really dark
stuff and make it fun and interesting
and educational and I was like I would
like to do a show an entire show of
biographies like this but with
celebrities right and so it took me like
I took two years to put it together like
do all the research SE and you know
figure out how I wanted to present it
and yeah yeah it was a rad show um the
the theater unfortunately like
everything good in Austin shut down
always pushed out yeah so we're still
trying to find a new spot um something
that's intimate enough that you know we
can do the show but nothing like bar
type stuff like it's not a bar show
right right yeah I would almost say kick
butt but that's almost in the middle of
you kind of want it darker in that
theery thing
yeah I hope you bring it back it was
really really sure as soon as we find
another venue which I'm actively looking
we'll we'll definitely be back awesome
so what's on the horizon after you uh
film tonight and get everything in the
can um then you know it's going to be
time for me to start getting ready to
give up my crown and Cake was that April
yeah April May bettersweet I know I was
going skip time with I was going to say
just move I was just going to be like
hell no y'all can't get none of this my
cake fool pull a Deo on there
bounce that'd be that'd be pretty
legendary that' be she never came back
right this my
cape well kill it this weekend uh thanks
so much for doing this I'm sorry it took
so long for us to connect like oh no
problem thank you for having me on
absolutely and uh plug your Twitter and
all that good stuff where can people
follow you uh okay so I have a Twitter
but I don't really [ __ ] with it like
that okay oh how refreshing I wish I
couldn't I don't want to you know I'm
afraid of Twitter real why because I see
people [ __ ] up and say the wrong thing
on Twitter and they get their ass handed
to them you know in several pieces yeah
it can be brutal it's uh it's also a
troll magnet in a kind of way so so you
don't do it at all uh I do it every now
and again um I know I get tagged a lot
in shows and stuff like that so if you
want to know what's going on with me you
can follow me at glamgirl 313 see what
shows I got but basically I'm at
Facebook okay yeah see I use Facebook
more too
uh you have website or anything like
that just as far as show uh we true
tales.com is uh the show site and
there'll be some new updates soon that's
got like my listings and stuff on there
so yeah awesome we'll kill it this
weekend and thank you again goodbye
bye and keep that Applause going for
lond
ler oh I'm so glad to see you how you
doing
tonight awesome this is way better than
the last show I did I did a show for
some
nerds it was a convention talking about
the future of
[Music]
Bitcoins I was like Bitcoins what the
[ __ ] is
that let me look on my
phone looked that [ __ ] up and was like
oh hell no uh excuse me before any jokes
get started are y'all trying to pay me
in
Bitcoins cuz if I had a choice between
that and some chuckecheese
[Applause]
tokens I'm [ __ ] with them tokens all
day cuz at least I know they street
value Bor what is that [ __ ] B by 12
Snickers bars and the [ __ ] Magic
Gathering card like
what y'all ain't even on the gold
standard hell
no oh man I got called out for Sledge
shaming last
week
right this what happened so I'm downtown
smoking a cigarette outside with a
friend of mine and we see this girl come
running by without no shirt on so I was
like damn girl if you got your titties
out on a Tuesday
[Laughter]
[ __ ] you going to do with
Friday and my friend was like oh my god
did you just [ __ ] shame that girl Asanda
and I'm like [ __ ] I would
never what's slush sh
aing and then she explained to me that
it was wrong that I had made fun of that
girl's raw ass titties like
that I should have been proud that she
was confident enough in her body to
share s raw tedes with the
public and I'm sitting here like
mhm
mhm and in my my head I'm like see
that's why I even be [ __ ] with white
people on Tuesday
nights always got to be some [ __ ] in
the
game hold on girl let me get this right
are you saying we can't talk about hoes
no
more who said
that the Huffington Post
[Applause]
that sound like something some hoes came
up
with no
M girl hoes make up like 32.4% of my
comedy
material it took me a long time to get
them jokes [ __ ] you can miss me with
68.1% of that
[ __ ] oh man I've been going on a lot
of auditions recently cuz I'm trying to
be famous not cuz I want to be rich I
just want some better [ __ ] to eat that's
all like my idea of making it would be
to be able to drive down I35 with a
plate of stakes and a passenger
seat and just ever so gently reaching
[Applause]
over that's
all I ain't got much I I don't asked for
a
lot I went to this one audition that I
found on backpage.com I should have been
like what the [ __ ] but whatever I was
desperate uh so I go to this audition
and this dude is very excited about
reaching his kick start too and his
project so I'm like okay so he's like
okay so right like this young lady right
here she's going to play your best
friend she's got something very
important to tell you I want your
natural reaction do you have any
questions Eh this ain't really question
more of a
declaration I wouldn't be hanging out
with this [ __ ] in real
life no offense
girl that's why they call it
acting I'm
ready action hey
girl hey girl I have something very
important to tell you oh what's
up I'm
bipolar
damn and the director was like
cut what the hell was
that that was my natural
reaction check this out I'm from
Detroit mtown the murder
Mitten and we don't have cute nicknames
for mental
illnesses either you is
crazy or you crazy than a [ __ ]
like
[Applause]
we don't even need to bring WebMD into
none of
this so he tells me what he looking for
he basically like I'm looking for a big
personality oh you want some ghetto [ __ ]
I got you please forgive my fox
paw let me try that [ __ ] one more
time action
hey girl hey
girl I have something important to tell
you I'm
schizophrenic I [ __ ] knew
it [ __ ] I knew you was
crazy I knew you was crazy when you had
a Bluetooth and that [ __ ] was even
hooked up to a cell
[Applause]
phone I say it to myself this [ __ ] is
off
and the director was like cut get the
[ __ ]
out which is why my ass is back for the
third year in a row in the finals trying
to win this [ __ ] thank you very much
have a good
one
leer and ladies and gentlemen this year
is funniest person in Austin winning
$3,000 in that sweet laptop right there
everybody leanda let w
oh man this is crazy cuz I'm drunk than
a [ __ ] right
now oh man this has been wow this is
crazy as hell I didn't think I was going
to do it I thought I was going to have
to beat up the judges this
year we cool though we cool oh thank you
thank you so much
it has been a very trying year for me um
I suffered kidney failure right after
last year's fpia so I'm on dialysis
right now and this is just so oh man
y'all gonna make me cry I'm A Thug [ __ ]
from Detroit I can't
cry we worked so hard doing this [ __ ]
y'all don't understand we be writing
these [ __ ] jokes and telling them in
front of four people and be like [ __ ]
what you think
like I love my Austin comedy people I
love the [ __ ] out of y'all we work hard
I promise I ain't going to embarrass the
crown of no [ __ ] uh thank you C city
thank you judges thank you Maggie May
girl black girls rock black girls rock
that you Bab I'm going go get [ __ ] up
thank you
Detroit Pimp [ __ ] Detroit Pimp [ __ ]
[Music]