thank you for coming out hanging out
doing it up I love it you're nice and
close those are your toes we're doing it
we're on
vac a man's toes is the ultimate
[Laughter]
vacation oh I've had a weird one I'm so
happy to be here I got to leave where
I'm at right now I find I needed a break
uh this is where my life's at I had a
nurse call me a liar last week that's
something they do now um it was I went
to the doctor and like the nurse was
like filling out my chart and she goes
hey how tall are you and I go
5'7 and she goes are you
sure yeah who lies about 57 dude that's
not a big number like she acted like I
walked in there I was like oh me I'm
62240 like a [ __ ] man like they make
them like men 62 63 I just grew an inch
that's sounds about right that wasn't
what I said I said 5'7 that's a very
reasonable
height and if I were lying how about you
let me have this
one clearly I need this extra inch at
this free clinic today is that too much
to
ask that too
much I think that lady in the third row
is dead I killed her with that joke guys
I killed her
oh so that happened uh last Monday and
then on Wednesday I had my weekly
conversation with my ex to see who's
having a better life you never play that
game with an X it's really fun I
recommend you try it um and she called
me to invite me to her wedding so I
guess she's winning yeah she's a natural
uh it was Weir she called me and she was
like hey Ro I'd love if you came to the
wedding and I was like I don't know if I
can make it and she goes damn it roow
it's my wedding we've known each other
for a long time why just for one night
can't I have my cake and eat it
too uh I don't know maybe because the
cake has feelings ever think of that you
psycho maybe because meeting your
husband isn't the best way to keep the
cake stable like that's an option maybe
the cake might get drug and try to [ __ ]
you on your wedding night that's bad
karma for
everybody nobody likes a drunk cake
wandering around the
wedding trying to tell strangers its
side of the
story We things never worked out we
dated for a while and it was weird
because it was like things never worked
out cuz she was into like she was a fan
of the rough sex
like she was like she was all about it
and I was like I could never get behind
her like she hit too hard like I was
never a big
fan but it was a weird that she was fan
of like that that ex like that rough sex
like the hair pulling and like the
choking like that sort of stuff and I
can't get behind rough sex I've never
been a fan I've always been more of a
fan of staring to your eyes till you beg
me to look away sex like that's my go-to
move it's like we call it the Mona Lisa
where it's like wherever she looks my
eyes just f follow
her some of you love me some of you are
just