[Music]
all right everybody we have um we
generally try to do topical stuff we try
to do stuff that's very recent tonight
we're going to go in a slightly
different direction is that cool is that
all right I know we're branching out a
little bit here people we're taking a
historic look at Salem you know Salem
you know the home of the witch trials
all that stuff exactly this is called
Salem a hasty document let's take a
look Massachusetts
1692 with an Indian War raging nearby
and Rifts forming in a traditionally
uniformed Church hysteria grips the
Puritan town of Salem from Winter until
the summer of this year hundreds face
accus a of
Witchcraft and many innocent people will
be executed you turn one guy into a toad
and and all of a sudden I'm the bad guy
I'm the bad guy the accusations come
from family neighbors friends and Men
about town I did not know she had cast
her lot with Satan not upon first gazing
her as it happens I asked to court her
and finding my wooing
denied that's when I I began to suspect
her of richer he asked me to show him my
ankles my ankles what do I look like a
god Lutheran evidence needed to convict
a woman of Witchcraft was minimal the
important thing is that the accused be
linked back to Satan but this was not
always
easy look I make sexual congress with a
lot of Puritans what am I supposed to
remember every goody and that I lay
under the full moon
Jesus lacking corroboration from The
Lord of Darkness a confidently spoken
rumor would often do the trick I accuse
you of the dark
arts or we'd say I accuse you of being a
witch or I accuse you of witchery or
sometimes just witch witch you know
whatever whatever you feel at the moment
it will be months before the Panic of
the Salem Witch Trials comes to an end
and after that there will be a time of
Sorrow of reflection of
healing but until then each person must
look deep inside themselves and ask
whether they have what it takes to just
make up in
court love getting me some
Pilgrim that was Salem
a hasty documentary done by your friends
at drinking with the big round of
applause for them