[Music]
got Segway
Warriors
hello you w into the bedroom
you're drunk we've done this
before you stumbled over like 3 seconds
later and kick your boots on to the
floor I can see your
eyes how you do how you doing Hannibal
I'm doing great Chris how you doing man
good good so how's the tour so far the
tour has been great anytime you get to
ride a segue
is fun it is one of life's great
experiences you got
it you only want it when you're
drunk my friends say you're
nonous you're not so bad we
you were just in Australia for a little
bit I was in Australia yes that was fun
Australia was a good City it was
exciting to perform there even though
they speak English it's always nice to
go to another country and do stand up
with people mad it's kind of it's kind
of surprising you still oh wow they like
too and then all the way over
here where else have you been in the in
the world you saying like that just I've
been to
Scotland and
Amsterdam and that's it in Canada that
count right ex we wen't hum they are
humans they are humans I have G Canada
give any advice for aspiring stand
comedian you got to go on segue tours
every city you go to that's my
advice that's all I got right perform a
lot go segue tours live life drink a lot
of good juice eat good sandwiches
and everything will work out itself and
and now last question what's your
favorite type of Taco Taco steak
taco take Taco s
shell
[Music]
true morning comes I know how the next
part goes One Last Dance then you delete
me off your
phone in the hallway
you're we can put it back together it's
okay
y seg
stous like knew that it was about to
happen but you can't I know it's like
can't correct yeah you like jumped off
so it was fine like