[Music]
everybody the lacan nooki round of
applause all right now Time Has Come
Today for a new superhero am I
right CU I walking the streets of
Minneapolis there's crime there's famine
there's problems are you guys ready to
be seduced by a new
superhero let's take a look at the big
screen
in a Land of moral gray areas there is a
man who separates it into two tones a
solitary figure trapped in a very dated
genre he wields his innate scab
abilities for the betterment of
mankind to many he is a relic of a
laughable era but to those in need he is
the lone
skanker darn it these naos have lost
their
wow these naos are great thanks lone
skanker an ordinary man who can
transform the mundane into the
spectacular this party rots I don't even
know why I'm friends with you guys
hey it's the Lo Saker
everybody a man whose unbridled Zeal can
lift the spirits of any party
than damn it I dropped my
keys using his power of telescan NIS he
writes wrongs at every SC opportunity
thanks a million loan
skanker help help my baby's done
[Music]
well it's not working skank harder but
in times of dire need when things look
their bleakest and it seems all hope is
lost one man will be there to pick it up
pick it up pick it up it's working it's
working
[Music]
you save my baby thank you bone
stiner he who started as a rude boy to
become a rude man too late to answer his
scaring but not too late to protect the
Meek from the dangers of a scarless
world if you're lost if your ties are
too wide and your horns are too mellow
there is a chance the lone skanker is on
his way
let's call the load skanker
[Music]
in all right everybody that's the load
skanker watch out he might be coming to
a party near
you look it up all right um