I was talking about Chicago.
My other favorite place to do comedy is Eureka,
California and the Redwoods.
I like that s**t. I don't make a lot
of money out there, but I like the trees.
So
people say, you know, the walk
of shame is like when a cool lady has sex with you.
And then in the morning she leaves
and they say That's the W of shame.
That's not the w of shame man. I used to hate that s**t.
Women would come over and they'd be like, I'm leaving.
He's got 10 dogs. It's like, f**k you Jennifer.
You know? Yeah.
Think you're better than me. Hate that s**t.
I didn't have 10 dogs. Okay.
I had two dogs, but every time my dogs had run away,
they'd come back with another dog.
Um, you see what I'm saying?
Eight of those dogs were my dogs'. Dogs.
Um, I try to tell that to Jennifer.
She ain't even listening, you know?
Uh, I'm Sam Miller from Olympia Washington.
Greatest town in the world.
All right. So you say it's the greatest town in the world.
Is that just fluffy, I mean, really?
Mm-Hmm. No, I've been everywhere man.
And I keep coming back to Olympia
'cause that's where my wife is.
Yeah. And my kids. That makes sense. Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I just love it. 'cause in Olympia I have one of everything.
You know I have a barber, I have a mechanic,
like all these beautiful people.
I hang out with a lot of musicians. I hang out with a lot.
I hang out with some poets, some painters
and a couple comedians.
Uh, and I'm very lucky.
Tell me about your first album. What's
This? Oh, first album,
first album's called Round Trip.
Recorded it at the Capitol Theater in um, April of 2023.
So recorded it almost a year ago now.
Um, or more than,
I don't even know, maybe it was more than a year.
I can't tell. I don't know how time works.
There's been a few moments in my life
where I've had real clarity
and one of those moments was watching Cops in jail
and giving these guys advice on TV
and realizing that I am in no place
to be given this man advice,
Considering my current predicament there.
And dude, man, yeah, I'm really proud of it.
It was funny, I was just hanging out with Dan, um,
the CEO deep guy and uh, we've become really good friends
and he was talking about some other comic
who says they hate their first album.
And I asked him if I was like,
do you think I'm gonna hate my first album?
And he goes, maybe someday.
But, um, I don't know if I'm gonna get that or not
because I'm really proud of that album.
I think it's pretty good. So I like, it's got a good arc
to it and it's got good jokes
and it's got solid laughs throughout
and I think I make some decent points here
or there without trying to, you know. Yeah.
And tell me about, you know, I mean since it was your
first album, you had your whole lifetime to write it.
What parts of your life definitely pop out of
The album? I mean, you're gonna
hear a lot, uh, homelessness,
incarceration, um, that's what I like to write about.
My, one of my favorite people in the world.
This dude named Gabe Rutledge, great comedian, you know,
he is also an Olympia, he told me a long time ago.
He is like, the best way to do standup is to talk about
what makes you laugh and then just
invite other people along.
And like, that's the s**t that me and my friends joke about.
We joke about crazy s**t. We joke about being locked up.
We joke about living outside
'cause it, that's the only way I could survive that.
And that's how I survived that.
Fans are also people that have been through a lot
of hard s**t and I don't, and I, I love them man.
It's, it's awesome. I get cool
messages from people all the time.
Standup doesn't have a monopoly on humor.
And um, to me humor is survival.
So like I was funny before I did standup
and I'd be funny if I stopped doing standup
'cause funny's funny, I'm a funny dude.
And then she told me that the CPAP machine I needed is
$1,500.
So I'm just waiting to die.
Like, I like my life, but I don't $1,500 like it.
God damn, that's a lot of money.
You can get a 2003 Kia Spectra of 1500 bucks.
I know. 'cause I bought a 2003 Kia Spectra.
Everybody's like, that's very specific. Yeah.
Some of these aren't jokes.
Touch a moment on how social media has affected
The game. Yeah, yeah.
Well,
people can think whatever they want about social
media and standup comedy.
I love this question 'cause it's interesting to me.
'cause I used to not like it. I was like,
I'll just be really funny and then somebody else will figure
that part out for me.
But that's just not the way the industry is anymore.
Like basically nobody's coming for anybody.
And uh, it's not about how funny you are.
It's, it's, it's how well how many people.
You can show how funny you are too.
And it's, people could be like, oh, that's, that's weird.
But I mean there used to be a lot of kiss asses
that would work comedy clubs
and probably get spots they didn't deserve.
'cause it used to be the comedy clubs put you in front
of the people, but now it's more like the people put you in
front of the comedy clubs, you know?
And I try to just stay genuine. That's what it is, man.
Honestly, it's just like on stage.
It's like the minute you start doing an
impression of yourself, you're f****d.
I see comics do that all the time and I see it online.
I see it in person where they're like, this is
what it would be like if I did standup comedy as opposed
to just coming up on stage and being funny.
I didn't, this wasn't like a plan.
Other people told me I should try it.
And now like in a lot of ways, like I love my life.
I'm like 53% happy. I used to only be about 51.
Now I'm probably like 53% happy. That's great.
And that's pretty good for a guy like me know.
So do your friends that told you
to get into comedy ever ring you up
and go, I would like a piece of that
Now? No, they
can kick rocks.
Alright, So what's kick for Sam?
Uh, you mean big picture or a little picture? Both.
Surprise me, man. Alright. Little picture.
I'm going to Eau Claire tomorrow. Big
Picture. Then,
Uh, I'm going to Chicago in a couple weeks.
Getting ready to do record two. Uh, my kids are growing up.
I have a, my family is generally like happy and healthy.
Um, I'm in the unknown, unknown.
Um, I never knew that I could have a life like this.
And, uh, I get to live it.
And people, the fact that people like
what I'm doing on stage and off stage
and like you're talking about like, people
that like my writing, I'm working on a book right now
with Pat Moriarty, um, who did my album art.
He was in Mad Magazine, all that.
I get to f**k with some really talented people, including
s**t heads like you and.