[Applause]
I'm trying to talk my mother into being
a suicide bomber right
now
well
seriously I mean cuz she fits the
profile she's terminally
ill basically it hasn't been diagnosed
but she's she's been chain smoking cool
mild 100s for 48 years she couldn't walk
up onto this stage without coughing up
chunks of green [ __ ] all over your
nachos like some kind of respiratory
Gallagher
event and she's miserable she really is
a miserable angry person I moved her and
her seven cats got them a one-bedroom
apartment in Hollywood and all she's
done in the last six years is sit in
that apartment and farm cats and and
chain smok and [ __ ]
it's down to three cats now with one
kind of teetering on the fence they just
sit there in her apartment and the
secondhand smoke she won't even let them
outside have a decent chance of chucking
themselves under a bus Tire to [ __ ]
end it all right they know they it's too
dangerous on the street they keep the
cats in so they say breathe a secondhand
smoke and then it turns into third hand
smoke fourth hand smoke that's the cats
they're like furry air filters that's
all they all they are and they're not
even furry cuz they're they're all
greasy with nicotine like old curtains
and they and they die right in front of
her and she she's just a hateful angry
just hates every she hates the traffic
and she hates the neighbors and God damn
she hates you and she hates just hates
she's like me without jokes she's just
hateful and she's suicidal I mean in a
logical sense like it's not a desperate
I can't go on another day and she's
suicidal in that way she knows that days
coming when when the lung tumors get
bigger than the breast implants she's
going to cash out she's not she's not a
woman who wants to die with a lot of
tubes going in and out of her milking
off the state yeah she's going to cash
out but instead of giving her the big
bottle of Xanax and the quart of vodka
like my brother and I have planned for
for the last few
years why not instead seriously rig her
up with some heavy explosives and have
her take out some [ __ ] we all hate on
our way out nothing with a political
agenda like the terrorists of today oh
this will solve Middle East peace Kaboom
no just take out some [ __ ] that we all
hate some personal pet peeve that's an
irrit have take out a DUI roadblock or a
Ashton Kutcher or something that's an
irritant to everybody something no one
would complain
about did you ever eat a Subway
breakfast sandwich
it's a damn good sandwich is it CU it
comes on the same bun it's the regular
deli style bun that all the other
sandwiches every fast food place has to
put their breakfast sandwiches on
something crazy it's on a mixed pancake
or you know it's a Lecky Quant or wacky
biscuit but the someway you can put it
on a regular bun and it comes you can
put vegetables on it so it gives you the
illusion that it's good for you and I
love the placebo effect I'm a sucker for
it but you can't get it after
11:00 I can sleep till 1: or 9 at night
depending on what narcotics are still
floating around in my system
right but I still try to get the
breakfast sandwich and I'll go in hey
come on give me an egg and cheese and
the kid will say I'm sorry sir uh it's
after 11: we put all that stuff
away you didn't put it away it's in the
second green cabinet it's right there
come on this place is as big as a photo
mat there is no away in the building you
don't own a away there's no Brinks truck
that pulls up at 11:02 and Yanks out the
eggs under armed guard and and you just
you just programmed to do this so I
don't want to give them
[ __ ] the entire breakfast menu at Subway
consists of nothing but the egg it's all
the same sandwiches they serve all day
long plus an egg you you don't have to
fire up the griddle for the flap Jacks
and
it's not a process like other
restaurants who really do have to stop
at 11: because they have a real [ __ ]
menu but you don't you're just stealing
their rule for no reason it doesn't make
sense and I don't want to be a dick to
you
but it's not even a real [ __ ] egg man
this is a this is a prepackaged egg
likee Patty product that sits in a stack
of egg patties in the second green
cabinet it's right next to the bacon
that you serve all day if I order a BLT
right now I'll see the away egg sit
right next to I see the egg on away and
I don't want to give you [ __ ] I'm gonna
give you one more opportunity think this
through please just give me an egg and
cheese and the kid's going to say I'm
sorry sir and I'm going to say no this
time I'm sorry
mother and
mother mother will come trudging in in a
ratty terry cloth bathrobe with E4
explosives strapped head to toe cool
mild 100 in one hand dead cat in the
other like Gale sers or a Heisman Trophy
plunger and she's going to say goodbye
[Applause]
Bo and now terrorism has worked as a
positive for