[Music]
now we have uh a guy who's on the show
every now and again he's always been a
bit of a bit character um a small bit
character but recently he went on a
vacation and brought some of uh some
footage with him oh and everybody uh
rousing Round of Applause for Steve the
furry guy
[Applause]
all right so uh so Steve uh what brings
you our way today well uh you're
interrupting a good thing I got going on
man sorry about that I hate to [ __ ]
block excellent very good very
good recently uh just went down to New
Orleans and I had a little of a uh
little sort of a vacation there for
business too uh they're in the big over
easy and uh did a little video diary
sort of thing that I'd like to show you
guys that's that's really cool I was
down in New Orleans not too long ago
myself all right let's take a look at
this video
[Music]
diary how's it going Steve Combs here
AKA fog horn Third Leg Horn chilling
here on Bourbon Street in New Orleans
man hoping to find some breasts and
thighs let's do it yeah uh I do furry
pornography oh
ouch well sometimes yeah but I I got
that surgery it's a little smaller now
so what what are you doing out here I'm
letting you know it's time to get
serious about God and you know stop
wearing a chicken outfit what do you
think of the Jesus
people um I think they're pretty good oh
yeah you're going to go see live
sex I didn't say I was going to see live
SE oh no you you're just standing out
front you're about to go in it's not
actually going in that is not what I did
I asked you was it actually live SE oh I
have no idea I wouldn't go in there so
do you watch furry pornography very
often furry yeah what's furry
pornography uh well basically uh you get
up and uh uh you you dress up like the
way you feel on the inside like this and
you just bang each other's brains out
really yeah it's very excellent so you
feel like a
[ __ ] yeah well the real question is do
you feel like a [ __ ] I do all right
let's go oh man I wish I knew I could
find some young chicks you know there's
some sort of place I could go that'd be
nice uh not finding it yet not uh whole
lot of not Big Easy here so far I don't
know we'll see how'd you get those beads
come across him
honestly I had to do what I had to do to
get
[Music]
him oh yeah do you want some beads I
won't make you motorboat all right but I
will need to see the
[Music]
rack yeah the Truffle Shuffle man come
on let's go yeah how's it going guys
good like a mother that's where you want
to be right here going wild
absolutely you get a pearl necklace my
friend see what most people would think
what I'm doing is a little weird now to
lunch this guy's like out to brunch
breakfast and lunch
together I do make a hearty meal now I
don't make a hearty meal is this for me
yeah
all let your teeth get
[Music]
it you need Jesus that's not a drink
it's not an LSD hit Jesus the king of
kings and Lord of lords I've heard of
him you need to know him no longer how I
know how I live I know I stay alive I
got all my life to live and I got all my
life to give a minute ago you said that
you're in the porn industry I'd say
that's not normal you're not supposed to
put your penis in just any vagina I'd
say that's a little freaky we wash them
first oh you're go to your man go
[Applause]
chick it pass the [ __ ]
out he's going to hell I'm going to hell
and we're having a great time doing it
right here B easy all right let's go