all drugs should be
legal there we go me and that
guy
yeah me and you we're making policy
tonight
bud here's the rule though right I feel
like you got to have some regulations
here's mine no drugs until you hit
30 after 30 you get to do whatever you
want and I know I'm conveniently in my
30s right now I understand
that but I was terrible at partying in
my 20s I think most people in their 20s
are [ __ ] awful at it you just don't
respect drugs you got to respect you're
too Invincible in your 20s see what I
mean like you got to [ __ ] you know
and you learn how to party you learn how
to keep it together when you get in your
30s because then you have to party in
front of your friend's kids all the time
you
are partying in front of children
constantly and that's why we don't see
us bin drinking ourselves to death we're
not doing beer bombs and K stands and
[ __ ] no we tell everybody we're going to
go refill the snack bowl and then we
sneak off into the kitchen and eat
psychedelic mushrooms like an
adult and then we play with your kids
and your kids have never had a playmate
like that before you are an unbelievable
Playmate they're like this adults off
the [ __ ]
chain oh we're having a tea party yeah
we're having a [ __ ] tea party this is
going to be the most amazing tea party
this little girl's ever seen
you get like an accent going you got
characters and costume
changes oh my tea is a bit
bitter can I have some sugar for my tea
please and then your buddy walks in
you're like are you interrupting the
princess during her tea time off with
your head and you grab that kid's father
and you drag him out into the whole
front of the whole party in the backyard
and you tie him up to that chopping
block right and then this is where you
get your executioner costume on you take
your shirt off leather pants leather
Hood eyeholes cut out and you get in
that shed and you grab that axe cuz it's
playtime godamn it and you get that axe
over your head you don't cut a head off
but if you take it as far as you can and
if that little girl's crying you've done
a hell of a job
[Applause]