I always wanted to be an artist when I
was a kid but I I just lacked the uh
confidence early on to go for it and
living in this city and being under the
influence of how cool this town is I
really decided to go for it and become
an artist and make my living at Art and
um that was that was my big defining
[Music]
moment I never felt like I fit in
anywhere I was always like an odd duck
in the
[Music]
pond as soon as I discovered Austin I
felt at home immediately and then when I
moved here I always kind of likened
Austin to like the uh the island of the
misfit toys you know it's like this is
the the land of the Misfits where all
the Misfits come and where they all fit
in
together I'd probably be the the saddest
diesel mechanic in Houston if if there
wasn't an
Austin the American neon sign is unlike
any other neon sign anywhere in the
world some of the First cartoons that
anyone ever saw was actually neon signs
that were animated they'd never seen
cartoon images in motion
before in college I just really started
falling in love with the glow of neon
the gra Graphics behind it and the
weathering of it and how they reflected
the American Spirit of the 20th century
you know they're they're just big
audacious you know over-the-top graphic
images with dancing tacos or whatever
you know and I just I just more and more
fell in love with
[Music]
it the proudest thing that I could say
about my professional life is that I
make my living at Art I feed my family
by being an artist and and that's like
the ultimate in living this life to me
is actually making a living by creating
things out of my imagination and being
an artist it it's it's the most it's the
scariest and most amazing awesome
feeling in the world to take that leap
and scare the hell out of
yourself if you're living your life
where you scare yourself a lot that's
really living you know a lot of people
live like if they play the safe bank and
don't color outside the lines that
they're going to live forever and you're
going to die anyway whether you take the
chances or not you're still not getting
out of here alive so you might as well
scare the crap out of yourself and do
things that really are important to
[Music]
you I could not imagine myself doing
anything else in fact if I uh just
inherited a million dollars tomorrow I'd
come into work there's no way I'd ever
do anything else besides this I can't
this is what I love to do this is what
my life work is and I feel a a sense of
responsibility to uncover all of the old
neon technology and apply it to my art
and that's that's what I'm going to do
in my
life I want to make art that when you
die your kids fight over it you know I
mean I want something that that that
lives a lot longer than
me my dad always told us whatever you do
try to be the best at it and I feel like
I am the best at what I do creating
vintage style neon signs as fine art