nice home isn't it probably a lot like
your own but it does have a few problems
it's got comedians hey you know how I
know my dinner's ready those smoke alarm
goes off hey I know you're out there I
can hear you brushing your teeth
extermin X is the area's number one
comedian control service our qualified
servicemen use the most proven
techniques which are safe for your home
and family from the common expulsive
complainer is this m on I don't know
about you guys but I look at it donut
right to my
head to the self assured
hyperactive keep the tip so for
controlling comedic pests in your home
call the experts call Terminex at 55500
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
and welcome once again to tight line um
tonight tit line is brought to you by
hamburger chicken it tastes like
hamburger but it's just chicken and also
by crackling nut crud bread you'll love
it it's crud today we have an
interesting and timely show for you um
we have a uh a defense expert from the
feminine defense systems company her
name is Betty vessel and she has joined
us today in the Studio to talk about um
weapons for um for people to use to
protect themselves thank you for coming
thank you Dr
sphincter well we we're all aware of the
uh the recent attacks which have taken
place in the metro area and of the
concerned citizens and we were going to
uh take a look at uh what um her company
has to offer in the way of Defense
systems for personal defense yes I uh
chose a couple of items that uh
conveniently fit into to a person's uh
purse so that uh okay well let's take a
look at some of the um weapons that u m
Mrs uh vessel has brought with
us well yes the first one that I brought
could we get a close-up of this yes um
first one is
uh uh one might think this was a tube of
lipstick or perhaps a keychain see that
or perhaps a bottle opener yes
but conveniently we've disguised uh my
company and I have disguised a small
bottle of Mace this is Mace this is Mace
yes as you can see it it has a um a pen
latch here just I just be careful yes it
it has a pen latch here which you can
use and you can fit inside your pocket
much like um much like any any normal
pen in a pocket liner so say that uh
later on we will be having a
demonstration of both of the products
yes um Mrs vessel will Mrs vessel and I
will be demonstrating how to how to use
this and another product which her
company carries called a stun gun yes
and we will be demonstrating both of
these items and how to use them for so
you can see at home what is the best way
and it is an actual demonstration this
yes yes an actual demonstration uh to
show how a a woman can protect herself
mhm against uh uh any sort of attack
from anyone specifically men
specifically men I have uh researched
this yes and have noticed that most
attacks on women are from men really yes
um generally your age group where have
where have you gotten this data where
have you where have you come up with
this hypothesis well uh I have
researched it in Rock Creek and out of
the four attacks that have been there in
the past 3 years they were all done uh
by men on women yes and so I felt that
it was my Dy what was the evidence that
they' hadd been attacked by
men there was uh one Polaroid picture
the uh other victim had uh after well
you know those can be
doctored and we'll be right back after
this word we'll be right back
hey woke up to have my toes this morning
and the first thing that I knew there
were sticks and mud and honey and a bowl
of orange Pips too and the sound pour in
like butterscotch and stuck to all that
n
crud oh won't you stay we'll have some
veggies and hay wrapped in Crunch and
crackling nut CR
[Music]
hello and welcome back to tight line uh
tonight we have Betty vesso yes who is a
um you you work for the fds corporation
feminine defense systems I am uh well
their their corporate uh vice president
really who manages the company that you
work for uh uh my mother yes yes you
have a mother you have your mother
running the company my mother's running
the company it's a family family uh you
know what I am a little bit tired of is
all this nepotism that's going on in
this country your your uncle owns the
company and your you said your mother is
running it and she's the the president
and I must say what really a little sick
and tired netism that's going on I think
that's a woman is the president of the
please listen to me for just one minute
I think that's part of the reason why
there are so many problems with this
country people are just being lazy
they're not trying to do anything new
they're just taking it easy and they're
just um not not doing anything
new their mother or
father not hearing you I can't hear you
runs a corporation they just they they
they choose would you excuse me please
would you please stop singing um I'm
trying to make a
point would you please stop that please
stop will you stop I'm sorry anyway I'm
trying to we're trying to discuss um
weapons weapons yes I would love to talk
about that well let's talk about weapons
now all
right what weapons the mace and the stun
gun the stun gun the stun gun how much
do they cost the stun gun is very
reasonably priced at $ 59.77 well that's
absolutely ridiculous $59 for it's a the
most simplest piece of electronic
circuitry I've ever seen I I took one
apart before the show it's simply two
electrodes and a a small circuit breaker
and a transistor that boosts the power
of the battery and it the voltage and
you're charging $60 for that I have my
own stun gun available now it's coming
on the market a Spiner stun gun for only
$30 I don't see what anyone needs to
spend $60 for a um a simple piece of
electronic equipment uh you can pick the
parts up at any store like Radio Shack
or Acme for a very modest cost and the
mace as far as the mace goes that's uh
very simple chemical compound which you
can find in any chemical supply store um
the chemicals are uh if if you write to
me I can send you the chemical uh makeup
of Mace just send a letter to Dr
sphincter and I'll send you the uh
chemical equation anyone want to know
the chemical makeup of Mace because so
they can make it themselves I make mace
on a daily basis want to why would
anyone want to make mace because it's a
it's a protectant you can put mace on
vinyl and other um products and it's a
very good protectant much better than
Armor All I found and it's uh quite it's
a very easy product to make um and and
you can also sell it which I do I sell
mace out of my basement um and anyone
can make it it's very simple and for you
to come on and say that you have these
products and they're that expensive it's
uh I don't know it's um you're just
making it in your basement also and
you're you're charging very high prices
well I'm very sorry um we'll have to go
to uh a break now and we will be back
with a uh a short uh brief demonstration
of these products and um we we will be
back to show you exactly how these
products
work thank
you Dr
sphincter has a
date with death
a golf
[Music]
date the seventh
green don't miss
it
THS hello and um here we are we're going
to uh demonstrate the effectiveness of
these new uh weapon tools from the
feminine defense Systems Corporation um
I would like to uh change um thank
you thank you very
much
oops if you could um explain to our
viewers certainly um I will be
pretending that I am on a uh Street
Corner any Street Corner in a big city
waiting for a bus and uh the doctor here
will be acting as an uh villain and will
be chasing me or trying to attack me and
I will then reach into my purse and very
easily pull out uh one of these several
instruments one of the several feminine
defense systems that I have in my purse
and show you how quickly and easily Dr
sphincter can be
stopped okay well that sounds good let
me just get this zipped up here okay
I'll just be on waiting for the
bus okay darn this
thing the bus what I lost my
microphone
sorry just uh keep keep going I'll be uh
standing here waiting for the uh
21 21A yes and I will I will attempt to
um be a an
attacker this is the uh
demonstration how does this go on does
this look good scary okay and I will um
demonstrate by holding a knife at her
and which point she will stun me to um
uh to illustrate how effective these
weapons can be against a potential
attacker yes knives are often used
against women one of the most common
weapons and this is a this is a real
demonstration this is not a this will
actually happen this this is a real
demonstration this is not a a uh these
are not
actors here I am waiting for the
best oh oh oh you now you want it come
on oh my give it to me you don't look
like a very friendly person to
me I'm S Walk come on
that was easy
enough completely completely rendered
helpless
oh
oh God
ah
[Laughter]
ah stop
[Music]
C
sorry I guess they really do work
feeling day you don't feel good
doc yeah my father got some of that he
kind of had that same you know that same
look that's not good you don't want
maybe that's one of the side effects I
think that's a side effect on
there
oh this doesn't look good I hope I hope
you're not going to sue the company take
it easy you relax a bit just shaking all
over you know you let it get to
youly glad I signed that waiver before
the
show this is not my fault not my doing
how you uh how you doing there
you and the music out music
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]