[Music]
it's time for fishing on the water
America's favorite fishing show
with your host alltime All-American
fishing Champion Billy
desan this week mission on the water
takes us to the industrial waterways of
the Great Northwest
[Music]
fishing along with Billy today is Dr
spinter so join Billy and the doctor for
a funfilled day of fishing on the water
coming soon
[Music]
called
compens
[Music]
hello and uh welcome welcome once again
tight line uh in our uh second season
now uh wa watch us um just look at us
now
um um to tonight Thailand is brought to
you by a dry socket um if something gets
wet don't drop it dry
socket
um tonight we have a very special show
for you tonight uh we have a software
professional and Doctor uh Wayne bunx
who uh who has developed a uh very
interesting and uh useful uh software
package called mind
prober and uh we're going to demonstrate
uh the uh the software package tonight
on the show and we're going to do a
little demonstration of uh of me and
we'll see how the program works thank
you for coming yes I'm very very glad to
be here and I want to thank you for
having me oh thank you um You' already
enjoyed the brief talk that we've had
yes yes um uh so so tell us U be before
we get into the actual demonstration uh
Dr bunx um what uh how long have you
been working on uh software
packages well this is my first one
actually I used to just write this by
hand but I had a friend uh describe it
and show me how to use it and I've just
recently bought this computer uhhuh uh
yes this is a this is a very very uh
useful uh uh machine uh Macintosh you
someday I hope to know how to use it I I
see that's a funny joke um uh so so you
uh did you actually develop the software
you you developed the software for uh I
figured out what to write down and then
they wrote it down for me they put it on
the software and they showed me how to
well on the the floppy disc they they
what language Square thing what what
language were they using in uh
developing this no uh the the uh the
computer language what what uh what what
uh Co what code was
it um well the the one with English
words where no no what what computer
what programming language was it oh I
see uh basic maybe I I'm not sure what
what what language is they used basic
I'm not sure I don't know that's the
only one that I ever used I remember in
second grade I was first introduced to
the computer and I I used basic at that
point I don't know what so you you you
uh you you program only in basic then
I'm not really sure what I program in I
didn't really program this I just made
up the test oh so you you um you you
simply uh designed the uh the uh the
test itself you weren't involved with
the writing of the software uh no I
wasn't someone else figured that out for
me and has showned me how to use this so
I'm I'm learning a lot and it's a an
it's an exciting phase I thought that
you I thought that you had actually been
uh been uh the the initial software
developer for the uh and uh someone
someone had come to you with uh well I I
thought you that you had done the the
whole thing that you um uh had written
the the the software well as I explained
I I'm not I wrote it so you uh and and
you know just a little bit of
basic uh you that's what it is you you
don't even know what language they used
I'm not for sure no I'm not sure I
should I should have that explain that
to me and I'm sure that I will that's
something that I'd like to learn all
about uhhuh well that's good that you
that that you want to learn yeah that
that's uh that's that's anyway we were
going to take this test well um uh let's
uh what what uh what what school did you
go to um our our uh did you go to a a
technical institute well I went to the
open school in R open School California
mhm and is there actually a school
called the open school the open school
we could design our programs I was I was
into non-traditional education at that
point
open why would they name a school
open should we had the freedom to
develop our closed in and and structured
and not open well actually I rebelled
against that I really really found that
confining and and it instilled a lot of
spiritual uh trouble in me to be in a
really
confining situation that that encouraged
Conformity and well it the the the whole
reason for school is is to uh establish
a uh uh something to conform too I think
um that's I've never I've never met
anyone who who really felt that way well
it um you so you went to the open school
that was in high school yes high school
that age high school was open open and
then so what was elementary school was
Elementary School uh uh easygoing all
over the place it was Redlands Sky View
Sky View elementary mhm it was it in a a
big big open building were these both
big wide rambling uh you know regular
regular old uh built in the early 60s
kind SCH yeah um well I I I I wasn't
well yes let's we can go on with a test
now if uh if you'd like um you're
disturbed about something there's
something well um I I didn't I I had no
idea that you weren't actually the the
the software developer on this you're
disappointed and that you went to school
called the open I don't know um uh what
our viewers would think um uh you know
someone going to to a place called The
open school I'm sure a lot of your
viewers went to an open school as well
there's one right here oh there is
there's several all over the country
it's an idea that really took root when
the non-traditional ways of learning
were first being espoused in the' 60s
well okay now let's not get into that
let's let's take a look at uh uh the
program the program is not open and uh
we can control somewhat uh the the
program is structured yes it is yes it's
a simple agree disagree format and then
after answering several things will come
up with a character profile that's very
good yes um so we can sort of uh skip
the first uh portion of the show because
uh we weren't actually looking at the
program um okay there ding there it goes
um okay now let's uh uh load up uh load
up the program and and uh we'll begin
okay um let's just uh get that no that's
um that's you you put yeah um to
Macintosh yes the arrow whoops I believe
that you you you you put that on on the
on the table I don't I don't I don't
what are you doing I'm move see when I
roll this ball it moves the arrow well
no that's that's you're supposed to that
is supposed to be placed firmly on top
of the the the surface there and then
you move I know that's called a for me
to do it that way I can't get the
perspective to move it around it's very
difficult for me to do that well I I I'm
I I I haven't used this computer very
much either I am currently a beta test
site for a cray 3 but but I do know that
I do know what a mouse is and I do know
the right way to use a mouse is to put
it firmly on top of the table to the
computer it's much easier for me to use
it this way but I will I will put it it
down if it will make you feel more
comfortable well I'm just trying I'm
just trying to I'm not talking about
feeling I'm not I'm not trying to to
make myself more comfortable I'm just
trying to to inform you the right way to
do it well and as the right way to do it
to put it on way I'm aware of the right
way okay start the program go ahead
okay mind prober yes that's what we're
going to be doing that's that's
it it should uh should work well it's
your program I wouldn't be surprised if
it didn't
work are you having some problems well
it should go on I I uh how long have you
had this computer I I've just I've just
uh started using this recently oh really
mhm I see I used you Haven taken you
haven't taken the time to learn how to
use the your it's kind of embarrassing
but see I set myself up for that I I
took a risk I wanted to learn by using
handson and so you you just you you
neglected to to study up on the material
you just you're just letting
unfortunately I that's true see this is
a problem that we're having that many
people I think are having in this
country we're not taking the time to
read and reread
directions um directions are not put
there um for for the someone to to be
happy directions and instructions are
there for us to read and to understand
the the equipment we're using or else we
get into these situations um like like
Dr uh bun wax is he's he's completely
well it's starting now but he was
completely confused I was pushing the
button I was doing everything that I was
told to do it just for some reason took
a
little little adjustment well it's
everything's okay now though okay now
let's uh let's uh let's that's so
embarrassing I can't believe how I feel
it's it's uh it's embarrassing I was
embarrassed so what well at least you
were embarrassed at least I was
embarrassed and I'm acknowledging my
feelings now and I think that that's you
know where you were speaking about what
people should be doing these days and I
you feel better now that for us you were
embarrassed you feel better about it now
okay are you done talking cuz I was not
quite finished with what I say I'm just
trying to to explain cuz sometimes our
viewers don't quite understand what's
happening maybe it's because you don't
let the guests get everything out that
they were saying well let's let's let's
just as a helpful start the test let's
start the test let's
go okay oh I think you want to put the
little arrow up to where it says file oh
okay and I just can't do let me do it
see you want to do this see I've studied
this program you haven't even looked at
it yourself well it's your own program
just roll the ball with my finger and
have no problem with it well you can't
just roll the ball you have to use it
the right way it's hard for me to do
okay first initial
D what what is your name by the way do D
okay capital D capital
D okay and then we'll go on to the
second initial second
initial gee this is so hard to do it
this way well it's hard to do it when
you don't know how to do it I can't
believe that that that that this is your
own well now you're supposed to click on
the second box see now you you you you
made an error s s s yes you have full of
s's in the first box and that's not back
no you have to backspace it see now
here's the D okay and here's the S this
is where the S goes you put them out oh
you you put well sometimes when we do
things really hastily and with a lot of
anger we tend to make it worse well
sometimes when we just sit back and let
things happen nothing happens at all and
we just we just don't we don't care
what's going on and and we make errors
we have to be uh constantly um
questioning and and uh probing and
that's why that's why I chose to have
you on the show because I thought you
wanted to probe okay you're very
aggressive thank you thank
you all right tative let's say
yes I would say that you're very
talkative okay I would agree yes I get
that arrow in there I I am I would I
would agree that that I am talkative yes
I would say you're egotistic well wait a
minute I would say so it's not a bad
thing well it's not egotistic no it's
this is my this is my test this isn't
your test this isn't what you would say
so it's what what I would say I'm
telling you that I'm not egotistic if
you would like an accurate portrayal and
and well that's what I want I want an
accurate portrayal then I would say that
you're egotistic no it's not what you
would say it's what I'm telling you you
see this is your ego speaking right now
no this is me speaking
I'm telling you to well well I'll just
do the whole thing myself if you're
going to be like this I'm just you know
I'm dealing with my own Impressions and
no see okay okay I don't you fine how
can you you you can't you can't tell me
the way I am you you you know if if you
don't want to learn
anything you're just going to I mean
it's you don't even know what you're
doing really do you I would say no
apprehensive you seem apprehensive your
body is full of apprehensive well yes I
am apprehensive that's very good
someone's got to be apprehensive you
certainly aren't if you're just letting
it things yes I'm
conventional is is insulting me making
you feel I'm not trying to insult you
I'm just trying to point out your own
problems cuz you you you had a
difficulty pyal you had a difficulty
before and you realized what it was and
you were embarrassed and you were much
happier after you were embarrassed I'm
just trying to help you okay rigid no no
I no that's not
right I am
kind okay this is your test we'll just
this is yes this is my test this isn't
your test if you say that you're kind
I'm just letting you use the mouse
because it's your computer rigid yes
otherwise I i' do it myself if it were
my computer well actually I wouldn't
even use a Macintosh I'd use my my my
cray but um no no you have to do it like
this you keep you keep I'm telling it's
much faster more efficient it's much
easier for me to just hold the
ball put down here and move it see you
see if I if I try to do it like this
look it it's not getting anywhere okay
I'm getting very angry my feelings are
really welling up right now and I would
like you to do it yourself well thank
you very
much but I still would like to have some
say I wouldn't say sympathetic or well
it's my test isn't it it's not your test
if you okay if you want this to be
inaccurate um although of course you
know maybe if you maybe you are right
maybe this is just a really high
pressured situation for you and well
this is a TV show and of course if you
are high press if you are you expect it
not to be high pressure well of course
not did you expect to just come on here
and just to to sit back and relax and
talk about the good old days at the open
school and and to bring on something
that you don't you didn't even know how
to use how could you come on with a a
piece of Machinery that you're claiming
not only claiming to to be the author of
but you don't know how to use it and I I
think that that's very um that's very
strange do you want me to answer these
questions or are you just going to keep
talking well yes I'd like you to answer
these questions
okay I'm
vulnerable I'm learning
I'm a fragile person well we're all
learning I'm in a process you're you're
not I'm learning how to use Ma you're
nothing special I mean because I don't
know how to use a machine doesn't mean
that I'm not going to present well no
I'm not saying that there's anything
wrong with that but what I'm saying is
that to to to claim to write and and and
to to be the originator of something and
and then to come on national television
and then not know what you're doing I
mean you're it's I I am I am uh I I
guess I am upset because you're you're
ruining the the Integrity of my show
which is not which is no surprise to me
now I mean this this is no surprise I'm
sorry we're we're trying to run a very
tight ship here as as you would probably
imagine okay and um okay I'm sorry okay
okay now we can go on okay let's go on
great let's
Okay um quiet um I wouldn't say I'm
quiet um uh sarcastic no um concerned
yes very much I'm very concerned very
very concerned as as my viewers would be
able to would my viewers would be able
to tell you I'm very concerned sure well
you know if if these are honestly the
answers that you think that will will
will Express the best in you then I'm
sure that the profile will become a
complete accurate portrayal of you yes
okay um competitive yes apologetic um
okay had a lot of interesting and funny
experiences working on this yes
independent yes I was set up in a
shopping mall once and I was seeing a
lot of people uh who came up and did
this did you were you answering the
questions for them or were they
answering it for themselves they were
answering it for themselves I was should
be done I think well I felt that you
know since you and I had spoken to each
other and sort of had an understanding I
thought well since this is your test I
think you I see I I I was I was
expecting that you would be running the
machinery and I would be giving you my
responses okay that's we all deal with
expectations in our lives sometimes we
we set things up in our minds that are
going to be a certain way and then when
they turn out to be different we don't
know how to deal with that okay we don't
know how to handle that yes could you
please um um you you run the machine
okay okay okay thank you
mhm now this is a switch for
you what you're letting me run this
you're trusting me again well because
it's because I've told you what was
wrong and I'm telling you how to do it
see I had to I had to instruct you how
to do it okay um okay um sensitive
yes no agree oh I'm I'm sorry put that
right well I I I um Meek um no no I
would agree with that meticulous yes
very yes okay as my my viewers would be
able to tell you I'm very meticulous
okay okay no now you're using your
finger again I know it just would go
much faster if I could just use my
finger there
suspicious
yes no I'm not funloving okay I hate fun
help seeking help seeking
no charitable yes
good that's another thing we need of
more in this world charity help kindness
no I'm not charitable no change
that
okay neighborly no achieving yes it's
what we need more of it's what you need
more of see I've achieved what I want
self-esteem well
you you you you you haven't achieved you
you haven't seem to uh mastered uh your
uh your your own uh profession yet M um
I don't well I have I'm I've mastered
enough to be happy with myself you have
I have extra time I'm making a living
I'm supporting my
family okay well let's just let's just
keep
going okay okay
next see we're wasting time here
um um okay just just keep
going I wish you could go a little
faster precise yes guarded yes why are
you so
slow why are you taking so much time the
show is almost over carefully
considering we haven't even we haven't
even we haven't even gotten we haven't
see my viewers are going to be very
disappointed we haven't even gotten to
uh to uh to the report yet because you
you you're stick you're you're wasting
time and you because you don't know how
to use
it I'm taking all of that
in that's okay you see it's a process
even going through answering these
questions we're learning something about
you and about
ourselves why are you so relaxed because
I feel good why do you feel so good
you're so relaxed and you're just and
you're just sitting there why are you
taking everything I don't understand
it it's okay I don't have to understand
everything what could we speed it up
please we've only got about 10 minutes
left on the show see we we the The
Producers have just come on we have to
speed it up let's go okay okay that's it
let's let's that's it
okay okay that's it now now let's look
we're done anyway we're right okay let's
let's see what it is see
okay I I can't I can't believe that you
you you come on here and you just it's
just it's okay is it all right if I
touch you like that where are you from
California of course
California well do it come on put it put
it on the the box it says okay okay now
see it's going to come on the screen
okay I'll read it if we don't have much
time Dr s is a very versatile person
unless you observe him in more than one
setting you may never realize how
skillfully he plays various roles well
what ises that supposed to
mean well that means that you do a lot
in your life yes judging from the
answers that you gave you are a very
versatile person you fit well in many
situations you're the kind of person
that a lot of people get along
with um
what what was the what was the criteria
for this for this um this program this
is based on the answers that you gave
yes but you you you somehow you you well
let's look at the next
one you're cooperative and a practical
friend you're Adept at the give and take
relationships considerate companion you
expect the same balanced approach from
those who want to be involved with you
you tend to be at ease interpersonally
being neither the overly dominant or
passive again these are based on the
answers you gave me well no this is
based on what you put into the computer
b i a no matter what you I have a
feeling that from what what I've seen of
you so far that it doesn't really matter
what you answer very carefully okay this
has been very carefully researched
everything is based on character
profiles people that I've spoken with
this is based on the answers you gave me
and maybe the answers you gave are
wrong when life throws um Dr sphincter a
curve he runs with it now is that some
kind of U I don't see why you need slang
why can't you be a little more
scientific in your description problems
in everyday living don't usually bother
him when all does not go well he can
usually stay calm well that's completely
wrong isn't it I mean you it's
completely wrong well this is how come
you've uh written a program like this
it's because it's based on the answers
you gave me maybe you should look at the
answers you gave well maybe you should
start thinking about your very carefully
answered I had to change hostility to
change of your sarcastic vitriolic what
about came on here subersive your
subversive fall over the you you don't
even know what's going on what's going
everything to crumble apart you you you
won't be happy until everyone's in
misery you're one of those destructive
people you probably you probably love
that there's there's garbage filling up
all over the world hate that how say
that about that people are hungry and
and buildings are being down histor
you're the one that looks garbage you
came on here here from California yes of
course I be torn apart by some angry
repressed little tight confused hard
you're the one that's confused you don't
even know how to use the
computer you're confused blood you you
probably eat eat pork I eat hot dogs yes
I do eat pork what do you eat are you
some kind of Hipp veget
I'm concerned theut this that's it
that's it okay that's it I'm very very
sorry um once again we we we've had
problems I I thought that he since he
said he was a a computer programmer and
he had written a program called mind
crober that he would be a uh a useful
guest for the show but but once again we
we run into of problems again um I'm I'm
I'm very sorry that it didn't go very
well today um
he he he didn't even know how to use the
the computer and he he started arguing
with me and he became very
upset I hope we don't get cancelled
because of
this goodbye
[Music]
hello as a public service uh we have
organize the Dr sphincter fan club
please send a self-addressed stamped
envelope to Dr sphincter P box1
16108 Minneapolis Minnesota
55416 send $5 to uh belong to the fan
club we'll send you a a small fan not
like this one this is my fan we'll send
you a smaller fan and uh uh the tight
tight newsletter um so um thank you