death Tech is there when you need
it and when you need death Tech there's
nothing like
it the highest kill ratios of any
weapons in the
industry and a commit to Excellence
shared by each and every single employee
of death
Tech The Pride goes far
deeper than the metal casings on the
bombs The Pride goes down
deep into the software that goes into
each and every one of our missile
Delivery
Systems you can be proud that a company
like death Tech is working to serve you
[Music]
[Applause]
hello and uh
well and welcome to uh thail
line it's a uh I wonder uh oh uh who's
in the news well uh um I always thought
it was funny that U wmar Gaddafi was a
uh a colonel and he was the uh leader of
a country um usually uh the leaders are
generals but I guess that's not so weird
when you stop to think that we uh had a
colonel leading this
country um well we have a uh great show
uh tonight um we'll uh we'll be having
an author who wrote a uh um a poetry and
Pros called tight corners and uh what's
around them and thank you very
[Applause]
much hello I'm Dr sphincter and this is
my minute section 2.1 introduction a Dr
sphincter minute is a minute long
lecture covering theories and studies
which I have developed each day is com
comprised of 1440 minutes of those 1440
1339 are spent with other doing other
things 825 should be spent working 325
should be spent sleeping 200 212 are
there for Quality bathroom time 27
minutes should be enough for meals hello
that leaves 1 minute for me Dr spinter
and this is my minute section 2.1
working in your spare time what is Spare
Time spare time is an inconsistent idea
because it is based on the lack of good
orientation in planning get yourself a
good planning schedule and know when
Spare Time occurs this is when there is
lack of good eye toand coordination
leaving the house for no good reason and
sudden muscular
relaxation hello and uh welcome once
again to tight line tonight tight line
is brought to you by uh dire Aid um
if you need Aid get dire
Aid um tonight we have a uh uh an
interesting um author who has written a
book called um if we get a closeup of
this tight corners and what's around
them uh his name is uh David Braham
brami and uh he's with us today to
discuss the book Thank you for coming Mr
how do you pronounce that uh bramage
brage brage is age okay um well well
tell us a little bit about uh what
started you writing poetry and pros and
poems well I've been uh
writing uh pieces of poetry and Pros
really since uh since grammar school
grammar school where was that but uh
that was in Buffalo New York Buffalo mhm
did you grow up there that was my place
of birth and I I grew up in Buffalo your
mother still
she I don't understand what that has to
do with the book but yes she is oh I was
just wondering for our viewers and and
viewers at home might be interested she
is still alive that's correct what's uh
I I noticed that there's a we can get a
closeup of this there's a very
interesting uh uh pattern uh did you uh
uh did did you uh decide on this who
whose work was this these little cubes
well I had a we get a closeup I had a
professional artist design the cover yes
we didn't go into a lot of detail about
the concepts it's a very handsome thank
you color cover it's
uh it's just a cover yes just uh has the
title where where did you uh come up
with a
title for tight
Corners
uh and what's around them
yes was a con concept I had uh early in
my college days M where did you go to
college uh this was in uh Michigan State
Michigan State yeah I moved to Michigan
to go to school is that a uh is that a
very big school it's about uh about 2000
did you live on the campus or did I was
I was in a dormatory in a dormatory
really throughout my uh were you on the
first floor second floor uh this was the
first floor well anyway about the uh
about the title corners and what's
around them MH had a lot to do with the
environment of uh school it was a very
tight cornered environment really and uh
and this it was a uh and it was
productive environment I I I suppose
well there there was some productivity I
I wrote a great deal during those were
your most productive years in this uh in
this uh tight um these tight
circumstances of the restrictive school
rules possible Right confined to my room
and and to the city and where you had to
do most of your work I wrote a great
deal it it wasn't
all uh work that I would publish and and
I've only published a small portion of
that work MH I notice uh the
uh uh it was uh published first in um
1974 that's correct and you started
writing it in what year well it's a it's
a compilation of work really when did
you so the it's a compilation of work
for from about 5 years or so or would
you say 10 no it's there was only about
uh uh well yeah four or five years it
was from 1969 to about
1973 and and there was still some pieces
that I wrote in 74 that appear in this
we uh uh as a new special excuse me uh
Mr brage but I just have to uh take a
moment um out of the show as a uh new
special feature of uh the new tight line
uh we uh will be having news segments
and uh we'll uh this week's News segment
is about a uh prophylactic delivery
service in Madison Wisconsin uh let's
take a look at
that what do you
[Music]
say who is it from healtech Services I
have a delivery for you not all right
thank you no this man isn't delivering
pizza he's delivering condoms that's
because here at the University of
Wisconsin in Madison Pizza emergencies
are giving way to prophylactic
emergencies what we did was we handed
out flyers at the beginning went around
posted them all over campus and we went
around and handed out some condoms to
people three students here have solved
the age-old problem of having to buy
condoms with only one phone call they'll
delivered two varieties lubed and non
right here
door uh it's Michael from Health tech
services
oh these guys will bring you a rubber
sheet so you can let the moment speak
for itself a yeah what we're trying to
get across is very professional and
discreet service including you a major
amount of confidentiality if we went
around parading our you know what we do
then it would be against our
professionalism see I think of the
species uh we do need all the help we
can possibly get and uh got a stiffy we
a
JY oh hello um and uh we're back uh
we're with uh wasn't that a nice News
segment I wouldn't know I I didn't see
any of of that work oh really none I I'm
not aware of any you didn't watch it
beforehand no I I didn't see your your
uh well we're back with uh Mr David Bram
G brage brage Braham G and we're
discussing his book tight corners and
what's around them what do you think uh
now when you say and what's around them
um uh most Corners uh is that some
indication of uh the the fear of uh
approaching the unknown uh of going
around a corner and not knowing exactly
what to expect no it's not a reference
to fear of what's around corners
particularly really uh it has to do with
the manipulations we go through yes in
uh in survival in our uh sexual survival
um in our survival for
sanity would you like to read some of
the book sure I have a few examples I
thought I'd share
now Mr brage will read from the book
whoops this is a piece I wrote uh
shortly after leaving the university and
I met my first wife
mhm oh so you've been married several
times I have had several wives really
how many
exactly well I'm now married to my third
wife third third what was the problem
with the no problem it was oh here let
me uh let me just just so you express it
in the I see mhm when I told you I
enjoyed it I felt disgusted with
myself truly it disgusted me yes as I
was afraid you'd see but I couldn't
bring myself to hurt you openly so I
told you it was great in such a way I
could be pretty sure you'd find out
later differently and I was
right so that is a uh a uh description
of a uh an intimate uh relationship that
you had with one of your wives this was
and that's uh your pry to a certain
cander that I don't usually yes reveal
about my work but and it was you were
disgusted by it
really I I felt disgusted with myself
not by it with with yourself doing it
like that no no you you don't understand
understand it
uh it's it's quite unique to our
relationship yes with with number
one with number one number one my my
first wife oh your first wife I see I
just I don't want to say her name on the
air and I thought number one is a a I
thought you speaking of a different
number one I'm I'm sorry Mr B um well uh
could you read U maybe possibly another
passage from the uh
the book I have one noted I you uh have
to misplace my
notes did you uh oh here I've I've uh
you find it we're uh kind of pressed for
time a second uh um you have uh
uh well this is another piece this was
uh later uh when when things were
becoming dismantled yes
this is about a different person by the
way this is not related to to the first
poem she was urging him to seize the day
to see his hour had come there would be
no second chance he would forever be a
weak Creature if he didn't stand on his
own two feet she leaned on him as she
spoke but then he was half supported by
her now her husband was tugging at her
sleeve saying just a minute the man
startled asked who's
minute ja like a TS no thank you I'm
fine I notice uh uh lots of times uh the
subject of women uh pops up in your uh
writings is there any particular reason
for this Mr Bram well there's no
particular
reason you find them
disgusting there there have been women
uh that have entered into my sphere of
experience and I've reflected on those
experiences in my writing but uh there's
there's no particular pattern PN to uh
no pattern to uh so you you've uh you've
had some uh bad experiences in the
past no they they haven't been bad all
experiences are good there are no bad
experiences there's just bad
interpretations well well how can you
say that there's no bad experiences the
uh uh you just said in the book that you
were disgusted by a bad experience with
a
person feeling woman the feeling of
disgust I had was uh very useful it uh
it wasn't bad it was a a Vitality it was
bad but it it became useful because it
was
bad I think it it was useful initially
before its uh before its existence even
it was useful before its
existence yes it well what does that
mean all experience uh that that you and
I experience in life is uh is sort of
weighted for us to approach it's it's
waiting in in the future this our
meeting was
predestined do you know the um Library
of Congress number of this book by any
chance I I don't know the Library of
Congress number why do you ask what you
don't know the Library of Congress
number that has nothing to do with the
work that's just a reference well it's
has if you don't know it's it's got I
think quite a bit to do with the work
it's the library of Congress as we know
is a uh Storehouse of the vastest amount
of information um in the world and um
for you not to know exactly uh where you
can uh find what you have done
personally uh I I keep track of all the
numbers of uh what I have done in my my
writings my work you have writings that
are in the Library of Congress of course
yes your your your clinical studies
maybe you use a Dewey Decimal System but
that is kind of
outdated as many of us know with the new
uh computerized um Imaging systems and
pro data processing systems doctor I'm
not familiar with uh the filing system
that various libraries have used to
categorize my my writings that's that's
not what I'm here to
discuss if we could get a uh closeup uh
once again of uh of the book I notice uh
there's a picture of you in the back
here with a little biography we can get
a closeup of this um we had a closeup of
the uh picture that you uh find here in
the back of the book that was taken just
after uh we had agreed on the
publication with uh with the Publishing
House mhm what's what's your question
about well I I noticed here that you
have a beard that's right I was why why
why Why Did You Have A Beard at that
point were you trying to hide something
I I had the the beard was just something
that that grew on me I didn't uh I
shaved I put on a suit to to be on this
program I I have beards at different
times it's of no significance to me
whether I well you're are you aware I
have no problem that you shave I don't
know maybe you shave every day maybe you
don't well I shave four times a day but
I you shave four times a day
a day I find it necessary myself to the
public people with beards I think uh we
all know what happened when everyone
started growing beards we immediately
had a fascination with uh recreational
vehicles and um CB radios and completely
destroyed the uh Integrity of this
country increased my interest in
recreational vehicles or CVS in which I
have none well not necessarily that but
also drugs uh most people who take drugs
wear beards I don't understand your your
uh relation between facial hair and
interest in CB radios okay I I think
that's not founded okay but uh but
that's not my concern anyway well let's
uh could I read some possibly of uh this
book um well if uh yeah if you'd like to
I guess
um find a
a good uh a good passage here um the
book works best as read cover to cover
the uh the various Pros are linked yes
mhm even though they're uh from various
how hard it is to speak of the death of
love if that is the death and the
emotion I do speak of here there's an
almost inter interminable search for for
the right word and what makes it so
difficult if not an equal determination
not to disclose oneself to what the
right word is I would be absolutely
clear at the onset on one point I'm a
man who doesn't always get what he wants
but possessed of such determination and
willpower that I believe had I wanted to
be president I would have come close
well that's an interesting passage that
you realize the potential which uh you
you you have in yourself that uh we all
have the potential to become presidents
and a Statesman and uh very powerful but
uh you you've uh kept to just writing uh
poetry I have uh that was not
particularly a reflection of my
aspirations see I had thought from the
the title of the book at first glance I
had thought the book was more about um
uh design uh interior design uh of uh
rooms and buildings like you might find
uh uh tight corner and what's around
them in the Next Room I I had not the uh
I I am a fan of poetry I I do write some
of my own as a matter of fact my
interest with with I I thought it it had
been technical of a technical
nature no it's not technical other than
the technical experience we have in life
and tight Corners certainly are uh a
thing that we encounter what kind of
corner corners do you see to be the
tightest Corners well
the the tightest
Corners would would have to
be the corners imposed by human
relationships
yes which are so tight in fact that uh
we may not be able to
maneuver uh through the door of our
apartment or uh or through the door of
this
studio well what maybe a tight cornered
relationship we're establishing which
will not let us leave this stage
potentially and uh that's something we
have to accept when it happens so you
find you find uh these tight Corners to
be something to
avoid or just be prepared uh that you
you may be in a tight corner and to be
at would you rather have a corner with
your tight corner be tighter or less
tight if you the tightness is is really
irrelevant it's the openness that you
experience irrelevant things with
exactly so you feel that the tightness
is irrelevant to the situation of being
in a tight corner it's one aspect of how
could you write a book called tight
corners and find the tightness is
irrelevant to uh relationships to it
could have been many titles tight
Corners life experiences tight Corners
is a useful title because it's something
that people identify with so people
identify with it because they understand
understand tightness and they want to be
uh uh tighter people and they're not um
interested in trying to avoid um the uh
uh the the tighter relationships I think
are the better ones if you say you're
tight with someone that is a good uh uh
thing to say that means working closely
with them and you're not when somebody's
tight with you that that has nothing to
do with being in a tight corner with
them it's just the opposite it's it's
not a tightness of a binding nature it's
a tightness that's open yes it certainly
is it's a a binding and and close-knit
uh relationship you don't you don't feel
that you experience openness in in your
close relations well you experience
openness in a tight binded um way uh you
don't um you you don't you're not open
with just anyone I can do anything with
my work I'm trying to expand people's
ideas and bring them to a more open
understanding of their experience well
it it it seems like the uh
uh it's uh I'm not sure I any impression
of that from the work read surprises me
I don't see why you don't uh well I
don't see why you you feel that you must
avoid these tight corners and you feel
that uh relationships that are tight are
uh unacceptable and uh not uh I'm not
involved in avoiding anything I've been
open to all experience guess you have
been avoiding my questions and you've
been kind of uh getting off the subject
at times and I'm just trying to find out
the uh what you exactly mean when you
say that relationships you're you're
pushing yourself into a tight corner and
why this is something that you want to
avoid especially if you've written a
book called tight corners and what's
around them I if I see a tight corner I
immediately want to see what's around it
I'm not uh afraid I want to uh prob
what's around the uh corner so you think
that you can prepare yourself for
experience and avoid pain and suffering
is that is that your idea that you're
going to be able to uh prepare yourself
in some way well I I think now you're
just you're getting philosophical
there's no need to get philosophical I'm
dealing with a a real issue I'm not
dealing with it is very real everyday
experience whether philosophic issue
like whether we're going to constrict
existentialism or something constrict
our experience we're we're we constantly
trying to constrict our experience
because that is that's what life is
about you don't go around life um uh
life is made up of constrictions and
constricting experiences your your body
is put into a a tight frame and and cell
each there are millions of cells in the
body and in each cell is a tight little
constrictive um framework and uh that's
how things work they don't work if if
things are just spilling out all over
the place um so I'm not sure exactly
what you're trying to get
at you you seem to be trying to do you
eat meat or are you a do I eat meat yes
I I eat no meat you don't eat meat I
didn't think so and that has very little
to do with our discussion you tipped me
off very early that you're if you could
get a closeup if his lapel uh is folded
over I I didn't mention it earlier um
because um I I wasn't sure if you wanted
it to be like that or not but this is a
television show and for things to be um
kind of slop slopp see I walk into a
situation without concern of uh total
preparedness I'm I'm prepared as I see
fit and
uh my uh my avoidance of red meat and
other red Foods you avoid red Foods I
avoid any red
Foods why is that well I feel the the
the red the red is a is a is an
influence that's going to be limiting to
me why is it limiting red it it has red
is a uh color it's an important color
out most other colors it's uh an
important color because it tells us that
there is danger approaching if you don't
like red how can you say tight corners
and what's around them it it it seems
like you're you're speaking of danger
and um red is uh a color that signifies
danger and and uh fear Poss it's it's
like a shut off exactly red is is like
the stop sign the shut off
yes go on
please and and the shut off is something
I'm I'm uh cutting out cutting out the
red meat cutting out the shut off
cutting out the shut off um what do you
want to shut off
well there there's very little
at no what are you saying I'm not
shutting anything off I didn't say
anything about shutting anything off
well you've been saying it all night I
think no I I haven't been talking
anything about uh about shutting off I'm
open I'm open to what you're saying but
I feel that you've missed my point
you've been too open that's why you've
missed the point and I I think that we
have to to leave you now um because uh I
I can see encourage you to read this
interview is not goingn this interview
just isn't going anywhere and what's
around them from cover to cover with an
open mind open to the ideas that I'm
presenting I have an open mind but I
have I can see that that you restricted
yourself to a very narrow no you're the
one that has closed your mind to new
ideas and Concepts I have a very open
mind when it comes to study and uh basic
uh uh nature of things and uh basic
research basic chemistry for example I'm
very open to that and you uh if you come
along trying to tell people that uh
tight relationships and uh working in
tight um areas is bad I'm I am not open
to that I'm sorry Mr Bram bramage and um
we'll we'll have to leave you now and
we'll have to uh come back next week and
we'll uh have a uh hopefully a more
interesting topic I have asked the
producers um for a uh some more uh
tighter control I hope that you give
them more opportunity to I've I've asked
for tighter control over the show so we
don't run into these kinds of problems I
am sorry um yes I'm sorry too uh I seem
to have wasted my time I'm trying to get
a uh some more interesting people on
chemists um doctors biologists um uh
people in uh many fields of study who
don't get a chance to come out and
[Music]