this is Bill he was severely injured in
a chemical fire the plant where he works
the fire was so bad that even the rescue
workers with their sophisticated
equipment couldn't put out the
fire there are burns on over 90% of his
body
bill will never be able to work again
and his medical bills are
astronomical his company is going to
need the best legal advice money can buy
call the law firm of sphincter and
Associates we have over 20 years
defending corporations just like yours
from people like Bill trying to file
injury on the job lawsuits a second
shift employee caught his hand in the
die stamp press he created a mess tried
suing the company for $3 million and
tried get the other employees to go
against the plant snon Associates came
in and in 5 minutes they put down the
employee Uprising and proved that the
accident was actually the fault of the
injured employee they did fantastic work
for us in New
[Music]
Delhi I can take the worry and fear out
of your employee related problem this is
all I do and I'm the best so call me at
sphincter and Associates 1 1800 destroy
call sphincter and Associates 1800 d s t
r o y
[Music]
oh
um hello and uh welcome again to tight
line tonight brought to you by perap
pile when the muscles can't give out
when the muscles give out give perap
pile a
try tonight we have with us a uh an
author who's written a book called don't
say yes when you want to to say no MH
and his name is uh Dr uh Herbert Herbert
fensterheim and he's with us tonight to
discuss his book Thank you for fer thank
you for coming Dr you're welcome thank
you very much for having me um before
before we actually get into the book
itself I I would like to uh just ask our
Our Guest a a few uh uh Star Trek
questions to get to get things moving
why sure I'm a big fan of St you are a
big fan of Star Trek um okay could you
name the officer
who whose H whose hallway conversation
concerning a takeover of the ship was
used to justify their execution for
Mutiny namely officers who were they I
think they were
Scotty yes and who else nurse Chapel no
she no maybe no it was Scotty and McCoy
Scotty and McCoy were the two officers
in the corbon corbomite maneuver who
said that the alien Bok reminded him of
his
father Leonard nemoy playing Spock
playing Spock I this cor you you so you
are a big fan of Star Trek there yes I I
am that's wonderful it's a very good
science fiction the uh story in how many
episodes excluding turnabout Intruder
are there two James Kirks in the same
story two James Kirks was that the was
that the one where the they're in well
how many were were there how many James
Kirks well how many stories were there
to James Kirks I think there was two no
the one where oh no there are four
actually well the Enemy Within Mirror
Mirror whom's God destroy and what our
little girls made of I wasn't really
sure but uh so I don't know actually yes
okay well I'm fine I'm fine with that so
you well you you have you have seen the
show but you you haven't seen it that
many times then not enough to memorize
it for btim I see but I see well let's
if you get to my book on to the book yes
it's a uh it's a very interesting and
compelling book it's uh it's uh getting
people to say to say no because as uh as
as we find out in in our in our society
today too many people are are saying yes
to too many things when they want to say
no that's the difference so so tell us
uh how did you uh what inspired you to
write the book Dr well first off I
wanted to make money let's be honest
about it yes the uh that's a it's a joke
yeah what it was a joke it was a joke no
about making money of course I I wanted
I wanted to write the book to help
people right yes to to stop them from
saying yes that's right when they should
say no right I mean so many of us we
have such a low self-esteem that we're
always trying to please people mean ever
since we were born we're trying to
please our parents we try to please our
teachers our peers in school uh in
college we're trying to please our first
girlfriends or boyfriends whatever we
move on to the business World we're
always trying to to please people we we
tend to lose our own self-identity in
this in this myopic uh sense of the
world so you're basically what you're
saying is that we're just we just should
say no more we should say no when we
really mean no yes take for in usually
we most of the time we do mean no don't
we did you you I I I suppose that you
you you realized that when you wrote the
book that no not sometimes when we say
no we're actually saying yes to
ourselves so you're saying that is the
dichotomy and the Paradox at the same
time I see um so well tell us um how
long did it take you to write the book
it took me well years of research uh I
started uh researching this in what kind
of car did you drive while you were
writing the
book well I started I was driving a
Volkswagen when I started what kind the
the the uh the beetle beetle that little
uh the further I got along the more I
learned about self assertiveness I I
bought a a Volvo oh you did by the end
of the book that's a that's a uh Volvo
is a very uh very well-designed and safe
car it's a yes car it's a car that says
yes it's I see because I wanted it
that's my you mhm what um where did you
uh do most of the uh the research for
this one on most of my patients actually
I I am a PS a psych olist you are you so
you're a uh you you went to uh to
college yes I did and you you you became
a doctor of assertiveness training a
doctor of psychology actually of
psychology of the the psychology of
assertiveness training that came out of
yes yeah well yes exactly came out of
that but I no I did research on all my
patients I interviewed them and find out
finding out what really makes them tick
and why they why they say yes when they
want to say no mhm and most of it comes
from a low self-esteem what kind of
people did you study were there were
were there large amounts of people large
amounts all my patients actually ranging
from you know semi mildly neurotic all
the way to did you study anyone that you
were related to I did study my um uh my
mother your mother yes and where does
she live well she's in a nursing home
now oh in really Santa Monica yes you
you put your mother in a nursing
home well she was getting very old and I
couldn't take care of her and father
died you had to buy the Volvo I suppose
the yes car well yes but I I did I she's
being taken care of very well I see I
mean I could take care of her myself so
do you think that uh by by writing this
book the the the writing of the book
itself do you feel that it is it is a a
uh the book itself is a a book on how to
say uh no or or how to say yes cuz you
you say that the don't say yes when you
want to say no but do you think the book
The basic premise of the book is to say
yes or to say no it's to say no actually
to say no that's the operative word
there no because too often we say yes
when we mean we should be yes we all
should we should always be aware that
that uh people will will try to use us
and people will try to take advantage of
us exactly and and in in order to to to
stop that we we should be saying no too
many times uh too many times people into
very unpleasant situations by uh uh
being LAX and and saying yes yes is The
Lax way I think no is it's easy to say
yes it's easy and it it doesn't take
anything to say yes but it it takes much
more to say no exactly I'm sure you say
that in the book here to say no you're
inviting conflict you're inviting uh
contradiction you're inviting uh a
disagreement and that's that's you
really sticking your neck out a long way
you're you're taking a risk and that's
what we need to do each one of us is
take more risks and that's what I've
been doing taking more risks I took a
risk writing that book yes I I see her
that um if if we can get a close-up of
this um I I see you uh you you worked
with this on on with a female I think
that's taking a pretty big risk right
there don't you think so well no I mean
she's a very distinguish colleague of
mine she's very so she did the the
typing did she like she was probably a
good typist and secretary she was my
equal in all the research she she she
did she made the the coffee and and she
was it was it was it upsetting to have a
secretary a female secret uh I didn't
have a we did not have a female
secretary we had a male secretary his
name was Julian he was very good at it
what what Julian was our secretary he
gathered all the information jul Julian
yes where did you find him Julian uh you
had a male secretary male secretary he
he lives in Los
Angeles uh we hired him because he well
and he was happy with being a secretary
he yes he was we asked him and he said
yes I'm very happy he
did yes he did well so this woman um so
you you actually worked with a woman on
the book itself yes we did she's very I
I I respect her immens well I suppose
you did do most of the work though it
was actually equal right down the middle
equal equal research equal time equal
writing it was it was a perfect
collaborate C collaboration well I I I
thought you had just you had been nice
and you had included the uh the the name
of your secretary on no no no I see no
don't say Yes um well if you could uh oh
would you like some
Tang um we have some Tang I'd rather
have sparkling water if you have any of
that well we just have we have plain
water if we could you like some sure
you do you like it strong uh yes I do I
haven't had Tang since IOP a child
that's kind of messy there yeah it is a
little messy I don't have a the the uh I
I've been asking for a spoon and the The
Producers didn't get me a spoon tonight
so we'll have to make do without this
spoon this is fine I'm very happy with
this not I just need
so tell us more about uh about your uh
education Dr ferim well I my
undergraduate degree was earned at
Columbia University yes are you all
right yes uh May perhaps if you undid
your shirt a little more you could
breathe easier no no I'm I'm I'm fine
you look like you're you're kind of
upset I no I'm I'm I'm I'm not I'm not
upset are you upset I'm not upset at all
I'm never upset well well you were you
were talking about about uh your your
college life yes Columbia University I
had my undergraduate degree and I
learned and and I earned my my masters
at the University of Virginia then my
doctorate degree at the if I was upset
you wouldn't be on the
show if I was if I'm I'm not upset
understand you still seem upset is there
something bothering you well you're
no good if uh so you you went to you
went to uh a Community College and uh
you were uh and no it was Columbia
University and your
secretary my secretary was Julian Jean
Jean bear my my colleague helped me
write the book Julian no Julian did not
help me write it Julian typed Julian got
the coffee Julian uh you let you you
made a man do those things yes I did I
see CU he wanted to and he said
yes what uh so you live in California
yes I do no I do what part of California
it's uh well I live uh near uh San
Francisco oh you do mhm you live near
San Franc and you are you uh are you uh
do you have a family not yet I'm still
looking for that perfect person I see to
share my living in San Francisco without
a family um well I'd like to read a uh a
passage or two from the book sure if we
could uh if we could if we could
uh uh read read some and and get a uh
I'll I'll read a case study for you here
Rick Schulman a recent PhD came to me
with a career problem yes he used to
enjoy teaching his college classes but
recently he found the work burdensome
and depressing our discussion revealed
that the change started while he was
working on his doctoral thesis because
he was so busy he stopped preparing his
lectures and depended on the offthe cuff
remarks after completing the thesis he
continued his newly acquired habit of
giving the unprepared lectures Rick
realized these lectures were
disorganized and superficial it was this
knowledge that brought about his
depression and dissatisfaction the
thought never occurred to him to do
something about it that's a uh very very
very interesting case study you you've
uh taken someone who who became LAX and
and as a result of becoming LAX and
disorganized he became uh depressed and
unhappy with his work which we can see
happening all the time exactly I mean he
should have been happy about his work
otherwise he uh she should have just
quit I mean in order we have to be happy
in order to function properly and we we
live under this illusion that we that
we're happy just by pretending we're
happy I see uh could you uh tell us a
little more about uh about Rick uh Rick
yes well he he quit I finally convinced
him to stop you convinced him to quit
yes and he moved to Montana He why did
you convince him to quit because he was
not happy you are you telling people to
quit to quit their jobs if they're not
happy they should quit they should find
tell them you're you're telling me to
say no to to to uh uh working and and
being not no to working to say yes to I
ask you what what you're doing it's just
a little I I I just felt uncomfortable
the other way this table's awfully big
and it was pressing against my
circulation because you push you pushed
it on me and I was just trying to push
it push it away oh well I was just just
wanted to make enough room for myself
but now we're both
happy we have certain regulations here
that um uh this this isn't this
is college Gathering where you can just
put your feet anywhere and and just
start um and gesticulating a certain way
I I don't agree with this but just to
make your happy I'll I'll do this okay
so uh he's in living in Montana now in a
commun you told him to move to Montana
uh he wanted to do that so I told him to
do it did you put your father in a
nursing home too or is your father dead
my father's dead your father's what did
he die of he died in a car accident when
was that it was uh 5 years
ago he was uh he was driving home drunk
he was a Shriner did you tell him to
quit too were you were you doing a study
on him no I didn't I was too late to
talk to him about uh he was a very
unhappy man he's unhappy with his life
and his wife and us and everything and
but I decided I'm not going to live my
life to please him mhm and then he died
and then you moved to California you
moved to San Francisco and and and
started this this research of telling
people to quit I think we should talk
about the book I mean that's that's
what's important it's not me it's what
it's my work it's what I'm it's what I'm
trying to do to help people that's what
I'm trying to I'm trying to help people
okay okay
um well we'll uh I'll I'll go to another
a chapter
here I'll just
randomly pick out
something um let's see I I'll try to get
a case here
um
35 35y Old Roy and 30 30-year-old Peggy
married for 6 years and with no children
nor desired any at this point wanted to
increase the frequency of
interourse their marital difficulties of
course say it their marital difficulties
came to a head when Peggy discovered
that Roy had had several brief affairs
with other women he claimed this was
because he continually felt frustrated
um quote Peggy and I rarely have sexual
relations he told me Peggy complained
that Roy hounded her constantly about
sex mhm
well I didn't know you were writing a uh
a a pornographic book here oh for God's
S no it is not pornographic
sexual relations are very important
that's that's a source of so much
tension and so much self-esteem it's a
source of tension because people are
saying yes to
it you are obviously very uptight about
your own sexual I'm not
uptight it's it's uh it's it's your
you're the one who's uptight I'm not
uptight I'm very relaxed with my body
with who I am well yes I can see that
you're let me ask you a question do you
say buttock or
buttocks um would you like some more
Tang
yes please I can get it myself thank
you um anyway uh I if I had known that
the uh the book was going to be a uh a
uh a book about telling people to quit
and about uh pornography I wouldn't it's
not telling people to quit it's not porn
it's not about pornography it's about
helping people to find their own
self-esteem their own self seem to be
you seem to be directing people to to
quit and to to quit things they don't
want to dool eles in uh in these uh uh
relationships with people that they
don't really want to that's that's what
it looks like to
me but uh if if if you could just uh get
back on the subject of of your uh
schooling mhm and uh the uh your college
life what uh did you have a roommate in
college yes I
did his name was Frank Frank yes he was
a he was a
uh business
administration did you get along with
Frank I got along with Frank but he was
he was from the old traditional sense of
himself he was he was he was too uh a
little too uh tight for you maybe he was
well he was uptight yes he was he he
arranged everything neatly in the room I
remember we had many fights over you
know how to if the chair was out of
place and stuff I really didn't care cuz
that was not important it wasn't
important to feelings are the most
important furthering yourself through
college did you even it wasn't important
to be neat and to uh to keep your see
that's part of it we put on this false
sense that if we arrange our lives
externally like nice little neat things
and everything's going to be happy
inside when it should just be the
opposite you should arrange your life to
what's happening inside which is free
flowing which is
sexual the same one well we I I think
people need to to arrange things more
people aren't that's that's why we have
so many problems because people are
letting themselves go and there people
are people are have the attitude like
you do that that we should uh be loose
people become we should not be loose
ever at and and that's that's what
causes the problem become pressure
cookers we become LAX and we become
loose and and lazy and and we and we we
don't realize what's going on and go by
and we we we say yes to everything
there the hand there's the hand what do
you
uh what what could I ask you what you're
doing is this some some kind of some
kind of uh nonverbal commun that that
you use in California hippie trick you
could call it hippie it's nonverbal
communication I was expressing something
I could not express verbally see I had
another I had another author I had
another author on here from Berkeley um
and I and I should have known that uh uh
uh uh two two in the bush uh one in the
one in the hand is is uh the way you
have to deal with these people fine fine
I okay well we can I don't have to deal
with your problems I don't have to be
part of your reality here what problems
I don't have any problems you're the one
who has problems problems you you you
come on the show and you you you you're
you're telling people to to quit their
jobs you're telling people to get
involved in in in relationships I'm
telling people to be happy well you're
you're you're telling people how you
think they should be happy I think
that's kind of dictatorial and I spent 5
years on that damn book All This
research talking to a bunch of crazy
people who are unhappy do you know how
depressing that is interviewing all
these unhappy people you know how much I
had to
fight not sympathizing with him just to
deal with him objectively all these
miserable crying people it was it was
depressing I thank God I got that book
out you know how many Publishers I had
to go to for that stupid thing you know
how many of them said no no yeah I'm
sure they would say no I'd say oh we
don't want to we don't want to do
anything about a book that we can't make
a movie out of you can't make a movie
out of that book yeah it took me years I
had to put up $100,000 my own money well
okay three mortgages you can complain I
mean you can there's you know you you
can complain you can come on my show and
complain all you want but the the fact
is is that this person is living in
Montana on a on a commune who very
happy oh I should say that tonight's
program is brought to you by uh Perma
pile when you when you can't uh when the
muscles give up remember there's perap
pile and uh tonight we we uh we're
discussing uh we're discussing a book
called don't say yes when you want to
say no I don't want to be on the show
anymore well um we we need to we need to
finish discussing the book you discuss
the book you seem to know everything
about it you seem to know everything I
mean you seem to have you seem to be
really you know self assured and
everything so you don't need me talk
about my own book well you don't seem to
need uh I you don't seem to need a top
button on your shirt either you don't
need seem to need oh why are there
things hanging off of your pants I don't
this is stylish you you look like some
kind of Disco King from the
the70s
something yeah I bet you uh you had it
you've got who knows what kind of going
on in inside why you just shut up buy my
book go to hell write your own
[Music]