[Applause]
[Music]
hello uh and welcome once again to tight
line um tonight's tight line is uh
sponsored in part by a grand from Easter
baskets by General Dynamics because
Easter is
special um well tonight we have a very
interesting show we have a famous author
who is uh with us tonight to discuss his
book called Falling Up The
Stairs can you get a closeup of this
falling up the stairs and he's here his
name is James Li Lex and we'll be
discussing the book Thank you thank you
it's a pleasure to be on the show Doctor
thank you very much uh would you like um
uh before we begin lunch Bol or
something it's do those have any broth
in them um possibly I don't know they're
very good and the package makes a very
that's okay a handy desk or organizer
when it's done well we can go back to
that later
anyway to uh go back to the book uh
falling up the stairs is a very uh
unique and uh intricate and interesting
book which conerns itself with many um
different topics mhm um yes I think I
think that'd be a fair assessment when
when did you uh first uh get the idea
for the book oh two or three years ago I
think when I was shaving that's why it
begins with the shaving scene Lyn I'm
going to tell you more little details
you had an accident when you were
shaving yes I did yes and that that's
clearly outlined in the book in the book
The there's many uh many um accidents
and um home safety hazards which take
place in the home that have to do with
the book um I'm not I'm not sure what
you're saying well many of the the the
scenarios the um the accident scenarios
that you that you outline in the book
take place in the home is that not
correct well there well no there's if if
you'd read the book um you know that
read the book well no you did you well I
hate to contradict you because it is
your show but you obviously didn't read
the book because
no if you had read the book you'd know
that there aren't really that many
accidents you okay okay okay well um so
anyway what's uh what kind of car do you
drive um I drive a Ford Probe why a prob
is that a new car um it's a about 2
years old um what color is the interior
it's it's a it's a charcoal gray the the
the book is is it a cloth or is it a a
vinyl it's a it's it's a stain resistant
fabric I used to have a car that I put
in the book um a Pacer that's why the
character drives a Pacer did you have
any of your uh relatives work with you
on doing the book yes well no I mean I
it's a writing a novel is a solitary
thing you don't ask your dad to come
over and help yes yes it's it's we we
all need to know that uh a a book
because I've written several books
myself you have it's a very uh a timec
consuming difficult individual uh
challenge do your relatives help you
with your books no I have none no it's
uh I'm just curious why you asked why my
relatives would help me writing a book
like I didn't write write it myself the
whole thing every word no I uh I was
just I was just uh uh interested in
finding out um if you uh cuz I did write
every word of that book oh yeah yes um
uh well could you tell us um a little
bit more about uh how did you come up
with the the title falling up the stairs
I don't know you know people ask me that
and um I wish there was an entertaining
story behind it but there's really not
um I I just it's something that happened
in the book and I just decid I I I
needed a title
I couldn't you know just come up with
anything like a book I just had to so I
I took that but it's really more than
the falling up the stairs part I think
you you're a little too fixated on that
it's it really is quite a rich and div
diverse uh book that I've written yes
well um it's a which part did you like
well the the the first part was good I I
like the first part the most first part
um uh we uh we have to go uh to a break
right now Mr Li licks but uh we'll be uh
right back right after this message and
we'll be right
back this
[Applause]
is oh my back it's killing me putting in
some overtimes do I don't know what it
is I've tried everything ibuprofen
aspirin even Tylenol nothing seems to
work try
mine backup yeah backup it works hard
when I work hard
it's got special chemical brain stem
Inhibitors stops pain dead
okay be at 1020 20
minutes hey how's that back feel now I
don't feel
nothing backup tablets for back pain now
with beta
katene oh
so uh welcome back to uh tight line
tonight on tight line we have Mr
James James lilx who has just written a
book called Falling Up The Stairs which
is a comprehensive book that um several
of um his family members uh contributed
to nobody in my family wrote this book
it's about home safety and the dangers
of um walking um on stairs it as we know
as we all know many people who have
homes and have stairways in their home
keep them Slippery People slip on the
stairs I hate to you know can I I hate
to butt in and contradict you but it's
not about home safety and my family
members had nothing to do with what then
why did you title it falling up the
stairs if it has nothing to do with
what's in the book it just I had to give
it a name that name and my mother said
falling and um it was something my
mother said one day and it just stuck in
my mind what's your mother's maiden name
Eloise Louise Mabel M she's she's not
here is she where is she well she's back
at home I imagine working no she's ring
she's cooking yes she's cooking what
does she cook um she cooks um a what
what is what what is it I um what in
besides the first part what did you
think of the ending um well surprise
surprise yes and um did you think that
the person who did it actually did it um
well it wasn't really a uh did you did
you suspect him uh no oh really it was a
woman it was a woman it was a woman you
didn't
you didn't Mr lilx I'm asking the
questions here um what's uh what's the
color of your house that you live in
look my house is white my house trim it
has a trim color it has it's um it's a
an eggshell white the trim is egg show
trim is egg show wa yeah do you have uh
carpeting yep we got carpeting no we
don't we don't have any carpeting we
ripped it all up no no none whatsoever
do you have uh do uh well besides of uh
writing these um these books do you uh
have which some people read do you have
a uh all the way through a job to the
end do you work yes I work over at the
St Paul pioner press dispatch columnist
feature writer the the what the St Paul
Pioneer Press it's it's it's a newspaper
in St
Paul a
newspaper yeah is that is that a
community um one of those small
community um the St Paul Pine the second
biggest paper in the state you know we
got boxes everywhere you put in a
quarter you take out four five
sections I don't subscribe to newspapers
how can you not live in this area know
the St Pine newspapers are very filled
with uninteresting and unnecessary
information you ever get over to St Paul
they uh the the ink if you ever read a
newspaper the ink comes off and it gets
all over your hands and you and you you
you touch yourself somewhere and it gets
all over all over yourself because but
that doesn't have the book black um
marks everywhere I I don't know why
anyone would want to buy or read a new
newspaper and and now they have the the
color they have all these colored
pictures on newspapers now you you you
you accidentally touch one of the the
color photographs on the paper and it
gets all over you yeah and it's a big to
say that you work for a company that
that i' I'll quit tomorrow I'll quit
tomorrow I'm not asking you to quit I'm
just it would make it would obviously
make you happy if I quit the newspap no
I'm simply making a statement that I
think there's something you could
improve in your product that's all I'm
saying I'm saying I'll take it up with
quality control in the meantime quit my
papers it will make you feel good go
back to writing novel go back to wrri
novel like that one like I like I have a
second novel do you have any
children uh no no no I'd rather you not
ask about that area of my life well um
what's uh what what was the uh the the
print style used in the book what was
the the name of this the font I think it
was badoni badoni or bodney bodney it
may have been a s you know what size no
but it's easy to read if you'd have
given it a try you would have found that
out well let's read an excerpt from the
book oh please and it's it's done uh the
falling up the stairs is done in bod bod
yeah in your never heard of that your
best DED voice if you could please
Geneva um oh well I've just been
informed that we uh have to take another
Break
um we are speaking with uh James lilx
Lix
um and we're discussing his new book
falling up the
stairs a a
classic one two three oh my back it's
killing me overdoing it again huh Dave I
don't know what it is I've tried aspirin
Tylenol even ibuprofen in my back is
still killing me here try mine back up
yeah backup it's got chemical brain stem
Inhibitors stops pain dead it worked for
me I'll try
it how's that bag now I don't feel a
thing backup tablets for back pain now
with
fiber these guys are waving at you for
some particular reason well I noticed
that I could tell that they were waving
um uh so tell us uh we we were going to
read an excerpt from the book
um which uh was called Falling Up The
Stairs we are with James
lyx where where what kind of name is
lick Li it's sort of Ukrainian sort of
Ukrainian partially Ukrainian H it's it
doesn't sound like it to me um sounds
like it's a madeup name like many
authors and actors people make their
names up to sound more that's right I
made it up and I chose one so easy to
pronounce so people like you could say
LX and stumble that's what it says it
says L say lilx it says lilx there's no
hyphen there's no hyphen that says Dr
sphincter here pause all right do you
see a hyphen on the cover of that I
didn't I'm not talking about hyphens I'm
simply talking about pronunciation
hyphen is the sort of thing you're doing
that vocalized
pause now an excerpt from falling up the
stairs I had one foot out of the tub and
was about to step onto the tile ooh this
is taking place in the bathroom yes it's
taking place in the bathroom when I
noticed I had already deposited a
substantial quality of quantity of water
on the floor but it's not dangerous and
the TV was on the floor plugged in war
still raging across its 6in screen I was
able to step onto the adjacent toilet
without touching the floor from there I
got the towel crouching on the bowl no
no it sounds it sounds like a gargoyle
coming to terrorize if you listen if you
read it on the page it sounds nicer it
really does it really does it no but if
the person reads it and kind of hears it
in their mind it really i' I'd
appreciate it are you you're one of
these are you one of these Zen people
that like to chant inside of your no but
sometimes when you I was simply reading
I'm I'm trying to read an excerpt from
your book and I'm trying to sell books
and if you realiz that's why you're on
the show you're trying to sell this book
right but if you read it in as a tone as
pedantic as the silly questions you've
been asking me all this time no stupid
book you didn't read it you started out
the show by admitting you read no more
than the first couple of paragraphs no I
I said I read the whole thing you don't
even know what the ending was you think
it's a book about home safety for is
about you're talking the the the the
excerpt that I read which I randomly
turned to by accident I I did not
pre-plan this the whole thing is about
the TV was on the floor you're talking
about a TV in a bathroom with water on
the floor which is a potential Hazard it
is but does he fall no does he get elect
no absolutely he's avoiding an accident
I'm not the kind but I'm not the kind of
writer who has to tell people be careful
when you're in the bathro you are
telling people no I'm not it's not my
place to tell people paragraph
completely randomly open to is which was
completely by accident luck of the draw
try it again see if you find anything in
there about I don't have to try it again
I know what the book is about let me try
I'm surprised that you you don't even
seem to know what's in your own book I
know what's in my book I wrote you know
you must be like on drugs or something
maybe you're simply my mother used to
say you're on
drugs if we had time I could see some
identification to see if you actually
are who my used say that's what my
that's why when she would when I'd be
writing and she would say do we that's
when she wrote part of she um she only
wrote the title she only wrote the title
well you see we've already dragged out a
a horrible truth which has taken place
which you've you've you've lied and
you've you've said it's not about home
safety which it is you you've told us
that no one in your family had anything
to do with it which is another just the
just okay she all right chapters the
even chapters she wrote but that those
are the only one everyone el else is is
is is my all mind absolutely and I chose
most of the words and I edited what she
did and I also I gave her a thesaurus of
Christmas well I'm sorry that we we had
to have you on the on the show I'm not
particularly pleased to been here it
didn't I I didn't I don't think it went
too well it's obviously you're you're
you're trying to be difficult you're
you're trying to to criticize and to
antagonize me and and saying that the
book was was about something how do you
think I feel when you've got 12 you got
cartons of Tang down there did you allow
to share did you ask me if I wanted any
well that's just enough for me I I you
can have one if you want to but what are
you doing going on an Apollo Mission
sometime soon well this is no time to
make jokes on television this is a a
serious television pardon me well this
is this is um I'm very sorry I'm things
didn't uh go very well um we we we've
got to end the show um well okay he's
leaving now um
I'm very sorry it didn't uh go very well
today we've had another um uh problem
guest on as we usually always have in
the past um please uh stay tuned next
time we will be back with another uh a
better I promise episode of tight line
thank you um um and remember uh Easter
baskets by uh General
Dynamics thank you
[Music]
shut
up
bye death squad death squad you're a
specially trained team you go in
anywhere there is trouble your death
squad a Strike Team so sacred not even
the president knows they exist they're
stuck the sniper Bob The Psychotic
homicidal maniac close the team leader
Bruce the homosexual and Michael dakus
using high-tech Firepower and torture
death squad eliminates any obstacle in
its way death squad Death Squad action
figures sold separately death squad
torture chamber and interrogation room
not included Death Squad