it's time for Dr sphincter narrow world
of Wonders
[Music]
with Dr
sphincter hello this is Dr sphincter and
this is Austin Minnesota and the date is
May 18th marking the 100th anniversary
of the horel corporation created in 1891
by George a horel and an associate using
some old packing equipment they had
bought from a defunct Packing House well
over these past 100 years the company
has grown remarkably and today we're
especially celebrating the food product
spam there's spam um products being sold
and spam contests of several kinds
including a sculpture and eating contest
they have one thing in mind today and
that is finishing their spam their seven
out serving of spam in the fastest
possible
time the time to beat now is 1 minute 18
seconds oh and here's a good one this is
the best one so far doesn't appear to um
represent any particular tank uh maybe
the does not look like the M1 Abrams or
Sherman but it is a a tank nonetheless
made out of the quality meat product
spam for Operation Desert spam
[Music]
you know there is a story about George
hormell who is who is known for his
Penny wiseness and his and his
frugality uh he was in the plant one day
and there was a piece of meat on the
floor and he walked up to the workers
and he took a dollar bill out of his uh
wallet and tore it up and threw it on
the floor and he said this is the same
thing that you do that if you throw meat
on the floor
[Music]
behind me is the main Hormel uh Factory
facility uh each day workers uh stream
in through the the massive parking lots
and the which surround the the huge and
massive factory buildings the factory
workers are wearing a greenish yellowish
smoks with hats with face Shields to
protect their faces from the splatter
[Music]
the horale
girls
well it's been another wonderful
celebration of the horal corporation
100th year this May 18th
1991 commemorating May 18th
1891 when George a opened his first
packing plant on the shores of the the
Ceda River and someday we will return to
this wonderful place we will return to
this wonderful place of Austin Minnesota
and the hormell
corporation thank you
[Music]
oh
um hello and uh welcome once again to
tight line tonight tight line is brought
to you by antix when it's time to relax
don't tonight we have with us a a
prominent author who's just written a
book called tight places tight place
and um his name is Dr Randy H hand and
he'll uh we'll be discussing the book
Thank you for coming tonight Dr hand
well thank you for having me on the show
drct F so tell us a little bit about um
your background of your research well my
my academic uh background is Berkeley I
I spent several years there thesis when
did you write the book well I finished
at the end of last year I spent about 2
years were you in a tight space no but
you know that's a very interesting
question thank you thank you and that's
what my book deals with human beings in
tight places yes yes yes I I noticed
right away here that there's some very
very interesting chapter names the first
chapter I I see here is called hard
architecture what what sort of
architecture do you consider to be hard
well by hard uh I don't necessarily mean
physically hard but um intrinsically
hard hard yes yes I think you know what
I mean yeah yeah yes it's the materials
the way things are arranged um the hard
bolted on things which confine the human
form into a natural position so so I
would imagine that you studied um
institutions um hospitals factories
schools yes yeah even things like like
airplanes there is a chapter on mass
transportation oh oh wow airplanes are
very tight and close yes they are that's
wonderful well let's let's look at some
of the examples that you have here in
the book They're they're very very
interesting um here is um a um a picture
I I I believe it's a picture of uh of a
um some University buildings yes that's
University of California for yes oh yes
yes you can see they're they're they're
building beautiful buildings very very
clean they beautiful buildings and this
I see this one even has barbed wire
around Library no no that's a different
space what's this um I don't know off
hand what is it is is a prison uh I I
don't know you don't know this is your
book I can't see
it
please what's on page
45 I really don't know you're you're
claiming to write this book and you
don't know you don't even know what's in
it
well okay okay well um let's let's look
at some other examples here the the
author whoever it may be decided to
include some examples of an airport of
the people and the area around an
airport mhm you you can see how the
people the people sit apart because the
chairs are arranged Too Close yes right
that is very close and that's the main
problem here I don't know about you but
when I get home in the evening I like to
relax I like to loosen up I like to sit
back and I think most people like to do
that so you you went to school at
Berkeley yes in California yes Berkeley
where where did you get these ideas well
where does one get ideas how did you
come across these ideas of being loose
at home and comfortable well I think
it's just basic human nature I want to
be comfortable you think it's just basic
human nature to allow yourself to be
lazy and and loose and to actually
rearrange constructed from cement and
other rock hard materials mhm well an
airport is a very good example of all
the bad things the hard architecture the
bolted on things the um the funnels and
tunnels well what an airport actually is
it's it's a funnel you walk in and then
you're funneled into smaller passage
waves you you go through and you go
through you go through the orange
Concourse through the metal detection
machine through yet yet another small
Passage
and you find that upsetting yes and
after that into yet one more smaller
tube into the airplane itself which is a
small tube I think airport should be
even smaller and more tub you walk into
an airport and immediately airports have
very very high ceilings and are very
very big and open yes they are very big
and wide and open let me when you walk
into an airport it should be like
walking in or or under or in a cave or
something I just don't feel like I'm
going in anything when I go into an
airport because it's just such a big
high ceiling in an open space I feel
like I'm still outside and I don't feel
safe or happy at all and for you to say
that airports should be less tubular and
and more open it's it's beyond me could
we go on to another
chapter well I'll go to another chapter
but it's just a waste of time go
ahead when the CBS building opened in
New York City there was a long list of
reg ulations governing Behavior people
couldn't put plants on their desks move
furniture or change their office without
written permission and that's an
experience I actually had at one point
it actually took two inter office memos
just to change a light bulb well I think
that's wonderful we need to have
structures in our in our buildings and
companies to ensure that the highest
amount of productivity is achieved oh no
the highest amount of productivity is
not achieved by all these M how can we
have a productive society when when
people are allowed to just put things on
their desks flowers clutter and
portraits um bags of of food and the
flowers will spill and things will smell
why don't you listen to me when when our
country was the most productive in in
the past 20 or so years we have straight
away from these hard tight settings and
we've adapted more loose LAX and lazy
areas to work in no wonder we've gone so
downhill in the past 20 years because
we've strayed away from this we're we're
working in these these these comfortable
loose open there's carpeting they have
carpeting in them and and plants and
flowers I guess I should have gone over
this book a little bit more but but
before I had you on I am sorry I I don't
know why but I am sorry I should have
known because I I I didn't see this
before but I should have known it says
up here it says
psychology psychology is something that
we all must avoid at all costs and you I
don't I don't know where you came from
some place Berkeley Berkeley yes place
that I know is very disgusting I can
just imagine what you tell me what do
you find disgusting about it about what
well about Berkeley what do you find so
disgusting everything Berkeley is a very
socially active school it's a very
socially pathetic School pathetic yes
it's it's got people who are always
whining about something and it's just a
it's just a waste of time listen here
you production time I spent 8 years at
Berkeley and besides that I was involved
in a lot of the demonstration and
marches we got a lot done you're trying
to tell me that that was all a waste of
time okay that's it I'm going to have to
ask you to leave now um I think I'd like
to leave thank you thank you for
watching tight line um how do I get down
from here I don't know we'll be back uh
next time and
and I'm very sorry it didn't go very
well today
[Music]
goodbye and thank you very much and
that's a
wrap G dock another great
show oh Bob you look a little sluggish
well to tell you the truth doc I haven't
been feeling so well I'm constipated
pretty bad and I got another shoot to do
in 2 minutes oh Bob looks like you need
the drip I need the drip no flux
intervenous laxative drip flux is the
new fast acting intervenous laxative why
don't you try some out now you may feel
some slight
discomfort just how fast acting is new
flux now that fad
hello this is Dr spher and this is
another
minute I don't know why people are so
upset about being embarrassed there's
nothing wrong with being embarrassed or
being ashamed of something being
embarrassed is very healthy when you're
embarrassed you're aware that something
is wrong something is always wrong isn't
it when you're embarrassed you know that
something is wrong and you know that you
have to take care of it when you're not
embarrassed you tend to be loose and LAX
and lazy but we we must not be lazy or
loose or LAX at all when we're
embarrassed we're tight and we're aware
at all times of what can happen when
we're when we're when we're not
embarrassed and we're uninhibited things
things can get get loose and get get LAX
and lazy but but we must always be very
very tight and very embarrassed I don't
see what's wrong with being embarrassed
being embarrassed has helped many many
people many of the of the of the the
finest actors get get very embarrassed
or or or stage fright if if you're not
embarrassed just remember that you
should be embarrassed at some point
Thank
[Music]
You seating Department God I haven't
been down there in 3
years okay
[Music]
it's a it's a good one
[Applause]
[Music]
all
oh
oh damn
[Music]
yes yeah I've got a telax for the
seating
Department thank
you jerk seating Department arrange 100
chairs for stress reduction meeting
stress reduction
meeting 4 M from mean
diameter diameter established at chair
45 46 50 and 56
[Applause]
perfect make a final Quality Inspection
oh oh I suppose you're waiting for
something silly or funny to
happen like all the chairs falling over
or some kind of stupid silly stunt
that's the problem with you people
you're not willing to just watch someone
successfully completing his task see