you feeling
good you're on the
move you're working
hard
[Music]
and today more than ever people all over
America are turning to the natural
goodness and light Taste of SLO and at
only 100 calories per serving SLO is the
perfect main course for today's on
thee-o active Lifestyles so choose SLO
it's not just a side dish
anymore now you're eating
light with every
B you're on the
top and you did it
with presented by the American SLO
Council and this station
[Applause]
[Music]
oh hello and uh welcome once again to
tight line um I'm Dr sper and tonight
tight line is brought to you by big
piles of uh brown rocks um uh tonight on
tight line we have a fisherman who's
going to discuss uh fishing lures and
baiting and and Tackle his name is
DeForest roykirk thank you for coming
thank you very much first time on
television uh really I'd rather be out
fishing though I'd rather be fishing yes
I got that splattered all over my truck
bumper sticker I would rather be fishing
I'd rather be F I'd like to get a big
one that would cover my entire truck yes
well uh M Mr roykirk has uh um worked
for several years in the fishing
industry yeah canning doing everything
canning net and then you you you do
canning and mostly fishing and I I I I
make my lures too I'm starting my own
company of lure making really yeah what
is that it's called Amore a lure really
which is in French it means I love so to
make lures how how many employees do you
have I have two there's me in the back
working all day just finding uh just
finding stuff on the the floor and
making lures out of it and then there's
Tim up front on the cash register yes
but uh then I I go you have any kind of
employee compensation or benefit program
yeah I pay them that's U that's better
than some communist
countries yes
yeah anyway I brought some of my lures
here if I could
start I'm doing some stuff Let's uh take
a look at some of your uh lures there Mr
Roy Kirk okay if your camera can pick
this up we're oh
over that's okay here we got um this is
uh this is I call this my uh this is the
first lure I ever made it's made out of
congealed uh Dippity Doo my wife's
Dippity Doo oh really and it's it's a
great lure uh fish go after this fish
who really care about their hair go for
this kind of stuff here and over here
this is this fish don't really have hair
do
they well they don't really feel they
want to have hair you see they want to
have hair okay and this one over here
this is made out of I had a triple
bypass operation two years ago and this
is a cholesterol that was taken out of
me and it's a very personal kind of lure
here and this is yeah this just
congealed cholesterol right here and
fish go after this they think they just
think they're going to get breakfast
when you eat this one this is a great
one and uh this one over here I just uh
I just found that in the cat box I don't
know what that is but I use that for a
lot of other things and this this is I
called my dep charger if you see right
here this is a little uh little uh fill
it with h with TNT the fish bites onto
this thing explodes blows the fish head
off blows all the skin off you pull it
up you got a nice fed fish sitting right
there ready to fry up there right in the
boat if you want to risk taking a bunson
burner on the boat which I I won't
recommend because that's not very good
and I got another lure right here this
is a this is well this is another
Dippity Do lure I don't know what's
doing over here it should be uh should
be over here I like like to keep all
these things straight here and this lure
right here is made out of uh this is
made out of old Prince
albums uh my my my my daughter buys
these Prince albums and they're all
purple and I don't know what the hell I
I always take them out and I burn
them and uh this is this is the material
I come up with is just kind of shoddy
little material here and U I got a lot
of stories I can tell you but oh here
here oh this is a scary one look at this
this scares the hell out of fish smaller
than this
you don't want any fish smaller than
this or otherwise you can't eat them uh
sometimes uh firsttime fishes are out
there and it's kind of a ride of patches
we make them uh swallow any the first
fish they catch you know if it's small
enough and they they have to take their
pants off and they swallow this fish
hole and uh but anyway I'm off the track
here this is uh this is the scare away
of the very small fish it's a it's like
a lobster here a purple Lobster and they
they see that and they just head for the
hills and over here we got this is these
are leaches you see kind of looks like
War of the Worlds there and
who yeah hor and Wells would love this
one anyway this is this is a leech uh
and a lot of fish they like to go after
leeches I don't know why I hate leeches
myself they they suck the blood out of
you they they they they get in your your
underwear you don't know what to do but
anyway this is a leech thing they just
they just love to eat up them leeches
and uh over here I got some hooks these
are Big hooks these are for your
masochistic fish who don't want any kind
of Illusions or anything they they just
want to go right after uh after the hook
they just want to jump right on that
hook they don't they don't want any kind
of false kind of you know playing around
with this stuff they want to know that
they're they're going to grab onto a
hook and they're going to their death
that's all they want to know about but
uh yeah I got some uh other fishing
stories too there was one day I was
fishing with my friend Wendell and we
were sitting in the boat we're sitting
in there and we've caught about our
limit more than our limit you know uh
anyway we're sitting there and uh just
getting kind of bored and everything we
didn't forgot forgot to talk for a while
so we decided to just have some fun
rocking the boat there all of a sudden
we're rocking and rocking and rocking
all a sudden both of us fall out we land
both into the lake there we're right in
the lake there can you see that we look
up there's fish in the boat and we're in
the
lake a that we we were just cracking we
were in the lake and the fish were in
the boat M you know it should be the
other way around should be always the
the other way around we were thicking at
at that time thought that was kind of
funny and uh yeah there's this other
time this uh this uh this this bear was
uh was uh out in the woods there was
running around and uh and we saw this
bear running around so we stayed out in
the
lake and there was this other time that
uh I was I got really burned really
really bad and I started to peel
immediately immediately started to peel
so I start ripping that off ripping it
off ripping it off and we actually I
made this lure right here out of that um
I haven't used it yet though I'm still
trying to figure out what to what to do
with that but I've discovered a brand
new fish out there there's uh you've
heard of your big mouth bass uh I I once
caught a loudmouth bass it's a it's a
very large bass that that talks back to
you it does it I don't understand what
it's saying but it's
just I guess it's ticked off cuz I
caught it and but anyway I've only
caught one of these I only know of one
of these and uh anyway that's how it
goes no more fishing stories I was out
there all by myself once and I was
leaning back and I was going to throw
you know do do the real thing here with
my new back there at a 10 lb line and I
whipped that sucker out there caught me
right here in the back ripped off my two
pay I had a toue at the time before I I
got that new chemical from Sweden now I
have hair all over my body even all the
way down my back I tell you my wife
won't even take a shower with me anymore
anyway ripped off my toue and that and
that's just a minute
no just a
minute please hello just a
minute
W sphin so you think you can get some
relief no you have been in violation of
many many rules of
kuna this you know you have been guilty
of lassitude laziness and in attention
to the topic at
hand I issue a challenge to you to your
native land follow me the land of Kun
khalip
[Music]
this is the land of my family it has
been held by us for more than 2,000
Earth
years this
[Music]
ISM s up
you are prepared to have this ceremony
viewed by an
[Music]
outworld well how far do you Pledge Your
Allegiance to this
Kirk he is my friend and he is tight
the tightest man I
know very
well what you are about to see is a
tradition in kunala that goes back to
ages and ages from time in the beginning
from time in Memorial it is the heart
and soul of
spinther very well let the ceremony
begin
you are within your bounds to have me
choose who this opponent shall
be I will have to pick the
Challenger
toow you must pick one of my crew people
pick a
cameraman very
well camera number
three fresh meaty Young he'd make a fine
prize camera number two full of life and
vigor and Camera number
one another good
sutor but I have made a
decision you
him I am his friend
[Music]
C you must forbid your choice remember
your ancestry and let the battle
begin
forbid
forbid in the name of my father and
mother forbid it he is my guest and my
friend
I cannot fight him
stin my word is the final word my word
is the law let the battle begin s
there's a strange power in me I must
fight present him with the weapons
oh
[Music]
spark
no spark
no TR
[Music]
car clear the
weapons and bring on the AR Moon
f
[Music]
CA
the deadly remains of a deadly battle
you have won this costly
Victory live long and prosper
[ __ ] I shall do
neither I have killed my guest and my
friend live long and prosper to
power and then our had this friend named
Raymond who was a really big fat guy he
was so fat his wrinkles looked like a
city I don't know but anyway he was so
fat anyway we spent a whole week fishing
out there and he was sitting there he
was very quiet guy very quiet he sitting
there and he was dead I found he was
dead but he could still fish I mean you
can be dead and you can still fish
that's the beauty of fishing you
Kirk yeah
Jim yeah oh oh I I I'm very sorry uh Mr
roykirk you've been a very interesting
guest um thank you for coming on the
show this evening and talking about
fishing and you're still there you're
still alive right I'm
alive you can't tell me you were about
to have an emotional display that was
about ready to bring the house down well
it was simply my my logical response
that you were conducting the show well
and you'd explained your fishing
techniques to all of our viewers right
right in a pig's
eye
well thank you for watching the show
this evening um we'll be back uh next
week uh with another show it's been a
pleasure having Mr on the show this
evening
[Music]
[Applause]