[Music]
Chase one this is tight link do copy
roger tight link this is Chase one we
copy
what what's the
problem F we receiving major turbulence
back here Dr sphincter are we at uh
nominal parameters now with our our
corner window yes the uh pressure is
back down to normal and the
toast toast is
done here's your
to thank you
day one of our journey after
encountering a slight decompression
problem inside the cabin of our
conversion van we approached our first
rest area to tour in Paris
Minnesota a perfect shape the circle ens
shrouded the rest area where the rest
rooms are located please observe the no
smoking sign as you
enter and here we are warmed by the
interior of the rest area you can see
there is an adequate phone and adequate
restroom facilities which are always
kept
clean we can't go in there now now we
will have an interview with the
caretaker of this rest
area hello your name is Homer Hansen
this is Homer Hansen and you are the
caretaker of the Moose Creek Harris
Minnesota rest station that's right
thank you for coming with us today Mr
Hansen when was this St
erected I don't really know for sure but
I think it it's possibly about 1972 or
1973 it's very nice well thank you for
coming with us and talking to us today
this is Homer Hansen we are at the Goose
Creek Parris Minnesota rest
[Music]
station he's not watching where he's D
watch where you're driving where you're
driving going
flat well here we are it is day one of
our safari and our CH team vehicle has
had a problem the rear uh right tire has
experienced some difficulties they are
changing the tire on the chase vehicle
keep in mind that we the main vehicle we
are in constant contact with the chase
vehicle which supplies us with updates
of what's coming up on the road and
keeps us constantly supplied with all
the necessary equipment that we need the
weather has been inclement towards us it
has been raining steadily ever since we
left our um first checkpoint uh in
Minneapolis it's been uh raining and the
weather has not been cooperating with us
as we would like it
to now the chase team has been trained
in order to make a tire change as
quickly as possible before we have left
our first area in Minneapolis they had
had a tire change done in 15 seconds
this however is not the case uh because
we've had weather problems now I but
they have been trained to do it very
rapidly uh before we left hold the guy
I'm holding it I'm only a human or is it
baby oil my technicians have just
informed me that there is a pudle of
fluid in the um anterior position of the
chase vehicle where the spare tire was
located they are fixing this by
installing makeshift sump pumps to
remove the fluid from the back of the
vehicle we should be on our way very
shortly
all right let's roll let's go with our
problem behind us and the chase team
once again operational we were able to
set out for the next rest
[Music]
area he's in the shoulder again he's in
this Arie get him out of the shoulder
Arie Roger uh Dr sphin is this a
tactical maneuver I don't know why more
people don't drive on the shoulder it's
never crowded
there's no one on here and it's very
SM is this absolutely necessary at the
same time it we drive on the shoulder
after making up L Time by traveling on
the shoulder the crew and I decided to
have a quick bite at Toby and Hinkley
Minnesota the crew chose Hardy yet runny
and sloppy meals however I ordered a
plain wiener later we spoke with a very
special
guest well we stopped to uh have a bite
to eat at toes in hinley Minnesota and
I'm here with Big Dave mura who is a gun
fighter and who performs a gunfighting
show here at a uh Park a theme park in
hinley Minnesota um could you tell us a
little bit about your uh gun sure this
is an 1860 Army Colt they consider this
the pistol that won the West first of
all to load it you have to put it on
half Dock and pour each cylinder with 30
grains of powder
then you put a lead ball on it and smash
the lead ball down
inside then you have to put a little bit
of grease on each cylinder so it doesn't
chain fire a chain fire is when they all
go off at once and that's a lot of fun
if you know what I mean then you put a
cap over each one of these little holes
down here and when you pull the hammer
all the way back it lines your cylinder
up with your Barrel you put your finger
in there to pull the trigger
in well thank you very much we finished
our meal at which I suffered only a
slight gastrointestinal
[Music]
disturbance and so we said goodbye to
toes in Hinkley Minnesota and we
continued our safari
after realizing our cameraman was
missing we had to pick him up and we're
back on the road 2 hours
later jerky time oh goody goody yes it
is 1658 we have uh our designated beef
jerkey break right now have that charted
on the log
[Music]
thank
you we approached our second rest area a
Hidden
Paradise oh this is just like the other
one it's the same exact
thing Beginning to Look a Lot white
[Music]
Christmas well we are now at the blue
star Memorial rest
area well this rest stop uh we will not
tour because it is
very much the same and there you see the
blue star Memorial Highway sign which is
a tribute to the armed forces that have
defended the United States of
America oh 99 and you saw capsules on
the wall 99 and you saw
capsules you take one down pass it
around 98 andn sou capil on the
wall 98 and South capsules on the wall
98 and you saw capsules you take one
down pass it around the man's crazy the
man is crazy suddenly the unthinkable
happened ice began forming on our
vehicle making it
uncontrollable it's getting pretty rough
up
here the barometer still dropping it's
down
7 6 should we engage shoot engage put on
safety helmets
now emergency safety gear in place shoot
engaging 5 Seconds 4 3
21 positive shoot inflation setting
hydraulic systems pressure 85 PSI and
holding we have a 5%
burnout compensate
[Music]
thanks to a skillfully trained team of
professionals we had made it to the next
rest area when the right equipment and
the right people for the job come
together any can happen thanks
boys hello and and welcome to Dr
sphincter
minute um this this is this is the
second season of the show and it's been
going very well thank you very much and
the lights just went
out um now I'm I'm distracted and I'm
all upset see yesterday I was upset too
and they made me come in here and do
this I've been very upset lately I've
been very upset about many things
primarily I've been upset
about about about about words that
people are using
and I I've I I feel that that people are
ignoring me I don't know why I I feel
that people don't have confidence in me
and I think many people share this
problem also we we can help ourselves
get get be become more confident can't
we see if if we if we just think that
that that um well I can tell you that we
we all can can do anything we want and
we can all be be very
Happ you know good guns really do mean a
lot to
me doct sphincter I've had my AK-47 for
years now and it's provide consistently
good
results
AK-47 it's a great assault
[Music]
rifle we are now uh approximately 20
minutes out of Hibbing Minnesota which
is where we are going to visit the open
pit mines uh supplying the whole country
with iron precious iron ore to uh
fashion Metals now this is a special
rest area since it is a travel
information center not only is it a rest
stop but uh Travelers can also come here
and be is fully equipped with a staff to
provide
information notice the the butts hand
we're going to check out the
Laboratories
now this is the uh men's laboratory here
at the anchor Lake rest area and travel
information
center it is a very convenient and clean
laboratory as you can see it has has a
nice Skylight for natural
lighting and urinals and um
[Music]
styles and so with dry hands we set out
for the exciting open strip minds of
Hibbing Minnesota cameraman he he gets
you know he gets everything I think him
and uh I think him and sphincter might
have something going it's possible
well we've made it to
the historic uh strip mining uh landmark
in Hibbing Minnesota called the kelet
hill Annex Park
uh the uh Park is
uh the uh the park is still closed for
the season so the uh trip up here was uh
a waste of
time there was a candy shop on the way
sh well there isn't a holiday end in
this town we'll just have to go with
this one two and a half Stars AC cable
TV all I care about is just got a double
bed what Road did we just pass oh there
it is initiate 180 maneuver all right
just a a second open the
door cold out here come on all right
rest and relaxation and big room let's
go what is this a minute bed is this
this was supposed to be a double damn it
I'm not going to stand for this this is
supposed to be aamn double I I think
they as tight as it
finally I can be back alone and wind up
ah oh this is very nice very clean
accommodations yep good thing I switched
keys with those jerks all right
33 I'm going to go check out the
[Music]
bathroom
M everything in order beer beer where's
the beer I don't know I got I got a beer
in my bag wait a minute no I got to get
special beer beer beerer beerer what
[Music]
time
what
what on around
here
this making this
noise excuse me excuse me what's going
on in here there's extraneous noise
leaking into my room from this room look
at this filthy mess oh I should have
never hired you from that dope top rock
and roll room oh look at that M okay
bring the microphone close here
okay you stupid idiot Give me the
micophone give me the microphone come
on
hello as you can see that's my
microphone hello as you can see the is
some hope we have seen some some blue
some some blue sky is beginning to poke
through and we can see now some hope
lies in the future for this horrible
weather to break turn
the would you shut
[Music]
up which way which way left left
left good
[Music]
hold it hold hold it hold
it we are on our second day of our
journey and we are uh in clo
Minnesota uh it's a small town
which there were several uh factories
located as you can see here is the
Potlatch Factory here in front of us now
it's a Uh Wood Products uh plant and
they
uh manufacture pulp from uh wood
products into paper materials and
products it's
uh clouding up
again and I hope we can make it to
uh miji get made the blue box and uh
just a moment just a moment the computer
is showing that our satellite link ml 66
will go 100% failure in 28 minutes would
you uh say that we have a reliable 28
minutes to the failure
Point yes that is a reliable figure well
uh I think we need to do uh let's go
ahead with an Eva to replace uh ml Echo
unit uh
966 CH team W this is GL wonderer our ml
66er Communications satellite is out uh
recommending Eva for replacement at
[Music]
copy sa team one I'm getting a break up
on that signal did you copy that last
[Music]
transmission1 this is pl1 do you
copy what are your coordinate
team
one1 this is tight link
one we have lost total
[Music]
communication
what I'm picking up readings here that
the ml 66 unit has been removed instead
of replaced repeat removed well whose
idea was that oh
hell I can't believe that wasn't open it
opens
tomorrow open pit mining was closed oh
it's not a total loss yes this trip has
been a complete loss the weather's been
terrible well there's still Paul bunan
land well that'll probably be closed too
it's warmer than
yesterday it's it's 16.3 de warm shut up
well here we are brard Minnesota and
this is it the granddaddy of them all
Babe the Blue Ox this as you can see is
Paul bunan land located in Brainard
Minnesota and we've just made it here to
see babe the blueox and Paul bunion
himself well let's go and have some
fun oh
damn it it's
close let's go come
on go let's go it's closed oh come
on I want to go on the
rides Dr spor we're leaving
now this is uh another rest stop we have
uh just arrived at you can see it is uh
quite a bit smaller than the other ones
we have visited they do seem to be uh
diminishing in size as we go you notice
here is a
monument um and this is seems to be all
which um uh uh makes this rest stop up
uh this is a very sparse rest
stop so you can see this is the the
entire rest stop is what what you see
here well
hello well I would like to thank you
very much for joining us today on the
Sprinter tour 89 a rest stop Safari
thank you very much for joining us I was
hoping that there would be a little bit
more I was hoping that there would be a
little bit more to show you but uh this
is our last rest area and they seem to
be diminishing in size so we'll have to
say goodbye for now and thank you very
much where's M what is going on around
here
jeez 350 hour what do you
expect come on let's go now move
[Music]