cats can be mean you guys they can be
mean I was at my friend's house and he
had a cat and his cat was just
scratching his couch just tearing it
apart just ribbing looking at my friend
like what are you going to do about it
this is my domain and I was like buddy
your uh your cat's destroying your couch
you should probably have them stop doing
that and my friend was like no man it's
just natural it's what they do it's just
natural I was like natural really I've
never been camping in the woods and just
seen a bunch of cats ripping apart of
futon like oh no way look at this it's
in their natural habitat you never see
this oh this is beautiful there's going
to town on that thing oh now now they're
playing with those laser pointers they
build in the wild this is a special day
this is such a good
day yeah animals are fun they're they're
cool some animals are weird three
grillas escaped from our Zoo did you
guys hear about that three gorillas
escaped from the Minnesota Zoo they had
to lock down the zoo the news was was
all over it they're like Zoo lock down
Zoo lock down and I was like what's a
zoo lockdown like I've never heard of
that is that like a prison lockdown
where the sirens go off and all the
animals have to get down on the
ground and giraffes are like son of a
[ __ ] oh man this is so far down I hate
these
lockdowns the fish are like I can't get
to the bottom i' have never we're going
to get in trouble that turtle's just on
a rock too I don't even know what he's
doing
yeah animals they're they're wild some
animals could be mean there was a guy
walking to work at 5: in the morning he
was attacked by three coyotes yeah isn't
that horrible I can't even imagine what
it would be like to have to work at 5:
in the morning that's
disgusting yeah I got up at one today I
wasn't not attacked by one coyote it was
the best day ever I was like this is
going to be a great day no coyote attack
so far ah love and life he was attacked
by three coyotes and in the article he
said he was just happy that it wasn't a
baby or an old person and I was like
what kind of baby attacks you at 5:00 in
the morning
you need to get a different job it's too
early you're getting attacked by the
elderly and babies