[Applause]
this uh this seems like a good City to
have a nice healthy beard in so I grew
it out just for
you you know what I'm talking about
don't you
[Laughter]
beardo it takes a real man to grow a
beard
I like saying it like that because I
feel like the bigger your beard gets the
higher your voice should go because the
testosterone in your body has been
diverted to the beard
cause so like the bigger your beard get
you're like oh
hello not every guy can grow a
beard I can't no you can't that's why I
look right at you
I have an uncanny gift at pointing out
people who cannot grow facial hair and
you their uh the
champ let me ask you this you try to
grow a beer that looks like a sick old
cat with diabetes on your face like
Jesus
Christ that poor animal on your
face put it out of its
misery I like that first week when you
grow a beard though because people don't
know whether you're growing a bearder
your life is falling
apart people are always like hey Tony
are you are you doing
okay and I always go yeah I always wear
[Laughter]
robes when did robes become the official
outfit of
sadness right used to be a time you
could sit on your front lawn and a robe
cleaning a gun
and people thought everything was all
right