[Applause]
uh another thing old T-Bone is scared of
uh scared of dying it's a legitimate I
mean it's a legitimate
fear I'm not singling out that she
should be afraid of
it although you are getting up
there terrified of dying scared of it
but when I do die I hope that they
perfect the Hologram technology they had
for
Tupac so when you come to visit my grave
it's a very interactive
experience there'll just be a big red
button on my Tombstone you you'll push
it and I
go
hello I'm Tony and as you know I'm
dead please press the following options
to complete your
experience press one to hear me OV
exaggerate a life
experience press two for a long overdue
apology press three to make it all about
you you've selected
three now please select your dance
move you've selected did Macarena for
some
reason just be
like I'm
sorry if you think this is weird you're
the one who keeps coming to the hole in
the ground where my dead body is buried