[Applause]
I saw a lost dog poster in my
neighborhood it make someone
sad
a did they well did they well did they
find
it I mean you're going to talk about how
the dog was rejoined with its owner and
oh God I hope this is a happy ending to
this I have so many hopes and dreams on
this premise that you just barely
said goddamn dog
lover there's so much more behind your
reaction than
dogs a lot more riding on
that but I
digress so yeah I found this lost dog
poster in my
neighborhood and I was like I need to
find this
dog I need to make this my mission if
only to take naked pictures of myself
with the dog and text them to the owner
is this your dog
be like what the [ __ ] are you doing with
my
dog like oh these two things are
mutually exclusive I'm just always naked
but I want to make sure it's your dog is
this your dog is this your
dog point a knife at the dog is this
your
dog it's like what is wrong with you hey
I'm not the one who lost him