[Applause]
I want to know why there hasn't been a
haunted house completely made up around
the idea of pregnancy
scares that be the scariest goddamn
thing you ever been to just walk in like
room after room it's more scary than
less like the positive pregnancy test
ah so we have to have a talk room ah a
you're going to be a father room oh the
miracle of childbirth room Jesus Christ
let me out of here and at the exit it's
just a vat full of
condoms and it's just dude's like Jesus
Christ why does this place
exist who came up with this
thing guys just putting one on after the
other we got to be careful you haven't
seen the things I've seen
so I've been divorced twice