I think we have to teach the Next
Generation about taxes folks if you have
kids teach
them and the best time you can do this
is on
Halloween yeah see cuz they're going to
put in about eight full hours of power
trick-or-treating they're going to be
bringing home a nice big bag of what
should be take-home
candy greet that little tyke at the door
hey that's a nice big B of candy you got
there Harry
Potter but first of all now see just
because you made this much we have to
take away this
much income
tax then to ensure you'll have candy in
your old
age pay the soul security
tags quit
crying you going to see it in 50 60
years okay tell you what we'll just put
it right up here won't touch it till
then I got a level with you man
Grandpa's going to eat all
that you have grandchildren of your own
don't you oh last of all we can't forget
that state tax can
we that's right we're Minnesota aren't
we you want to take that train to St
Paul don't
you there's your Snickers
bar oh wait wait here this is funny hold
on payday
oh who who you can eat that right now
H sales
tax you know I think kids are smarter
than that I bet if you did that your kid
he wouldn't even get dressed up the next
year probably spend the whole evening on
the couch in front of the tube and when
Mom put out that big bowl of candy for
the other kids he just going to walk
over to that bowl dump it in his bag he
I'm on welfare
oh