hi I'm Tim slel and this is Tim slel
live uh this is the third video I did
all of them were actually done live I
don't know why we chose to call this one
live but we did uh we we kind of rushed
into it it was it it was I was doing I
was booked at the 200 libertarian
National Convention and my distributor
says well we got to tape that and uh so
we did but I I I wasn't ready I had just
bought a brand new suit and uh the
tailor when I was getting it fitted uh I
said are you going to put belt loops on
it he goes no no the lay of the suit is
better when you don't wear a belt well I
did not realize that meant you had to
buy suspenders I I thought because it
was tailored it probably would fit so
snugly that it would just just be fine
without a belt I thought that's what he
was telling me um so as I was walking to
the stage in my new suit my pants
started falling down and I I I you will
notice in this video that I have my hand
in my pocket almost the entire time and
basically I was just trying not to
expose myself and uh uh I I've I've
never enjoyed the show for that reason
but uh maybe you'll find the Shaden
Freud funny
good evening ladies and gentlemen my
name is Tim slel for those of you who do
not
know and I'd like to take this
opportunity to announce my candidacy for
president
oh good lord
[Laughter]
no uh v no no I don't like
politics if I if I like if I like
politics I wouldn't be a
comic that'd be crossing over to the
wrong side I uh I I love this I I've
been I've been having uh a gas here
since I found my
luggage and and and I'd like how I about
to hand for the balam group for making
everything right with this event
and me I've got a clean pair of
underwear on right
now and my cheeks are happy
so so yeah this is this is I I love
doing these things man I've uh um I
think I think the first one I did was
Salt Lake City in 1992 and it was it was
a big experience for me because I I've
always heard heard stories about what
happened when they filmed The Wizard of
Oz how when all the munchkins got into
this movie Set have you heard about
these stories that that these were short
people who lived in Rural America all
over that never knew that they were
anything more than a circus freak in a
small
town and when they all came to Hollywood
all of a sudden they realized how many
people there were just like
themselves and that's what Salt Lake
City was for me was yeah
[Applause]
that's uh yeah that's uh I think I think
we need more events like this to en
encourage uh us to you know to realize
that we're more than just the freak that
lives at the end of the block that the
neighbors tell the kids to stay away
from yeah that man has
guns don't play near there
Billy I got myself I I I I I'm like I've
been having a great run as far as being
a comedian I uh I've I've I enjoy the
hell of what I do that's why I couldn't
get into politics I I I got into this
business 20 years ago after flunking out
of college and finding myself unable to
hold on a day
job during one of my last meetings with
one of my last bosses he actually looked
up at me from behind his little desk Mr
Slagle what what do you want out of a
job and I thought about that question
like just heard it for the very first
time
you
God what do I
[Music]
want I want to sleep till noon every
day work hour or
less I want to be able to say whatever
the hell I
want hang out travel around the country
I out of parties and drink free
beer lo and behold 20 years later that's
exactly what I'm doing
nice to know we live in a country where
you can achieve anything you aspire
to I actually think the yellow mic was
supposed to be mine because that one
comes off got is it is is this one is it
yellow one on can can I switch the red
one but it's taped I can't it's got a
wire I've got
a this is very limiting to me I can take
it off you sure it's not it's not going
to fall oh oh I see what you've got oh
you've got a bug on
that you're watching
me you know what happened actually when
I uh uh with the last uh the last one it
was Washington DC 4th of July
weekend and yeah that was a blast but
when I was when I was actually when I
was actually going away I was getting on
the plane to go to that one it it was
kind of funny I just I just dropped off
my bags with the sky cap and and he you
know of course asked for the government
issued
ID which which I was wondering what what
happens if you lose your license on
vacation
you I guess you become a
sovereign I'm sorry I can't go
home don't have a birth certificate
don't have a Social Security card don't
have a voter's registration so I can't
apply for a new license I guess I live
here
so anyway I handed my government issued
IID to the uh um aot's uh government
employee that was disguised as a skyc
cap and he was typing in my name and as
soon as he I could hear see right when
he hit that last e of Slagle cuz he just
kind of
went and he just goes come with me
grabbed my bags and started walking to
this place of the airport I'd never been
before and I'm just what is this he go
it's just
routine and like a routine know everyone
else bag went on that that that little
card that would be the
routine you know my bags going into some
mystery
place and and there was this huge room
and there was there was actually a bomb
sniffing machine
which yeah which was you know funny
because on my carryon I had some
fireworks that I had
brought probably would have pegged a
couple of
needles but they didn't look for they
they wanted that and fortunately it
wasn't a pot sniffing machine
either cuz you would have been short one
comic if that had
happened so anyway so the bag goes on
the conveyor belt and it's going through
this machine and I go why am I here and
he goes well well your your name popped
up and I why why did why did my name pop
up and he said well it just happens at
random and I go well isn't that funny
that randomly I'm the only one in line
that's not a godamn
Arab so it was at that moment that I
realized I I was probably on El Gore's
profile
list well which is interesting because
you know if a cop says oh there's a
carload of black kids in a white
neighborhood maybe I better ask them if
they're
[Music]
lost Al Gore says you can't do that but
if it's Arabs getting on an airplane he
takes care of the job
himself which uh El Gore I actually saw
El Gore talking about global
warming he actually said that that that
that he was talking about El Nino was
elino he actually said that El Nino is
Spanish for global
warming yeah I
yeah I think Al Gore is Democrat for Dan
[Applause]
Quail Grant I'm pretty sure that Al Gore
can spell
potato i b that Dan Quail knows that
people from Bosnia aren't called
bosniacs
[Music]
and that Michael Jackson never played
basketball because he's
white yeah I don't I don't like El Gore
he actually it's it's kind of funny he's
he's really hiding his face while while
gas prices are going up two to $2 a
gallon you know he kind of forgot that
10 years ago he thought that would be a
good
idea cuz I mean that's what he's all
about man he's a control freak wants to
tell us where we can live and what we
can drive and thinks that the world
would be better if we all road trains
and or anytime a person in government
starts talking about putting more people
on trains
[Applause]
you know and I I don't care if they run
on
time I don't like the stations they stop
at one of the things he wants he wants
he wants us all to drive electric cars
you know not
him no no he still needs a limousine
motor Cade and dc9 you know he's talking
about you
people you people should drive an
electric like the the GM ev1 have you
heard about this first production the
car
$35,000 for a car with no heat or air
conditioning top speed about 60 miles an
hour for an hour before you plug it in
overnight oh where do I sign up for
that like Al Goran doesn't even see that
there might be a flaw or two with this
design sure you're going to have to make
some small
sacrifices I'm sorry two days to drive
100 miles is not a small
sacrifice further than a day in a
goddamn covered wagon than an electric
car yes but at least it'll help the
environment how does an electric car
help the
environment cuz you know the electricity
has to come from
somewhere it doesn't just grow out of
the
socket you have to generate it this
country we generate the majority of our
electricity by burning fossil fuel same
exact thing I'm doing under the hood of
my
car electric cars have exhaust pipes
they're just out at thre Mile
[Applause]
Island
anyway and I I don't mind global warming
either you know I think Minnesota might
be pretty with a palm tree or
twoo and i' tell you think global
warming would be a godsend to the Iowa
Citrus
Growers you want to talk Farmers with no
Lucker but
bad see I I think these people that are
like that are preaching global warming
they're the same kind of
people that that that thousands of years
ago would tell us that that if we didn't
throw virgins into the volcano that that
sea monsters would eat
us and then like there there would be
like a lunar
eclipse and they go see I told you if we
weren't throwing virgins in there that
this would
happen well no you you told us that sea
monsters would eat
us well what do you think's blocking out
the Sun
well we better throw some virgins in
there hope we can find a
couple yeah but of course in A Primitive
tribe it would have been easier to find
virgins than it would be say in
Washington
[Music]
DC you know census Administration took
over
[Music]
which you know I really don't understand
why Hillary thinks that she'd be a good
Senator I mean she didn't do such a good
job at the last position she
[Music]
held well I mean if she did Bill
wouldn't have needed interns
[Applause]
look I mean really what what isn't that
the job of the first
lady when you think about it you what
else does she have to
do she doesn't have to clean house she's
got a staff of housekeepers to do that
she never has to cook she's got a staff
of chefs a staff of servants a
helicopter Air Force limousine at her
disposal she all he has to do one
[Applause]
thing doesn't take a
village little lip gloss and some
mouthwash
no I mean really folks I know what it
sounds like being sexist and cruel but
isn't that why we've always elected
almost always elected a married
president in this country is that we
kind of feel as citizens of this nation
we have a right to know we're Patriot
one is being hangered at all
[Music]
times and it's kind of an important job
because remember Bill Clinton still has
access to the magic
button that button which is capable of
raining nuclear winner down upon us all
remember that for five minutes a week
Monica Lewinsky was the most powerful
woman on
earth she could have gained access to
that button just by threatening to bite
down hard
[Music]
am I getting too off call or
no no I've I've always tried I've always
tried to keep my my performances at
these events as clean as possible but
you
know that was before Clinton got
[Music]
elected actually actually wanted to talk
about taxes how how many people think we
pay too much in taxes
by oh yeah stop I'm sorry I I forgot
where I
was it was like you all recognize that
was a suck up question
too oh yeah right we've heard it all
day see because usually when I do it
like out on the road then I can ask who
who doesn't think we pay too much in
taxes and there's always a couple
teachers in bag going
[Applause]
sorry I like
NPR CU that's what we got to we got to
teach the Next Generation about taxes
folks if you have kids you're going to
have to because the people that are
teaching your kids right now are the
only people in America that think we
don't pay enough in
taxes you're going to have to homeschool
at least this
one the best time you can do this is on
Halloween
see because they've just put in about
eight full hours of power trick-or
treating they've got a nice big bag of
what should be take home
[Music]
candy greet that little TI there hey
that's a nice big bag of candy you got
there little Pikachu
but first of
all see just because you made this
much we have to take away this
month income
tax
then to ensure you'll have candy in your
old
age hey the s Security
tax qu crying you're going to see it in
50 60
years I tell you what we're just going
to put it right up here won't touch it
till
then okay here here's here's George Bush
Jr's plan go invest
[Music]
oh last of all we can't forget that
state tax can we
uh oh oh we're in California tonight
aren't
[Applause]
we there's your Snickers
bar oh wait wait here this is funnier
hold on just a minute
Heyday oh whoa whoa whoa whoa you're
going to eat that right now hold
it snack
TXS you know I think kids are smarter
than that man I bet if you did that to
your kid he wouldn't even get dressed up
the next
year probably spend the whole even on
the couch in front of the tube and when
Mom put out that big bowl of candy for
the other
kids they just walk over to that bll
dump it in his bag I'm on
[Applause]
welfare
oh I love
America America is home to the fattest
poor people on earth
you don't believe me just watch Jerry
Springer some
evening every one of them 300 lb and up
and on food
STS we are a nation that for the first
time in any history or geography has
conquered starvation there's there's no
one Starving in America and I know
there's people
hungry there there's people eating stuff
they'd rather not be eating
you know there's no one's
starving if there was wouldn't it be in
the
papers last person I remember reading
about starving to death in America was
Karen
Carpenter oh okay maybe kalista
Flockhart
but that's that's not over
yet there could be a
sandwich is that actually in Chicago not
long I was actually watching a homeless
man feeding stale breadcrumbs to the
birds a little too stale for his
liking I'm watching this I'm going you
know there really is no one Starving in
this country if there was you would not
see a homeless man feeding bread to the
birds you wouldn't see birds
[Applause]
in Cuba right now there's no such thing
as a stray
animal I doubt there's many pets
left I mean that's why 12 people died
getting little Leon Gonzalez
here that's why people are die literally
dying to get out of that country they
they'll swim to the shores if they stand
on the beach too long that's why the
Coast Guard has to drag shrimp Nets
around the panhandle of Florida scooping
up the refugees so he can send them
back and then we just little sent little
Alon back which yeah I guess he should
be with his
dad you know I would have liked to seen
what his dad had to say once his parents
were out of the mental
institution you know they weren't going
to let that happen cuz man the minute
that he would have thought they were in
the clear he would have chased his ass
to a Miami parking meter don't make me
go back there I don't care take the
goddamn boy don't make me go back
there I don't think he want Leon wanted
to go back I mean think of the things he
saw saw Disney World and Toys are
Us played PlayStation in Nintendo
64 kind of hard to go back to the
streets of Avana playing cat's cradle
with rat end
Trails he saw buildings that didn't get
hot when you close the
windows cars that don't make noise and
smoke telephones without wires or
dials they gave him a
puppy D it's like to be a six-year-old
boy with a puppy getting his face licked
and go oh please don't make me eat this
one I don't care I go hungry this
Christmas well we had to send him back
would have been tragedy if we
didn't you know if we hadn't to sent him
back and him and his dad got to stay
here the very next day Cuban families
would be walking their children down to
the beach stuffing them into inner tubes
and he them out to the ocean like
frisbee call for us when you get
there I can't believe the wealth of this
country they're they're like you mean in
America you you have
boulevards and
Parks just full of
pigeons and nobody even wants them
there and like they're so tamed that
they'll eat right out of your hand even
if you got a big stick in the
other it's poultry every night in
America we must have really upset that
kid too when we went and got
him I mean you see that picture oh my
god well you don't mess with Reno do you
boy he was clinging to that fisherman
going when did I go back to
Cuba and I noticed that
weapon was suspiciously absent of a
childproof trigger
lock seems to me if there was ever a
place for
one it would be on a fully auto aut atic
weapon pointed at the head of a
six-year-old
boy well not Adam you know off to the
side
anyway yeah this country we forget our
wealth in this country man we are so
well fed that people will pay a dollar
extra for a dozen eggs that the chickens
were treated nice
in the third world people don't worry if
animals have their
rights which I don't understand animal
rights they're
animals okay I'll tell you what when the
animals publish a newspaper I won't
Outlaw
it I I think an animals have the right
to worship freely at any church they
choose you have the right to speak
that's a free
doggy yeah animal rights in the third
world are you have the right to be
dinner any part of your body can and
will be used for said
meal if you do not have a side dish one
will gladly be provided for
you I know these animal rights people
meanwhile but man their energy so
misdirected breaking into fur farms and
setting chillas
free he about this they'll dress up in
pig suits and break into a fur Ranch and
open all the cage doors and chinchillas
aren't stupid they're like
hey could you close that door there's
coyotes around
here now I I don't think I want to go
anywhere I'm warm
here that that fat farmer lady comes in
here every afternoon and cleans my poop
and brushes
me I like
that and you see this Sho right here I
got food pellets rolling out of this
shoeld every single day I don't have to
hunt I don't have to 4 in just food
pellets bam right there all you can eat
Purina chinchilla Chow they're crispy
they're delicious and they're just about
do
so so the animal rights people will poke
them with sticks
to get him to start stampeding and they
run out of the cages and get about
halfway across the road before
but but they're free red
spots which is I guess what we're all
willing to be
too one way or
another I I I I'm sorry I I I and I know
there's a few vegetarians in the room
and I I don't get
that and what I really don't understand
is what do vegetarians feed their
[Music]
cats a little weird to be a vegetarian
and keep cats because they all have
cats yeah you're usually
several I've actually heard some
vegetarians though that they decide
because they've become enlightened that
they will also Enlighten their
cat you heard they actually try to turn
their cat into a
vegetarian that's that's
goofy cat cats are meat
eaters they're Predators they have all
pointy
teeth they were put on this Earth to eat
small birds and rodents that's what they
do that's what they are all meat and
nothing but the meat that
there's actually a scientific term for
turning a cat into a vegetarian I
believe it's called starving the
[Applause]
bastard you don't want to do that to a
cat you live
with they're up all
night way too much time oh there he is
just sleeping there while I am sitting
here starving to death he says he loves
animals well what about the animal that
is starving in his
house I hate him I found that Mouse
today and he took it away and let it go
what an idiot you are just sleeping
there 120 lb of pasty
white meat
I think we can take
[Music]
him any there's actually several level
levels of vegetarianism there's and you
know and and let me say right here if
you do it out of preference if you do it
out of religion that's your own business
I don't mind that and especially if it's
your religion I really respect that you
know I I love people to be able to
practice their own religion but admit
it's religion take out of the take off
the pig suit and get out of the state
house we have separation of church and
state in this
country there's there's of course you
know the the the the oval Act of
vegetarian that's those vegetarians that
are allowed to eat cheese and and eggs
and then there's the
vegans these These are the these are the
Twisted
ones these are the ones that won't eat
honey because it exploits bees
they won't wear leather shoes cuz an
animal shouldn't have to suffer to
prevent their toes from freezing off and
I think if you're a true vegan man you
should just strip yourself naked go
running into the forest and let the
animals Peck you to
death I love the animals more than
me there's actually a study a a report
on N March 23rd New England Journal of
Medicine a vegan a person that had been
a complete vegan no Animal product for
20 years went completely
blind you hear about this he had nerve
degeneration because of a vitamin B12
deficiency because he was such a pure
vegan he never touched Animal product
and hence went
blind which uh probably pretty hard to
hang out with your vegan buddies after
that
happens get hard to listen to that
humans are meant to be vegetarians when
you're bumping into
walls I don't think that people should
ever eat meat oh shut the hell
up and you know what I wonder if you're
a blind vegan can you have a seeing eye
dog I guess if the dog
volunteers and there's actually a lot of
people a lot of vegans don't go blind
not everyone does because you only need
a very little bit of vitamin B12 and you
can get it from you know sources other
than meat you can get it from cheese or
feal
matter it's why kids that are vegans
don't go blind because
they don't have sanitary habits that we
wish they
would so if you got a vegan buddy next
time you see him go like this right in
his eyes and if he blinks
he's got a nasty little
secret either he's sneaking
cheese or he's got some funny
Play-Doh then of course there's a third
variety ovala of vegan the third variety
of vegetarian the person who's dating a
[Music]
vegetarian I would bet Paul McCartney
fit into that category
oh I would bet the night Linda died Paul
grieved over a New York
[Laughter]
[Music]
strip I was doing this bit one night I
got some vegetarians so mad at me they
came up to after the CL people like you
you're just so narrow-minded you're just
so shallow you just have to put labels
and stereotypes in every whoever said
that a vegetarian can't eat
[Music]
meat
dictionary granted Webster was a rich
white
guy but they actually enlighten me they
they pointed out to me that there
actually are several varieties of meate
eating vegetarian
I I didn't know
that yeah I thought it was not eating
meat it was a
prerequisite but but there's the uh um
first of all there's the nothing with a
face
vegetarian yeah these are vegetarians
that still like to go out for
lobster even though lobsters have faces
they're not very
cute they usually take them off before
they serve
them and of course there's the nothing
that walks
vegetarian and these are vegetarians of
course are allowed to eat things like
like like like uh fish
and legless lizards
and
[Music]
ve I'll bite me that's
funny and then of course there's the
very popular College variety the made a
big big stink about the turkey at
Thanksgiving dinner but grabbed a Big
Mac on the way home
vegetarian and I think I think me eating
vegetarians I'm sorry if you're one but
they're just picky
eaters that are tired of their friends
making fun of them cuz you know
sometimes people get to be about 25 35
years old and they can't eat anything
but macaroni and and chocolate cake
you'll go out to eat with them and
they'll go there's no macaroni or
chocolate cake on this stupid menu
you're like what's wrong with
you well I'm I'm a
vegetarian and then see all of a sudden
it makes them sound like they have a
conscience like they're better than you
and they love this they love to be on
the one on the plane when the steward is
says who had the vegetarian meal oh that
would be
me oh look I'm the only enlightened
person on a playload of goddamn
neanderthals oh and this one go go down
there'll be no weight in heaven for
me did you ever one of these freaks over
your house to
eat do you know what they expect you to
do you got to fix him something
special in a special pan that's never
touched meat
before and if you don't you're going to
hear about it they come over what are we
having for dinner
tonight steaks on the grill
are you forgetting
something no not forgetting a thing one
for you right
there but I'm a vegetarian oh oh yeah
that's right I uh uh didn't M the front
lawn go knock yourself out
Elsie yeah work those mullers you high
life
form and you know I would not mind
preparing a special vegetable death for
my dish for my vegetarian friends I'm a
good host I just wish that once in my
life that favor were ever
returned but when you go over a
vegetarian's house to eat do they
remember that you're a carnivore
prepare you a special meat
dish in a a pan that's never touched
beans
[Applause]
before oh they try to convert you oh
tonight we're having tofu sprout salad
you won't even miss the me the hell I
won't brought your steak from last week
see I think if God intended us to be
vegetarians he would not have made pigs
and cows so
delicious and don't let the vegetarians
fool you they know that meat is
delicious go to a vegetarian grocery
store what do you
see vegetarian hot dogs vegetarian bacon
substitute vegetarian be stroken off
what about vegetarian vegetables huh you
don't go into a butcher shop and see all
meat tomato
[Applause]
substitute see I don't know how anyone
could settle for
for for eating macaroni cheese when you
could have a New York
strip it's not any better for you cheese
is still beef fat artery clogging
cholesterol Rich beef fat almost
identical in chemical composition to the
stuff that Rings the outside of a steak
it just comes out of a different
[Music]
hole yeah see go that's the
problem I don't think it's as mean to
eat macaroni and cheese
cuz we all have this illusion of a dairy
farm that comes from watching too many
butter
commercials that when we picture a dairy
farm we picture a peaceful
pasture surrounded by snow peak
mountains every morning Heidi comes out
and a little milk made outfit L low cut
with ruffled panties and
coffee filter on her
head maybe Pats the cow a couple times
places a daisy behind her ear and grabs
the thick long hempen rope and leads her
back to the Milk Barn with a cowbell
clanging softly in the morning gentle
breezes sits on a rickety three-legged
wooden stool and M milks her with firm
gentle hands while she sings her
soothing songs from the
Homeland I would eat that
cheese but that cheese is 100% processed
American
fiction dairy farms are cruel places a
dairy cow will spend the three short
years of her life locked inside of a Yol
of a dairy barn in front of her snout
the only thing she'll ever get to see is
this SLO that hormones and steroids and
GRL come rushing by hanging off of her
utter is 525 5 lbs of milking equipment
that turns on three times a day and
won't shut off until it's
dry and there she's kept in a state of
permanent lactation till exhaustion and
calcium depletion makes her collapse at
her own brittle bones at which point
she's dragged out by the LA back legs
thrown down the Shute and turned into
hamburger that's the gentle dish that is
macaroni and cheese
see cuz the dairy industry is not a
career
choice for a
cow just a temporary
position kind kind of like Miss
America you based on the the the
plentifulness of your
utter you know what do vegetarians think
think that after cows are done with the
dairy business that they get to retire
that there's cruise ships of retired
dairy cows cruising around the Bahamas
playing Bingo and square
dancing and let me tell you the dairy
industry is not equal opportunity either
the dairy industry does not have any
jobs for the boy
cows well no you can't milk a
bow well oh okay you
can but you you don't get a
lot makes the cheese kind of
salty see the sad truth is that cows
were put on this Earth for one reason
and one reason alone and that's to be
consumed by a human
being if we stopped eating cows they
would become an endangered
[Applause]
species we kind of have this agreement
with cows in nature this is called a
symbiotic relationship is that we give
them life and in return they give us
food and clothing and comfortable car
seats we give them life and they protect
us for we protect them from disease and
predators they protect us from
starvation
cold
man a the only reason why a cow is ever
born into this Earth the only reason why
a cow ever gets to open her long brown
lashes on a sunrise is cuz some farmer
had his wrist up the hind quarters of
her mother with a turkey baster full of
bull and imagine if you will as that
farmer is about to compress that bulb
and bring another cow being into
existence that you're standing in front
of
God and God goes man I got I got some
bad news for you you're next in line to
be born
and and so's that
cow you're going to be a cow but but I'm
a merciful god I'll let you decide for
yourself would you rather be a beef
cow or would you rather be a dairy cow
now if you're a beef cow you're going to
spend the four short years of your life
out out in the open on a feed lot maybe
out in the range but you'll be out there
underneath the Open Sky you'll be able
to see every Sunrise you'll see every
sunet you'll be able to see the deep
blue of a clear spring
sky you'll feel the warmth of the Sun
the cool of a fall Breeze the sting of a
spring rain you you'll taste
snowflakes Every Spring you get you get
to nibble at flowers you you'll have
long grass and clover every summer
you'll have grain in the fall and hay
every winter and that's going to happen
for about 16 changes of season at which
point you're going to be led on a truck
you're going to go for a little ride
you're going to be L up a shoot feel a
sharp blow to your head and you're going
to be right back
here either that or you can spend three
long years in a Dairy Barn with an
electric calf gnawing at your
teeth
myself would prefer the sharp Blow To
The Head
so if you really really love
animals eat
beef and if I were a cow I think I'd
have a t-shirt that just said lay off my
tits just eat me
well I'm sweating up here
huh I'm sweating like the candidates on
Al Gore short list let me tell
[Music]
you boy could you imagine be one of
those suckers right now every time the
phone rings and that's Al gorm dead
not letting him bring me
down so what else what do you want to
talk
about Star
Trek oh my God what libertarian
convention would be in its place without
a Star
Trek that's what I've always thought if
that we really wanted to attract
membership into the party we would just
have have a Star Trek convention
concurrent with a hemp rally and a gun
show the people that hung out in the
center they'd be
ours the hemp thing I'm I'm very happy
in
California well I'm feeling a little
sick right
now I
don't so there's a doctor
here yeah I I that's nothing to joke
about man that's that whole that whole
that whole Bill Clinton thing that
really drove me nuts and it's you know
his personal business that's his even he
to even presidents have their own
private
lives okay that's fine I'll extend any
president's personal business as long as
he does the same for
me next April 15th when I get down my
1040 form down to 33a how much money did
you make last year I'm just going to
write right in there personal business
[Applause]
at the
audit I'm just going to look at that
little accountant geek go well you know
that kind of depends on what your
definition of income
[Applause]
is because I mean you know why doesn't
personal business extend to to to
people's right to smoke
marijuana Marijuana arrest have doubled
since Bill Clinton took office that'll
teach him to inhale
I look at Al Gore man know Bill Clinton
said that well he tried it once didn't
inhale Al Gore man he he invented the
[Applause]
bong well I was there with Tipper and
all I could find was this toilet paper
roll and a piece of aluminum
foil and I said hey Tipper I think I can
do something with this
cuz you know Tipper was the one that
wanted to get rid of rock and roll
music it kind of makes you wonder what
music they were listening to when they
got stoned in
college oh Pat Boon is so awesome
man and if you've never smoked marijuana
before I want you to know right here and
now that you've been lied to
you've been told horror stories and
probably believe them you've been told
that if you smoke marijuana even once
you who you're going to start shooting
up you're going to murder your family
you're going to have threee headed
babies you smoke marijuana all you're
going to eat do is eat a bunch of
cookies and watch The
Flinstones you why do we keep these lies
going I don't get it why do why do we
test people for why do we test Olympic
athletes for marijuana does that make
any
sense cuz you know you think about if
everything they told us about marijuana
was true there wouldn't be in the
Olympic athletes smoking
marijuana there couldn't be they have to
test them to protect their little
lie because nothing spoils a perfectly
good drugs kill campaign more than a
pothead that can win the triathlon
[Applause]
yeah I'm a little twisted myself I think
we find a pothead that can win the
triathlon he should have two
medals a triathlon and 100 meter
bong like got Canadian snowboarder man
that cat was a two metal winner in my
book oh man if I had the money I'd hire
him to do real drug awareness
ass put him on TV with with his goil ah
my mom said like if I smoked dope I
wouldn't amount to anything
E look like you
L you see the ads they're running on TV
now they see they say tell your children
the truth about
marijuana it's not too
soon
truth does anyone hear really believe
they want us telling
kids the
truth nah they want us telling them the
same lies our parents told like how
would the truth come
out like
well when I was about your
[Music]
age I was probably smoking a aboutt a
lit a week
High School got so damn fun after
that oh yeah when I was your age we
didn't need any of that goddamn
[Applause]
riddling we had herbal remedy for
attention deficit disorder
and then I
uh still
graduated went on to
college graduated
again got got a great job met a
beautiful woman had a had a wonderful
family you know what man you're only
young one
here's five bucks first bags on
[Music]
Dad see cuz I'm over 40
now when I was his age for five bucks
you could buy something called a
nickel I understand now that five bucks
Will Roll you a really tight Roach
right
anyway I guess I guess one last thing I
want to talk about and uh like I said
we're just we're just a little bit away
from bringing Melanie up
[Applause]
here there's a
spirit I think I think one of the things
probably that the bug bugs me out about
Mo about the most about the prevailing
culture right now is this whole fasc
fascination with
Europe how many you ever noticed that on
the on the news and you talk to liberals
and it's all the same thing well in
Europe they have socialized medicine in
Europe they have gun control and there
doesn't seem to be any
problem well you know what in Europe
they have state religions and monarchies
do we want that
too yeah I'm so sick could being
compared Europe is nothing more than a
third world country with a very bad
[Applause]
attitude Europeans are nothing more than
the descendants of peasants that didn't
have the courage to overthrow the
tyrants that run their little duchies or
the ambition to immigrate to the United
States
W Europeans are hairy back Savages and
have been a war with each other for
thousands of years and would have
annihilated each other twice in this
Century if we hadn't have gone in and
saved their greasy
butts can't even agree on a Common
Language and the languages they do have
don't have wonderful words like we have
here in America words like courtesy or
gratuity or deodorant
they say they like to drink their beer
warm come on they don't have
refrigerators in Europe a dishwasher is
an apprentice
ship they're so proud now that they
finally got their common currency called
the Euro this will replace their
previous common currency known as the
dollar
you'll say yeah but there's so much more
literate than we are well of course they
read a lot their television
sucks number one show is
bayat just cu the entire continent is
fascinated of the possibilities that can
occur in a country where women can
afford razors
Europe is a vulgar Place full of crooked
yellow teeth and tiny little cars where
people live in cold water Flats with
squat toilets devoid of toothpaste or
toilet paper they spend dinner time
eating parts of animals we Americans use
for pet food and
fertilizer wash it down with a couple
gallons of wine and a carton of
cigarettes praying that the combination
of lung cancer and socialized medicine
might mercifully shorten their miserable
Little Lives
[Applause]
thank you thank you very much I wish you
Liberty thank you all
w
[Applause]