Mormons get sent to hell for drinking
coffee yeah cuz caffeine's a drug if
you're a Mormon it's a sin to drink
coffee it's kind of funny if you think
about it to a Mormon a thermos is drug
paraphernalia that's a caffeine
ball an espresso machine is kind of like
a free base unit
I love the Mormons though cuz they bring
it door
too there's nothing I like better than
seeing a couple of white shirts and ties
get off their bicycle in front of the
slle
compound cuz I know that they're going
to spend the rest of the afternoon
trying to convince me that that Joseph
Smith found truth in the bottom of his
hatch
I'm going to try to convince them that I
found it at the bottom of a bottle of
Jim
Beam cuz I'll listen I love to hear
people try to convince me that their
religion is the true one cuz you never
know somebody might they might have it
right I was actually watching a
televangelist and he actually was
talking about the scripture being a
prophecy versus a coincidence he said
those odds were
calculated and do you know what the odds
are of the scripture being a pure
coincidence a 100 million billion to
one okay here's a little hint for all
you upand cominging tele
evangelists if you're going to lie to me
use a real goddamn
number a 100 million billion is not a
real
number a 100 million billion is an
amount of money a fifth grader bets
another fifth grader to jump off the
roof it's like a$0 zillion
dollar it's one of those numbers that
people make up just when they want to
you know when they want to say it's
large and they don't know like like my
wife the other day she's looking out at
the front lawn and she just goes
man we have a buttload of squirrels on
our front
lawn now I don't know how many squirrels
she
saw and maybe I'm
unique but I think for
me a buttload of
squirrels only
one just
one tiny
angry
confused little
squirrel all the time people talk about
a buttload of this and a buttload of
that I I have no idea how many's in a
butt load and I think it changes
depending on what you're talking about
it you it
should I had a buddy went to a NASCAR
race and he came back he goes oh man you
should have end to that race there were
a buttload of rednecks at that NASCAR
race I don't know how many rednecks in a
buttload so I asked a friend of mine
who's really really
[Laughter]
gay and he swears
that a buttload of
rednecks no more than
[Laughter]
two two rednecks make a butt
load three rednecks is a squeal
[Laughter]