hi I'm Tim slel and you're about to
watch a nation of criminals this was the
second video I did about 18 years ago uh
you will notice that the artwork does
not match the look I had at that time in
the early days I was changing my look
all the time another IC once said that I
spent more time looking for my hook than
a blind pirate on Shor leaf and I did
the show while I still had my dreadlocks
I had the artwork paid for
um and I had two shows that night the
first show was probably the best show
I've ever had in my life it was uh uh 20
minutes I did two shows it was 20
minutes longer than the other show even
though it was the exact same show
because of all the laughter and Applause
that's that's how solid that set was
I've never had a better show before or
since and uh both cameramen thought that
the other one was recording the sound
there was a so there was no sound for it
it was just me talking into a mic and
I'm not that good of a mime so uh I I
after I changed my look I realized that
I I didn't want to waste I didn't want
to burn the the the money I had spent to
to to create the box so I filmed it
right here right here in this club uh uh
couple years afterwards and uh well you
can see it
now ladies and Gentlemen please help me
welcome Tim slagel
[Applause]
thank you all thank you for coming out
tonight there's a it's a nippy night in
[Laughter]
Minneapolis yeah I think I think
Winter's
coming and man if if it's going to be
winter I hope we have a winner exactly
like last year wasn't that great yeah
man February was like 50° no snow the
entire month God if that is global
warming I'm in favor of
it of course not everyone had the nice
winter you know that you had in
Minneapolis or I had in Chicago you know
they had a little trouble in
California screw
[Laughter]
them you know they had some
mudslides in fact all winter long they
were having mudslides roads were closed
because of piles of mud you know screw
them you know how many februaries would
you have come in after shoveling through
2 feet of snow to hear the weatherman
say sunny and 90° today in Southern
California screw
them last winter it was their turn to
shovel all winter long we were treated
to videotape footage of multi-million
dollar mansion sledding down the faces
of cliffs and yeah yeah we're supposed
to feel sorry for
that you know not like it might be a
little their fault for not realizing how
that Cliff got there in the first
place continents smash together half of
the ground Rises half of it falls away
voila
Cliff just cuz it looks still doesn't
mean it's not moving
people in California man they figured
because they purchased the real estate
the continents have ceased to
shift he'll check out the property and
they go hey you know what man for some
reason the ground just kind of stops
right here man it looks like a lot of
stuff hey will you look at that
view oh man I'm going to put my house
right
here no in fact this isn't enough I'm
going to build a platform 20 ft out over
this Chasm so I have 180° view of the
Void from my hot
tub screw
them if you don't like Cliffs move to
Minnesota we have millions of Cliff free
Acres available for immediate occupancy
saw one guy had a sinkhole in his
backyard you ever see these sink holes
yes it's like it's like a worm mouth
from the movie Dooms eating the backyard
from
underneath this guy's entire backyard is
being sucked into this sinkhole his lawn
his wwn mow his shed his driveway and at
the end of the driveway right about to
go into the void was a cherry Carmen Gia
convertible yeah the guy's like crying
he like look at my car man I can't do
anything to save it I'm going to lose
it supposed to feel sorry for
that Michigan road salt took my Carmen
Gia convertible 20 years
ago it's about time his followed mine
into the
Earth and I know we probably got at
least one environmentalist in here
thinking oh yeah you're laughing now
yeah when those ice caps start melting
you're going to be laughing underwater
pal cuz that's what they're telling us
is going to happen that the ice caps are
going to melt the oceans are going to
rise and we're all going to
drown last time I was here somebody
actually told me that because the Twin
Cities have the river going right
through them that you know they're going
to be underwater really
quickly yeah forgetting of course that
the Twin Cities are 1200 ft above sea
L if the ocean comes up that high we're
pretty much screwed
anyway at that point you're going to be
the east coast of
[Laughter]
Denver I don't think that's going to
happen you know you granted we might
lose you know a little beachfront
property screw
them shorter drive to the ocean for
me yeah don't look at it as tragedy look
at it as climactic
Justice and I don't even know if it's
true and I know you've all heard it too
that they they said that that ice caps
are going to melt well the ice has to go
somewhere where else is it going to go
well it's going to make the Oceans Rise
you forgetting of course that the ice
camps
float how much does the level of a glass
of Coke rise when the floating Ice Cube
melts in
it I think they're lying to
us either that are they flunk
geography and did you see what happened
in Montreal last last winter it got
cold they had 6in sheets across most of
Montreal sheets of ice across the city
for the majority of the winter
it looks like the Glaciers are coming
south again to me and I said there you
go you can't have 6in sheets of ice in
Montreal and global warming but I was
corrected by USA
Today they said don't start thinking for
yourself they actually said that the
reason why it got so cold in Montreal
was because of global
warming I guess I'm just stupid
you know cuz I was kind of figuring that
Global would imply
Earth warming might
imply
hotter well that goes to show how
environmentally ignorant I
am would seem global warming can cause
anything it can cause it to get warmer
sure but it could also cause it to get
colder or it could cause celebrities to
ski into trees for no apparent reason
oh what a strange winner we had last
year that's El
Nino I actually heard Al Gore say that
El Nino is Spanish for global
warming yeah I think Al Gore is Democrat
for Dan quail
[Applause]
[Laughter]
granted I'm pretty sure Al Gore knows
how to spell
potato I would bet that Dan Quail knows
that Michael Jackson doesn't play
[Laughter]
basketball you don't you don't know what
I'm talking
about you didn't hear that here did you
they they actually asked El Gore what he
said about what he thought about the
last Bulls championship in Chicago last
basketball and Al Gore responded and I
quote boy that Michael Jackson's
probably the best basketball player
we've ever
[Laughter]
seen the man is a cigar length from the
Oval Office
[Applause]
know that don't
you does that worry anyone but
me I think I think that Al Gore is the
number one reason why Bill Clinton
should not
[Laughter]
reside Al Gore man Al Gore is one of
these control freaks Al Gore is one of
these guys that want to tell us how we
live cuz we're doing it wrong you know
he thinks that we be a much better place
if we drove electric cars yeah not him
no no he still needs you know the
petroleum drinking armored limousine the
motorcade and the dc9 you know he's
talking about you
people and you people are spoiling the
Earth by driving your
cars wants us to drive electric cars
like like the ev1 heard about this first
production electric car GM
$335,000 for a car with no heat or air
conditioning top speed about 60 M an
hour for an hour before you plug it in
overnight oh where do I sign up for
that and Al Gore man he doesn't even see
that there might be a flaw or two with
this
design he's like well sure you're going
to have to make some small
sacrifices wait a
minute 2 days to drive a 100 miles is
not a small sacrifice you further in a
day in a godamn covered wagon than an
electric
car yeah but at least it's going to help
the
environment
how cuz the electricity has to come from
someplace it doesn't just grow out of
the
socket you have to generate the
electricity in this country we generate
the majority of our electricity by
burning fossil fuel the same exact thing
I'm doing under the hood of my
car somehow cuz it happens in the power
plant where you can't see it that helps
the
environment yeah could you imagine how
stupid you would have felt driving an
electric car in Montreal last
winner yeah cuz they didn't have
electricity for like 2
months you would have had to actually
walk to the gas station to buy a gallon
of
gas so that you could run the generator
for a couple
hours to charge up your
car you could drive to the gas station
for a little more gas
see I think people just have to get used
to the notion that there's absolutely no
natural way to fly through the
countryside at 70 M an hour if pollution
bothers you
walk and that's what I think we'd have
to do if we were serious about all this
save the Earth
crap each and every one of us would be
perfectly willing to spend the rest of
our lives without cars or toilet paper
or underarm deodorant man I'd rather be
dead who wants to live like the
Amish corn cops don't even sound
Pleasant to
me I think that death would be a
preferable option to a life of hard work
and
ouses death I have no trouble with
I'm like 40 years old
now granted a hard
40 you know what at this point I've
already outlived James Dean Elvis
Presley and Jesus
Christ hell I'm in the bonus round
anyway and I think you people that are
afraid of death are ultimately afraid of
change and death probably isn't that bad
you can sleep in every
morning sounds way cool to
me oh I meaning I really admire those of
you that find themselves able to get up
and go to work every day God bless
you I don't know how the hell you do
[Laughter]
that now myself I've been able to get up
in time to shave shower and have the
application in
early you know what after you get the
job they expect you there at that same
hour every goddamn
[Laughter]
morning I could work 9
to5
Wednesdays any more than that severely
hinders my drinking ability
Oh My Philosophy has always been that a
hangover is just your body's way of
telling you you shouldn't have stopped
drinking you laugh but I'm Stone
serious I got in this business 18 years
ago after flunking out of college and
finding myself unable to hold down a day
job during one of my last meetings with
one of my last bosses he actually said
Mr slel what do you want out of a
job I thought about that question like
like I just heard it for the very first
time I thought God what what do I
want I want to sleep till noon every
day work an hour or
less I want to be able to say whatever
the hell I
want hang out bars and get free
beer Yello and behold 15 years later
that's exactly what I'm
[Applause]
doing Isn't it nice to know we live in a
country where you can achieve anything
you aspire
to I love to tease the Amish though
cuz you know they they can't come
[Laughter]
here and it probably wouldn't matter
anyway because I'm sure that the Amish
have such a great sense of humor I think
they're one of these groups that you
know everyone can still make fun of them
and everyone has a good time which is
great because man there's other groups
today that you cannot make fun
of and sometimes the difference of
between a group that you can make fun of
in a group that you can't is just a
hairline for instance how do we
celebrate St Patrick's Day in America
what do we do we drink yeah we drink
until we puke up every green thing we've
had to drink that
evening yeah that's the reverence that
we hold for Irish
heritage in America and its impact on
our diversity
by taking what was at one point the most
holy day in all of
Ireland using it as an excuse for
everyone else to imitate the worst
stereotype of the Irish
[Laughter]
people man isn't that kind of like
spending Martin Luther King Day eating
ribs and drinking Malt
Liquor woo
oh I sense a few of you uncomfortable
with me saying
that I don't know
why the Irish think it's
funny now go to an Irish Pub on St
Patrick's Day I guarantee they will have
an all you can eat corn beef and cabbage
Buffet cuz we all know that's the only
kind of food that Irish people
eat next to
potatoes go to Chi-Chi on Cinco de Mayo
have chimy chungas and margaritas cuz
that's the only thing that Mexicans
eat on Chinese New Year's it's eggu
young and fortune
cookies you dare to mention fried
chicken and collared green
well you're not working for
[Applause]
[Music]
Kmart they fired fuzzy Zeller for saying
that actually what fuzzy Zeller said was
that Tiger Woods might enjoy eating stir
fried chicken and collard
greens because he's half asian
he's actually half tie and stir fried
chicken is a Chinese dish but but nobody
griped about
that it was the fried chicken and
collard greens hey hey hey
hey I don't get
that why do we think that black
Americans should be ashamed of fried
chicken that's
wrong cuz you know what black Americans
invented fried
chicken and next to rock and roll I
believe it's one of the greatest
contributions they've brought into our
culture yeah could you imagine living in
a country where there was no fried
chicken or rock and roll be like living
in
[Applause]
Utah come on admited Italian Americans
gave us pizza German Americans gave us
hamburgers Mexican Americans gave us
chili and black Americans gave us Fried
Chicken man that is the four basic food
groups as far as I'm
concerned I oh that is not true shut
up oh you are so
ignorant Fried Chicken is a traditional
Southern dish popularized around
1840 yeah and who was doing all the
cooking
[Applause]
yes it was cruel there was no choice
they stole their blood and sweat at
least let them keep credit for their
recipes everything we call Southern Home
Cooking was invented by a black American
you think Colonel Sanders invented fried
chicken that lazy cracker never cooked
for himself a day in his
[Laughter]
life
sorry I get carried
away and actually you know I think you
know seeing as I'm here in Minnesota I
think I might have just committed a hate
crime you see I thought I was exercising
My First Amendment right to free
speech not when you're being
hateful no time for hate
here cuz you do have hate crime don't
you which is great I I think that is
great
idea cuz you know you should punish hate
crimes worse than other
crimes no I mean come on if you killed
someone because you hated them that is a
whole lot worse than if you were to just
kill
[Music]
them you know like if you were robbing
them or
something that's just business
man you got to make a living
somehow so if you're going to kill
someone please do it with love in your
[Laughter]
heart where do these laws come from hate
crimes Barney the purple
dinosaur oh even murderers need love
that's what I think's wrong with America
personally I think we've got too many
big purple dinosaurs writing
laws like Teddy
Kennedy oh he is big and
purple just one varicose vein ready to
pop I I actually like to call Teddy the
control Kennedy
if you remember your your labs in high
school you would always have a control
to prove the results of the
experiment see I think Teddy is what
happens when you let a Kennedy live past
[Applause]
50 oh it's been 30 years people it's
time to let
go and if you can remember back some to
to the glory if you can remember back to
some of the touch football footage you
know back before they thought of playing
it on
[Laughter]
skis back when Teddy was playing
football alongside Bobby and Jack Teddy
was the cute
one yeah imagine what trolls those other
two would have turned out to
be oh man if I were John John I'd steer
for the tree
cuz you know in 1993 they named People
magazine named John John Kennedy the
hunk of the
Year people yeah yeah which is kind of
weird if you think about it because you
know when you're talking about something
other than Kennedy's like candy or
cake isn't a
hunk the same thing as a piece
could you imagine People magazine
calling Carolyn the best piece of
93 that doesn't seem
right see I think though men have a
better sense of humor about stuff like
that oh come
on men call themselves dick
yeah short for
Richard don't know how it's short for
Richard I have never figured out how you
can shorten by adding a d and a
[Laughter]
k I think that men named Richard just
like the fact that they can go around
going hi my name's Richard
but why don't you just call me dick
[Laughter]
I have never seen the name constant
shortened Beyond
[Music]
Connie where's the sense of humor
now could you imagine a woman
introducing herself to you like
that coming up and going hi my name's
really constants but you can call
me
[Laughter]
[Music]
Muffy oh I can't even say that
word you all seem to know what word I'm
talking about too yeah so you must have
heard it
once L you've survived
but if I were to DARE string together
the four letters necessary to form the
Forbidden
word 90% of you would get really mad at
me I know the other 10% would laugh like
hell you got to work on demographics
when you're forming the Forbidden
one men don't mind if you call him
dick when you call a man dick he will
brag about
it yeah that's
right I'm the biggest dick in the
[Laughter]
room with women size isn't so much an
issue
[Laughter]
yeah I once heard a man brag that he was
large enough to perch a
vulture I have never heard a woman claim
she could hold three buckets of golf
[Laughter]
balls yeah equal rights my butt
cuz personally I don't think that we'll
ever have gender equality true gender
equality as long as that word is an
offensive
one and I think the reason why it's a
much more offensive word than
dick is we've kind of been brainwashed
by society and into believing that men
are born with something good that you
should be proud of and women have
something shameful that you should wash
a lot
[Laughter]
it's
true I have never known a man to own a
vinegar and water
squirter but you watch afternoon TV
women are made to feel like pigs if they
haven't been using one three times a day
have you ever seen a can of masculine
hygiene spray
deodorant and I know there's probably
men that can use it
too men
won't men figure if it stinks it's
supposed to
[Applause]
you can't get man to spray anything
until it starts to
EG even then he's going to try to
scratch it away for a week or
two before he makes that embarrassing
trip into Walmart
[Laughter]
you might well laughing
here that's the one that kept me off
star
[Laughter]
search that's what's known as a bad
judgment
P I thought it was a hot five minute
bit judges did not
concur zero stars for the she
[Laughter]
crotch people are just too dang
sensitive
that's that's my
conclusion see the National Association
for the blind boycotted Walt Disney did
you hear about that they boycotted Walt
Disney because Walt Disney did a remake
of Mr
meoo and Mr Meo happens to be offensive
to div vision impaired
like they're going to see
it oh and might I remind everyone we are
talking about a
cartoon how seriously are we going to
start taking cartoons now are the French
people going to boycott Warner Brothers
for their little peepy Lew
character cuz if you think about it
isn't pepy law an offensive stereotype
of a Frenchman over sexed and very
stinky right now Hispanic groups are mad
at Taco Bell they want dinky the Taco
Bell Chihuahua pulled off the air
because it's offensive to
Hispanics cuz you see it's a Mexican
dog that eats tacos
and speak
[Laughter]
Spanish I think it's offensive to Taco
Bell they're saying they serve dog
[Applause]
food no I mean think about it what else
have you seen dogs eat D you want that
compared to your supper
oh normally I prefer a stinking pile of
crap oh and I cannot find one yier Taco
[Laughter]
Bell Joe Camel there's another cartoon
people have taken way too
seriously we had to Outlaw Joe Camel at
the federal level cuz you know he was
just just a tun gone
bad making kids smoke that's what they
said I don't know how they did it he
wasn't even
animated but their proof of this
ridiculous allegation was it's a cartoon
duh and I guess 133% of kids that smoke
smoke camel so what more do you
need but you know what that doesn't mean
they started smoking camel there is a
big
difference I would bet that 99% of all
kids that smoke probably started smoking
the exact brand I did that's whatever
you can rip off from Mom and
Dad not Joe camela Joe
parents my first brand was Paul mul
nonfilter
yeah oh I was hooked in about an
hour see I think anyone that really
believes that they were using Joe Camel
to Target cigarettes to
Children probably thinks that
Metropolitan Life uses Snoopy and
Woodstock to get kids into life
[Laughter]
insurance why else would they be using
cartoons
hello they're trying to get kids hooked
on
[Laughter]
annuities I understand they actually
manipulate the interest rates to get
them hooked
quicker yeah I mean come on I grew up
watching The Bugs Bunny Road Runner
hour and I have never strapped on a pair
of Acme rocket powered roller skates
yeah I have never tried to catch my
little brother by dumping ball bearings
into his Cheerios and getting a giant
magnet I have never dropped a safe on
anyone well okay there's been instances
not not me but there was that one kid
that allegedly watched beas and
Butthead started his family's trailer on
fire I think trailer is the
[Applause]
opportunity I think it's the same thing
that happened after after the the movie
the program do you remember that
incident movie about a movie about a
high school football team that would
prove how tough they were by laying down
in the middle of the
expressway yeah and some kids saw the
film and on the way home thought that
they should test the boundaries between
fiction and reality
and guess what
[Music]
happen reality yeah you know this is
just an
exception and when something like this
occurs this is just St Darwin correcting
a genetic error
[Applause]
I mean come on if all of America were as
impressionable as these idiots
spawn society would have never survived
the onslaught of The Three
Stooges the United States would have
been wiped out overnight after the first
stoes episode premiered 150 million
people left Dead with their eyes poked
out hatchets and shovels in there
head I left a Al going
W
woo see I I think as a nation we're
trying to do too much to help stupid
people
survive and man if that weren't enough
we make the millionaires on top of it
but by letting file lawsuits for their
stupidity for things like spilling hot
coffee in their
crotch the best example I can point out
about this you ever see the sticker that
they wrap around the cord of a hair
dryer know what I'm talking about do not
use in
water on the cord of a 3,000 watt hair
dryer plugged into the
wall you know why that sticker's there
don't you yeah yeah some inbred [ __ ]
[Laughter]
did and after St Darwin performed his
glorious
Miracle after the new Believers had the
time to clear out the smoke and
reset the
fuses sweep the Beloved out of the
shower they had the G to sue the
manufacturer of the hair dryer cuz you
didn't tell him he couldn't do
that and the hair dryer company's aware
of the thousands of morons still walking
in this
country the potential billions that
could be lost in lawsuits said you know
what we're going to have to
do we're going to have to put a sticker
on that
thing oh let the smart people make fun
of
[Laughter]
[Applause]
us cuz we do make fun of these stickers
every time you read one of these
ridiculous warnings it always makes you
laugh and you cannot buy anything
without a long list of ridiculous
warnings but remember the fact that
every one of those warnings even
exists means the Earth was once
inhabited by a creature stupid enough to
attempt the stunt
describe with relatives littered enough
to find an attorney in the Yellow Pages
[Laughter]
on gas
pumps on gas pumps there are warnings
that say can be harmful or fatal if
swallowed oh where we going to go after
last call
now when you go to the market to buy a
package of raw chicken
it will bear a label that says you've
got to cook
[Music]
this oh what a negligent host I've
been usually I serve it right out of the
[Applause]
bag wondered why no one was touching the
chicken salmonella wings
how far are we going to let this
go are we going to pass a law that
requires every American male to get a
tattoo that says has been known to cause
pregnancy do not straddle
[Applause]
[Laughter]
because we already have laws that
require warnings like the one on
cigarettes it's a law that requires that
warning to be there and I I guess they
want to change that law so that warning
is going to have to be
bigger which is why the nearsighted have
been coming down with
cancer yeah I can't see well enough to
make good health
choices I don't think we need the
government to to get us to quit I think
your own body tells you when to quit
smoking myself I really believe that
each and every one of us has been born
with a built-in traffic
light like hey it's green I can keep
[Applause]
going yellow would mean slow
down red means stop
[Applause]
let anything be more
apparent there's actually another law if
you're a smoker and you might not even
be aware of this is a law but I
guarantee man it's changed your
life because before that that it
happened after that beas and Butthead
trailer
incident because before that trailer
went up into
flames you used to be able to walk into
a 7-Eleven anywhere in America
for about 89 cents you could buy
yourself a disposable lighter that you
could light just by going like
that we were in
Peril it's a wonder any of us survive
the fiery
Holocaust cuz now you know when you get
these things they all have that thing in
the side you got to kind of click it and
flick and dozen lines and you got to
click it and flick
click and flick and click and flick and
SP it I'll use
matches they they call this a childproof
lighter cuz only kids can figure out how
to use
it and the thing is that really bugs me
is that you don't have a choice on which
form of lighter you'd rather
buy I don't have any kids but yet if I
want to buy a disposable lighter I have
to buy a child proof lighter well why
don't you just make me buy a safety seat
for my car while you're at
it you're already making me buy an
airbag for the
car you have no choice in this matter
yeah and it's easy to see why the
government was solding airbags you know
cuz those demonstration films are in
slow motion and in slow motion and
airbag looks
great it it appears as though as the car
Carin into the
wall a big comfy pillow
appears so you can kind of snuggle your
head down in
[Applause]
there you take a little nap before the
crash turns out that they erupt from the
steering wheel with a trifle more of a
line
vity this Zeppelin actually explodes
from the steering
wheel at a speed specified by federal
law at 200 mil an
hour 200 miles an I don't know where
they came up with that figure you know
probably some genius nephew of a
congressman got a job the job doing the
math
well let's see if the car is going 70 M
an hour that way and it'ss another car
coming 70 M an hour that way windshield
now approaches your
[Music]
face 140 M an
hour the bag has to beat the windshield
to your
face 200 mil an hour
[Applause]
exactly can I have my grant
[Laughter]
now in order to get them out of out of
the steering wheel that fast they have
to have something inside their a little
device called a propellant canister
which sounds really harmless and inert a
little aerosol job freshen you your the
air and saves your life in one
puff but it's actually packed full of
magn magnesium compound
explosive yeah and it's roughly the same
size and shape as a shotgun shell
yes so if you would like to experience
for
yourself the joy of an airbag
deployment go get your daddy's
shotgun tie an old vacuum cleaner bag
around the end of the
muzzle then stick this safety device
through the middle of the steering
column right behind the horn button cuz
you know you are not that coming out and
smacking your head on the way
out just kind of put your face under
there
and give that trigger a little
flip I'm sure you're going to say well
I'd feel safer without
that but you know that's not an
option right even though you know people
have been killed by these things heads
have been thrown across parking lots
faces have been torn
off they're still adamant about these
things being in cars and I I'm sure it
has nothing to do with the fact that the
propellant canisters are manufactured by
uh government contributor
TRW I'm sure that's just a
coincidence but they do have a few
Solutions if you're a little
concerned uh number one they're
requiring that children and elderly
persons always always always ride in the
back
seat which is going to make it really
hard for Grandma to drive to church on
Sunday going to have to reach over that
driver's seat and kind of hook her cane
around the steering
wheel Rudder that sucker
in the the other solution is uh bigger
warning
labels which I don't know how they're
going to get any bigger they already
cover the entire back of a window visor
yeah going to have to make a window
visor that folds down two or three
times how do you work this are H do not
read this warning label while operating
V
oh and if you've seen the sticker it's
Universal it's federally mandated it
goes in every single vehicle regardless
of type my sister just bought a brand
new Don Dakota pickup truck two seat bed
in the back and the ferally mandated
warning label on the visor says children
must always ride in the
back yeah I I smell a lawsuit
here I know you're cold honey it's for
your own
good you hold on to the dog you want to
keep warm
[Music]
the truth and you can't disconnect this
thing do you know that it's a federal
crime to pull out the fuse to disable
the airbag in the vehicle that you just
bought yeah I I don't know what they're
going to do to you if they catch you
you'll probably send you to mattress tag
Federal
[Laughter]
Penitentiary and people wonder why
there's so much crime around today it's
not because of global
warming we don't don't have room for the
real criminals
anymore there are so many laws on the
books that I highly doubt there's 100%
Law Abiding Citizen left in the United
States of America we have become a
nation of 250 million criminals just
waiting to be
arrested cuz I would bet that each and
every one of us violates at least one
law a day especially if you
drive you know unless you're over 65
yeah if there's a cop
around yeah me too man when there's a
cop on the road I've got those hands at
10 and two seat belts is locked that
speedometer is dead nuts on the
speed ain't no one got the nerve to fly
past a
cop cops know
this so they
hide underneath Bridges and behind
shrubbery
cuz they know full well if they were out
where you could see them everyone would
abide by the speed limit they'd go broke
CU they couldn't write speeding ticket
yeah so they Park their cars in these
hiding places just hoping somebody's got
the nerve to fly past them at a speed
everyone normally drives
anyway why do we let them do that we're
no isn't the government supposed to be a
representation of us yeah isn't it
supposed to be We the People yeah we
would not hide on
ourselves if we're going too fast you
want to slow us down you don't have to
hide no put a cop car right there in
plain view lights flashing you know may
maybe an ambulance next to it
yeah three or four stretchers with
mannequins covered with ketchup
I guarantee no one will go more than 10
miles an hour past that
spot be slowing down to snag a better
look you think that was
real we're paying their
salaries they should entertain
us stage little performance pieces on
the side of the road little bits of
ditch the
theater hire actors to dress up like
cops and criminals and just let them
beat the snot out of each other
there you even have a fake General Store
where a cowboy gets shot in the chest
and does a somersault into the mattress
every hour on the hour make it like a
Universal Studios
tour make it
fun you know
government doesn't like us having
fun that's why fireworks are
illegal well I know every year there's
always a couple accidents fingrid loss
details at
10 they come on the news and show you
Stumpy and his little brother
winky this is why fireworks are illegal
well hold on
every 4th of July we predict that we're
going to lose two 300 lives on the
highways seven fingers in an eyeball
ain't that
bad turns out it's actually more
dangerous to spend forth of July driving
the family to the beach and it is to
hang out in the backyard whipping lames
at each
[Laughter]
other I'd rather have him
8s but we
can't well they give us
some black magic
snakes oh I'm feeling so
patriotic sparklers and smoke bombs and
caps
yawn I like these things things you got
to drive out of state to
get some of you made that road trip I
can
tell in the state of Washington you know
where they they go to get their
fireworks there they go to the Indian
reservations isn't that kind of
funny that we have become such a nation
of
weenies that the white man is buying
gunpowder from the Indians
[Applause]
if you've never been to one of these
fireworks malls do yourself a favor
check it out the stuff they say is sell
there is
incredible bottle rockets as big around
as your fist and industrial strength
fireworks and they've got these things I
just a door they've got these cardboard
cannons they're like that big around and
that tall for like 10 bucks you get the
cardboard Cannon and six gunpowder
shells and man when one of these suckers
goes off the percussion is magnificent
you hear it right in your chest it
[Music]
just that was a good
one you can't have
those they're illegal to possess they're
illegal to transport across state lines
and you sure as hell better not light
one
off but we all
do on the evening of Fourth of July the
summer sky is filled with the flares of
illegal
fireworks what a great way to celebrate
independence
day kind of our way of telling the state
yeah bite me we're still
[Applause]
free probably shouldn't be talking like
this yeah saying that the government
sucks and you like
explosives that just ain't as popular as
it used to
be neither is
Clinton man his popularity has been
dropping like a pair of trousers on the
Oval Office floor
yeah I sense the hostility
already every time you start in about
the Clinton Lewinsky stuff he like shut
up who cares big deal leave him alone no
one cares it's over leave him alone it's
his personal business shut up and all I
think is well you must have voted for
him cuz that's where a lot of people get
mad I know they're a little embarrassed
that they bought into that I feel your
pain
scam I feel your pain
while I'm at it I'm going to feel those
titties
[Applause]
too it's okay darling I'm a
feminist I I think the thing that
bothers me the most about President
Caligula
[Music]
yeah there a this whole notion of
personal
business it's my personal business this
his personal business and comes there
even presidents are entitled to their
private lives well that's
great but you know what what about my
personal
business you know you see for instance I
decided that I wanted to plant a seed in
my backyard
never mind what
kind personal
business now see I wanted to spend a
summer watering that seed and
fertilizing it and letting it grow nice
and green and
stinky sometime in the fall I decide
that I want to pull every flower off
that shrub set them on fire andhale them
into my
lungs personal business right right
right unfortunately 2.1 million
marijuana smokers have been arrested
since Bill Clinton took office he has
ordered the justice department to close
down the cannabis clubs in California
that were dispensing mer medicinal
marijuana to AIDS patients glucoma
victims cancer patients he won even give
the sick the blind in the dying a little
weed there are people in this country
that are going to spend the rest of
their natural lives in prison for
nothing more than smoking their personal
business until he's ready to Pardon
every single one of them nail his ass to
the
[Applause]
[Music]
wall ju just you and me man
how many marijuana smokers do we have
man yeah yeah
right yeah 400,000 tons a year in this
country me and you two guys did it
all
right oh come on folks get
honest that's how they keep us down they
make us ashamed of our little Vice they
make us think that we're the only ones
that have ever done
it the best thing we could do in this
country to get marijuana legalized is if
everyone just picked a day like July
4th twisted up a fat
one then on July 4th at 4:20 in the
afternoon anyone who has ever smoked
smokes or had the inkling to do so she
just March out on their front porches
and torch those suckers up yes
they could never catch all of
us be too busy chasing down bottle
[Laughter]
rockets man I guarantee you would be
surprised to see how many people came
out on their front porch for a smoke
that
evening okay
Joe he's a cop
hey I know where I'm going when I'm dry
man I'm not breaking a secret here am I
no you know there are cops that smoke
marijuana don't you yeah cops don't have
to obey the laws they
enforce no did you ever drive somewhere
with an off-duty
comp speed limits are just a damn
suggestion they got the pedal to the
metal and the badge on the
dash man that badge is better than any
radar detector you can
buy cuz you know a radar detector ain't
going to let you drive with an open beer
and a loaded
handgun but man as long as you got that
badge it's woo
[Music]
[Laughter]
and with a pot man who can really blame
them cops have access to some of the
sweetest spliff on
earth like young man this here's
marijuana I have the duty to inform you
that you have the right to remain
s there ain't a seed in this
sucker sweet Mother of God
a oh you have just won the right to get
the hell out of here real
quick
yep and the sick part
is is that we don't have room for the
real criminals
anymore we are locking people up for
such stupid things like like like
smoking marijuana or or or or filing the
wrong income tax form or pulling the
fuse out of the
dashboard yeah that we do not have room
for the real criminals
anymore you can do mandatory life for
smoking marijuana under the three
strikes your out Bill meanwhile do you
know what you get for stealing a
car two years well well probation the
first
time first first you are on us
I'm I'm taking talking about after five
or
six 18 months it's actually 18 months
for stealing a brand new car a year and
a
half it takes four and a half years to
pay a new car
off it is triple the sentence to acquire
a car
legitimately and the truth isn't man if
the guy next door to me wants to smoke a
joint in his living room he's not
hurting me
if he steals my car I'll kill
him
yeah yeah that's not a bad
idea start treating start treating car
thieves the way we used to horse
thieves should hang
them yeah I know you're going to hang
someone just cuz he took a car yes well
it wasn't
his he should have noticed it didn't
look familiar when he was jamming that
screwdriver in the ignition yeah
you sure you're going to have to hang
two or three but where did get
[Laughter]
out people rather walk than
swing but you know I forget that this is
Minnesota you're a progressive
State they've got the attitude more well
you know if they had cars they wouldn't
take them
so we'll start a program where we paint
a bunch of cars
yellow leave them parked in the side of
the road with keys in the
ignition bring it back when you're
done you guys are great I've had a lot
of fun here tonight thank you so much
[Applause]
I I wonder I wonder I wonder how much uh
longer before they start making jokes
illegal about two years yeah that's what
well actually two votes in the
Senate that that this last bit right
here I believe is exactly two votes away
from uh becoming an illegal joke
because right now that's all there
stands is two senators in between a flag
burning
Amendment how how many people here have
seen someone ever burn a flag
by yeah just a crisis sweeping the
nation isn't it
yeah in a day when everyone wants the
IRS off their backs they're working on a
flag burning Amendment
yeah I think they're trying to distract
us you know cuz who's going to oppose a
flag burning Amendment you might as well
Outlaw the torturing of
puppies yeah
yes and I have no idea where we're going
to start putting flag burning
criminals what we going do parole parole
Charles
Manson that'd be good for
America right and then the strange thing
was or is I uh I myself happen to have
been raised in a traditional uh Suburban
House house I uh was raised a Boy Scout
Cub Scout I I was raised very
patriotically with uh total respect for
the flag I would have never ever dreamed
of burning a
flag well until everyone started talking
about
it you shouldn't do that to an
impressionable boy like me that thinks
the government sucks and likes
explosives
oh you can cut the tension in the room
with a B knife right now
yeah would you guys actually get mad if
I
uh
click well it's okay it's not even a
really American flag there there there's
only 49
Stars yeah this is the official
imitation Tim SLO burnable flag yeah
made in China
at 30 cents a week right yeah ra rather
rather than um amend the uh Constitution
to protect the flag I thought maybe we
should just amend the flag to protect
the Constitution
yes because people think this needs
protection it's it's something they hold
sacred well I I've got something else in
here that I hold
sacred yeah
this is the Bill of
Rights how come no one's talking about
an amendment to protect the fac of
this well sure this is you know prettier
it looks nicer in parades and doesn't
require any
reading you know maybe that's the
problem maybe we should print this in
red white and
blue because you know this is just the
school colors this is the
diploma yes and this starts by saying
that Congress shall pass no law
prohibiting free exercise of religion
well you know I'm sorry I'm a devout
Anarchist My Religion requires me to
burn a flag from time to
time it's just a
flag every tyranny has a flag some of
them are the same colors as
ours North Korea Chile and Cuba all fly
the red white and blue the only
difference is that we B ours up with
this and this protects all speech no
matter how offensive including the right
to burn a flag the ironic thing is that
what makes it an American flag is that
you can burn it yeah it might stand for
America but at one time it also stood
for slavery and the Holocaust of the
American Indian and the only reason why
we were able to rise th above those
injustices was because this gave us the
ability to stand up in public and say
all men are created equal and almost 80
years ago thanks to the right to
organize and the right to protest women
were brought into that equality Club too
yes yeah this might stand for America
but this stands for
Freedom this is the one men went to war
for this is the one our fathers died for
this is what makes this the greatest
country on Earth and this I shall defend
with my dying
breath take your pick you can't have
them
both so connected are they that if you
destroy this this goes along with it I
wish you Liberty good night everybody
[Applause]
[Music]
oh