so I hate men with small
penises yeah don't don't get squirely on
me you know it's not like I prefer the
large
[Laughter]
ones I hate men with small penises
because they're the reason why I had to
clean out 250 emails out of my inbox
this
morning yeah some the same crappy spam
filter I do every single morning she
wants it harder she wants it longer she
needs more girth delete delete
delete every time I hit that delete key
who the hell is ordering this
crap men with small
penises for me it's an annoyance but
somewhere on the other side of town
There's a pathetic individual with a
double a chubby in his hand
suddenly gets an anonymous message from
the ethernet all the way from
Nigeria says to himself could this be
the answer to my
problem
guys if there's one of you out there
right
now don't order that
crap cuz here's what happens you figure
they send out 1.2 million emails doesn't
cost him a dime all it takes is one
idiot to say Well it's only 20 bucks
maybe I should try
it whole village in Nigeria parties for
a
month cuz I've seen those late night TV
commercials you can feed a family of
five in Nigeria for like a
quarter so 20 bucks is a pretty awesome
keger oh we have to send out more of
these
emails I mean honestly don't don't buy
that get a better job become a
linguist because if you got a lot of
money and a clever tongue she won't look
at your
[Laughter]
dick I mean really do you think if there
was a pill you could take that would
make it grow you wouldn't have heard
about it by now
everybody would have heard about it by
now guys would be eating that stuff like
breakfast
cereal cuz guys look at inches the way
crazy women look at
[Laughter]
cats 12 is just never
enough if there was a patch you could
wear that would make it grow you'd see
guys walking around wrapped up like The
Mummy
you see guys W with garden hose reel
strapped to their shoulder they can wind
that sucker up so they won't trip over
it
anymore you'd see guys with one so fat
they'd have to push them around in a
shopping
cart not just your regular Walmart
shopping cart no that Home Depot
shopping cart that you put the drywall
in the 2x4s on you would be reading
stories about guys walking through the
mall past Victoria Secret and getting an
ere and dying right there on the spot
from all the blood loss from their brain
just their whole life Essence just
sucked into this throbbing cold blue
python flopping around on the floor till
it slowly
stops don't touch that kids it looks
dangerous Billy that is not a ride