hi I'm Tim slel and this is my show that
I called awake I did it back in 1993 I
pretty much did it all myself right down
to the title card that I uh uh banged a
pot lid to make it sound like a church
Bill uh it's in black and white so it
looks a lot older than it actually is
the reason is because uh back then you
couldn't color correct in post and uh
the white balance was brought was out of
the sync on both cameras so uh what
happened was we just had to take the
color out and and uh uh the haircut
looks older than it is too it's you
you'll see what I'm talking about
[Music]
[Applause]
w
uh no it's not a wig and I don't like it
anymore than you
do but my mom doesn't [ __ ] about me not
going to church anymore
you know you think Mom would have
learned about me in religion when I was
13 years old into heavy metal and she
asked me to say grace for the first
time holy Satan Prince of Darkness BL
the garbage on the
[Music]
table that was an Easter to
remember poor Grandma never quite
recovered
oh I've got nervous faces looking at me
right
now have we got Catholics here is that
here well
relax I'm
Catholic did you think I could be
anything but the product of the Catholic
system
me and
[Music]
Madonna see we don't have to worry about
going to
hell we're
Catholics they send Baptist to hell just
for
dancing they send Mormons to hell for
drinking
coffee did you know that because
caffeine's a drug if you're a Mormon
it's a sin to drink coffee
it's kind of funny if you think about it
to a Mormon a thermos is drug
paraphernalia well that's a caffeine
[Laughter]
bong an espresso machine is kind of like
a Freebase
[Applause]
unit see that we're
Catholics we can see our entire lives
and still get into
heaven we can have sex we can drink we
can swear we can smoke we can miss Mass
every day until the day we die just as
long as we get to confession right
before we
die we're in
there might have to spend 9 10 years in
purgatory
sure the way I got it figured with the
way Catholics have been breeding
Purgatory is going to be terrible
overcrowded I'll be out in 6 months good
[Applause]
behavior I I I have no respect for
authority I don't that's that's why I
can relate to Rodney King you
know yeah I I really feel sorry for
Rodney King you've got
to just a poor innocent crack
addict driving 100 m an hour drunk
through a school
zone oh next thing you know trouble with
the
[Laughter]
law and what I don't understand and the
police were really basing their defense
on this was that in their eyes he was
not acting subdued they felt that he
kept trying to get up and I don't
understand that when you get hit with a
night stick you're supposed to play de
that saved my life on a number of
occasions oh in my rambunctious youth I
knew all too well the distinctive sting
a night stick leaves and I'd lay real
still no one ever had a riot for
me of course everyone says well that
whole Rodney King think now that that
was just racism and I think no that was
just CS
we hire people that like to do that kind
of
stuff see I once felt that it was my
duty to give a comp a little lesson in
constitutional
law oh he was so grateful he returned
the favor by giving me a little lesson
on how the system really
worked actually I felt I was exercising
My First Amendment right to free speech
when I said bite me you wife beating
alcoholic donut stuffed
pig he didn't seem to notice what color
I
was I laid real
still not that I'm saying that that
prejudice does not exist it's
rampant every single one of us in this
room here tonight is prejudiced in one
form or another it's just that some
forms of prejudice we recognize as bad
and there's some that we completely
ignore for instance when I came up here
on stage just about 25 minutes ago you
all
applauded now if I were standing on your
front porch at 4:00 in the
morning with a tire
iron your response wouldn't be quite so
benevolent tell I'd probably just be
looking for a call to the motor
club you'd be looking for a comp to give
me the Rodney King
workout but you see that's the way we
are there's racis and we recognize as
bad there's racism we completely
ignore when a black kid gets beat up in
an all-white neighborhood that's
racism when a white kid gets beat up in
an all black neighborhood that's
stupid didn't he know where the hell he
was
[Applause]
[Music]
we're that way about names too there
there's names we can use there's names
we can't the owner of the Cincinnati
Reds had her baseball team taken away
from her because she used a word a word
that's not protected by the First
Amendment and we can't have racism in
baseball we never had it
before you forget the we've got a team
called the
Braves we've got a team called the
Indians with Chief waho as The Smiling
mascot we got a football team called the
Redskins now that word redskins now that
word is just as offensive to Native
Americans is as the word that shoty used
is to
African-Americans forget that there are
no Native Americans on the Washington
football team there's no Native
Americans even living in that part of
the country
they had to
move so that we could build the East
Coast kind of the same way that the
native Africans had to move so that the
English could build South
Africa talk about a part th I think we
invented it right here in the US of
a how would we feel if that all-white
South African soccer team the Petoria
porch monkeys
was going up against the Johannesburg
jigaboos well the silence I'm hearing
right now that wouldn't be all right
would
it but it's okay to use
Redskins there's a chain of stores in
the South called the Thrifty
Scotsman the idea is here that the
prices are so low even a Scotsman might
enjoy
shopping a Scotsman are
cheap that's funny cuz they're
Scotsman you'll never see a chain of
stores called The Frugal
[Applause]
Jew the same thing isn't
[Music]
it well except for the fact that Jews
probably own the Thrifty Scots
[Applause]
a lot of people use AIDS as a way to
Prejudice themselves against groups they
never cared for much in the first place
and they think that's all right because
it's just good health sense
and God actually uses aids to punish
Sinners you know people believe that in
1993 they believe that just kind of the
way that they used to feel about leprosy
in the time of Christ you the Catholics
figure that aids is God's way of
punishing promiscuity and the
Protestants figure it's God's way of
punish ing substance abuse and I guess
the Jehovah's Witnesses and Christian
Scientists figure it's God's way of
punishing blood
transfusions I don't think God really
works that way punishing with
disease if he did wouldn't there be some
form of incurable attorney virus
[Applause]
we don't know how it's spread but it
seems to only strike injury attorneys
and
congressmen must be
God right now our Congress in Washington
is frantically trying to put together a
tough anti-me
Bill aren't all bills anti-me
bills isn't everything they've done
supposed to be preventing crime it's
like yeah yeah but this is a tough one
this one's got gun control oh that'll
work yeah cuz if we make everyone
register their weapons people will come
in and turn them in some guy will go I'd
like to get this pistol
registered hey aren't you a
criminal okay take
it just passed a law against carjacking
too yeah that's why people were
carjacking
oh we forgot to write that
law forget that we've already got laws
against armed robbery Grand Theft Auto
abduction kidnapping now we got a
specific law so when some young punk
takes a gun and holds it up to a car
window he's going to go oh wait a
minute oh they just passed that law
didn't
they so if I put this gun up against
this car and take this car
I'm guilty of a federal
crime oh I just better get a job so I
can buy a
car while I'm at it I'm going to get
this handgun registered
too see I don't think the solution to
carjacking is more laws I think the
solution to carjacking is something very
simple we've had it for a very long time
it's called
holsters mounted permanently into car
doors right about crotch
level say you can tuck a pistol in there
and you wouldn't even want to put a hole
in the car door either that way some
young punk won't know if there's a
pistol in that holer or not and if there
is there'll just be a little extra
shrapnel in the
[Music]
wound and you know you wouldn't even
have to use you wouldn't even have to
use a trigger you could hook up a
hydraulic release mechanism and put a
switch on the
floorboards like where that dimer switch
used to be in the older
models you wouldn't have to take your
hands off the
wheel stopped at a red like get out of
that
car
[Music]
no course you know it get really
tempting to use this thing
like when you were stuck in
traffic and had those impatient jerks
passing you on the left and cutting in
front of
you of course they'd only do it
once amazing what a little Gunplay will
do to increase driver
etiquette see I I I don't believe in gun
control I I think it's
wrong I I I don't see how we really
think that we can get rid of all the
firearms in America you know I'll just
make them illegal and we'll get rid of
them just like we got rid of all the
drugs in
America see I think we have the right to
own oozies if we want
ues a lot of people think that's funny
they go well you know if you have to
fire 60 shots in 10 seconds maybe
hunting's not your
[Music]
sport which is very funny but it's
ignoring the real issue you see the
right to bear arms is not the right to
hunt
deer our founding fathers were not
worried about having the right to hunt
taken away from them the right to bear
arms is the right to arm one's
population in the event an unjust
government has to be
overthrown right now the right to bear
arms is the only form of term limitation
we have in the Constitution
that's why we need
ues cuz you got to know without a doubt
in your mind if you're going to take out
Clinton you got time to squeeze a couple
in Gore before the Secret Service takes
you
[Applause]
[Music]
down some of you are taking this way too
serious he's talking
Revolution no I I'm
not of course I would like to add that
Hitler was elected by a democratic
process oh no I'm not comparing Clinton
to
Hitler no no Clinton's a lot more like
Stalin except I think Stalin kept a lot
more of his promises
[Music]
[Applause]
I know for a fact when Stalin promised
the middle class attack cut they they
got their tax
cut I'm still waiting for mine of course
maybe I'm rich because that's what we
were going to do we're going to tax the
rich I hate to tell Bill that idea has
been tried before it's as old as Robin
Hood
you know the thing is in this country we
can't find the
[Music]
rich we can't no one in this country
thinks they're rich we all think we're
Middle
Class Bill Clinton defines rich as any
couple that makes more than $200,000 a
year now to him that's rich do you know
what he and Hillary pulled in last year
like
a198 they're not rich
I'm sorry forget that he made half of
Little Rock Arkansas's gross national
product forget that he's got $111,000 he
can blow on a year schooling for his
little
[Applause]
troll I I yeah you're right I I I
shouldn't say that
the only thing Chelsea's done wrong
she's just a dorky little girl with
dorky
parents that's hard enough as it is but
it just really ticks me off Bill's
attitude about sending her to private
school it's like well yeah but there's
nothing wrong with the public school
system yeah for you
people I guess it was kind of a personal
issue though it seems that the students
at the DC Middle School had the Secret
Service out gone
yeah nothing more tax dollars won't
cure see all you really doing when when
you're taxing the wealthiest uh 1% of
America at a higher rate than the rest
of us all you're really doing is you
leave the remaining 99% that thinks it's
a good idea and will still vote for you
it's not really a solution it's just
playing the odds if Mexico were a state
we'd all be
screwed we'd all be in the wealthiest 1%
then I think everybody in this room
makes more than a 100 bucks a
year see that's what we forget on a
global scale we are the
rich We're a nation we're no child born
with in these borders ever has to worry
about starving to death that's an
amazing
thing there's nobody starving in
America if it was wouldn't it be in the
papers the last person I remember
reading about starving to death in
America was Karen
Carpenter that was n years ago and
self-induced
don't get me wrong I know there there's
people
hungry there's people eating stuff
they'd rather not be
eating there's no one
starving we have fat homeless
[Music]
people our Farmers grow so much food we
have to pay them off with tax dollars
not to grow
anymore because we even waste so much
food at restaurants you can get a hot
meal out of a
dumpster some of you are looking at me
like I know that a little too
well I was in Washington DC a couple
weeks back uh looking for the
change you and it looks exactly like it
did during the Reagan Bush years a lot
of homeless people and a lot of
limousines
didn't see any change but I actually was
watching something that really changed
my perspective I I saw a homeless man
feeding stale breadcrumbs to the birds
they they were a little bit too stale
for his
liking I'm watching this and I'm going
man there's nobody starving in
America if there was you would not see a
homeless man feeding bread to the
birds you wouldn't see birds
in Somalia there's no such thing as a
stray
animal I doubt there's too many pets
left I don't really why do we want to
think we're more miserable than we are
that's why people in Haiti are dying to
get into this country they they can't
believe this well they're willing to
risk 600 miles of open shark infested
ocean to get here and Bill goes oh I
didn't say
no they can't believe this country
they're like you mean in America you got
Parks just full of
[Laughter]
pigeons and they're so Ted that they'll
eat right out of your hand like even if
you got a great big stick in the other
one it's pouy every night in America
if we're not going to let the Haitians
into this country we should turn the
Statue of Liberty
[Music]
around turn out the
light kind of like turning the No
Vacancy sign in a
motel you got to get rid of that plaque
too cuz I think that's what's attracting
them you know the
one send me you're tired you're hungry
you're huddled masses yearning to be
free cuz I know right now when garbage
Sloop outside of Haiti some guys going
tired hungry huddled
Mass Ro
trip let's put up something a little
more truthful like send us your wealthy
you're white you're
educated you're foreign doctors who
can't speak a word of
English love to feed the rest of you but
the breast of Liberty are only so large
[Applause]
anyway Bill's going to change the
Student Loan program around
too yeah he's going to offer a volunteer
service to pay off your student
loan now that doesn't seem right to me
it's kind of backwards you get the
student loan you go to school then you
do volunteer service that's kind of like
saying well here's your paycheck when
you get it spent you report for work
[Laughter]
no not only that you're going to be able
to borrow as much money as you want now
he's going to remove all limits from the
amount of money you can borrow and
rather than borrow the money from Banks
because Banks don't know anything about
loaning money you'll now be able to
borrow directly from the
government apparently Bill isn't aware
of the student loan default rate as it
stands I found it quite easy to flunk
out a with $2,000 worth of
liquor H if there was no limit I'd be
drinking there
[Music]
still no probably
not I'm too old for the college party
scene i' I've done too much it bores
me now anymore it's got to be some form
of life-threatening Pagan origy for me
to enjoy myself
and how often does that
happen it gets really hard too cuz I
play a lot of colleges I get these kids
coming up to me after the show want me
to come back and party at the frat house
and I
decline then they get really indignant
they can't believe I've just turned down
the social event of the semester they're
like yeah dude but you haven't party do
you partied with the
teeks wait a
minute I haven't
partied look at me
I used to be
handsome what you see in front of you is
the result of 13 years of life on the
road hanging out in small town bars
across America living every night like
it was New Year's
Eve I bet a lot of places done a lot of
things a lot of people only get to dream
of I I did cocaine with Sam kenison I
did heroin with the Red Hot Chili
Peppers I once did 15 hits of acid at
Marty Gro I spent a night in Montreal
with three bisexual French Canadian
[Music]
stewardesses somehow I feel your awesome
little keger is going to leave me a
trifle
disappointed not like I'm bragging or
anything maybe a
little you know what I'm talking about
if you ever been to Disney World once
you been on top of Space Mountain the
teacup ride's just going to make you
[Music]
sick a lot of you got that that's
cool it shows your hip you
know cuz you know that's that's the only
nice thing I can say about Bill Clinton
he's one of
us he's a pot smoker
[Applause]
what better opportunity to get this
ridiculous marijuana legislation off the
books for good here is positive proof
that marijuana is indeed
harmless Bill Clinton smoked marijuana
what happened did he go an addict that
had to steal to support his habit did he
became a lunatic inside of an insane
asylum somewhere did he become a burnout
still living in his parents basement at
35 years of
age he became 42nd President of the
United States of
America of course he didn't
inhale maybe that's
why it's time to be honest I
think I mean come on Clarence Thomas was
the second Supreme Court nominee that
admitted to smoking marijuana apparently
Dan Quail was kissing the bong back in
71 Alan Tipper Gore admitted to smoking
marijuana in college yeah Tipper isn't
that
weird cuz Tipper is the one that wanted
to censor rock and roll music no kind of
makes you wonder what they were
listening to when they got stoned in C
oh bat Boon is so
[Applause]
awesome no no no leave it on Perry
Como's
Next Star Spangled Banner awesome
Jam I mean even Ron and Nancy Reagan
once smoked
marijuana just say no
maybe no Frank I'm
[Applause]
sore oh I'm sorry that saying no to
drugs thing always burned me up you
don't know how much money I would give
just to take one peak in Nancy Reagan's
medicine
capab she looks like a vum hag if I've
ever seen
one Mommy's got it
headache say no to
drugs now Nance
babe say no to Poverty say no to Greed
say no to hunger say no to corruption
ignorance War violence bigotry Prejudice
hatred cuz if you can get rid of all of
those I won't need any goddamn drugs
so you can mind your own
business this country we're supposed to
be entitled to life liberty and pursuit
of happiness and the way things are
going drugs are about the only happiness
I can
afford I I don't want to freak you
people I know it's a little late to
worry about
that it if you've really never smoked
marijuana before I want you to know
right here and now that you've been lied
to you've been told horror stories and
probably believe
them you've been told that if you smoke
marijuana even
once you're going to start shooting up
you're going to murder your family
you're going to have three-headed
babies
no you smoke marijuana all you're going
to do is eat a bunch of Twinkies and
watch the Flintstone
[Music]
[Applause]
well don't get me wrong that's all
you're going to
do 5 six hours at a
[Music]
crack if you want to spend the rest of
your life in Bedrock that's your own
business I figure it's supposed to be a
free
country remember that when you a little
kid like if your buddy wanted you to
leave his house and you didn't want to
go I don't have to go home it's a free
country did you ever wonder what a
little kid in China would in that same
situation oh I don't have to go home
it's a totalitarian socialist
systems you don't even own your own
house it's the people's house
that's what scares me the most about
this War on Drugs we're just handing
over our freedoms and no one seems to
care the Fourth Amendment the
Constitution says quite plainly that
there should be no form of governmental
search or seizure but now well we think
it's perfectly acceptable just to seize
all the property any even suspect has
been using drugs forget due process
we're not letting the government search
without warrants inside of our homes our
cars even our bodily fluids just to keep
our neighbors away from Fred and
[Music]
Barney they're now requiring drug
testing for all employees of Blockbuster
Video oh thank
God well you don't know how many people
have died just cuz some punk kid forgot
to check if the tape was
rewound something happened just recently
made a lot more people clamor for drug
testing Subway worker in New York passed
out at the wheel ran through three stops
derailed and five people were killed and
now everyone's saying well we need more
drug testing for Subway workers which is
fine except this guy wasn't on any
illegal
drugs he was
drunk he was good oldfashioned All
American
loaded his blood alcohol was twice the
legal limit 3 hours after the accident
yeah yeah impressive by my
standards you know you see people saying
well we should outlaw alcohol we tried
that once we know it doesn't work
especially in the Chicago
[Applause]
area oh we had gangs with automatic
weapons long before
crack I hate to tell La I think the
driveby shooting was invented right here
in Chicago in the 20s
I know there's a few of you going yeah
but would you wanted that driver have
been smoking marijuana
2 well
yeah had he been smoking marijuana he
would have gone through the same three
stops but he would have only been going
2 miles an hour
[Applause]
I think it's just
Prejudice I think it's just prejudice
against substance
preferred we send our pothe heads to
jail while we send our alcoholics into
the House and Senate
[Applause]
you know if we divided your careers by
by by race that wouldn't be accepted but
substance it we do alcohol is just a
drug I think we all know
that especially
tequila some of you know that a little
too
[Applause]
well ever drink Miss skull oh yeah good
that's the tequila with the treat
yeah I saw an ad from his scol cracked
me up they a picture of the bottle with
a treat in the bottom
treat they said at the top the best part
about Miss scal is getting down to the
bottom and they had an arrow pointing at
the treats there' be no mistake what
they're talking about over in this
corner they got this government
warning starts out
please always drink
responsibly wait wait a
minute now you're talking about drinking
so much straight liquor that you would
not find it unnatural to chew up and
swallow a bloated mutant insect
L I think responsibility is gone when
you crack the seal on this
[Music]
beverage then they had this new one I
know you've seen this one too it says
pregnant women should not consume this
product hold it
again if you don't know enough that you
should not be drinking a fifth of mcal a
day with the worm while you're pregnant
you've got no right reproducing in the
first
place aren't our trailer park
overcrowded
[Applause]
enough yeah sure I can get away with
that in Chicago
but don't boo me I didn't say where I
couldn't
anyway yeah I think I think it's stupid
that that the amount of jail space were
taken up with with drug
criminals right now more than 50% of all
prison capacity is occupied by drug
violations alone think about that we
could double the prison beds just by
calling an into this war that we're
losing
miserably we are send we are um letting
murderers and rapists out of jail early
so we can lock up the people who have a
Yabba Duba do
time here's how this works against us
Jeffrey
dmer well we had him once before all the
nonsense
started but because of overcrowding he
was let go after only 12 months of work
release for molesting a child 12 months
that should have been the death penalty
right there I
figure it would have freed up a lot of
newspaper
space meanwhile if you get caught with a
pound and a half of cocaine in Michigan
which is not that much
[Laughter]
this just a good party backstage Guns
and
Roses I might add an awful lot of you
seem to know exactly how much a pound in
a half of cocaine
is how much is compared to a molested
child a pound and a half of cocaine in
Michigan will now get you life
imprisonment it used to be mandatory the
state supreme court said that's a little
strict but right now the legislature is
frantically trying to get it reinstated
mandatory life no parole ever turn now
you can be paroled in Michigan for
murder or rape after 6 years so I guess
that's what we learn here if you get
caught with a lot of cocaine in Michigan
you better rape and kill that
[Applause]
cop you want to get off and entirely you
eat him and plead
Insanity I'm not
serious I'm finding out the hypocrisy of
the judicial system how do I see any on
the side of the road after the show
[Applause]
going well the comic told me to
see I I I I think I actually think we'd
be a lot better off in this country Ju
Ju Just legalizing the stuff taxing it
and put the farmers back to
work no subsidies
necessary encourage Americans to buy
American that's true maybe take some of
this money that that that we're not
spending on this war we're losing
miserably and and maybe pay back a
little of the national
debt which if the Clinton economic plan
goes as planned will be another trillion
dollars higher in
1996 it took 204 years to get the
national debt up to 1 trillion it took
12 years of bush and Reagan to get it up
to four trillion now Clinton's getting
it to five in only four years that's the
kind of deficit reduction we need I
think how do you run up five trillion of
debt I I don't understand that Visa cut
me off when I hit 20
grand when I stop sending them money
they got nasty with me they were calling
me at home they never cared how I was
before they're calling going Mr slle you
had $20,000 in debt last year and I said
no you kind of got thatt wrong you see
last year I ran ran a $20,000 budget
deficit I don't care what you call it
you owe it's
$220,000 I go no you got that wrong
too last year you purchased $220,000 of
high yield junk Bonds in the Tim Lego
[Laughter]
Corporation in the future I suggest you
be a little more shrewd with your in has
been
[Music]
procedure folks if you've got kids
please teach your children about
taxes and the best time you can do this
is on
[Laughter]
Halloween see cuz they just put in about
eight full hours of power trick or treat
they've got a nice big bag of what
should be take home
candy just greet your Little Tike at the
do say that's a nice big bag of candy
you got there
Donatella first of all see just because
You' made this much we have to take away
this
much income
tax
then to ensure you'll have candy in your
old
age pay the Social Security
tax F quit crying you'll see it in 50
years oh no we'll put it right up here
won't touch it till
then
right oh last of all we can't forget
that state tax can
we oh wait a
minute I forgot what state we're
[Laughter]
in there's your Snickers
bar oh wait you can eat that right now
hold it just a minute
sales
[Applause]
taex you know though I think kids are
smarter than that I'll bet if you did
that to your kid he wouldn't even get
dressed up the next
year probably spend the whole evening on
the couch in front of the tube and when
Mom put out that big bowl of candy for
the other
kids he just walk over to that bull dump
it in his bag hey I'm on welfare this
[Applause]
[Music]
year for