[Music]
streaming at you digitally the tape live
at The juk Joint Comedy Club Lilydale
Minnesota just 15 minutes out of
downtown Minneapolis the standup Channel
presents
Uprising dedicated to bring you the best
comedians we can find tonight's Comics
are Ryan Miller michah Walsh Colleen
Doyle Justice and Ray Harrington ladies
and gentlemen start screaming now your
host Mr Chris
[Music]
madic well God damn what a
night thank you so much for coming folks
to Uprising the greatest comedy show
this
night I'm Chris I'm your host selling
CDs after the show folks I had this
happen in South Dakota I was working in
South Dakota I wasn't there for like a
vacation and uh had CDs for sale after
the show 12 CDs on the table I know
there's 12 two rows of
six yeah that's 12 I thought I could
leave the table for a second right no I
come back for after like two minutes
look at the table [ __ ] 13
CDs somebody brought one back from a
different show from a different town I
did one show in that town somebody drove
five hours this is not for me thank you
throw it away that guy didn't want that
CD anywhere in his house he didn't want
it in his landfill he drove so far I
think it's a good
CD folks I'm going to start the show I
mean I've started the
show but I'm going to start the show I'm
going to bring up your first comic of
the evening folks ladies and gentlemen
Brian
[Applause]
Miller hope you guys are having a good
winner hope you had a nice uh holiday I
had a very nice
Christmas but every year Christmas
people always say to my wife uh oh but
Christmas just isn't the same when you
don't have
children yeah but the other 364 days
just aren't the same when you have
children the reason Christmas isn't that
special when you don't have kids is cuz
the other days are fun
too it just Blends right in you buy
yourself [ __ ] you have a party you eat
bad food every day it's great
I'm lucky because my wife does not want
to have any
kids yeah
jackpot those are hard to find you guys
I really don't want kids when I found
out cell phone radiation lowers your
sperm count I got a second phone for my
other
Pockets I'm on the Verizon Wireless
birth control
plan it's a good one it's a friends and
no family
plan I really like my nights and
weekends free you know
you can everything about it half a
second too late it's PR fun it's pry fun
it's like we're talking on a phone in
Australia and it's like oh man I'm
killing down
under takes a while to get there but
it's worth it when it
does crocodile done dears really
enjoying
it say they whatever you're the best
you're the
best my my father-in-law really wants
Grand kids but uh so he knows he can't
just go straight forward with it he has
to be subtle about it so he tried this
one on me he said Son don't you want
someone to carry on your
legacy
what Legacy what's this kid supposed to
do bounce a check in an adult
bookstore it's the Miller boy right
there
yeah carrying on the family
name we have Brian Miller with us
everyone Brian Miller fantastic comedian
Minneapolis Minnesota home base let me
ask you you were on to you you you were
on television I was what was that like
what were you on what happened I was on
The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson
uh it was like three years ago I was
pretty new to Comedy he was in the uh
crowd at a show I did and um at Acme in
Minneapolis he because he's very cool he
shows up to shows just to watch which I
thought was great and uh he was there
and he just asked me to come do the show
and and uh it was a crazy fluky thing I
was really new I was woefully unprepared
uh I'm still kind of shed about how
unprepared I was um but it was great and
uh when they called they called me like
two days later to see like and they hey
you want to be on the Craig Ferguson
show and I thought it was uh our friend
senson praying a prank and I said [ __ ]
you Sai and the guy goes excuse me I was
like oh I don't think s would have
reacted that way I don't think that was
sson what was the response like it was
good it was a good response uh I got you
know it was uh people were surprised cuz
I was new and I was also surprised yeah
uh but yeah it was generally a pretty
positive response and you know got a
little got a little work out of the deal
but it it was a very exciting thing to
do you know what I say is one of those
things where the worst case scenario if
you never get to do comedy again you got
to do that this good I'm I'm doing good
this winter so far I last year I got
kind of down in the winter I got I got
that I got that sad I got that Seasonal
effective disorder thing and I see a
psychologist about it and uh she told me
I had to do some indoor exercises to get
my endorphin levels back up she
recommended jumping
rope so I got a prescription strength
jump
rope no Nike jump rope it's made for a
man yeah it's made by Nike it's for a
man to jump
over I never used it so like two months
go by I'm out 30 bucks still depressed
now I have a
rope it's just staring at me from the
shelf right in the Box it says just do
it like
[ __ ] it's
heavy I'm a little I'm a little crazy
but I'm not the craziest guy around uh I
saw the craziest man in Minneapolis last
week he was at a bus
stop I was pulled up at the bus stop and
he uh he had a KitKat bar and he opened
up his Kit Kat bar he unwrapped it and
then he just he just took a big bite
into the middle like
toast like what the [ __ ] like no sense
of symmetry no possibility of sheries
just I was like this is anarchy drive
drive we got to get out of here I don't
know what the [ __ ] this guy's going to
do
next if I ever go to prison that's going
to be my
move first day in the yard just walk out
there now you [ __ ] that guy eat the
Reese's Peanut Butter Cup like a normal
human being that's a safer bets
I don't know what I might
do I had a good I had a good summer I
went to the best part of my summer I
went to my first black strip
club yeah thank you people know the
truth which is that black strip clubs
are way better than white strip clubs
like a million times better I didn't
know this until I went well because like
first off right when I walked in the
door I got to answer the Eternal
question what would make 50 black dudes
simultaneously stop staring at a naked
lady yeah answers me walking into a
black strip
club like what's the white woman from
the library doing here like hey
everybody Make It Rain I did it was
awesome it was great but I never
realized all this time i' only never
been to White Strip Clubs I never
realized that the strippers there are
terrible at their
jobs they're awful they just stand they
just hold on to the pole and they do
like slow motion aerobics big frown in
their face we're all supposed to be
impressed whatever no black strippers
they are real entertainers they are true
entertainers
they earn that money man they do that
crazy stuff like that dancing thing they
twerk they pop their hips and their butt
cheeks like they smack together and they
clap they clap with their
asses it's the greatest thing I've ever
seen in my
life right in the club there was like
three dancers doing it all at the same
time sounded like somebody just won a
golf
tournament well I was very excited you
know cuz if someone in the room did win
a golf tournament it's probably
me so you you during the day sometimes I
know you do movie uh reviews for your
movie reviews for the night life in
Carbondale Illinois where I've worked
for 17 years yeah who hasn't who hasn't
and uh also I know you're a proof reader
very exciting I'm a Comm Baron as I like
what's the biggest word you know what's
the biggest word I know anti- anti-
disestablishmentarianism I think is the
longest word in the dictionary I thought
thought it was pneuma ultra microscopic
silico volcanic coniosis that would be a
medical term I'm talking the Webster's
Dictionary Miram Webster what's the
difference between count
Scrabble what why why is it a medical
term a word it's not that it's not it's
just not necessar a word it's more a
medical term this a subtle distinction
so I'm right no I'm
right correct guys I'm going to level
with you I'm not actually [ __ ] Steve
I just made it up for the joke uh I did
actually go on a real date recently so
and by that I mean I met a woman from
Tinder at a sports bar in
Roseville and we made out in the parking
lot cuz we're both
14 I'm kidding only she was 14 that's
not
funny what's the deal with consent laws
am I right no uh no but she was like 23
or something it's not really important
to the story but the point is we made
out it was a good date by all accounts
we made plans to hang out a couple days
later couple days later I text her hey
how's it going and she responded pretty
good funny story I got back together
with my ex today and I was like well
that wasn't funny or a
story you set that up so
wrong I think she should have said uh
pretty good relevant
anecdote won't be making out of Buffalo
Wild Wings
anymore I've been married for 18 years
myself so um yeah I know amazing I was
married at 12
um yeah it's been it's not the most
passionate relationship anymore I'd have
to say um this year we bought each other
um a sectional couch for our anniversary
and it was like the biggest couch that
they had to offer and then the year
before that we bought a king-size bed so
basically what we're doing is we're just
buying furniture that's so big that we
don't have to physically be near each
other when we use it so it's working out
great yeah and I I'm sure it's my fault
that the passion is gone I think I have
I just have like body image
issues I just don't like my husband's
body
and I don't like it near me or around me
or on top of me it's just
G enough
welcome yeah you guys are here all right
having fun yeah I'm going to bring your
headliner to the stage folks he performs
comedy all over the world ladies and
gentlemen Ray
Harrington language uh I moved I moved
to Rhode Island and uh when I moved my
my aunt-in-law my wife's aunt she was
very excited she wanted to point out all
the places to go and visit in Rhode
Island and she's like oh now that you
live here you got to go visit Purgatory
Chasm you got to go see the chasm it's
beautiful at the chasm you can pack a
picnic have a whole day at the chasm
bring the baby to the chasm it'll be a
lot of fun at this she said Chasm 300
times blood was going to start trickling
down my face I had I said finally it's
Chasm right the word you're thinking of
is Chasm it's like a Gulch Chasm and
then she said to me very [ __ ] I think
it's
Chasm CH
chasm really did you learn that in
stoel so we don't go to her house for
Christmas
anymore yeah we're here with Ray
Harrington the Piston of
Comedy um and uh he uh piston the like
an an engine oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you're like a piston that's your that's
not you you you read my bio yeah yeah
the ray the pist
I would love somebody to be like Ray the
Piston is coming in and then just walk
in my name's octane Octane and the
Piston welcome back to Octane and the
Piston we're talking about and then we
need an effect where the camera cracks
camera cracks a lot of shaking yeah cool
can we do that do we have that is that
in the budget's got it are you on the
road all the time right now I'm not on
the road all the time I had a a a a baby
and oh you did yeah I had a little human
being and oh boy every audience
oh he made people support the troops he
is he is in the military um how old is
he what's his name he's uh well it's I
can only talk a little bit about it
because he he's embedded is what he is
give him a good name or is it have you
seen Homeland no based on my infant son
wow yeah he's he's Brody from that show
I told you I didn't see it oh I'm sorry
worst show I've I've ever done was uh it
was a charity show I did it for charity
cuz I'm a good human being I am I'm such
a charitable person no I did it and I
did the it was for free guys that's how
charitable was um it was for National
Rare disease day that's a
thing rare diseases disease is so rare
that they don't even get a full day they
just have to lump them all together and
go you share you share that that one day
like a family plan right and and I was
being charitable and I was going to go
tell jokes half hour keep it clean okay
that's how charitable I was I was going
to go into a room filled with 400 people
that had rare and hard toidentify
diseases and then just
mingle so two weeks later I could be at
the doctor and go oh it's weird my knees
bent forward now I don't know why that
is really that is rare and hard to
identify so the lady that hired me she
said uh you're going to go up do a half
hour of comedy please keep it clean I
said okay that's fine she said before
you go up we're going to do a couple of
presentations I said great that's that's
cool I'm waiting backstage first
presentation was a woman who had a rare
disease it was that caused macular
degeneration she went blind and she
became a
photographer over the course of her
illness to overcome it was beautiful
don't laugh at that it's genuine that's
not that's this is the setup part of the
joke where you're not supposed to
laugh but no it was beautiful all of her
shots looked great they were in Focus
everything was nice and it was uplifting
and then they had another presentation
and it was a girl with a bone disease
and she became a [ __ ]
ballerina that's not a joke she did she
overcame she climbed the mountain it was
beautiful they showed a video people are
all uplifted I couldn't wait to go out
and perform for everybody and then they
had one more presentation which was a
slideshow of all the people in the
organization that had died over the year
of rare
diseases with the music and
everything I will remember
you will you remember me everybody was
crying right and then the woman that
hired me walked out onto the stage and
said here to cheer us
up the very funny Ray
Harrington I walk fed out on the stage
with tears in my
eyes what are you do at what at what
point what am I going to say I'm
sorry here's a half hour of Dick jokes
here's a half hour of Dick jokes that's
what you're getting I hope you don't
have a rare disease of the dick cuz this
could get
awkward so that was the worst show I've
ever done this is so much better and you
guys aren't sick you know what I mean
like every day is a
gift I don't know if anybody has a rare
dick disease I I'm real sorry you
probably did not expect to come out
tonight and have somebody bring it up
right in your face this is very rare and
easy to
hide the documentary yeah be a man uh
when my wife said she was pregnant I I
panicked because I never had a dad
growing up I don't know what that means
to be a man I never saw a man yeah doing
anything in my life so I set out to do
the things that I thought made a man a
man mhm fighting drinking cars you
fought people you're huge I fought a a
five-time world champion boxer good did
you win and no he he hurt me and what
else did you do I found my man drink cuz
every man should have his drink what was
it it was it was Black Russian that was
my man drink it's pretty good is that
all right it's pretty good I thought it
was is it passible I thought it was
going to be whiskey uh no you might have
beat that guy if you drank whiskey and
then I drove cars uh I don't know
anything about cars yeah no I drove
drove them I drove a quar million dollar
Porsche no not Porsche uh Ferrari see I
don't even remember the names of them
that's cool Ferrari and I could barely
fit in it yeah and then I found um the
one privately owned Back to the Future
DeLorean that exists the one from the
movie we did a Kickstarter it was very
successful uh we shot pretty low and
then we raised 20 250% of of our goal
awesome yeah so uh people were really
cool about it and it's very exciting to
see people get excited about it yeah
awesome lot of excitement excitement all
around here at the joke joint Ray
Herington everyone all right so uh I'm
going to tell this uh it's a secret now
that you've gotten to know me I will
tell this happy birthday here comes the
secret that sounded weird like I was
going to pull my pants
down what a weird Chuck-E-Cheese trip
you're about to
[Laughter]
have keep pulling tickets come out
uh I'm going to I'm going to say this
and the room is going to get weird and
please just don't just just follow me
through this okay because I have Solid
Rock Solid Logic for this okay uh guys I
I wish I was black I I said
it and it got real uncomfortable in the
room so a lot of white people giggling
going why it's great like that's fine I
wish I was black for one very specific
reason uh it's cuz I'm a big dude right
I'm a big fat white fat white white
white white fat white guy right that's
who I am and the universe gives fat
white guys this voice
hi right if I was if I was a big black
dude the universe gives you a whole
different gift and it's not what you're
thinking of it's something totally
different it's that voice the Luther
vanross Barry White kind you know what
the voice I'm talking about right it's
like a it's like a like a damn like that
kind of voice like you're laughing cuz
it's weird if I have that if you saw me
walking through Target going wear the
[ __ ] Sun
Chips y'all got harvest
cheddar right you'd be like what
happened to that guy did he hit his head
is he okay do you know how lucky my wife
would be if I had that voice she'd call
me every five minutes every five minutes
what's going on oh not much was hanging
out at the comedy
club telling some
jokes 900 people
yeah I told this one joke about harvest
cheddar sunship that did pretty
well all right I'll call you back
goodbye I'll be honest I've been doing
this voice for about a minute and a half
and uh I'm feeling real uncomfortable
about it
cuz I'm worried that being a big fat
white dude doing this awesome voice
could be construed as
racist and I I want to ask a black
person if it's okay and I'm worried that
asking a black person if this voice is
okay while doing this voice would
definitely be
racist and also because uh there's one
black lady in the
room is this that's a if I could get
that in writing I would really
appreciate it um my god did you hear how
uncomfortable everybody got just then
nobody was saying anything like we'll
wait for you to decide you're the
spokesperson for an entire [ __ ]
culture right that did you oh my
[Music]
god a documentary I want to make a a
shot forsh shot remake of Back to the
Future but with zero budget that would
be amazing cuz I know lots of
skateboarders and then I could uh you
know I could cast the skateboarders yeah
like and then uh except for instead of
uh his b instead of them when they play
Huey Lewis at the uh audition for the
talent show um instead of playing Huey
Lewis they just play Death Metal and
then uh and then and then when he's
playing it in the 50s and then the guy
says um you know it's your C cousin
Marvin Marvin Danzig you know that sound
you're looking for and uh those are the
only changes I made hey it's Dave Allen
your cousin no GG it's me