streaming at you
digitally but taped live at the joke
joint comedy club in Lily Dale Minnesota
just 15 minutes out of downtown
Minneapolis the standup Channel presents
Uprising dedicated to bring you the best
comedians we can find and tonight's
Comics are Maggie
Ferris Andrew wake Lightner and Paul
Hooper so ladies and gentlemen start
screaming now for your host Mr Chris
mad what a
night thank you very much folks for
coming to Uprising the greatest show
this side of the other side thank you so
much for coming my name is Chris I'll be
your MC tonight I saw a sticker on the
back of a car today uh it said porn on
it with a circle and a line through it
no porn in that car whatever it's their
car I wasn't trying to [ __ ] throw
porn in anybody's car especially this
lady's all right I've never thrown porn
in anybody's car ever I've never even
seen it happen once yet this woman this
poor woman has had it happen so many
times that she felt the need to get a
sticker to put on her
car that's not one time folks you don't
get porn thrown in your car for the
first time in history and go I got to
get a sticker right now I need a warning
no that's more than
once and that's a sticker too folks you
don't they don't make them you have to
have that made how many times you have
to have porn thrown in your car before
you have a sticker made have you had a
box of stickers made they don't make one
there's no one guy that's selling
stickers custom made for 75 cents a
piece you got to buy a box it's like 35
bucks I've had stickers made I know
what's 35 bucks how many times is this
poor woman over and over just had porn
thrown in her [ __ ] car she's the only
one feel bad for her don't fight porn
how about that there's [ __ ] in this
world you could be fighting that's much
more horrible and evil and wrong like
soft
porn seen one of these films they're
frustrating nothing but fuzzy
airbrushed making out you don't see [ __ ]
dudes with ponytails that's what it's
got dudes with ponytails I don't get it
I don't know how you feel like a guy
every morning in the shower with your
ponytail get me some [ __ ] tonight folks
that's how this is going to go right
here watch the
game drink some
beers get some [ __ ] where's my
scrunchie give me my scrunchie yeah
put a fan on me I looks
sweet if you're a dude with a ponytail
you cannot have sex anymore you can only
make
love for the
record making love to a woman is gayer
than [ __ ] a dude that's how that
works I'm sorry as your shampooed
conditioned ponytail gently Cascades
into your lovers
face lay you down on a bed of Road oh
God get off
me folks I'm going to bring up your next
comic are you
ready your next comic coming to the
stage folk could suck the light out of a
black hole I tell you what ladies and
gentlemen the super funny Maggie
Ferris it's true I can do that hello Joe
join how are
you awesome uh I'm Maggie I work at the
Mall of America in the lost and found uh
it's really fun I love it you meet
people from all over the world there and
everybody who goes to the mall always
loses the same thing they lose their
phone or their hat or their umbrella
every time but so I get to meet people
from all over over the world and talk
about their lost phone their lost hat or
their lost umbrella it's not the
greatest job in the world like it's only
minimum wage so I had to supplement my
income somehow so I started a small
business where I sell phones hats and
umbrellas they're all refurbished so
it's you think that's easy but the
serial number on an umbrella is under
the handle so you have to peel the
handle off really rub it out put the
handle back on it's a lot of work but
umbrellas are a big Market that's um no
one wants to get
wet in the rain why was that gross oh my
God that was your mind you [ __ ]
um Maggie Ferris
everyone right that's me yeah that's my
name welcome oh thank you how are you so
well what's
new I want to get a pet rabbit but I
haven't got it yet I had one with when I
was a kid I had one ear up one ear down
come on that's too cute for words it
happens that's C why do you want a
rabbit oh they're really cute I just saw
a movie the other day that had a rabbit
and it made me want a
rabbit to get no so a squirrel right you
don't want a squirrel M and you don't
want a mouse but the rabbits are the
cutest rodents probably is a hedgehog a
rodent good question thank you next
topic okay what else is new cuz that's
not new that's just something you want
right what's going on with you um you
have a podcast oh yeah I have a podcast
it's called magnetronic yeah it's fun
we're on season three does that have to
do with your name Magie kind of yeah
yeah it's a nickname that a friend of
mine gave me really yeah that's a good
nickname mine's octane
oo I have several nicknames but uh
enough about me oh well um so uh how can
people hear the podcast if they go to
magnetronic dcom you can just play it
right there or you can get it on iTunes
or however you want I was on it you guys
it was fun wasn't it it's a fun podcast
we like we have way too many sound
effects and we play way too many stupid
jokes yeah and it's just silly it's
gotten a lot sillier even since you've
been on it if I remember I was in a bad
mood and I was in a good mood when I
left that's how we like to do it and in
the middle it was the I was in a good
mood in the middle it was awesome good
you should listen to it okay I don't
really work at the Mall of America I do
what I do is I walk dogs for a living
and um I love it I love dogs are you
guys dog people here yeah where are my
cat people too right here out here you
guys are stupid okay um cats are just
dumb but listen I don't just like walk
dogs like on a leash or anything like
that what I do is I go in my car and I
pick up like 10 different dogs okay
these are predetermined dogs they're not
just like loose dogs in the neighb I
don't break into people's homes and just
pick a dog okay this is a agreement
we've already set up ahead of time okay
10 different dogs put them in the car
take them to the offleash dog park make
them run around for an hour hard back in
the car drive them all home that's what
I do I love it but I drive a tiny Toyota
yis
so it is like dog clown car when we get
there it's just like dog dog dog dog
people are like how many dogs are in
there I'm like there's 10 dogs okay just
shut up I have a lot of poop to pick up
which is true there's a lot of poop
involved that's
true talk to me about your
Awards um well I won I won a couple of
contests and stuff like I won one
National contest that was like the
search for the next funniest queerest
comic who is funny is that what it's
called I don't remember sounds like
you're making that up well no I wasn't
it was like queerest funniest why didn't
we lead off with that that's incredible
I don't know you want a national contest
yeah great that was fun I think what
helped me a lot is that I don't really
identify as a queer comic and I I feel
like I'm a comic that happens to be
queer so I don't like play to a queer
audience I play to everyone and I think
some of those Comics get stuck in plane
just to a queer audience and so there
their their stuff is more tailored
toward that which didn't suit them well
for that contest right do you know what
I'm saying like I I I play to everyone
sometimes you go to the dog park I don't
know if you ever been there but the dogs
they like to hump that's what they do H
they call it twerking now I'm like
whatever dogs whatever I like to call it
the congal line cuz I like the classics
you
know one time I was there I was like
look you guys there's three dogs doing
the conga line this guy pipes up he's
like yeah that's cuz there's too much
testerone in the
air test what did you just jerk off on
my pizza what just happened really
testerone
yeah if you're ordering a pizza at the
dog park and you're getting testerone on
your half maybe I could get Esten
chovies on my half I don't think
anyone's going to deliver this
pizza no one
did almost sad I'm just saying if you're
confusing the word
testosterone and
pepperoni you should have to get your
testoni cut off all
right no more breeding for
you my album my comedy album that's
coming out it's called hot lesbo
action ah but it's not it's just me on
the cover
welding I I really think that um uh you
know the the night I remember like we
recorded a few different times you know
but the one I think I'm going to do one
show that it was in it was just electric
and everybody was grooving on it and it
was so much fun is it your first CD yeah
killer and I've been doing company like
107 years it's time it's long yeah yeah
there's more girth to it than a
length I uh sometimes I board dogs at my
house and uh one time I had this dog and
he was blind and half deaf and after
walking around a few days I realized oh
my God I am a seeing eye
person you guys it was awesome I got to
wear a vest that said don't pet me I'm
working we got to go to the front of the
line at Disney World yeah Space Mountain
12 times you guys I don't know if you
know de blind dogs they love the freef
fall
sensation there there's nothing
disoriented dogs love more than being
more
disoriented all right I got got to go
but I got to tell you you guys uh I have
this really gross pair of mittens
they're really dirty I don't like to
wear them but my grandma made them so I
wear them but it says right there on the
cuff it just says [ __ ] you [ __ ] waffle
and I'm like
Grandma that is gross that is dirty she
has embroidery Tourette so we just let
her do whatever she needs to do I know
I'm like thank you for the mittens grma
she's like get out of here you [ __ ] I'm
like okay I love
you she's like don't forget your dick
hole scarf I'm like what it's a dick
holes it turns out it's just a scarf
with like various size holes in it like
like a Rings Sizer
chart it's nice it keeps you warm and
cool I like it so yeah thank you so much
guys good night
make sure you take good care of the
weight staff bartenders tonight you guys
tip them really well I work as a
bartender it sucks when people don't tip
you like I had a guy come in pay with
this credit card one time and on the
credit card slip next to tip he just
wrote
nope that's all he wrote used to work at
a place called Rock Bottom Brewery you
guys know that place Rock Bottom yeah I
hate it it was the worst place ever I
they used to make us whenever we'd
answer the phone we'd have to say you've
hit rock
bottom I can never get it right though
I'd be like I've hit rock
bottom I um it's hard like trying to
work and come out and do comedy at open
mics and stuff like cuz you also have to
budget time for
depression you know my buddy will call
me up and be like hey man you want to go
uh to a movie on Thursday I'll be like I
can't I have depression on Thursday so
I don't think it'd be a good idea for me
to own a gun because I'd always be
forcing people to do my bidding at
gunpoint you know like go clean my room
do
it like go buy me a pack of smokes do
it you're like uh pull my
finger do
it all right folks are you ready for
your headliner yeah all right ladies and
gentlemen he's got an album on standup
records the incredibly funny Paul
[Music]
Hooper thank
you thank you I I swear to God if you
guys cause me to bomb on this
videotape uh actually I hope it sort of
happens because this should be
documented I need to learn how to uh
greet people properly and I know I come
up here with a deep voice and baggy eyes
you don't [ __ ] trust
it but I'm not giving into the corny
greetings that I guess everyone finds
okay you got to knock it off please with
the I was on a plane of course I was guy
across the aisle is a bigger guy so he's
having in trouble taking his seat he's
heavy can't get between the armrest now
he's got to make his humorous quip about
the situation directed at me he's like
oh I should have put a brought a Vada
Chrisco to put on my hips to Help Me
ease into this seat here huh
a and I'm like you can't bring more than
3 ounces on a plane yeah so that's right
yeah your shitty joke won't make it past
security all right how about sitting
your fat ass down and saving that crowd
work for your next flight I'm not into
it you obese [ __ ] extrovert I am
trying to KN off you're doing goddamn
internet jokes look at the bags in her
my eyes my father left when I was 3
years old I don't need you reciting your
little corny
[ __ ] it's always corny
that's all I just want it to be [ __ ]
somewhat authentic you know at some
point like the bags in my eyes people
cannot resist women cannot resist men
are not even wear this thing we're just
the home remedies for the bags under my
eyes we're going to give you home
remedies put cucumber slices on your
eyes wake up tomorrow you're cured it's
[ __ ] I tried that 20 years ago this
is my head then the one they really get
giggly about is the preparation
age that's what you do you put prep
operation h on your eyes and I guess
they're giggly cuz that's hemorrhoid
medication that you apply to your eyes
and that's silly in a normal person's
world but I'm like I don't know why
you're giggling it's just chemicals that
reduce swelling it's not prepackaged
with [ __ ] in it
you unless you told me like listen you
have to apply this to someone's
hemorrhoid then smear their rectum on
your ocular cavity then I'd be like God
damn it your home remedies are a tad bit
extreme but now it's actually funny
however I punched that up for you so
that's not your [ __ ] joke you would
do [ __ ] off a
website I know I'm a
turd I just can't take it I cannot
[ __ ] bear it
anymore all right here we are with Paul
Hooper Paul how are you all right how
are you man I'm good uh I'll ask the
questions okay well it's adversarial no
that's I didn't mean that can we try to
I'm
sorry
um yeah um I'm gonna try uh I'll ask you
a question all right all right um do you
have any
dreams dreams like just like when you
sleep and you no that's you talking
about just when I fall asleep I don't go
into Rim sleep first of all okay I
twitch in my sleep yeah someone told me
that multiple people have told me that
and so I dream reality is basically what
I do now so whatever I'm worried about a
check being late an email not being
returned I dream that for seven or eight
hours and then I wake up and it's real
and I just carry that anger with me 24
hours a day sounds exhausting I don't
escape there are no fantasy dreams I
don't get any of that knowing that you
look great thank you not really with the
bags in them eyes but you'd think they'd
be worse you think
so I used to be a suicidal
alcoholic I used to be that's the way I
phrase it not really recovering suicidal
alcoholic I feel like that has more it
carries more weight and that's the way I
drink too I know you guys are having
drinks so I'm not going to be a killjoy
and I know you don't really want to hear
it but it's a big chunk of my life that
I have to explain I know people don't
want to hear your sobri I always go I'm
sober and they're like oh how long they
just strain it out like that they're
just [ __ ] exasperated but they always
feel the need to prove you know they
care about others that's all that is is
I don't but how long and I toy with him
I'm like well you know I've been sober
eight years now he's like muscle now
he's like well you're very strong then
they're like do you go to treatment or
meetings or anything I'm like no I never
have and they're like really I'm like
yeah you meant to say I'm the strongest
person but you know whatever I
understand it's difficult to approach a
champion that's how I do it because I
never went to recovery I never went to
rehab AA I don't know how that recovery
World works you know there's an AA
meeting across the street from my
apartment in New York because there's a
church there you know churches will take
pity on these AA groups they'll invite
them in they'll give them a little space
like this little banquet space give them
a little PA system let them sort their
[ __ ] out in the daytime I don't know if
you've ever seen a AA meeting let out
but it's a real problem in the community
all right because they don't disperse
they're not done meeting all right they
just [ __ ] flood out of the chapel
onto the sidewalk now there's a gaggle
of darix out front smoking crying or
[ __ ] comparing car wrecks whatever
people do at AA it brings my afternoon
down and they make a lot of goddamn
racket in front of my apartment while
I'm trying to take my afternoon nap I
have to March over there every day in my
pajama pants and go excuse me fellas can
you keep it down the exception to the
rules trying to sleep over here huh I
mean would you would you like to get
coffee with me and see how a grown man
keeps his mouth shut and doesn't have to
throw a public pity
party that's how I stay sober by being a
dick and you got to respect it perfect
streak not one
relapse I have a lot of comedian friends
in AA of course because comedians are a
troubled sort like musicians they have a
lot of trouble so when I'm on the road
with like a comedian friends in AA I try
to respect their little program I was
with my buddy Clint in South Carolina
doing shows we're at the hotel and he's
worried about how to get to the AA
meeting and he's like I'm going to have
to catch a cab to this AA meeting and
I'm like well you know I got my car but
I'm not taking him cuz I I want to eat
Chipotle and I like the hot sauce of
Chipotle but it upsets my stomach gives
me a little acid reflux I figure if I
drop him off first these depressing
characters in front of the chapel upsets
my stomach too early can't get to the
hot sauce I haven't started my PC
treatments I just think it'd be best
Clint if you caught a cab to your AA
meeting it's like a lesson on the way to
your lesson you know what I mean atone
for your transgressions you [ __ ]
heretic that's the way I talk to him and
anyway he goes to a meeting and then
some old man a agrees to get my ride
back to the hotel on the way back
through casual conversation the old man
finds out he's a comedian so of course
the old man's like hey if I bring my
wife to the show tonight is it a dirty
show and my buddy Clint's like yeah the
other comedian's quite dirty talking
about me just putting my [ __ ] out like
that like I just do an hour of sodomy
jokes but you know it's lazy promotion
on Clint's part but he's an addict he
doesn't have to form sentences his life
is [ __ ] falling apart and he can't
piece it together that's why he's in the
goddamn Chapel every day trying to make
amends anyway the old man hears this and
he's like oh the old man from a is like
I can't bring my wife to that if it's a
dirty show she'd hate that and I'm like
what old man you're an AA you did some
[ __ ] so I'm sure if your wife is cool
with spending the last 20 years writhing
around on the bathroom floor praying for
your contaminated Soul I'm sure she'll
be okay coming to hear an angel speak
you know get back in your goddamn
Cathedral and read your literature
repent through the pages of your leader
I don't know what you do I muscled up
and did it myself but you need to get in
there you need to get in there and show
some kind of goddamn
reverence before your liver blows
out what did you do before the comedy uh
I didn't do much I was I mean I started
when I was was like 22 so I only had
like four years of adulthood yeah so I
thought I joined the military backed out
was going to go to college decided not
to and worked a bunch of dead end jobs
yeah and I worked everywhere like uh Ric
Flair's Go's Jim and Charlotte I worked
there he was a Nature Boy Nature Boy Ric
Flair lunatic a local lunatic so anyway
Gold's gy he put Ric Flair's Gold's Gym
on the Marquee on the sign and then the
franchise like you don't own all of gold
gyms you got to take the Ric Flair part
off and he refused to he just kept it up
I got I was working for him when I was
like 19 years old I got alcohol
poisoning at his Christmas party so I
got alcohol poisoning at his Christmas
party I I was a rookie drinker so I went
to the
hospital right for an IV and all this
[ __ ] my girlfriend had to take me and I
missed a day of work so I brought the
note from the hospital to the general
manager of Gold's Gym I was like here
you know I miss work and I guess Ric
Flair was working out a couple days
later and saw the the doctor's note and
he's I like passed by the office and
he's like are you Paul and I'm like yeah
he's like you get alcohol poisoning at
my party last night or two nights ago or
something and I'm like yeah and he's
like that's great yeah he loved it that
was my sort of introduction to drinking
and then later it got out of hand yeah
yeah that's okay do you want to talk
about that or should I talk about
something else no I don't care I'll talk
about my dram I'll talk about whatever
cuz you you from the way you talk on
stage you uh put everybody to shame I am
a I am proud that I did like original
work in my drinking days that I did some
really strange stuff my idea of drinking
was this is that life is truly boring
and when I drank I wanted the fantasy to
come alive but none of it ever lived up
to it none of it but I walked in a bar
and I go all right here's what the bar
is it's [ __ ] people talking about a a
football game or guys hitting on women
and then there'll be a fight there will
be vomit it's predictable it's old what
can what new things can I bring to this
what would I like to see as the audience
I always thought about that like walking
in a bar I would create something that
if I was a guy dancing with a girl I'd
go what the [ __ ] is this guy doing so
you pee on people yeah you slap your
friend you make out with men in a
Southern bar you do those type of things
you throw trash cans at each other you
do things small scale things like that I
get excited by different things now like
I have a I have a strong desire to feed
ducks that's what excit if I see a duck
anywhere I'm like
hey by the way I don't know how to call
Duck so I just go hey which is usually
alarming to the bird and I don't travel
with food but I tell that duck I'm like
you stay put I'll get you bread
quesadillas you want some Reese's Cups
I'll provide that for you that's no cost
to you whatsoever I feel a deep bond
with a duck that I don't feel with
females don't you think a duck would
make me a happier person I like a pet I
put a duck on my lap it quacks I giggle
I'm better for it right people I'll come
on stage people applaud they'll notice
an energy shift he's got a duck in his
life he's settled down he's so much more
likable now he just all [ __ ] for an
hour he's just grinning all over the
goddamn place he quit
cursing that's what it is my dream is to
move to a cabin in New Mexico and have a
duck there I don't know why think New
Mexico is beautiful then I went to New
Mexico 3 months ago and I'm like I
should live out my fantasy and go feed
ducks while I'm on vacation so I'm like
where uh where can I feed ducks to some
of the locals and they're like it's a
desert [ __ ] there's no
water you all sve when you lit a candle
like I didn't do it wasn't an alter boy
let's make that clear I was not an alter
Boy And as far as I can remember nothing
happened but I uh why did you not do it
I don't remember okay I just never lucky
I guess I don't know but I uh um why I
did play the Trump I just did anyone I
hope that I just hawked the tiniest
lugie tastes nice I just hoed the
tiniest lugie for that onto Maggie which
I do with all my guests give me that
beer it's that open I was going to open
it with my teeth oo that's why they call
you octane that's why they will call me
octane I used to be able to do this for
real shall we no let's do it don't do it
don't do it yeah if you break a tooth
off what I'm nervous for you uh
insurance is retroactive 3
months I used to be able to do this hang
on it's not about pulling it's about
pushing damn I've started
it you're making me so nervous me too
okay you could stop you still can stop
there's no your ego doesn't have to
break your
tooth I can't I can't look at hang
on what are you loosening it up I'm
trying to open it
I can't
look it was so much more anticlimactic
than I thought it would be you did it
though who did it you octane did it damn
right