streaming at you digitally but tape live
at The juk Joint Comedy Club lyale
Minnesota just 15 minutes out of
downtown Minneapolis the standup Channel
presents
Uprising dedicated to bringing you the
best comedians we can find tonight's
Comics are Robert
Fones Jeff foser and Tommy
Ryman ladies and gentlemen start
screaming now for your host Mr Chris
[Applause]
madic what a
night I was driving home with a friend
uh from a show once we had a long
drive he wanted cocaine it's a long
drive I didn't blame him we were at a
gas station we didn't have any cocaine I
offered to uh buy him a Red Bull his
answer was it's not the [ __ ]
same which I don't know I think it might
be if you you realize that they cost the
same you know like uh you do $2.50 with
a cocaine it's probably not going to do
too much however you drink $50 with a
Red Bull it probably
work I don't know I uh I saw I worked at
a bar because um I don't know you need
life experience to tell these
jokes I had a woman leave me a fake $10
bill for a tip recently it was fake it
looked like a $10 bill all right what
was it a booklet what did it say no
one's ever been wrong Shout It Out Jesus
why is everyone right everyone knows
like that it's never Buddhists or
anything there's no because Buddhists
don't advertise that's why it's only the
Christians who advertise they're the
ones with the bus benches or the kids
you know quit you did the do now do the
Pew that's one I
saw get the kids involved you know there
never a Buddhist on a billboard like
come
on never right quit what you've been
doing start hind doing there's never any
of
that folks I'm going to bring up your
next comic I've done a lot of shows with
this guy and let me tell you he could
suck the robe off the Statue of
Liberty ladies and gentlemen Mr Robert
[Music]
phones hey keep it going for Chris
everybody let him hear
right oh my God I'm happy to be here
guys I am I'm happy I don't get to do a
lot of comedy in nice clubs like this I
don't yeah a lot of the comedy I do I do
in dive bars right kind of place that
might have a Ural trough you understand
yeah if you don't know what yal trough
is I'm going to tell you it's like they
found a way to make peeing in public
just a little bit more humiliating just
hey all you dudes together right here in
this giant bathtub don't worry there's
ice in it it's
classy but I was standing at the Ural
trough of one of those clubs the other
day focusing on the task at hand and
this drunk stranger came in and he kind
of stumbled over next to me and he
unzipped and he slapped me on the back
which which is not the order to do that
in and he said to me hey man trust
me trust me don't [ __ ] in this bar
couple things sir first off if I'm
pooping in a bar it's probably not by
choice right think it's safe to say
something went horribly wrong today
neither you or I are really in control
the situation here anymore second off
not how you start a conversation not at
all bad small talk right right off the
bat don't do that but I thought about it
for a while and I realized like the only
thing worse than going up to a complete
stranger and going hey man don't poop in
this bar would be going up to a complete
stranger and going hey man poop in this
bar trust
me with us this evening Mr Robert phones
Bobby Chris can I call you Bob yeah why
is it Robert is Rob and Bob
I don't know that a good question thank
you next question so what do you hope to
get out of this whole thing um you know
like millions of dollars FX show right
on FX show yeah just like endless uh
respect from everybody yeah don't That
Could That Could is that what isn't that
what happens not yet for me not yet no
not for me people are bad at small talk
it's not their fault right we're just
impulsive everybody does it we do it all
the time you know right and uh hey how
are you today oh I'm very good uh hey
it's nice weather we're having yeah it
sure is it's not nice weather ever have
you been outside it's disgusting all
right it's just ice and bees that's it
that's the entire year right down the
middle but I had the worst bit of small
talk I've ever had the other day I was
at a buffet which is not specific to
that day and uh I like seconds it's cool
I was standing next to this lady I'd
never met before she had a sandwich on
her plate and at one point she leaned
over to go get more food and when she
did top half of her sandwich fell off
right onto the ground and that's sad
right yeah if you don't think about
anything else that's ever happened
that's sad sure but at that point in
time she and I had not interacted all
right she could have handled that the
way I would have handled it she could
have set her plate down she could have
gotten in her car she could have gone
home and just been ashamed forever like
an adult right instead she goes okay
great time to snag a co-starring role in
Robert phones' life I'm going to get a
little way in here on the sandwich
conundrum I'm having so she looked at me
and said oh my sandwich at which point I
said without thinking about it
impulsively well miss that's the good
thing about sandwiches you can always
put them back together what the [ __ ]
does that
mean what am I just fat Forest Gump now
am I just wandering through life
spouting folksy nonsense about food oh
that's the nice thing about soup Miss
it's like stew you ain't got a
chew it's a nice thing about meatballs
it's like spaghetti put a hat on this
morning ma'am I may not be a smart man
but I know what lunch is
what do you like to eat what do I like
to eat on the road when I'm on the road
uh the best road snack is gas station
hot dogs they're disgusting but do you
have problems with people like eating
like with the
sounds you know do you have
like yeah like that like that that's
nasty you really why are you bothered by
that it's not bad this isn't about me
but I am bothered by that I'm not
bothered by it um you're not no that's
weird friend of mine uh told his horse
died and I laughed in his face cuz
that's not a problem no it's not a
problem you get to have anymore it's not
I'm sorry every other Century sure a
horse dying that's a problem this
Century no what do you one of eight
people in the world that still uses a
horse the cast of Deadwood I don't feel
bad for you your outdated sign of wealth
doesn't work anymore that's a
tragedy right you have to drive the ATV
around the plantation this morning your
crazy jalopy with the horn that goes a
wuga not start oh
I don't care about horses first off
horses are monsters right you ever
looked at a horse's mouth it's garbage
right why do they have teeth like that
they don't eat teeth like that are they
eating bone they're eating bone they can
have teeth like that if it's
apples there's two animals you get to
care about in this world I don't care
about horses there's two animals you get
to love it's dogs and it's cats and if
you have another animal and you love it
I'm real sorry it does not love
you at all and that might sound mean but
if it does sound mean I want you to go
home tonight open up the cage you hold
that animal in see if it wants to be in
your house
anymore no it'll run away every time
your fet is going to die at a gas
station alone in cold not knowing your
name so uh do you have an album coming
out uh no right on do you have anything
online that people can kind of check out
standup wise not really right on do you
have a website not yet right on
Robert phones everybody nice to see
everybody so uh
apparently if you put the name of
another country in front of the word
Bakery some people lose their minds have
you seen this happen I could say to a
handful of people there's a
Czechoslovakian Bakery a couple of
blocks down and somebody will pipe up
are you kidding me are they open right
now how come we're not there I bet they
have some of the most amazing pastries
put inside of my body let's go let's do
this come on it's like an exotic
Adventure but if you put the name of
another country in front of the word
prison oh
no oh that then becomes the scariest
place on the planet we've all heard some
weird old guys say the last place you
ever want to find yourself is a Turkish
prison it's cuz they do all kinds of
messed up stuff to you in there you
might not ever get out and if you do you
walk funny have nightmares the rest of
your life it's no good it's no good you
put the name of another country in front
of the word prostitute well now we're
back to awesome
again right you ever been with a
Brazilian prostitute sir you learn all
kinds of new tricks you might walk funny
have nightmares the rest of your life
but it is worth it every dollar for sure
for sure that's a that's a fun game you
guys can play anywhere not the
prostitute part but the maybe
maybe but but you just you think of a
name of another country you put it in
front of one of those three words it
works every time except Canada doesn't
what's that a a new Canadian Bakery I
will not be going in there well that
sounds boring and
awful no thank you it's not for me it's
not hey did you hear about Tim got
locked up in a Canadian prison for a
couple of years well that sounds kind of
nice
and they have great health
care sure he's having a wonderful time
lucky guy lucky guy hey I just got off
the phone with the escort service turns
out the night of the bachelor party
there's only one employee available a
Canadian
prostitute oh that
sucks huh guess we're just going to have
to have dinner and call it an early
night I mean unless you want to hear
this all evening oh
yeah oh
yeah are you ready for your headliner
are you
ready folks you've seen this young
Gentleman on Last Comic Standing he is a
standup records recording artist ladies
and gentlemen Mr Tommy
Ryman what we time for Chris everybody
at all the comics you saw tonight give a
huge round of
applause and your way staff too take
care of them make sure to take care of
them
oh man what a night it's could to be
here it's been a crazy couple of days my
lava lamp erupted I didn't even know
they could do that did you know they can
erupt it's terrible I just bought 42
hamsters too wiped them all out insane
it's like a tiny adorable pompe it was
awesome you can see how some of the
hamsters perish like somewhere with
their loved ones one was by himself
eating a sunflower seed one was on a
wheel like he thought he was going to
get away but he didn't have a
chance oh
man my dad's a goofy guy do you guys
know my dad oh you should get to know
him he's so goofy he makes his own kale
chips have you heard of kale chips makes
his own he loves them he's like Tommy
you got to try these kale chips I just
made a new batch of kale chips once you
try these you're never going to want
regular chips ever again cuz these are
so good so I finally tried one I was
like oh no my Dad forgot what chips
taste
like this sucks now we have to put them
in a home oh man I thought we had to
take his keys away first but girl chips
will do that
they're not good you guys if you haven't
had kale chips keep up the good work
you're doing so good at
life they're gross they're basically
like somebody left a salad out for 5
days and was like I made
chips I made chips on the counter took
five days they're real
gross but they're supposedly good for
you so get in your
body my mom's Goofy too she's weird
she's a super hippie uh she's retired
and I I called her a while ago I was
like hey Mom what are you up to and she
she's like I'm activating
Rivers I was like
what I think you just said you were
activating Rivers she's like that's what
I'm doing I was like that's what I
thought you
said what is
that she's like I get all my crystals
out and I go to the mouth of a river and
I do a little ceremony and I activate it
I was like so you work for the city
or what does this do you just activate I
was like who told you to activate Rivers
who trained you in for River activation
and she's like TR myself in I was like
we're going to put you in a home
too this is not right and I was like
what happens when you activate a river
what makes how do you know it's
activated does it change colors or
something like the duck's real happy
like oh yeah that's been activated for
sure I'm going to swim so
fast and she's like no the energy is
just good when it's activated I was like
okay sometimes I mess with her though
like I'll call her I'll be like what are
you doing she's like I'm in Missouri I
just activated a river I'm like Mom I
already activated that River you just
double activate that River this is too
much power people are going to die
mother you got to get back
home she's weird she told me she could
summon a buffalo yeah she was camping in
in Yellowstone National Park and she's
like I summon a buffalo I was like like
that State Farm commercial you sum summ
a buffalo I was like how'd you do this
she's like I really wanted to see a
buffalo so I put the energy out there
that I wanted to see it and then one
showed up I was like well you also were
in Yellowstone National Park where all
the Buffalo
are I was like I'd like to see you do
that downtown and make a penguin show up
too cuz those two don't normally hang
out together and I want to see him hang
out I want the penguin riding the
Buffalo when it shows up too can you do
that you can't do that that's what I
thought you got to get out there
activate some more Rivers maybe you can
make that Buffalo show up downtown with
my
penguin yeah
exactly ladies and gentlemen here we
have Mr Tommy Ryman
standup records and
Beyond Tommy what a year it's been for
you comedy wise and otherwise right yeah
it's been a good year I did a lot of
stuff I got to be on uh Last Comic
Standing uh and uh that was the how was
that that was fun was I was a
semi-finalist yes and it was a lot of
fun Roseanne Bar said she was a fan of
mine yep to your face to my face that's
so awesome man and yeah I met a lot of
great comics and it was a great
experience Y and that's not it what what
else
I thought you'd tell me I got a new
album yep that is that is that will be
coming out hot lesbo
action no it's not called I think uh the
the tentative title is having the time
of my life nice so as a followup to bath
time with Tommy yep yeah so this is my
second album with Stan up records which
I'm super excited y to have out and I
think I think it's going to be better
than the last one and I'm really really
pumped about it killer yeah and and that
was it I feel like he had a better year
than that I uh I like animals like my
wife and I we just bought a dog recently
got a dog we got it from a breeder
people were mad at us they're like you
should have got a rescue dog why'd you
get a brand new one you should have got
a rescue one but like I understand where
they're coming from like I think it's
super nice to have rescue animals that's
a wonderful thing it's really important
everybody should do it like in fact I've
had rescue animals my whole life like
all those hamsters all 42 of them they
were all rescue
hamsters but I just wanted one animal
one time I was like just let me have one
brand new one one time one that I can
mess up and somebody else can rescue it
later technically it is still a rescue
animal just not right now get out of my
face I got some dog walking to
do we got yeah we got a I got a rescue
dog it's a boss interior my wife dresses
it up I didn't know dogs were supposed
to be dressed up in clothes but my wife
was like oh no they have to have outfits
they have to have a lot of outfits like
my doggy has a a bizarre amount of
clothes you guys it does it has a uh the
first thing we bought it was a bee
costume cuz that's
practical in case my dog was ever sworn
by bees throwing in that bee costume
she's fine she's Incognito they didn't
even see her they're like that's just a
giant
bee carry
on but we bought the be costum when my
dog was 8 weeks old it's eight weeks old
and my wife is like let's get the bee
costume and I was like well maybe we
should hold off on the bee costume until
she you know grows a little more cuz
she's growing so fast right now we're
going we only be able to enjoy that bee
costume for about 4 days but my wife was
like but look at the bee costume and I
was like well when you put it that way I
didn't even think of that that's a great
argument get that in the basket I don't
know what I was thinking I
apologize so we got a bee costume uh the
other uh clothes we have like 15
sweaters for the dog uh when whenever
she's in a different mood she can pick
one that she wants to wear we got boots
for the dog cuz we live in Minnesota so
we bought boots cuz there's snow
which was weird I didn't know dogs
needed boots cuz I watched a documentary
on wolves you guys none of them had
boots
on yeah there's running around the woods
Barefoot eating deer I was like how are
they going to catch that deer without
their boots they got some boots on then
they'll catch some
deer but we put we put the we got the
boots for the dog which was fun cuz it
only took about an hour and a half to
put the boots on
her which was weird it took so long cuz
it only took her a minute and a half to
shoot him off her feet right when she
got outside she's like I watched that
wolf documentary I'm not wearing
these got that my wife wanted to we were
going to my wife's cabin she wanted to
get a life jacket for the dog I was like
they have they have life jackets for
dogs I was like are we taking her deep
sea diving I thought we were just going
to the lake and she's like no she needs
a life jacket you know in case she falls
off the boat and I was like isn't there
a swim move named after
dogs isn't there like called the doggy
pal right I've heard of it I'm pretty
sure like I'm pretty sure you just put
the dog in the water and then it if it
doesn't swim then you just get a new dog
on the way home cuz that one wasn't
working
correctly but we got it it has a handle
we got the life Jack it's fun you can
dip it in the water and take it back out
and dip it back in take it back out and
it moves a pause the whole time it's
pretty fun the last thing we purchased
for our dog was
goggles yeah goggles those the real
thing they're called Goggles somebody's
making a lot of money out there selling
goggles for Animals calling them doggles
and I was like why does our dog need
goggles is she going Sky dabbing that's
the only reason unless we're going to
put her on a skateboard and she's going
to go super fast then we need to get
goggles those are the only two examples
I could ever think of my wife is like no
she needs the boss interior so she has
those bug eyes so she needs them for
protection in case she ever runs into a
door or gets sand in her eyes or maybe
another dog is beating her up for
wearing a life
jacket we got to get these goggles so I
was like all right get them I want to
see what this looks like just for fun so
we got the goggles and we put them on
the dog and they worked you guys they
really worked uh cuz she did not run
into any doors and she didn't get any
sand in her eyes and she also didn't
move for two
hours cuz she was terrified cuz she was
wearing goggles if you did that to a cat
it would murder
you he just like come on mittens get
your goggles on like slice you're right
this was a terrible idea I don't know
what I was
thinking Tommy you're a seasoned comic
what's the worst Road story you got like
the worst Heckle I've ever gotten I was
doing a show and I used to do this act
out where I would like get up on a stool
and be like now now now you can hear
that joke on my first album B time with
tmy r it's a bag of thumbs joke it's
really good but so it was this was like
a credit card swiper but I'd get up on
the stool and I was doing this big
elaborate act out and the audience
wasn't feeling it and they just got dead
quiet and then this lady like in the
Middle Road just goes why don't you go
back to Comedy
school and I had no I never really dealt
with like Heckler so I didn't know what
to do so I just slowly like climbed down
the stool and like now I've come up with
so many comebacks like I want her to
come back someday so I can Rec it why
don't you go back to that that school
where mean ladies go to be mean or you
probably graduated already cuz you're
really good at being me like I could
just really nail her with stuff like
that you really come a long
way but yeah I like being married my
wife she loves cuddling she loves
cuddling which is fun I like cuddling
she's like an aggressive cuddler like he
gets weird sometimes like I'm pretty
good at it I'm a bony like I show up
though you know put on a couple extra
two or three sweaters we're good to
go but she's really aggressive like I'll
come home she like you want to cuddle me
I'm like oh I'm not really feeling like
it right now she's like get her here now
I'm like all
right I got some spooning in me let's do
this let's take care of business she
loves cuddling though I just wish there
was a place women could go sometimes to
get cuddling out their system so you can
get right to the good stuff I think that
would be nice like kind of like a strip
club but opposite you know just for
cuddling so women could pay like $20 and
some guy would just put his arm around
for like two songs right that'd be
great or here you go here you go pay $75
go upstairs to the real fancy room where
some guy will spoon you you can cry
about something
stupid yeah this a really good idea I'm
going to make
$1,000 my wife doesn't like that joke I
think it's a really good joke
it's called
cuddles your next cuddler just got off
the phone with his
mom you want to buy your cuddler of hot
chocolate come on it's only
$20 so Tommy such a fantastic year
you've been on television has that
affected you in any way uh the
television it it's been a great
experience my family finally like
respects what I'm doing cuz they've
always been wondering like where are you
going and like now there's proof like on
television they like oh that's what he
does we see it like my mom's always been
pretty supportive but she was like a
musician herself so she she was just
always amazed that people would put me
up in like a hotel cuz she was a f
musician I was like I think you chose
the least lucrative uh musician like
rock star you could be so that's the
purest art form but yeah it's been it's
been good my my wife is is proud of me
like she'll pick up all the when I call
her she always answers normally now
instead of like screening it like she
used to but so and then my my dog
respects he sits more often and like
yeah they just they bring me treats and
stuff so I feel like everybody's it's
been an overall positive experience from
everybody in my life what kind of treats
they bring you they're like uh like a
like a dead rat whatever dog would bring
you they bring me that it's a thought
that counts even if it's a dog thought
yeah Tommy Ryman ladies and gentlemen
when my wife and I first moved in
together she wanted a rat for a pet she
wanted a rat which I I didn't know
people had those for pets I thought they
just lived in sewers and hung out with
turtles but
she was like nope we we got to bring one
in and love it I was like okay I love my
wife so I was like if you want to get a
rat we can get a rat and so we went to
the Humane Society and we bought a rat
here's some advice if you're ever going
to do any Rat purchasing in your future
you definitely want to go new on the
rat this is the one time you can't go
rescue you got to go new pay the extra
$3 get a brand new rat cuz we bought a
used elderly senior citizen rat and rats
only Liv two to three years anyways so
this thing lived 3 months and it died it
died in my wife's hands like she was in
the living room I was in the kitchen
making grilled cheese having the time of
my
life when from the other room I just
heard deep sadness that I'd never heard
before like real guttural
like I was like she needs to go to
cuddles something's going on and I was
like maybe she's watching a sad movie or
something so I walked into the room and
she was just holding a dead rat in her
hands and I felt really bad cuz that was
her and her friend but at the same time
I was like we need to get that dead rat
out of your hands as soon as possible
cuz I'm pretty sure that's what took
Europe out I read about
that yeah that did not end well for them
and it should not be in our living room
so we took the rat and we put it in a
shoe box and double bagged it and some
Target bags to put on the deck I was
like what do you want to do with the rat
and she's like I would like to bury it
but it was February in Minnesota so I
was like have fun with that I was like
what are other options and she's like
maybe we could cremate the rat I was
like okay uh I've never done that I just
made the grilled cheese we could try
it and she was like no professionally I
was like that makes more sense that
makes way more sense we should pay
somebody to do this and we looked into
it there's places that are rack
cremation places I'm pretty sure they
same places that sell doggles
uh but we looked into it and it was
going to cost $100 to cremate the rat
which exceeded our rat cremation budget
by
$100 so we couldn't do that so we just
had a dead rat on our deck for a couple
days which was kind of like a visitation
for the neighborhood animals to say
their goodbye like the dogs and cats and
my wife came home and we're like we need
to figure out what we're going to do
with this guy so what we decided to do
was just drive around the city until we
found the most beautiful spot that had a
garbage
can and we we said some beautiful words
and we laid Lex Luther to rest so he was
by a really pretty Lake for at least a
day and then he was CED off to a giant
landfill and then we thought about it
like that's where he would have wanted
to be the whole damn time
it's rattle of
[Music]
garbage oh yeah oh
yeah you like that how about
that oh how about
that
oh that's so
ridiculous statistically though there's
at least one couple here tonight that's
going to home after the show and have a
little Hanky Panky and one of you
whisper in the other person's ear oh
yeah how about
that yeah and you'll Giggle and then
you'll both remember what I look like
and throw up in your mouths a little
bit or climax immediately I don't know
what you're into