streaming at you digitally but taped
live at the joke joint comedy club in
Lilydale Minnesota just 15 minutes out
of downtown Minneapolis the standup
Channel presents Uprising dedicated to
bring you the best comedians we can find
and tonight's Comics are Cory
Adam Michael
O'Keefe and Ryan
Singer so ladies and gentlemen start
screaming now for your host Mr Chris
[Applause]
mad thank you thank you so much for
being here what a
night welcome to Uprising this is the
show so uh yeah I just went uh I I took
a little vacation but it was uh I don't
have a job but uh I still went somewhere
but it was by myself and when I came
back my friend said uh she asked me how
is your
mancation and uh that enraged me because
it doesn't just because I'm a guy it
doesn't it doesn't sound like vacation
it's a bad pun there's nothing worse
somebody told me the other day I was
instead of explaining they said
mansplaining that doesn't sound like
explaining mancation doesn't sound like
vacation right I've heard uh L
manscaping for when you shave your back
that sound sounds like landscaping
that's a good pun use that
one don't use mancation all right makes
me
angry I was talking with my brother
earlier my brother used to be my sister
he had a sex change when I was 27 turned
into my brother true story um did so
when I was 27 that doesn't do me any
good um if you're going to do that you
know do it when I'm 16 or something I I
could have got away with anything you
know think about it Mom Chris got a
tattoo
Lynn got a
dick go going out you two have
fun circumcise that one too I don't
you change his name and everything you
know just like uh had to say you know
after 27 years I want you to say he not
she you know I'm your brother now not
your sister I want you to say as such
you know the whole thing I'm not Lyn
anymore I'm lonus I'm a guy I'm like G
you know not because of the sex change I
don't care but lonus like
dude you're unique in the family just be
Steve and I'm lus
okay but my dad's had a very hard time
with that he's very religious you know
he had to have been praying every night
until then if you know Lord please let
my daughter not be a lesbian
anymore
right God said
okay check this [ __ ] out
there straight dude is that
better it's not what I
meant I was like Dad what's the lesson
what'd you learn you have to be very
specific with your
prayers I have I have jackass friends
I'm not saying that I'm not saying it's
your brother what's it to you really I
mean you know one of my friends goes
what does does he have a
penis I didn't
check as a matter of fact I've never
checked like I never thought of this but
you you can be a guy to me if you want
to be so long as I don't have to check
how about
that this is my boyfriend
Tom really
[Laughter]
okay make double
sure hey folks you are a fantastic
audience and I don't want to keep you
any longer I'm going to start the show
what do you
think
awesome keep that Applause going folks
he's a standup records recording artist
ladies and gentlemen the very funny
Corey Adam everyone
hello how you guys doing you having a
good
year yeah better than last
year yeah last year was probably the
worst year of my life yeah let's keep
the fun rolling at the comedy show shall
we last year I had two good friends die
within a week and a half of each other
oh yeah shut
up and it was weird cuz like I'm 35
years old and I've never had a close
personal friend die before and I made
the mistake of going to my grandpa for
sympathy I'm on the phone I'm like
Grandpa I'm sad some of my friends died
my grandpa said Cory I'm 86 years old
All My Friends Are
Dead I said that's not true Grandma's
still alive he said All My Friends Are
Dead Grandpa's a dick that's
essential when it happened I had a buddy
of mine that was there for me which was
really cool he took me out right after
the first friend died and we went out to
dinner and I was a Mis little mess I was
crying like it was bad and the waitress
comes up to me and she goes are you okay
and I said no my friend died she goes
what a free meal help I said
yes then she walked away and I went
yes and my buddy looks at me and he goes
you're disgusting and I go I know but
why this
time he goes you realize you just
exploited your friend's death for free
[ __ ] oh yeah it was pretty awesome right
he goes do you think your friends would
want that you exploiting their death for
free stuff I said ah yeah they were my
friends if you guys have friends who can
look at you right in the eye and say
when I die I don't want you to get any
free [ __ ] guess what those aren't
friends those are enemies should
probably just kill them for some free
[ __ ] be way
easier yeah right one of my friends that
died his name was Gus and he was like my
best friend in the world right and I
actually when he died I got a tattoo of
him right there you guys see pretty cool
right now my buddy Gus was one of the
biggest [ __ ] I've ever
known and he hated two things in this
world windmills and portrait
tattoos died first doesn't get a choice
all
right I had another friend of mine like
you ever regret doing that and I go no
he goes never and I go well sometimes I
get home and my roommates aren't around
and it's time for a little adult alone
time and I get home I flip up the laptop
I set to work and I realize that I have
tattooed my friend's
face just eye level to watch me
masturbate I have to go to my closet and
put on a Christmas sweater just so not
feel like a
creep and I mean let's face it I'm used
to masturbating in front of cats
right but like you throw in my dead
Buddy's ghost and it feels
crowded not the threesome I've always
dreamed about all right I have with me
standup records recording artist Corey
Adam and satanic beard hair Enthusiast
yeah I tried Corey and I have been on
the road a lot together it's true do you
remember when I taught you to clip your
fingernails I do yeah yeah yep I taught
him to clip his fingernails it looked
like he was trying to scratch his way
out of a pit it was amazing he didn't
know where to buy them or how much they
cost I'd never it never been act to my
life before let me see him now that's me
that is awesome uh what else did we do
remember that time I stuck that soccer
mom sticker on your car and you didn't
notice for 3 days cuz you were drunk the
whole time I wasn't drunk the whole time
I was hung over the whole time I was
only drunk the one night and I was like
man hardboiled eggs and gizzards this
will get me through the night M we you
were puking out your window remember the
A&W it took us 4 hours to get from
Milwaukee to Chicago because you were
puking out the window and you wouldn't
let me drive you didn't have a license
what do you want from me you're puking
out the window I I should drive I am the
one that was registered as a legal
driver not if you got caught
whatever that was like a really bad
thing that happened also last year I had
an emergency wisdom tooth extraction
yeah that's the best right you guys ever
had tooth stuff it's awesome right I got
home from a I got home from a show on
Christmas Eve and I was flossing my
tooth and the bottom part fell off and
all I could do was scream and then fall
face first into my filthy filthy bath
mat it sounded like somebody was big
game hunting a
[Applause]
dinosaur and I'm not a small guy right
so when I hit the ground the whole place
went a
rumbling my roommate comes over cuz the
door's open I'm not scared of him spying
on me while I floss and he looks at me
and he goes are you okay and I looked up
from our filthy bath mat and I said I I
lost my tooth he said Cory if it landed
on that bath mat you let it go
but I'm proud so I grabbed a toenail
jammed it in there and got on with
Christmas Eve oh yeah you're gross out I
live with roommates I don't even know
whose toenail it
was then I had to find 24-hour dental
care on Christmas Eve in the Twin Cities
spoiler alert doesn't
exist I didn't know what to do so we
went down to the ER like I'm sitting in
the ER waiting to see a doctor and the
lady on my left is holding a sick infant
the guy on my right arm is broken and
bending the wrong way they look at me
they're like what's wrong with you I'm
like my my tooth
hurts the doctor proceeded to call me
first the lady with the baby booed
me I'm like shut up ah and I walk in I
sit down and the doctor comes in and
this is Downtown Minneapolis and this
dude is Christmas Eve he is talking to
me like a surfer this is Minneapolis
where where are you
surfing he comes in he's like what's the
problem little dude he goes besides
Point Break MD
well I was flossing and my tooth fell
out and it really hurts and he goes whoa
I am not a
dentist it's cool I'm I'm not a bird
could you help
me he goes you're going to need to see a
dentist man I go well are there any of
those open he goes ha
no and I go well could you at least give
me some pain pain killers he goes whoa
is that what this is about and I go yeah
I have a toenail in my mouth it's about
painkillers and he wouldn't give me any
which made me angry right but he did
give me a an appointment to go see
somebody like two days later because
they were closed on Christmas I get to
the dentist's office I sit down I open
my mouth he takes one look at me and
goes whoa that's
infected you're going to need to see a
doctor said I did see a doctor he
wouldn't even give me any painkillers
dentist goes is that what this is
about I get so pissed I stormed out of
there I went to a chiropractor made him
pull the tooth he's like I don't usually
do this I'm like shut up I already
cracked it that's like all your job
let's
go you got a new album out don't you
yeah I have a new record out it's called
no
joke and it's uh all recorded and then
we cut out all the jokes so it's all
just crowd work I don't really want to
call it like heckling it's like heckling
interaction it's not even really crowd
work it's just you guys are drunk and
shut up I recorded it off all the open
mics I went to and what's really cool to
me is that like Minneapolis is a pretty
big comedy town and there's so many
people that have such cool like
recording spots like when you did first
a like that was super cool like like all
these different like like AC stuff and
mine is just like Northeast Palace
grumpy downtown like I'm in the pits I
love it it's great you got a really good
way of promoting it too
um oh yeah by putting it in the uh he
puts copies of the
CD in Jewel cases that are not his CD
right so whenever somebody's like oh can
I borrow this prong CD I'm like here you
go you're like Dylan here take this home
and then you get and open it and it's
his CD trying to be a better person I
don't know if you can
tell thank
you uh my New Year's resolution was to
be a better person which is funny cuz
like one of the things I targeted was
weight loss I was going to lose some
weight this year right
and it's funny cuz me resolving to lose
weight is just me getting blackout drunk
and ordering Insanity off the
TV you guys know what insanity is yeah
it's this hardcore like workout here you
go show a hands how many people here
made it through all of the insanity
program oh I didn't see that coming did
you [ __ ] yeah I made it through that
whole 90-day program which means this is
the body of my
dreams and I'm really really bad at
dreaming I
guess it's funny I was blackout drunk
when I ordered it so I don't remember it
right but I do know at least how big of
an [ __ ] I am when I'm drunk so I know
exactly what happened like I'm watching
TV these guys are smiling about jumping
jacks I'm at home Lean Back eating Taco
Bell off my top
belly like I could do jumping jacks
these guys aren't special call up order
it like oh want the insanity thing like
yeah we'll get you hooked up and when I
got it I got a yoga how many people here
got it and got a yoga mat yeah it's me
I've done this joke all year and I'm the
only person that got this yoga mat which
means I was so drunk they added on a
sale like I want that inanity yeah want
that b we got a yoga B sale get in
here and I don't remember ordering it
right I've said that what I do remember
is coming home 7 to 10 business days
later to a giant box on my steps that
just says insanity
I have never been more conflicted about
whether or not to open a package in my
life nobody told me what Pandora's box
was made of you know might be stamps and
cardboard I don't know and I bring it in
the box is huge there's a yoga mat in
there I set it on my table and there's a
little voice in the back of my head that
says Cory you should probably check this
to make sure it's not a
bomb which is funny you guys because I'm
very stupid me checking something to
make sure it's not a bomb it's just me
shaking it till it does or does not
explode 2 minutes in I'm like not a bomb
we're good I open up the box I look in
and it's got the yoga mat and it's got
these DVDs and I'm like holy [ __ ] these
guys want me to work
out that is
insanity should have got the workout
program sanity it's just cheeseburgers
and porn but I get through that
quickly not too quickly ladies
yeah thank you you're welcome all
right one creepy guy in the corner is
like I feel
that negative negative sir and I am I am
pretty cheap I'm from Hibbing Minnesota
so I grew up real broke so like I
already realized that I ordered this
thing right so I'm like damn it I'm
going to use it I'm going to get my
money's worth out of this shitty thing I
did to
myself and so I get it out and the
company for those of you that don't know
like the company of insanity like
everything is like all like happy and
like these guys are more happy doing
jumping jacks than any [ __ ] any man
has ever received oh this is the best I
love it like I hate these
people and I get the yoga mat out the
whole company's called beach body get
your beach body yeah and like it's so
intense yeah you guys are nodding yes
you've seen it right yeah and it's so
bad that like the yoga mat they can't
even call it a yoga mat they call it a
Beachbody jump
pad they should have called it a fat
alcoholic tear sponge cuz that's what it
[Applause]
did seven sit-ups in super
absorbent my roommate comes home are you
crying no I'm working out please
leave so I finally get ready to do it
right I put the DVD in I'm like let's do
this and for anybody that's done it do
you remember the first thing on those
DVDs I'm going to say it and you're
going to go oh yeah the first thing on
these DVDs is like a page and a half of
[ __ ]
warnings right oh yeah all three of them
oh yeah and like the shitty it's like a
page and a half right but these are the
kind of warnings you should never have
to say out loud to another adult the
first warning says and I quote these
exercises are
strenuous that's
exercise you never got done working out
and like well that's a Brisk nap I
should do something with my day
no maybe yoga but not jumping jacks calm
down and then the next one is the one
that just really got my goat it goes
please consult a physician to make sure
you're okay for physical
activity that is never going to [ __ ]
happen you guys never going to walk into
a doctor's office and be like hey you
think I'm too fat to work out you guys
get the joke over
here over here you get it you guys think
I'm too too fat to work
out can I eat these vegetables or will
my system reject
them do you have any painkillers cuz
that's what this is
about and you do a uh a cooking show yep
cooking it with Cory as a standup comic
I've kind of always been on the poverty
line so my cooking style directly
resembles that of my immigrant
[Music]
grandparents just the cool thing about
that show for me is like I've never
claim to be good at this I just I'm from
Hibbing and there's a lot of weird
dishes that are from there pasties yeah
is that what they're called yeah pasties
yeah meat filled meat Pockets Michigan
meat Pockets Michigan Michigan meat
pockets it's a meat it's meat in a ball
of dut it's like it's like no it's like
a pastry it's not like cake Donut's a
pastry is it [ __ ] I don't know well then
it's a meat past you're the one with the
cooking show ladies and gentlemen Cory
Adam I'm here all night seriously I need
a place to stay do
it that's right I drank because I grew
up right outside Detroit Michigan it's
uh you have to to deal with it uh grew
up outside Detroit went to Catholic
school that's why I don't believe in God
anymore
uh while I was in Catholic school I was
on What's called the football
team yeah this
football
team my junior year every day after
practice we would lift us some goddamn
weights while we would lift those
weights we would listen to the
soundtrack to a little movie called Top
ethn
Gun you're right that is super
badass until
Take My Breath Away comes
on and it's all about not looking anyone
in the eye that's all that
is yeah I don't want to play anymore
it's done how did your eyes get so
blue hey this has been a great night so
far you ready for your
headliner are you ready for your
headliner folks put your hands together
you C on Marin on the IFC Network ladies
and gentlemen the very funny Ryan Singer
everyone how about for
everybody
everybody that's a TV taping get out the
gold spray paint for the picture
frame woo I'm like delirious right now I
got so man H so much red bull inside my
body so much shouldn't drink it
shouldn't drink that stuff Monster
Energy drink Red Bull if if I misspeak
if I say some words incorrectly it's not
cuz I'm dumb I mean I'm not real smart
but it's because I drink so much of this
stuff it's got torine in it right uh
torine is synthetic bull testosterone I
want the real stuff but they won't let
me have it right so we got the scientist
to synthesize
make bull ball juice so you can chug it
down your stupid face just to feel alive
you know what I mean it's like a steroid
steroids make your muscles bigger that's
if you work out uh this is me working
out I look like a chimpanzee doing the
macarina right so I've only got one B
one muscle inside my entire body that I
use and I'm not even sure it's a muscle
to be quite honest with you and that's
my tongue it's CU I just don't shut the
hell up I'm just always talking so it's
like I'm chugging all this Red Bull all
these steroids into my body and I'm just
it's like my mouth is inside are my
tongue's inside my mouth getting all
jacked up like it's on CrossFit which is
my new he was talking about insanity but
like I love crossfit's my new favorite
exercise fad dude like five years ago if
I saw a dude running down the street
carrying a TV I'd be like that dude
stole that
TV but now I'm like oh I bet that dude's
doing CrossFit look at him like if I'm
driving my car through a neighborhood
and somebody's got a kettle bell like
jogging I just want to yell out my
window every time she's never going to
love
you she's not coming home home it
doesn't matter how many abs you
have the older I get the more I realize
I should always be yelling into a mirror
but uh it's okay it's it's okay some
jokes and sad and that's
okay I'm here with Ryan Singer and uh
standup comedian extraordinaire and uh
welcome thanks for having me yeah no
problem how'd you get here where you
from oh I'm I live in Los Angeles now
originally from Dayton Ohio the former
home of uh Oliver and Wilbur Wright
yeah the inventors of flight but I
thought they I thought that was
Kittyhawk no I mean we don't need to get
into the Ohio vers North Carolina
discussion that war is being waged on
license plates currently Ohio Dayton
Ohio was where they were born and they
had their bicycle shop and where they
invented the airplane is that okay they
just didn't have the proper Hill to fly
it off in Dayton so that's why they took
the plane down to Kittyhawk so basically
that's like saying uh you know let's say
I invented like the coolest time travel
machine but I didn't have the right
temperature uh in where I live to do it
so I brought it over to your house and
then you start uh just putting banners
on your house the birthplace of time
travel it's like no no see Ohio license
play say birthplace of Aviation because
they were born there yeah North Carolina
says First in Flight first and flight
yeah it's like people in North Carolina
are a bunch of idiots it is good to be
alive though God technology in general
carpet sometimes I just get baffled
looking at carpet dude it's like indoor
grass you
know sometimes inventions get creepy to
me too like I got creeped out the other
day thinking about
leather who the first person who ever
wore leather was you know it was
probably a man
you allegedly it happened over 100
thousand years ago it's when it first
happened there probably a man standing
in a field like oh look at that peaceful
sentient
being just chewing grass mining its own
business I'm going to sneak up behind
it and then I'm going to kill it cuz I
can and then I'm going to peel all of
its skin off of its body so I can wear
it like it's my
own you do that to a cow It's Fashion
you want to do it to another person
you're a
psychopath what's the real difference
dude you like these pants
these are Theodore from
accounting he was a real heer that
one you have a podcast yeah I sure do
it's called me and paranormal you I call
it a minecast because I'm a weird I try
to differentiate it I think as far as I
know it's the only mind cast out there
many people have a podcast that's right
I'm not sure how many people have a mind
cast I interview people with paranormal
abilities or experiences so it's pretty
fun
kind of like a coast to coast thing
maybe I love Coast to Coast Coast to
Coast uh big big influence on me because
when I first started doing standup
comedy on the road from Ohio and many
late nights driving in the middle of
nowhere yeah always find Coast to Coast
that was the one radio program you could
usually find yeah at 2: in the morning
when you're driving through the hills I
wonder why maybe they must have had a
lot of fans that would just Bounce It
Off different things and oh yeah I mean
pretty much every Fox AM news station AM
radio station carried it so it was
syndicated it was one of the few huge
syndicated programs yeah so yeah loved
it man loved driving through the
mountains at 2 in the morning listening
to like outof body experiences and you
know alien encounters and all the other
Atlantis most of the time though
inventions are cool to me like I was in
the hotel today just kind of
like not because I use it but I was
holding the blow dryer just kind of like
baffled by the device like I don't know
if you've ever just been baffled by a
device like what who did this how did
how does this what you know like
sometime in the past somebody said I
want to harness the power of the wind in
my
fist but slightly warmer you
know they invented the blow dryer well
done person [ __ ] it's got electricity in
it like oh that's magic dude electricity
is just invisible [ __ ] like oh I'll
never I'll never understand it like
television how that works oh don't
[ __ ] try to explain it to me uh
there's two things in this life I will
never understand how television works
and craps I lose so much money playing
craps I just can't figure out I know the
casino's close by and I'm going to go
later tonight and just lose everything I
can't wait but
uh I was raised in an Irish Catholic
gambling family so it's like I've been
gambling since I came out of the womb I
think I probably was a bet actually
uh I don't if I was a winner or a loser
but I think my mom's still holding on to
that ticket it'll pay off one of these
days just show kid just show what's
don't even have the
place that's
okay I do I've been gambling my whole
life oh man I love it too my family they
gamble on everything cards poker
horseshoes darts all that kind of stuff
cornhole that's a backyard game not a
I remember one Christmas I lost was
close to $200 at the poker table and
most of it to my grandma
and that's a lot of money to lose right
so I was upset about it and uh and my
grandma noce I was upset she goes well
you shouldn't be gambling with money you
can't afford to lose I was like I'm 11
years old
grandma my gift this year was just a
card with a $50 bill that said see you
at the table this is some
[ __ ] like you're setting me up for
this I was set
up of all the things paranormal why are
comedians into
Bigfoot I think comedians are into
Bigfoot because there's mystery there
and there's also there's danger there's
mystery uh and we also have more time
during our days to be on YouTube is it
because of the long drives and that's
the long drives you you see all of the
unexplored area and you're like oh yeah
easily
could living that we Haven and there's
also very Stakes about it comedians
devote their life to the SL possibility
that they'll make it yeah it's so rare
that we can make it right so being a
successful comedian is almost like being
Bigfoot you just hope people find you
yeah ladies and gentlemen that was Ryan
Singer Bigfoot is
real God my family is pretty cool I got
cool parents uh my parents got divorced
when I was about to 16 years old um and
they remained single for about five six
years before they got remarried so I
turned 21 years old and both my parents
were single which meant I got to go out
drinking with my single parents which on
which on paper might sound cool you know
like being out with your dad trying to
meet your new mom together but
uh but it led to some like weird fights
at the bar my dad would be like hey look
at her she should be your new mom I was
like no no that should be your new
daughter he be like no she should be
your new mom and I was like dude if you
end up marrying her I'm just going to
have to move in the house and act like a
Sleepwalk every time she showers that's
going to be
weird but leave her to leave her to me
and your will if you don't mind uh women
are not property
uh it's a socially conscious joke uh
even worse though being out with my mom
my mom is beautiful she's gorgeous right
cinematically beautiful too like Greta
Garo ah and here's the thing dirty old
men they don't have a filter over the
over the [ __ ] that comes out of their
mouth they will say anything to anybody
it doesn't matter who you are or where
you are uh one night uh my mom and I
were out and she wanders off at this bar
and this old dude walks over to me he's
like hey excuse me son is that your
mother over there I was like yes sir
that is and he goes wow she's one fine
piece of ass isn't she boy and I was
like what I was like yeah and she's got
crabs
[ __ ] moving along
sir take your $50 bills in your pocket
full of blue pills and hit the road
Jack why do old dudes always got 50s I
don't
know my dad's a pretty cool dude my dad
is a common please court judge in the
state of Ohio where I grew up uh Ohio
has capital punishment which means that
if someone's found guilty of murder in
his courtroom uh he can sentence them to
death right and uh which is a crazy
power for a person to have especially
when they're in charge of your curfew
and
discipline you better be home by 11 yes
sir I
will my dad is a uh Republican which is
fine he's a Christian which is fine I
don't have a problem with either either
one of those things but what that
combination means is he's against
abortion but for capital punishment
right and my simple brain locks up when
I try to figure out that combo like like
to me that's like saying I'm I'm against
you know totally against the consumption
of cookie dough but I believe it's
perfectly okay to eat
cookies you know
you'd have all the same political
arguments too you know what I mean you'd
have you'd have the liberal left you
know like oh everybody knows cookie does
not a cookie until it pops out of the
oven unless you can stick a fork in and
out of a cookie cleanly it's not a
cookie it's not a
cookie you'd have the middle of the road
we believe in partially cooked
consumption uh cuz our chefs have proven
that after 4 minutes in the oven cookie
dough gets a brown
bottom and the signifying trait of a
cookie is a brown
bottom you'd have the conservative right
did you know that at its Inception
cookie dough has completely formed
chocolate
chips listen as a man I don't believe
I'm entitled to an opinion on this
matter uh cuz I know the kitchen is a
woman's place and
uh that's the kitchen
okay don't let the metaphor break down
at the end this is this is where babies
get cooked in the
kitchen okay