[Music]
streaming at you digitally but taped
live at the joke joint comedy club in
Lilydale Minnesota a convenient 15
minutes out of downtown Minneapolis the
standup Channel presents Uprising
dedicated to bring you the best
comedians we can find and tonight's
Comics are Earl
Elliot John wi and Dave
Williamson so ladies and gentlemen start
streaming now for tonight's host Mr Cory
[Applause]
Adams
yeah what up how we
doing good yeah we're doing good
yeah my name is Corey and I guess
because I'm here instead of Chris I got
to say what a night right what an
audience let's do this make noise get
ready yeah
I'm uh I'm trying to watch my weight
like that was one of my New Year's
things right like I started working out
and then I quit doing that cuz that
sucked uh but one of the things I did is
I decided that uh I was going to cut out
fast food and like you know and soda and
all that right and so it's funny cuz I I
was able to cut out the soda or pop or
whatever and the fast food I was able to
cut out almost 100% right except for the
Wendy spicy chicken sandwich
yeah right I [ __ ] love it I love it I
do and I was having a really shitty day
and I am born and raised in Minnesota so
I decided to eat my feelings like an
adult Lutheran that's what we
do yeah and I was having just a terrible
day and I wrote the funny part is like I
still eat as many spicy chicken
sandwiches as I ever have right but now
I just feel really terrible about it
whenever I do like I roll into that gas
station I look like somebody that's
cheating on their wife like I turn off
my lights I put my hat down lower take
the battery out of my phone and just
Coast
in and I was having one of those really
bad days and I rolled in I'm like I'm
going to get a sandwich I don't even
care and I roll in I get to the like
drive-thru mic thing and the L's all
like because you can't understand them
nobody gives a [ __ ] and I said I'll have
a spicy chicken sandwich and she goes
would you like anything else and I said
No thanks just the sandwich she goes
would you like anything to drink and I
said No thanks just the sandwich she
goes would you like to make that a
combo and I lost my [ __ ]
mind like you guys ever have one of
those days where you're like I just want
to murder everybody I come across and
then you get home and you're like I
didn't murder anybody I deserve all of
this tub of ice cream that's me for not
murdering I deserve it you know that's
the kind of day I was having right and I
said no just the sandwich and she goes
is there anything else and I said yeah
why are there two drive-thru
Windows
silence she goes uh what and go why are
there two drive-through Windows you can
get food and money out of the same
window why are there two
silence she goes so nothing
else and I said No and then this brain
scientist decides that now is the time
to really add on to my sale and so she
says to me would you like to donate a
dollar for a coupon book yeah you know
where it's going already would you like
to donate a dollar to a coupon book that
goes to help adopted
kids now I had already told this woman I
wanted nothing else three times I was
having a bad day I decided I wanted to
hurt her with
words so I immediately said no thanks
I'm very against
adoption which isn't true but [ __ ] her
you
know I go no thanks I'm very against ad
option and she goes
what and then it just pauses and she
goes pull up to the first window and I
go why are there two windows and I hear
her throw her headset and she goes [ __ ]
this
guy and so now I'm sitting there right
and like I get it like I'm an [ __ ]
that's fine I understand that I am an
[ __ ] I know that about me but I've
never been to like make somebody throw
their headset at work kind of an [ __ ]
right we're in undis discovered
territory right I don't know the
protocol do I sit here and wait do I
pull to the next window do I say screw
it and go to Arby's for some curly
fries I don't know the protocol so I
waited I froze I was thinking it out and
I heard the headset scrape and somebody
else picked it up just guy puts it on he
goes uh will there be anything
else and I go yeah why are there two
windows and I hear the guy cover the mic
and go you're right he is an [ __ ]
he goes pull up to the first window sir
I go why are there two windows he goes
just
go so I pull up to the first window
right and the lady is there waiting for
me she looks at me I look at her she
goes you know I just thought of
something I go yeah you think about why
there's two
windows she goes if you don't want this
coupon book that goes to help adopted
kids you can just buy it and then give
it away to somebody that does want it
right
to which I said oh just like those
orphans families did to
them yeah oh don't groan at me I know
I'm the [ __ ] calm down I go just like
those orphans families did to them and
she goes and and her response took me
back she stops she looks at me she got
super serious she leans forward she goes
I'll have you know that I gave away my
kids for
adoption yeah I was like whoa they tell
you why there was two windows when you
did
it she goes are you trying to tell me
that everyone that gives away their kids
for adoption is a bad person I said no
I'm trying to tell you that I want a
chicken [ __ ]
sandwich she goes pull up to the next
window I go why are there two windows
she closes the door in front of me and
walks away so I pull up to the second
window cuz I like the ends of Adventures
let's do this and I roll up to that
second window she looks at me I look at
her except now she is laughing Laugh In
For The First Time In This encounter
right like hysterically like just she
goes hold on let me get your food and
she grabs my food and walks out of my
line of sight with it right and here's
something you could take home with you
guys if you're harassing somebody and
they're making your
food don't eat that food right she came
back she left with a bag that was folded
over it was awesome it was nice it was
pretty you know she came back with
something that looked like somebody had
been playing a wet
tambourine it's all mangled and weird
and here's the thing that really creeped
me out it was
leaking yeah you follow the story I
ordered a chicken sandwich what's
leaking don't know and she's laughing
she she goes here's your food and I said
oh no you can keep that she goes you
don't want it I said no she said why not
I said based on everything I I know
about you there's probably a baby in
that
bag yeah then I went to Taco Bell and it
was delicious one drive-through window
not a
coincidence yeah you guys ready to kick
this off
yeah all right we're going to bring your
first comic up here uh your next comic
coming to the stage you may have seen
him on Tinder please welcome Earl Elliot
everybody
let's give it up for Cory
[Applause]
Adam everybody's drinking that's
good my dad drinks old duels like I'm
I'm trying to drink less so I smoke more
weed that's how my math works like but
my dad drinks old duels I was like man
how do you drink this tastes like [ __ ]
don't do it he was like yo you just got
to put some vodka in it and it goes
right I know that sounds silly like I
made that up but I do actually have a
father I
just naturally fighting stereotypes I
can't help it just naturally I over tip
everywhere I go even at the second
drive-thru window I'm like n you keep it
man that's
all I can
swim proficient swimmer I can't dance so
it's a [ __ ] like it sucks cuz
apparently women can tell how good a guy
is in bed by the way he dances I feel
like that's not fair cuz I can never
make it through one
song I feel like that joke should last
longer I don't I
know hey we're here with Earl Elliot
what's up buddy nothing much what's up
Cory what's going on I'm here no what's
going on what's happening what's going
on Siri's been bombed I think I don't
should we start like that I yeah we can
do whatever we want man how long you
been doing comedy now uh it'll be 5
years in July yeah is it everything you
hoped it would does it make you happy on
the
inside are you finally a complete human
being um with my talents cuz I'm not
good at anything else so
so you're more a fan of Comedy out of
necessity yeah cuz there's nothing else
you're going to do nothing else I can do
okay all right comedy's good though like
it's it's a good uh exercise mentally
see now that feels like you're lying no
I mean it how long does it take you to
write a joke typically before you're
happy with it the answer is you're never
happy with it never yeah uhuh it's like
you know when you do Ecstasy and you
know that high you can't reach it high
and then you're just allegedly and
allegedly and then you come down and
your crash is when I've had good shows
that crash and then I try to explain it
to my girlfriend he like I'm just going
to be bummed out for a couple days oh
man relationships are the worst with
comedy I can't sleep most of the time my
girlfriend's like why can't you sleep
and I'm like cuz my adrenaline's pumping
see usually I get really drunk at shows
so going to sleep's not a problem so I
like what it's nice outside cuz like I
like uh I can bring my dog to like
patios like so I can go to like patios
with or bars with patios on them so I
can bring my dog so I don't got to drink
alone like the dog's cool around people
he's fine people pet the dog he's cool
but he gets really excited when he sees
another dog and I get that he sees one
of his own but I never truly respected
it until I went to a hockey game
this just me walking around a stadium
trying to get excited this side of the
room didn't get it I'm the only black
guy there
that's every time I think see another
one of me it's just my [ __ ]
reflection in a plexiglass man like just
trying to go wild like everybody else
like I was in this bar recently and I
was inside so I was alone so and like I
was in I was by myself and I was wearing
my glasses I noticed that when you wear
glasses and can't grow a beard at the
same time people don't respect your face
they just they always think you're
underage and like on top of that there
was a guy who's like a tough guy next to
me who just kept like shouting at the TV
and just kept like shoving me he was
like a tough guy he was by himself he
was drinking lroy water is weird at a
bar but he just kept shoving me like
after the third time tough guy shoved me
I politely shot him in the face with a
spitball cuz I'm
mature it was polite it was it wasn't a
wet one that stuck it was like a a
bounce off kind it was a warning shot to
tough guy tough guy tried to start a
fight with me he didn't like that the
bouncers go to pull tough guy out as
they're pulling tough guy out he tries
to start a fight with the bouncers he's
a tough guy as they're pulling tough guy
out keep in mind I wearing my glasses he
points across the bar and goes I'll meet
you outside
URL that's your verbal haym maker tough
guy Urkel really I don't you're supposed
to be a tough guy you submitted to the
whole body you watch Family Matters I
don't think you're that tough that's
that's one two Urkel is not an insult
like I'll gladly be a Steve Urkel show
up to your house unannounced break
something in a Charming way eat all your
food and politely try to [ __ ] your
sister every day that's all the did
every day I'm at your door just oh is
your sister pregnant yeah I did that
it's got urle
[ __ ] so where you from Columbia
Maryland why did you start comedy I
don't
know oh I I was actually that's a look I
don't care what anybody says that's the
greatest answer I've ever heard I don't
know screw this degree I want to go bomb
at a bar I never said I was smart I
cheat that's
right I always want to try it like I
came around for like 2 years but I was
too scared you know was there like
somebody like as a kid or like an
influence that made you want to try it
like I never I never knew that you could
just do it like what do you mean like I
never knew that you just go to an open
mic that's how everybody starts and then
I found out you think it was like a
casting couch or something yeah I didn't
like cuz you see famous people you don't
know like I always love Comics I always
love people on TV shows who write for
like Simpsons you know all that but it's
just you never knew that you can just go
to a bar and do it yeah and then you
keep doing it and then you just get sad
and you just keep doing it ladies and G
gentleman Earl
Elliott do I got to do anything
now a lot of people ask if I protest for
black lives matter no I don't protest
it's hard to protest if your voice still
cracks black lives matter like it
doesn't do you justice like I don't and
then a lot of people say the protests
are annoying and I get it cuz one time I
was at a Twins game we were overlooking
the light road tracks and there was a
black lives matter protest going on it
was all white people protesting but
everybody in the stadium was looking at
me like I did it like this is [ __ ]
annoying like
I and I live in this new gentrified
neighborhood where everybody puts black
lives matter signs in their yards so now
I know where all the white people
live so I started stealing them the
signs not white people like in during
the election season I would take black
lives matter sign and put it in a trump
yard and just sit in the bushes and just
watching I feel like black lives matter
is doing it wrong instead of throwing
protest they should throw parades cuz
you can't get mad at a parade if you get
mad at a parade a place of throwing
candy out of a slow moving vehicle
you're the [ __ ] it's you like it's
candy out of a vehicle like you they can
also subtly slip in their message they
throw candy out and just throw Jolly
ranch or lollipops but the only Flav is
watermelon I do uh I do like being
married and we have like a little
four-year-old girl it's exciting it's a
lot of fun and my buddy we only have one
we're only going to have one my buddy
was like are you going to have more kids
I was like no way no way I'm a little
bit an older parent you know and I was
like no I'm not going to do it and then
he was like well what if she gets lonely
and I started thinking about that I was
like you know what that is her [ __ ]
problem you know what I mean guys right
I got to make another person because
she's antisocial no no no no no I'll
just get her like a library card or
something cats something I don't know it
was all whole new world I I don't know
if a lot of you guys have kids or not I
you know so I was you know in my late
30s when my wife got pregnant and so was
a whole new world I didn't know anything
about it concept of it my wife was very
gassy during the pregnancy which I
didn't know was a side effect of being
pregnant this lady knows what I'm
talking talking about this guy didn't
Goa at that but yeah it is weird it's
like disturbing how gassy and my wife
was like hey it's totally natural for
pregnant women to pass this much gas I
was like really is it natural for them
to be holding their husband's heads
under the covers while they're doing it
I don't think so she's super strong so
are you ready for your headline Make
Some
Noise your next com coming to the stage
as a standup records recording artist
please welcome Dave Williamson everybody
[Applause]
hey all
right how's it going
guys all right all right thank you oh
thank you sir that was very polite that
was just he's like I'll answer for
everyone
good good that's cool man how about
those other guys I I give it up for
everyone you saw so
far it's a tough world to raise children
in everywhere you look kids for the most
part turning out to be spoiled little
punks it's kid on my Street's 8 years
old last Christmas his parents bought
him an iPhone my six-year-old sees this
he's like Daddy why can't we have stuff
like that I don't want you to be that
kid in two years that kid's eight he
sucks already he's got a neck tattoo and
two failed
marriages cuz his parents just green
light whatever trying to put some effort
into this Christmas is a good example of
something we're doing ourselves to
instill the wrong principle in our kids
cuz we have not updated these traditions
we just pass them down lazily from
generation to generation like they still
make sense and they might have made
sense back when rocking horse was a top
five
gift but it's not anymore yeah we still
tell our kids hey write the top four or
five things you want down on a piece of
paper we're going to send that list away
to Santa which means now I got to give
credit for the most expensive most
competitive gifts to buy that particular
season to a guy that does not exist for
a lie I did not
start how's that fair to Dad when you
work your ass off all year long but you
only take credit for gifts like 6
through 11 and now some stranger you
meet at the mall once a year bought you
the good stuff I got you socks to school
supplies that's why I tweak things at an
early age I told my boys hey guys
remember Christmas is coming up which
means Mommy and Daddy are going to buy
you a lot of gifts cuz we think you've
been really nice this
year but don't forget Santa's going to
come visit us on Christmas Eve and
depending on how good or bad you
actually were he's going to take as many
presents as he sees
fit so hope you were good boys when no
one was watching cuz he always is night
night
Traditions that makes more sense now you
have Santa working for you not against
you now when they throw a tantrum on
Christmas morning I asked for a Star
Wars robot why isn't there a robot you
don't have to be a bad guy or explain
lay
away you just jump on board what I
bought you a robot it should be
[Music]
right that's probably one of the gifts
Santa
took you know how hard that was for me
to buy for you what did you
do now I'm pissed off you owe me a
robot they're going to be appreciative
for every other gift under that
tree seems mean but it works out better
for the kids too cuz now when they're
like seven or eight years old some bully
convinces them saying it isn't real
instead of being devastated they're like
oh thank
god dude that guy's been jacking me for
years that's a happy day all of a sudden
we're lying the right direction away
from therapy
was working so well I started
incorporating the same philosophy some
other aspects of parenting a while back
one of my kids was being a real
knowitall wouldn't listen to me when I
tried to impart
wisdom incidentally around that same
time he lost his first tooth I recognize
that as a teaching
opportunity I was like oh
[ __ ] dude that is not supposed to happen
I told you to brush those every
day you skipped once didn't you it's all
takes one
time going to listen to Daddy when he
tries to teach you stuff from now on
aren't
you all right all right stop crying stop
crying stop crying stop crying I don't
want your I mean you don't want your mom
to hear
you all right listen there's something
you can do to try to fix this but you
did not hear this from me
okay your only chance is tonight when
you go to sleep you got to leave at
least a dollar under your
pillow for the tooth fairy and maybe
she'll let that [ __ ] grow
back it's probably not going to be nice
and straight like your last one but
that's on
you it's just going to be a constant
crooked reminder of how smart your daddy
is
he's not going to be happy with that
information he's going to brush those
teeth every night till they're all gone
by the time he realizes that's normal
you got 30 something dollars saved up
towards his future dental work that's
not a shitty kid like the kid down the
street that's a great kid shipping in
for his own braces one day we're here
with Dave Williamson yes sir how are you
doing good man how you good pleasure to
see you real good so let's talk about
your album thicker than water
yeah it's uh one of my favorite records
that I own uh from standup I remember uh
cleaning and pitching in just to get a
copy of of it and uh the thing about it
and I'm sure you get this a lot but for
me my favorite part is easily the ice
cream music like that like it was my
absolute favorite and I remember uh I
listened to it and me and my buddies
were on a road trip it was me and two
other comics and we were going to a gig
and we're listening to it I looked at my
buddies and I said if he does not have a
hidden track with ice cream music this
whole album is [ __ ] yeah and then uh
we got so wrapped up in the rest of it
cuz it's a very good album it's very
funny totally forgot about it and then
it's just running and then just all of a
sudden what was so funny is like it
starts in So Soft right so we're just
driving and I just hear this and I I
literally forgot about I'm looking
around and I'm like is there an ice cre
oh my God [ __ ] it just cranked it rolled
down the windows and like there were no
kids we're in the middle of nowhere but
we're like oh and I've tried to do that
at least twice now to try and like do it
in real life with that that makes me so
happy I mean that was like one of my
first jokes that like I really like you
know was a staple for me you know and
then uh when I was like you know putting
all my old material together to make my
first album uh you know and I was
talking to Dan um at the label I said
like hey man do you think it'd be cool
if we actually put a a song on there and
whatever and he was like let me look
into it and he had to buy the rights to
whatever the famous ice cream truck
music song was like KY the Dario or
whatever it is we did and we put it on
there man I mean like the the thing too
that I really like is I really like the
cover like the cover is a really cool
picture and I and I how many shots did
that take you to get that like how how
long were you like at any point did they
have to drag you out of a pool and like
resuscitate you to get another better
shot of it no I mean I was playing to my
skill set there because you know I grew
up in Miami and we'd go uh spear fishing
and and free diving stuff so I mean I
have really good lung support but uh the
harder part was getting my kids to
swimming around on the background uh for
so long cuz it was actually even though
it's Miami it was still winter when we
shot that oh so the water was cold kids
give you perspective too man I know
that's cliche in itself but it's true
like like I love I love doing this
that's my job man it was always my dream
you know it's what I wanted to be and I
worked hard and I you know I've been
doing it full-time for for a long time
now and everything and you know I'm not
complaining for a second but just like
every job there's like good days and bad
days and recently I was in a little bit
of a funk and I just didn't want to
think about work I just want to like
take my family and go do something and
try to concentrate on what's important
in life you know you ever one of those
days where work just finds you like you
can't get away from it some of you guys
were like teachers and you're like yeah
we [ __ ] try not to think about kids
and it's all you talk
about no well I went I took my family
hiking and I was on this hiking trail
and I found a Heckler right I could spot
these dudes from a mile away too like
this is what happened my youngest son
got hot while we were hiking so he took
his little Chewbacca sweatshirt off and
he asked me to hold it for him and I
don't want to hike with it in my hand
hand so I put it up over my shoulders
you know like stretched it over my
shoulders and then this dude coming the
other way just looking at me and his
eyes were all lit up and I'm like oh
[ __ ] man I know exactly what this dude's
this type you know and he gets right up
next to me and he looks around see how
loud he's got to be to make sure
everyone can hear him and then he goes
hey
buddy looks like you bought that
sweatshirt a few sizes too
small and he thought he was so
funny and I could have zinged him back
and made a joke but then he would have
thought I was enjoying this exchange
probably and it would have encouraged
him you know and then he I would have
done it some dude at Starbucks the next
morning it would done to the guy who
sits next to him at work every day and
this dude would have been a menace to
society for the rest of his life so
instead I made a split second decision
to shut this guy down it's really out of
character for me but I looked him in the
face and I go
what no oh no man it's not my sweatshirt
this is my
son's he's been missing for two days now
it's the first clue we
found if you could keep your eyes open
as you're hiking today we would really
appreciate that you know and this dude's
face was like oh
[ __ ] like I don't think he he still
might not have talked to another adult
to this day like that's how devastated
this guy looked I thought my family was
going to give away my lie you know like
they're what are you talking about that
but I look over at them and they were
totally unbored my kids were like
looking in bushes for Clues and [ __ ]
like Cory
where are
you we miss you come
[Laughter]
home so this guy couldn't wait to he
hiked away from us turned the corner and
everything you know and then uh we start
laughing we're having a nice little
family bonding moment everything and my
oldest son gets real serious for a
second and I thought that he was a shame
like what he realized we did was
terrible but turns out it wasn't shame
it was Pride cuz he looks up at me and
he goes man
that guy had no idea he was dealing with
a famous
comedian
right I realized something in that
moment man all this dumb stuff I was
letting get me bummed out that week all
this ridiculous [ __ ] we used to equate
with success like money and fame
whatever like that doesn't matter in
life that's what matters right there
it's tricking your kids into thinking
you already have that
[ __ ] cuz it felt so good
and it's so much easier than working
hard you know how gullible kids
are now every time I'm feeling a little
bummed out I just throw a YouTube clip
of myself up on Roku on the big screen
I'm like look Daddy's on national TV
again like Daddy you're so successful I
know that drives me for another month or
so what are some of the worst rooms
you've done oh
jeez how much time you got as much as
you need I uh I mean I always feel a
little guilty telling this one story but
it was definitely probably the most I
ever hated being on stage but uh I did a
show in gr Cayman in the in uh down in
the Caribbean you know yeah and I was
like so I feel bad like complaining
about going to a beautiful place for
work sounds terrible but it but it was
so bad like so we had to lie on our on
our customs forum and say that we were
there for like uh just for a vacation
it's like me and another comic I'd never
met before so then we go to this bar and
they were trying to do this like comedy
night or something thing and uh it was
like four tourists showed up and like
they had us down on a dance floor and
then the people watching the show or up
higher than us looking down on us and
the DJ was set up off to the side and
every time i' do a joke the DJ would go
like pick P or something like that and I
was like what are you doing dude you're
not helping man you know and it we had
to feel all this like a rim shot but
techno version oh so bad so you've got
another album coming out so yes we um we
already recorded it okay we did it on a
in a really cool theater in uh Miami
Beach um it's actually so the Filmore is
a very famous um giant theater it's been
there a long time and uh Jackie gleon uh
used to basically it was where he
performed that's like the history behind
was like Jackie Gleason's theater and so
there's a sound stage in the back where
Jackie used to practice for the TV show
and and things like that so um they've
turned the back Sound Stage into like a
little Ballroom so we did it back there
we we shot it as a DVD and a CD so um
we're just working on editing now and
hopefully get it out pretty soon you got
the cover art down we don't man we're
still talking about that the problem is
that we set the bar so high with the
first one that that's really the hard
part is coming up with something that's
going to be equally as cool Dave
Williamson everybody
heyo freeze
frame I did um I did a cool thing uh I
took my family on the road with me
actually for a year and a half like cuz
I was traveling so much I was getting on
airplanes every week and my kids were
more developmental ages at the time and
I didn't want my kids to grow up weird
because I was being like an absentee Dad
so we sold our house we bought an RV we
started homeschooling them and they came
on tour with us for a year and a half
all right yeah it's kind of cool cuz
that'll make them normal you
know so this is one of my favorite
stories from that trip it was the best
time of my life it was like it ended up
being one of the greatest things ever
and uh this is one of my favorite
stories from that trip I was doing a
show just outside of Chicago the comedy
club was inside of a resort so they gave
us a really nice hotel suite for the
weekend we parked our RV and we parked
our car in the uh parking lot and just
left it and stayed on premises for the
whole weekend it was cool for a few
reasons one there was posters of me
everywhere which my kids don't usually
get to see so they were like Daddy look
it's you Dave Williamson I'm like I know
it's told you I'm very
successful but even cooler than that was
the pool there cuz it was like super
kid-friendly it was just all parents and
kids they didn't have to worry about
accidentally splashing someone there was
an awesome waterfall that they could
climb on there was a DJ playing top 40
hits felt like MTV Spring break but
several years
later everybody had their mistakes from
spring break with them you know it's
like a reunion
episode so the DJ would stop the music
every 30 minutes or so and she'd call
the kids over to do a little contest for
prizes and stuff and my oldest son like
I said super competitive so he was on
board every time at one point they were
doing a race in the pool they just
swimmed to the other side of the pool
and back and she had prizes for first
second and third place there was only
four kids that were going to race the
other three were much older and bigger
than my son so I knew he was going to
lose you know he was going to be the
only kid that didn't get a prize and I'm
like dude you sure you want to do this
he's like I'm going to do it Dad one of
the other kids even had water wings on
which is [ __ ] right off the bat
there's no integrity this race you know
I'm like all right man all right go for
it and he came in last and he was
already crying by the time he got to the
side of the pool you know and I looked
him in the face and I said listen buddy
it's not always about winning or losing
sometimes you got to just try your
hardest and let that be enough because
when you're a good dad you say [ __ ] you
don't believe all the
time so fast forward to about an hour
later the DJ stops the music again and
she goes all right guys we're going to
do another race in the pool and I have a
great prize for first place and first
place only it's a really good prize but
it's more of an adult prize so I'm going
to need some adults to race in the pool
so my son gets up out of the pool and he
comes racing over to me where I'm
sitting in a lawn chair and he goes
daddy you got a race like he knows he
disgraced our honor and I got to regain
the family's dignity right I was like
dude I don't really feel like racing man
I'm chilling like I'm just going to sit
this out he looks me in the face and he
goes daddy if you're scared don't worry
about it it's not always about winning
or
losing sometimes you got to just try
your hardest and let that be enough said
I see what you're doing you little
[ __ ] you want to prize so bad you're
throwing my own words back in my face
all right fair enough I will show you
that it is always important to try now I
tell you this for context not to brag
but I played water polo most my life I
still swim from time to time to keep in
shape I'm not the fastest guy on Earth
but I'm pretty sure I can do all right
it's some stupid race in the outskirts
of Chicago for some [ __ ] prize if I
want to is all I'm
saying but I decided it would be a
better lesson for my son if I lost and I
was a really good sport about it so that
was my plan as I walked over to the
pool but then I got over
there and there were these two dudes
that were like helping each other
stretch making real aggressive eye
contact with
me and there's this guy over here who's
doing this arm motion like he's
competitively swam before and or seen it
on
TV my competitive juices started flowing
I was like oh all right you little
[ __ ] want to race oh we can race and
I had to stop myself just shy going out
to my car to get my emergency
Speedo cuz I always have
one this lady's losing her mind she's
like I got such a good prize for first
place swimmers on your mark get set go
and I shot off that wall
rocketed to the other side of the pool
did a flip turn in like one foot of
water pretty sure I kicked at least one
of those dudes in the rib cage on the
way
back I slapped the side of the pool so
hard as I finished I hurt my thumb I
whipped my head around as if to check an
imaginary time board in the
Olympics and in my brain it definitely
said Williamson Phelps right I was
feeling pretty good about myself until I
scanned down and realized
none of the other swimmers had even made
it to the other side of the pool
yet like I put way too much effort into
winning this
race now every single person that was
staying at this Resort had gathered to
watch and they were all just looking at
me like look at this
[ __ ] see how hard that guy just tried
to win this race oh my God who invited
the Mead family huh it's probably cuz
his kid was crying like a little [ __ ]
earlier you guys saw that
and I'm sitting like I didn't even want
to race I got talked into this you know
but they were right I toed it up pretty
bad and I had to climb out of the pool
and pretend like I wasn't a douche you
know which was hard cuz you know this
lady shoves a microphone in my face when
I'm trying to act like I didn't just try
my hardest you know which makes it
difficult he's like congratulations you
won I was
like my are you sure I mean I think it
was a pretty close contest I turn around
these idiots still aren't done with the
race yet and she's like oh no I'm sure
and I think you're going to be pretty
excited to find out that you just won
two free tickets to see Dave Williamson
in the comedy club
tonight I was like oh
no that's literally the worst thing she
could have
said the only I going for me to that
point is that nobody knew who I was and
now I got my son running towards me
screaming he is
Splash my name's Carl you know I helped
my son out of the pool and I was like
today's life lesson son is sometimes
when you win you're really just a big
ass
loser but don't worry you get a special
prize you and I are going to walk around
this whole property and take down every
poster of my picture on it for these
people realize who I am no one wants to
go listen to some douchebag meat P
talking about himself for an hour on
stage right I kept trying to still those
lessons of humility in my son throughout
the rest of the evening but later on
that night I felt guilty about it cuz to
be fair turned out kind of sweet since I
took those tickets I went to go see
myself that night and I was
fantastic was really good it's worth it
it's worth
it thank you for being here for this
fake TV show
or we're recording we lied about that we
just wanted you guys to be a good
audience so we just made that up just
just tell them we're recording a TV I
don't know just kidding I literally
think this is one of Cory's mustache
hairs on the microphone you guys see
that I literally think that's what Cory
come
here it definitely is look it [ __ ]
curls
up are you down here come
[Laughter]
here it was like tickling my nose as I
was doing that joke and I didn't want to
check the microphone in the middle of
the joke and then I just looked at I'm
like that's [ __ ] his mustache here
hold on you son of a
[ __ ] that is definitely your
mustache oh my God now it feels like
we've kissed or
something tickled by another man's
mustache in front of front of 70 other
people
[Music]