[Music]
in the big city the streets are
tough but he's
tougher and where there's trouble you'll
find him
Pike starring Willam geralis Jr as
Pike solid as
[Music]
steel you better talk son cuz my
partner's got a pretty bad temper don't
you
Pike all right you got me let do my
guess undercover yeah man I'll take this
shipment off your hands
but is it any good the deal's going down
let's
move oh
yeah burnt to a crisp in a space
accident he's back on Earth fighting
crime they're taking back the
streets also starring Rod
Nelson I love you
honey and Farah
Cheryl if you're running from the law
you'd better just keep on
[Music]
running Pik
welcome welcome
Partners you're watching clown hunt the
Suns at our back and the wind's just
right a perfect day for
hunting joining us today is Big Ray
[Music]
foot he's the winner of the prestigious
MIM shoot award in both 1985 and
1987 hey Ray
[Music]
and it's Billy
Des Billy is a well-known lecturer and
author of the recent bestseller 12
gauge so sit back relax and enjoy the
show today clown hunt brings us to
beautiful Washington State one of our
our country's most well-preserved
National Treasures
[Music]
welcome welcome once again to clown hunt
America's favorite hunting show I'm
Billy desant and this here is my partner
Big R but that's right Billy today we're
hunting clown in Northwestern Washington
State it's about 60° and there was a
cold front that moved in a couple days
ago that's right Ray and from a looks
around the place I'd bet my wife these
Woods is just crawling with
clown clowns is
smart and flushing them is easier said
than
done I spotted the first clown up a
ways Ray noticed he was wearing
headphones thus making our approach much
easier we worked our way around the
clown so as not to Spook
him clown spook easy
sh
[Music]
well that's half CL each nothing wrong
with
that it's a fine clown sure
is well should we uh circle around again
that sounds good
[Music]
Billy it wasn't long until we spotted
another
[Music]
it was a good
kill and I got myself a honey of a
[Music]
trophy we had begged too but after an
hour so our luck seemed to dry
up Ray and I talked a while and decided
to change our
plan what we needed was a different
strategy I suggested a lure of some sort
Ray agreed
silly balloons clowns just can't resist
silly balloons
we couldn't believe our
eyes a clone a piece
[Applause]
[Music]
and now the clown hunt tip of the week
you know hunting is relaxing and fun but
it can be dangerous too that's right Ray
that's why you should always be cautious
when using Firearms last year alone over
50 Hunters were hurt is that so maybe
they would not have injured each other
if they would have followed these four
easy
rules one treat all guns as if they are
loaded two treat all other Hunters as if
they are loaded three only point a gun
at something you intend to shoot and
number four always be sure of your
target before you shoot follow these
rules and we will all be better
Hunters well thanks train loads for
joining us today until next time I'm
Billy des and big Ray foot signing off
good hunting
[Music]
join us next time for another exciting
adventure with clown hunt
[Music]
he sold over 10 million albums in 46
countries More Than the Beatles Elvis or
The bgs combin Who is he he's Chaz dick
and this is his latest double album set
hard drive yes Chaz dick who's worked
with today's hottest stars Madonna
Prince Cheno Jaden Jackson and many more
here he's put all his greatest drum
machine hits together for you like
sequence
69 sequence 152
99 sequence
187 sequence
629 and sequence 2000 yes that's Chaz
dick's hard drive available on our DDD
CD or LP call 1800 chcd i k Visa
American Express or Mastercard accepted
that's 1800 CHC di I call now and let
Chaz dick Rock You all night long