this
[Applause]
is oh my back it's killing me putting in
some overtimes do I don't know what it
is I've tried everything ibuprofen
aspirin even Tylenol nothing seems to
work try
mine backup yeah backup it works hard
when I work hard it's got special
chemical brain stem Inhibitors stops
pain dead
okay we'll be at your 1020
minut hey how's that back feel now I
don't feel
nothing backup tablets for back pain now
with beta car
welcome once again to factory floor
bloopers here your host Dr sphincter and
Russ Beck hi there Dr spor hi Russ boy
do we have some blunders this week boy I
can't wait you know some people think
that when it comes to American industry
and the loss of thousands of American
manufacturing jobs that there's nothing
left to laugh about but we here at the
show feel like it's our duty to keep the
American worker in stitches l
well Russ if you think that's funny
let's take a look at our first blooper
of the week I can't wait let's get
Roland we took our camera Crews into the
seaside metal working plant in akan Ohio
we figured the workers there could use a
few laughs after their recent hostile
takeover we planned a little funny
business at the emergency eyewash
station nobody uses those things anyway
but we wanted to prove that sometimes
there really is more than meets the
you're killing me Doc we pulled a little
Switcheroo there at the emergency
eyewash station the bottle said sterile
water but something sure smelled like
ammonia watch now as our man Jeff
secretly replaces the water with ammonia
and then sprays mace into the safety
goggles of the technician about to use
the grinding
machine now this guy had just been hired
the day
before and he hadn't even worked on this
machine yet and I'll bet he's pretty
gullible when it comes to instructions
from the
foreman what oh ye gee what's happening
to
me he's a little low key but boy
he but it was all for fun he looks into
the camera and sees that it's all just a
Big Blooper flunder practical joke he'll
be fine now our second unlucky suspect
was uh had a little bit bit of a chip on
his shoulder but wait till you see what
happens here boy doctor I hope that long
hair doesn't get caught in one of the
grinding machines
oh something seems to be going on here
something doesn't seem to be
right my eyes hurt he doesn't even
qualify for medical coverage yet ow what
do you get when you mix ma and ammonia
what a pain in the eye
oh it's all for fun though it's just a
practical joke for blunder gr our man
Jeff comes out and assures him that it's
just been a joke but he gets a little
bit
peed oh he doesn't look too happy oh
true yikes oh boy I guess some guys just
can't take a joke of course they'll all
be rushed to a Trauma Center they'll be
fine
[Music]
oh
yeah oh
yeah the
oliv
edible the
[Music]
meat even more
edible oh
yeah oh
yeah oh yeah Olaf brand olive loaf oh
yeah what do you get when you combine
today's sluggish economy overseas
competition firing and layoffs with the
wacky bloopers and blunders crew
fireworks and a lot of laugh we've
Enlisted the help of a couple of back
office NBAs to help us with some phone
firings in the inventory control
Department watch now as they enter the
cafeteria for what they think is a
routine
[Laughter]
review here's our first subject little
did we know that he had a dirty little
secret yeah we got way more than we
bargained for on this one and so did he
over the
[Laughter]
years how's the job going it's going
really well really well I can we'll have
some bad news for you we're going to
have to let you
go
what we have no use for you oh wait a
minute what are you saying you're done
you're fired but it seems as if our
friendly mbas from the head office break
him I can return everything that I took
man I will return it all I can give you
back the microwave ofing and I can I can
pay you for the two typewriters I took
and I don't have any use for the for
listen to the laundry list of stuff he
has in his house from the
company boy I wish I had some of that
stuff please I'm begging you what are
you telling me I I can't I've got to
stay here man this is my home I just
can't take
it the news is hard to take listen to me
I I got
thing our final victim had just been
rehired after a 26mon layoff hi nobody
expected what would happen next but it
just goes to show you when the bloopers
blunders and practical joke crew is on
the scene anything can happen and it
does good good how's Wife and
Kids what do you think the job so far I
like it you like it a lot that's really
good um unfortunately I have some bad
news for you we're going to have to let
you go
you're done can you wait here for a
minute I'll be right back he seems to be
taking it rather well pretty mild
mannered as a matter of fact his
neighbor said they never heard a peep
out of
him whoa oh God that's a big machine
gun oh ice somebody better call the
company nurse we even get our sound
band look at that oh look out
oh
W
uhoh boy I guess some guys just can't
take a joke no that time the joke was on
us
well join us next week when we visit the
Hill Valley rendering PL until next time
byebye
bye hello welcome to another do
sphincters minute this is only a minute
people ask me what's your show about and
I say it's about a
minute anyway I'd like to tell you today
about the the the best value for your
car the the best car that there that you
could you could
get the best car that I've found that
that has worked well for me is a call
Car call a car called a a Maverick a
Maverick is is a perfect car
unfortunately it's not manufactured
anymore a Maverick combines um um
economy with with very with very tight
styling you don't want loose styling
like you have in the the cars of the
late 70s but you want tighter styling
like they had in the' 60s this is a
Maverick a Maverick is a very good car
it has ample seating for five people
although you may never want to take
anyone anywhere but I I know I don't I
know I don't but it's it's a very fine
and well-made car
thank hello uh welcome to uh Dallas
paste
uh we uh were going to have Cathy Lee
Crosby on the show today but uh she
couldn't make it she was going to talk
about her uh uh new exercise video this
would have been real good
um but uh we got somebody to fill in at
the last minute um and my neighbor's
friend her name is
Michelle
well say some
something
dingdong uh do you uh so what are you uh
what have you been up
too
NADA that's Spanish for nothing
mhm what uh do you drive here or how'd
you get here
today I
walked it's about 20 miles but my car is
not working
so it was really important for me to be
here so here I
am uh I uh what do you do what's your
job I heard you're in the the food
industry yeah I'm a I'm a I'm a
server that's the 80s term for a
waitress well okay let's uh I think uh
you brought a clip to show us and I want
don't you uh well this is a a clip about
um it was a Friday and uh it was a
really busy lunch and okay that's enough
that's enough uh let's just take a look
at the clip all right
excuse me there you
go there you go no I didn't order this
yeah you did you said you wanted the
pizza no I believe I said fetan no I
heard Pizza I darling didn't I say fet
Manan she fet I I didn't know I'm sorry
we don't have any steak so you have to
try it at least I don't want to try it I
don't like pizza can if you please take
this
back just try it okay I don't want to
try it it's not what I ordered I'd like
I'd like can I see the menu then we
don't we went to the dinner
menu
oh just one more chance just just give
it a whir see what you think I don't
want to take it
back
wow well that was
uh that was really interesting thank you
I'm really proud of that clip in fact I
was thinking about submitting it to to
some agencies because I've always wanted
to pursue an acting
career what are you laughing about well
thank you for uh I think that's why you
asked me here because it's very obvious
that I have a magnin personality and
we'll be back next time with wait a
minute a real celebrity wait a minute
this what you talk about next time
byebye excuse me but I if the truth be
known you call me to be here as a guest
on this incredible show we we'll get you
a nice cheeseburger excuse
byebye hello welcome once again to
another doctor spinter minute this is a
new show and and people have been
calling and we've been getting letters
and things are happening um something
that is on the minds of all of us I'm
sure is a a problem that we have with
our scalps and that problem is called
dandruff if you have dandruff you
shouldn't be ashamed or you could be
maybe you should be ashamed you should
be always ashamed of something but
dandruff tells people that you you are
ashamed of something if you see someone
that has dandruff you know that they're
ashamed and you know that they are they
they are keeping their outer forces in
check and they know you know that they
know that they they are trying to be
tight and they're they're aware of their
problem dandruff is very easy to spot
you it's little flakes collecting on on
the on the shoulders and on the necks
and and if you if you if you shake your
head you can
see death Tech is there when you need
it and when you need death Tech there's
nothing like
it the highest kill ratios of any
weapons in the
industry and a commitment to Excellence
shared by each and every single employee
of death
Tech The Pride goes far deeper
than the metal casings on the
bombs The Pride goes down
deep into the software that goes into
each and every one of our missile
Delivery
Systems you can be proud that a company
like death Tech is working to serve you