[Applause]
[Music]
Gary yeah Tom I have something I need to
tell
you what
[Music]
this there
[Applause]
tired of being
overweight it's being fat holding you
back are you sick of never getting laid
well then you're a perfect candidate for
weight loss therapy hi I'm Dr Steve
Slater and I've been performing a
variety of non-surgical techniques to
lower your butter rate since
2012 maybe you should call that guy I'm
actually in really good shape I do
push-ups andial
I was think about going I could friend
you're
not
your meeting you have a problem is the
first step I'm proud of you arms come
with you isol the way to have awesome
upper body call now if you're not so
physically unfit that you're physically
unable come on
Alan all right all right what brings you
lard asses here wait let me guess you're
fat that's right that's why we're here
not me I'll be the judge of fat have you
heard of BFI of course you haven't I
invented it behavioral fatness index
because your fatness isn't based on how
much you weigh or How fat you are it's
based on how you behave is that
scientifically accurate take this quick
questionnaire it's got simple questions
on it so I can calculate How fat you are
like how do you handle stress yes does
your mom still love you why not that's a
good one it's a really good one when you
answer that then I'll know how we can
change you from lard ass to spelt get
started all right okay the test has
already begun going fine should we just
fill it out right here like we go in the
lobby just this is the lobby okay just
fill it out WR
faster He-Man or
Thundercats I went He-Man Dolph lungren
have you seen a can around here going to
take a leak maybe cut some weight before
we weigh in don't you just go through
the fence no's look they'll see that
you're behaving like a thin man who pees
through fences okay I don't know it's
good call dud I'm throwing it out there
I could be wrong but just go
man plus Skeletor is just a [ __ ] see
here Gary Thunder Thunder Thunder
Cats good answer Gary here 5 six 195 lb
good good uh What do you do when your
cart is declined at the grocery store
answer get embarrassed and leave great
answer all right well Gary based on your
answers your BFI is 135 that's 15 points
below average you're in great shape let
me see your muscles man oh on oh yeah
hurts I do push-ups and situps oh I've
noticed and more importantly your BFI is
based on your mind being a spelt
man Tom you're fat as [ __ ] what yeah
your BFI is 203 that is fat as [ __ ]
you're fat I do yoga like every day is
it fat [ __ ] yoga no it's just the
regular kind cuz it seems like it is
it's just regular yoga well maybe that's
why you can fit your own head so far up
your ass okay that's not even possible
come on y it's possible I've seen it and
you wouldn't like it your behavior is
fat so so fat we need to find a way to
take your behavior and shape it up make
it more Gary less T First Step you need
to quit your job I don't have a job
that's the spirit now you need to stop
eating ice cream every time you're
stressed out okay but Gary eats ice
cream like all the time A lot of times
eats it and it's all gone and there's
none left for me exactly Gary eats it
all the time you only eat it when you're
stressed out which makes your BFI higher
it's different Tom it's different Tom
and lastly you need to start pursuing
your childhood dreams Gary wakes up
every day and tries to become what he's
always wanted to be you need to find a
way to become a Harrison
Ford Hat's a little small
but ah
oh oh dude oh my ear oh dude you hit me
in the ABS those aren't ABS that's just
fat that's great Tom way to assert
yourself very healthy for your BFI
where's the ice cream Gary why don't you
go get me some ice cream Gary it's cuz
it's all inside of you fatty about that
stop hit me in the hit me in the muscle
fatty the muscles
butter no
no job Tom high
five you deserve a low five oh uh no
yeah no
yeah guess who's BFI it's the lowest of
all
boom pounding it every time you balance
you increase my abs my abs can't handle
How fat you are great work get up all
the fat get up great work oh you're fat
great work get up I'm up Gary you up or
you down are you up or you down I'm up
are you up or are you down I'm up go
down you seem down are you up or are you
down are you up or are you down are you
up or are you down are you up or down
don't kiss kissing is not a way to
Fitness I thought you were trying to
kiss me I wasn't trying to kiss you I
was trying to talk to you thought mouth
I wanted to talk to you mouth to mouth
let you know
you all right now that we're relaxed I
want us to go to our place where we're
winners where we're not disgusting bags
of [ __ ] easy are you in a thin Place
Gary
totally here's your
reward how you doing
Tom uh really really good maybe uh maybe
I could have some of that ice cream
too Tom I'm going to ask you a question
what would Harrison Ford do what would
Harrison Ford
do
maybe maybe this hey off
my [ __ ] you Tom that's not how you churn
butter it's not how you do it
[Music]
physic
I'm missing
[Music]
there's nowhere left to go you got the
wrong man I'm not the fat one Dr Slater
I don't
care give me my ice cream back Tom why
so you can eat it all without sharing
just give it back I I earned it [ __ ] you
Gary don't throw it don't throw it Tom
[ __ ] I know what you're about to do
don't throw it
Tom that's my ice cream [ __ ] you Gary no
[Music]
[Applause]
Gary yeah Tom there's something I need
to tell
you what you're a fat l
I do eat a lot of ice cream huh all I
ever wanted was for you to share it with
me I don't think I can do
that we'll just buy twice as much there
you
go you guys really like ice cream huh
damn right cuz cuz we're ice cream
arist it's all about the hunt when
you're digging for chunks cuz I'm an ice
cream AR
just getat your shovels and spad cuz
we're about to get paid we don't go to
Egypt to find treasure in a trunk our
Treasure's in New York super fudge chunk
just chilling on the couch with my
digging team trying to unearth some
cookies from this cream can't wait to
find out what goodies are buried ooh a
cherry thanks Cherry I'm like Indiana
when I get that Jones for some americone
to call my own to the freeer
or as I call it the holy land where the
goods are buried in Cold Cream not hot
sand I've been searching for The Grail
going near and far what's the holy grail
and ice cream a whole godamn heat bar
king T we're an oatmeal cookie we travel
to his pyramid and have a look because
we're tomb Raiders we collect all the
booty from the peanut butter cups to the
Tutti frut cuz we're ice cream
archaeologists digging through Swirls
and chocolate chip because we're ice
cream
archaeologists who don't know how to
spell
archaeologist what's your favorite
flavor Pistachio Pistachio Pistachio no
Pistachio Pistachio when I go down on
Pistachio Pistachio I come up pistachio
Mustachio CH on sale yo two for five
bucks that's a good deal we better not
[ __ ] this up only six per customer man
ain't that simple I want to eat Chubby
Hubby hubby till I'm full and chubby
then take my girl to the Clubby take her
home let her rubby ice cream on my
chubby I thought you liked ice cream
that's why we're in such good shape
right cuz we're like sure of
ourselves uh no you you both look pretty
fat to me but I'm not a
doctor wait but yeah it's weird cuz your
name is Dr
Slater I made that up
do you want to be you or do you want to
be someone wrapped in fat that's
you oh no my clothes are so dirty time
to wash them on this
washboard so time to get off of that ass
and turn that butter
[Music]
I want him so high that people think
that you're stepping cuz you are you're
stepping out of your old body into a new
one
[Music]
what