[Applause]
hey
Gary you noticed something weird going
on with Neil he's always acting weird
yeah but he just seems a little more
upset than usual why what's he
doing pretty sure he killed
himself what a goofball
[Music]
I didn't think it would come to this but
Tom and Gary's album isn't selling well
my car needs new tires and I can't
afford them the toilet only flushes if
you hold down the handle it's super
annoying I ordered a new charging cable
for my smartphone but I think it was
made in China because it only charges my
phone up to
85% the goddamn kitchen table is still
wobbly and I'm tired of putting coasters
under the short
leg I guess what I'm saying is I've had
it up to here
well I don't suspect there was any fou
play it just seems like your stepdad had
it up to here he sure did yeah what are
those oh that's our El you want one how
much
$15 no I'm good two for 10
no hey um do you think we'll ever be
able to make toast again Tom no it's all
right I actually get this question a lot
I think that toaster died when your
stepdad did the good news is that Target
has toaster on sale the bad news is they
don't sell step dance and you just
murdered
himself so if you guys made any funeral
arrangements
yet well yeah yeah we'll figure it out
we'll figure it
out we'll figure it out
thanks for being my
stepdad got
anything
uh see you later
[Music]
Neil you don't mind it
it's good it's just bread it hasn't even
turned into toast
yet well go buy one oh okay hey Neil we
need to borrow money to go buy a new
toaster oh wait you're
dead you know what what we're going to
fix this
thing fix this thing and we're going to
make some [ __ ] toast
[Music]
toast it toast it do it make it toast go
go go toast
it I just really wanted toast and I
thought we fixed it I know guess it just
wasn't meant to
be I am a Chinese hunk of
junk what did you say Toaster I don't
work because I was made in China I've
had it up to here with Chinese [ __ ] Neil
we did fix it I'm sorry that I killed
myself I'd really had it up to here with
everything but now I'm back as a toaster
does that mean you can make toast if you
want toast I would buy American Neil we
always got our money from you yeah we
don't have
any
whoa here's a 20 get one that does
Bagels too and get something nice for
yourself your stepdad is the coolest I
know anything for you
Slugger eight settings eight different
settings USA USA USA USA USA USA
USA
USA us
he seemed
happy we just bought that
toaster looks like your toaster stepdad
killed
himself again with a
toaster you know thank you officer great
job thank you thank you appreciate it
okay all right yep it's okay I know I
know these things happen did good this
is the worst part of my job right here I
mean this this feels nice but you did a
great job telling you guys that hurts
you did a great job thank you
have a good day
officer it was
short but while it
lasted it was so sweet you were the best
step there that ever
had we'll miss you
[Music]
I'm sorry I killed myself again I'm
better now that's great Neil we love
you you're my stepdad and I don't want
to lose you again I love you too but I
have had it up to here with
something
what tell
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah a lot of people ask
me if I think it's weird that my
stepdad's a
toaster I mean yeah I think it's weird
I mean he's a toaster
[Music]
man but there are cool things about it
too like he takes me to ball games
and teaches me about life things that my
real dad didn't do for me and so what if
he's a toaster he's still my
stepdad my stepdad's a toaster I don't
care my stepdad's a toaster and I don't
care [ __ ] makes toast like every
m I stepped as a toaster and I don't
care stepped as a toaster and I don't
care [ __ ] makes toast like every
morning I've got these settings and I'm
stainless steel I make one part of your
day's first meal I drive Tom and in my
Honda cord I drive [ __ ] crazy with my
toast bagels and toast bagel and toast
those are the things that I make the
most bagel and CH bagel and CH those are
the things make the my stepdad's a
toaster and I don't care my stepdad's a
toaster and I don't care [ __ ]
makes toast like every morning my
stepdad's a toaster and I don't care my
stepdad's a toaster and I don't care
[ __ ] make toast like every
morning women see me and they fall in
love bread inside that I pop it up cover
it in jelly it in butter color it in
chocolate I can be the perfect lover
blender just mix it
up just straight up suck microwave ain't
cool to me and juicers
like3 my step's a toaster I don't care
my stepdad the toaster I don't care my
stepdad the toaster and I don't care
[ __ ] makees toast like every
morning my step danad a toaster I don't
care my step's a toaster I don't care my
step a toaster I don't care [ __ ]
makes toast like every
morning if you're an
appliance and you ain't a
toaster you ain't
[ __ ] but a kitchen coaster remember that
than you get it or did you set it and
forget it what else you got a coffee
maker that bruise too hot I'll make you
a popart when you're Bor just get off my
co you
just get off
myu get
off get off my toast I'm only 6 in
tall but I'm going to PL your
girlfriend's W my stepdad's a toaster
and I don't care my stepdad's a toaster
and I don't care [ __ ] makes
toast like every morning my stepdad's a
toaster and I don't care my stepdad's a
toaster and I don't care [ __ ]
make toast like every morning my
stepdad's a toaster and I don't care my
stepdad's a toaster and I don't care
[ __ ] makes toast like every
morning my stepdad's a toaster and I
don't care my stepdad's a toaster and I
don't care [ __ ] make toast like
every morning my stepdad's a toaster I
don't care my stepdad's a toaster I
don't care my stepdad's a toaster and I
don't care [ __ ] makes toast
[Music]
USA
USA USA
USC USC
[Music]
what