[Applause]
God damn you bill
[Music]
collector hey can you wait just hold on
a second
[Music]
oh yeah he's here just a second Gary
telephone Valley Meadow
South met South High yeah know I know
sorry dude that was a bad one it was bad
I'll open the window here you go
uh hi this is
Gary yeah I don't normally sub at Valley
Meadows South you need to be the Fish
Out of Water substitute who miraculously
saves their life in one day you show up
and Inspire them to rise to new heights
you need to inspire them to rise up dude
rise up out of the ghetto keep them all
sing
exactly you need to show them how much
talent they have give them a
reason to want to
live I'm only going to be there one day
yeah that's one day where you'll either
give them a reason to want to live or
get stabbed I don't want to get stabbed
now choice is up to you
dude Mr Johnson who's that guy damn it
who's that I don't know that guy I don't
know that guy not all right I got to
split man I'm not here okay right have a
good day okay thanks ma'am I'm off
to not get stabbed go get him
champ not get stabbed today Mr Johnson
he's not here oh then you don't mind if
I take a look around you don't have the
authority to do that I'll have you know
that in 1996 Mr Johnson signed up to be
in Columbia House and in return received
five free CDs including crash by Dave
Matthews Band Tracy Chapman the reality
bite soundtrack The Fuji and Sarah
Mclaughlin Sarah mlin wasn't for
me I got to
go
Mr shinen Chen
shensi if you can't pronounce that call
me Mr
s you will respect
me because I'm not not here to be your
friend all right I'm not here to teach
you about
calculus or
whatever and I know that you guys don't
have it like the kids at North Valley
Metals high so I'm not going to treat
you like North Valley Metal high
students I'm here to show you how to get
out of the
ghetto and be
somebody see but this is calculus we
were talking about anti-derivatives
yesterday looks like we've got a smart
ass in here but we shut your mouth essay
you think I'm going to take this like
I'm just like the other teachers you
push around cuz I'm not all right you
try to stab me I'll stab you first oh my
God can anyone in here
sing pregnant girl can you say I'm not
pregnant yeah well No One Believes that
you little strumpet so start singing
[Music]
okay you need to come out sooner or
later I'll never pay you pig then we
want the CDs back not going to happen
they're gone I sold them years ago
everyone seems to say that m Mr Johnson
but I always get what I came for where
are the Fuji not this time champ you'll
never find
[Music]
them we got to rise up R rise up out of
the ghetto you got to rise
up rise up and be somebody stop doing
ghetto drugs and stop being pregnant
thugs got to start getting better grades
and stop giving each other Aid good job
guys I'm proud of
you hey students hey principal Peters
how's it going today weird
inspirational all right uh kids sit down
uh dress can I uh talk to you for a
minute
yeah so what's up so you've got these
kids singing songs to inspire them out
of poverty yeah it's working I mean just
because the other teachers aren't
showing these gangsters how to get out
of the ghetto doesn't mean I'm not going
to this is calculus as a matter of fact
it's AP Calculus these kids aren't high
risk yeah right all right look I mean I
appreciate your enthusiasm but I mean
let him do some homework or I don't know
teach him some
math okay I think I got you hom okay
good
glad all right yeah just let him do some
[Music]
homework we don't want to hurt you
Johnson we just want the Fuji
[Music]
it's my Fuji you didn't pay for them Mr
Johnson that makes it our Fuji okay
first of all it's Fuji and you probably
don't even like the Fuji it's not my job
to like the Fuji Mr Johnson it's my job
to get them back fine
here this is just a y cleff album he's
one of the Fuji I need all the Fuji all
right another Fuji coming out
this is just a DVD copy of Sister Act 2
back in the habit starring whoopy
Goldberg yeah Lauren Hills in it she's
also one of the Fuji that's only two
Fuji you're still short one
Fuji every time your name was brought up
I would act all nonchalant in front of
an
audiance like he was just another shorty
I put the
naon but uh truth be told you threw me
for a loop it's Hove
I'm too old to be fronting what I'm
feeling Denzel like you ain't appealing
when you
are
Stunting Like You Ain't My only girl
when you are I'm ready to stop when you
are does anyone know what Jay is trying
to say in this piece again Mr s this is
calculus I don't know how else to reach
you kids I thought some rap lyrics would
inspire you and get you more interested
maybe he's trying to say that he's too
old to be playing cool and it's time to
settle down hey someone's getting an a
can we please learn some math oh now we
want to do math all right yeah I'll show
you math uh x + y uh carried by a equals
Fuji do you guys know about the Fuji
here's a math equation for you how many
mics do we rip on The
Daily say me say Min
Moy many many
many how many mics is that so Mr hon
will be back tomorrow
right
yeah unless he's sick again
or maybe he's on
vacation all right Mr Johnson I have
somewhere else to be so you win this
time
busted
we meet at last give me the Fuji they're
my Fuji they're my Fuji they're my Fuji
oh
yeah oh oh I'm sorry I didn't know I
thought there was a no I thought no
that's fine no you just buy stuff
without paying for well you know what
they been mine for a long time love the
FI and you don't even care about the FI
so I
guess I care about the f I don't Jesus
Christ man what the [ __ ] D dud fi okay
okay give them okay take the Fuji take
the godamn F just don't are we done here
yes yes I say you're sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry say I'm sorry Colombia house I'm
sorry colia
house I'm
sorry just please just go just take the
CDs and go
really hurt my cheek skin
man I hurt your cheek skin for the
Fuji who am
I I'm a
monster you know I really hate this job
you know like all I do is collect CDs
and try and Shore up assets yeah yeah no
I dig that man music industry is tough
right now tell you what
I've got the reality bite soundtrack
okay I'll give it back to you there's a
Lisa Lobe track on there it's really
gotten me through some tough times
thanks you got it man so you have the St
mlin then
too [ __ ] you
Kevin [ __ ] you
Tom
H oh friendship man like when there's a
number in between one of those half
circle
things that's what an integer
is you guys may know it as an integer
what are you even talking about you you
guys wouldn't sing so I'm going to get
real with y'all I'm going show you about
integers hey hey no come on
guys come on what the hell is going on
in here I was trying to teach the kids
about inas all right k let just do
homework for the rest of the hour and I
promise you you won't see Mr s here at
Valley Meadow South again unless it's as
a
[Music]
[Laughter]
janitor I might show up at your class on
any given day your teacher might be sick
or they might be on vacation we'll have
fun cuz when it comes to substitutes I'm
number one one one one every day I come
to class to pour out my knowledge so
that you kids can get your very first
choice of college but none of you listen
and for that you should a poge get wise
and start applying your minds don't
substitute
respect for me and you will find that I
will leave no
child be yo Tyler guess what this waps
for you remember when you threw that
giant ball of glue at the map of North
America that wasn't cool it took me 3
hours to get it clean after school Tyler
you really need to take the advice I
gave you it's time to grow up and modify
your behavior who knows the substitute
might turn out to be your savior Jesus
was a substitute teach you too don't
substitute
respect for me you will find that I will
leave no
child when your teacher doesn't leave me
with a lesson plan I have to improvise
by the seat of my pants and when I'm all
out of ideas and I'm all out of stuff
guess what we'll play heads up seven up
I know you all think my life is pathetic
and funny well you're right my job sucks
and I don't make any money but someday
you'll know at least I can hope that
pathetic loser Mr s was actually dope
don't
substitute
respect for me to a find that I will
leave no child behind don't
substitute
respect for me to find that I will leave
no child behind I'm sure some of you
girls have a little student teacher
Crush I mean why wouldn't you I'm smart
and stuff but I'm sorry all you ladies
cuz that would be illegal plus you
laughed when I was down by the parking
lot seagull
[Music]
you got to be tough as Nails bro pretty
much what I did today you know who else
was tough as nails today [ __ ] Kevin
yeah yeah yeah it's pretty sweet I
almost I almost killed him see Lauren
help right there it's Lauren Hill that's
Lauren Hill I told you I didn't even
know who Lauren Hill was until like
she's a Fuji she's one of the Fuji I
don't care about the Fuji at all the
Fuji Fuji Fuji I don't I I can't I don't
care no Fuji my boss said Kevin he's
like go go get those Fuji and huh well
[ __ ] that guy it's fui man yeah [ __ ]
that guy fui
he's probably wondering where I am I've
been here since like 10: