she married into a really conservative
family my sister really really
conservative which made me nervous for
the wedding and the like close- in-laws
seemed great but like I think it was
like an uncle-in-law or something um
that I heard talking to another one and
and he
said I don't know how I feel about this
gay marriage thing if we let a woman
marry a
woman what's to stop a man from marrying
his Pig
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't know why he's so terrified that
pig [ __ ] are going to inundate local
legislature with marriage certificate
request I don't picture Pig [ __ ] the
settling down type kind of think it's
the
point [ __ ] a pig is the lack of Comm
I don't want to be swine exclusive
though when it comes to any inner
species intercourse I don't think the
future is on your mind you
know think you're dreaming of a nice
house with a big backyard and a picket
fence so your wife can run around but
not
away my goat husband left me oh did you
have an argument no I left the gate
open come back
[Laughter]
it came at a really interesting time my
sister's wedding
and because there was this case before
The Supreme Court uh it was called
Masterpiece Cake Shop versus the state
of
Colorado and if you don't know what it
is uh essentially these two dudes were
getting married and they wanted to get a
cake and they went into masterpiece cake
shop and the guy who ran that was like
no no gay cakes here I don't like gay
things
you named your cake shop Masterpiece
calm
down and they wanted to get a cake and
he was like no I'm not going to do it
because making a cake is my art and I
don't want my art to serve something I
don't
support which I am in full support of
the culinary arts I think they're
wonderful and fantastic but the last
wedding you went to who made the
cake yeah you don't you don't know you
know the only person who really cares
about a cake at a wedding is your
diabetic Aunt Debbie who's like is it
[Laughter]
moist no my Apple's great is it moist
how it also kind of like his argument
presupposes that every gay wedding is
just themed gay
which is not true gay weddings have a
bunch of themes there's Wizard of
[Applause]
[Laughter]
Oz there's Melissa
eich there's
woodworking that's a bisexual Theme by
the way it goes
I don't want to get down on marriage I
think marriage is great uh I was close
to marriage once with an ex we'll call
her Amanda even though her name's
Melissa
yeah I'm kidding I'm kidding Amanda
Melissa actually are the names of two of
my exes but I would never do that I
would never really name someone and then
talk about them on stage so Amanda
Melissa if you're listening this isn't
about you it's about Chelsea so Chelsea
and I
h