you better run and don't stay around
here don't want to do nothing don't
disappear the fire in your eye just do
it you please just beat it just beat it
beat
it fancy fancy R fancy R no no no it's
eat it just eat it it's weird out fancy
Ray yeah FY R what is this the land of
adjectives before names is this the
Twilight Zone no no no this is time to
get down with it hello my name is fancy
I am the best looking man in comedy talk
show host AD DI doen The Only Exception
is me cuz I've got the gro of moves and
looks and this incredibly Charming
personality now when I first saw s Jesse
Raphael my eyes they started to Sag I
said the networks are trying to fool us
that ain't nothing but down H dress and
drag now some people think Oprah Winford
is the best they think oppr wears the
crown well she may be the heavyweight
champ honey I'm the best under 200
lb stay tuned I'm fancy R it's time to
get down with
it I said get
down come on
baby all right this is fancy Ray MCL the
best looking man in comedy I speak with
Clarity I'm here with the man of
hilarity he has made millions of dollars
doing his great song parodies Mr Weird
Al Yankovic no Q cards or anything what
a guy look at this guy man what a guy I
say that all the time man you copy that
for me I've got it trademarked really
yeah oh my Lord me some royalties on
that one I think I do man I'mma pay the
royalties real soon thank you my man now
my name is fancy Ray and I could have
had a lot of different names like
flamboyant way Ray fantastic Ray infer I
want to know how' you get the name Weird
Al well Al short for Alfred so I just
shortened it a little bit mhm uh-huh can
we on a first adjective basis yes oh
thanks fancy thank you weird a this is
feel like I'm at home you do man very
kind of home you can be my homeboy I am
your homeboy and sometimes a home girl
oh but that's later on another part of
the show where' the weird part come from
oh uh that was just an a name when I was
doing a radio in college it was the
Weird Al show every Saturday night
because they played kind of weird music
and it just kind of stuck mhm where' the
fancy come from the fancy come the
flamboyant part of me I understand that
in the fertile part uhhuh and the
yeah and fragrant but you're not close
enough but go the last name is Yankovic
yes yeah y yov my fault you're come from
a musical family why yes my mother
played the nose flute and uh my dad
played the lottery no no no your dad is
the legendary Nick Yankovic yeah that's
right no no no he's legendary to me but
he's not famous you're thinking of
Frankie Yankovic America's P King you
not related to him not as far as I know
we're old friends like this fancy Ray
however not related in a bloodly like
way okay so when did you start pursuing
your career music well I've been doing
this for a long time but I only started
getting serious about it about 15
minutes ago it just kind of overwhelmed
me I said now I'm really going to be
serious about this so this is the new
Sirus L the sirious L U well I got my
record deal I've been doing this for a
long time I'm an old man fancy Ray no my
first record came out uh 15 years ago
when I was but a teenager back when they
had such a thing is a vinyl 7in um
record a single uh I had my balona which
was Rec a parody of my shirona by the
Knack and it was recorded in the
bathroom across the hall from that
campus radio station that I worked at
really uh-huh I wouldn't lie to you I
wish you'd believe me there has to be
some trust I me there is some trust here
out okay I feel the trust feel that
trust and I smell the
musk we're going to keep talking until
it hits dust man now so now you like you
you're DJ and you're making these parody
songs for the radio station yes how does
now a lot people radio DJs do that how
do you do that from a local radio
station and make it to a commercial
success uh well I was getting airpl uh
nationally through the Dr Demento radio
show he he was on a couple hundred radio
stations and he's still doing quite well
around the country uh and uh I got a lot
of exposure on that and became kind of a
cult figure uh on the show and uh got
kind of a a fan base and then started
hitting the record companies over the
head with a piece of salami until they
sign me okay and the next hit that you
had come out was Another One Rides the
Bus uhhuh and that was a big hit which
was of course the song uh a parody of
another one uh bites the D called
Another One Rides the Bus right what was
it about song parodies why did you pick
song parodies as your vehicle for your
music um it was just kind of a accident
almost I was I something i' done since I
was 12 years old and uh just made fun of
the songs on the radio I think I think
most people go through that stage it
only lasts a couple weeks but in my case
I'm still going through it mhm so you're
12 what was the first song You parody at
12 oh boy I I I have a big mental block
about that they're pretty bad they're
pretty bad they're pretty bad see the
thing that's really unique about your
songs they've held up so well over time
and I think part of the reason is is
because they are so good you know my
balona means as much to me today as it
did 15 years ago it's still it's a
Timeless song it is it's has something
to say to everybody uh do you write all
your own lyrics yes I do now the big hit
that really really like exploded you and
made you just the superstar that you are
was of course Michael Jackson's Ed it
well yeah beat it which I yes that that
kind of changed me into an overnight
cartoon character I all of a sudden I
was the eat it guy mhm mhm what did that
do to BR your career well it made me
recognizable actually uh kind of helped
me get permissions cuz I do get
permission when I do the parodies and up
until Ed it it was a little bit
difficult because people didn't want to
return phone calls from some guy named
Weird Al Yankovic you know but after
Michael Jackson gave his permission it
was really the the magic key in the in
the in the lock of people were saying oh
well if Michael Jackson thinks you're
okay I guess you're all right okay you
can do it right do a lot artists turn
you down not anymore no they they want
you yeah now I heard that we got local
Superstar out here in town that actually
turned you down oh you do
yeah that's the rumor yeah the symbol
guy you know the symbol guy yeah look
like has use the bathroom all the time
I'm talking
yeah yeah that guy that guy yes what
song of his were you trying to do oh
there there are several over the last
decade or so that I wanted to do but he
well I hope I'm not giving away any
secrets he doesn't have much of a sense
of humor
no well you got a great sense of humor
we're going to take another look at
another clip we're going to be right
back with Weird Al yank of it tell them
to stay tuned tell them to get down with
it okay stay tuned get down with it
won't
you my my my weird
H you know the problem with this country
is people like you what do you mean
people like you what because I'm black
you some kind of racist bigot or
something no no no you're probably on
welfare no I'm not on welfare I got a
job and I pay my taxes well I pay my
taxes too do but I like to take a peek
of your criminal record wait a minute
you're going a little getting a little
carried away here I've never committed a
crime I'm just in college trying to get
an education and if that's a criminal
offense then I'm guilty yeah but what
about drugs but you do drugs I may have
experienced with drugs before but have
you well uh you know yeah yeah are you
doing drugs now no no not now me neither
I'm just trying to prepare myself
economically and mentally for the future
well that's what I'm trying to do am my
kids too well I guess we got something
in common don't we now the point of this
skit is this we all have common ground
look you're white you're
black but neither one of us is as pretty
as you shake hands stay tuned I'm f is
time
[Applause]
to hi this is Gloria dyam and when I'm
in the Twin Cities I watch the fancy Ray
Show all right this is fancy Ray the
best looking man in com we're live on
location here at the State Theater with
the wonderful talented wacky Weird Al
Yankovich yes we are he tell the truth
oh man yeah he's getting it right you're
getting much better I'm getting better
oh if I get better that'd be scarier o
that would scare me it would scare you
now on every album that you put out you
include original music on your album oh
yes it's about half original is is that
really important is that something that
you want to see happen comose from here
from my
pecs can I touch your pecs no oh okay
but the PEX is where it comes from yes
with the with the with the original
music is but that's what you want you
want to pursue that more well no I mean
uh I I like doing the parodies and I I
like the idea of having like a kind of a
50-50 mix with the originals and the
parodies um and the the originals are
hopefully funny uh as well uh I just
wish they'd be a little bit more popular
because to this day people say you know
the parodies are funny but you ever
think about writing your own music right
and then I have to hurt them badly
really see I mean in the music
profession of course it's known for the
one hit wonders like that they're gone
you make a hit and you're gone you
disappeared you're gone but you've had
longevity I think with parody I would
expect it maybe one hit if you got lucky
maybe two but you've had longevity I'm a
freak of nature yeah it it was actually
very difficult for me to get signed to a
record deal because uh what I do is
considered novelty music which is kind
of a derogatory term because it implies
one hit wonder because that that is
basically historically how it works
somebody will come along with a funny
song and it'll be a huge hit and then
you'll never hear from him again and
I've somehow managed to Buck the trend
and and you know have somewhat of a
career for close to 15 years what do you
attest to that um I eat from the four
basic food groups every day really
didn't as simple as that and I had all
the bones removed from my body
surgically really yeah see you know it's
very
yes okay now I guess I got to do
something
now oh my
Lord Weir now we're starting to get
where the name came from now I suppose
so the weirdo part what is a typical day
like for weirdo there is no such thing
as a typical day every day is special
and unique is that right this is the the
uniquest day I've ever had why is that
because of this interview this is the
Pinnacle of my existence on this planet
this is the Apex this is the greatest
moment of my life sitting here talking
to you a lot of PE celebrities I've
interviewed it felt exactly the same way
that you
do we had another great accordion player
on the show uh Judy Tuda oh I love Judy
Dolly Judy She's My Pal she is yeah
she's she's kind of different though she
is different she is different like her I
like her better after the operation
uhhuh
yes now I see all this flamboyant energy
but I mean like when you go back to the
Dress room are you like a loner and you
sit all by yourself and you and you like
get really quiet and yes do you have a
girlfriend that's the deeply
introspective ow you know the AL that
nobody know thank you for digging deep
and peeling back the layers and exposing
the real ow that Nobody Knows the deeply
introspective L yes see you're a deep
guy see I see all the wackness but I see
a serious side to your nature I'm way
profound give us something profound for
my viewers out there give us something
really profound life is like a bowl of
three-legged
salamanders swimming around in an
infinite ocean of cherry
Kool-Aid okay that's that's that's Al's
philosophy let me tell you my philosophy
if life's AA cherries I said oh
someone's got to be the whipped cream wo
doggies okay so you're pursuing the
music now in fact now Michael is a big
suppor of yours why is Michael's Music
so good for you to parody what's well
Michael uh obviously is extremely
popular he's got a lot of interesting
idiosyncrasies to play off of and uh
he's got a great sense of humor he
allows me to do the parodies and he gets
the joke and you know he's he's a nice
guy has anyone that you did a parody of
and after they heard the song didn't
like what you did with their song Never
every time somebody's given me
permission to do a parody they've always
been happy with what I've come up with
some not you've never done a rap parody
or have you oh I have done a few yeah um
see Gerardo and Hammer and uh the Chili
Peppers I guess kind of sort of
considered right right the Flint own
thing that you did you know what now
before we go here tonight you know what
I want to do I got a little song parody
that I wrote that I want to try oh no do
you get that before I do mine do people
like send you song parodies and say this
is a great song parody every day of my
life I'll be shopping for broccoli in
the frozen food section oh ow oh you
know I've been thinking of this idea for
the last 10 years oh I I got to tell you
oh this is great this is great tell me
yours I really can't wait
can this is I want the sincere L isn't
the sincere isere is he in there he's in
there please okay now if I need some
help though you know the Rolling Stones
beasts the burden uh can you give me the
music Rift and I'll do the song to it
okay I didn't bring my accordion though
uh we can just I'll give you the finger
snaps okay ready I never let my pizza
burn the crust is brown the cheese is
bubbling all I want is for you to serve
me so what do you think it's brilliant I
loved it it's coming on my neck I never
take I never take ideas from anybody but
that's going on my next album I loved it
it was
great well I really appreciate it out my
pleasure man what do we got to look
forward to do you ever think of like
doing a Mot toown like weirdal tribute
to mot toown that's my next album weird
tribute to mot toown out next month on
Scotty Brothers records look for no
actually I have a box set coming out
next month uh a four CD retrospective of
my career care as it is it's called
permanent record available soon at a
record start near you in fact I tell you
what they can check out the Electric
Fetus which of course is a big friend of
ours of course why not exactly man
exactly plug them right in I'm plugging
them right in man I'm plugging you in
and check out the new stuff in al man we
really appreciate it my pleasure good
time here and make sure you check out
Weird Al Yankovic oh got to go now
goodbye my my my My Weird Al stay tuned
in get down with it oh my name is
Charles fler and I'm your guest here in
the Twin Cities and guess what I'm
happening now with the man who can say
his name is fancy Ray the man who makes
the night turn to day the man who can
make the dead dogs play I'm talking
about Fancy Fancy Fancy Ray the man that
makes Little Richard look like a priest
the man that makes yogurt taste like
yeast the man who can take the moon from
the sky and put it into Hercules and
make the monkey cry
F all right I hope you're enjoying
tonight's show next week on get down
with the fancy race show we are
featuring former heavyweight champion of
the world Larry Holmes you can't believe
it we're going to take a little sneak
peek at that we'll be right back with
Weird Al Yankovic stay tuned honey and
get down with
it okay man can we get a closer let's
take a look at your fist and my fist
next to each other got small hand really
oh I got a see your hand is big as mine
but my hands are experienced oh that's
true that's the difference that's a
difference my hands are like lightning
uh with the jab here and if you don't
have you can have lightning but if you
don't know what to do with it you ain't
got nothing going to strike you man if
your' hands about the same size and I'm
almost as big as you I got a guy in the
back there that's going to put some
money up I like to challenge you to a
fight you and I here at Mystic Lake next
month on USA you know that's this would
be the easiest payday that I ever picked
up if we can do
that hi this is Bridget from Dream Girls
and when I watch TV I like watching Ray
Ray's gorgeous Ray's strong Ray's
handsome and I don't mean just any Ray
she means fancy Ray oh my my my stay
tuned It's Time to Get Down
[Music]
Down Rose are red violets are blue I
know I look good and honey I know you do
too I am the best looking man in comedy
before we go any further I want to thank
my fantastic sponsors I want to thank
Insight newspaper we can find my cable
cash schedule hereby J with Styles my
hairdo new location on 36 and pin in
North Minneapolis and also my new
sponsor the Electric Fetus you know what
if you need jazz blues rock and roll
whatever you need do like fancy Ray find
it at the fetus when you go check out
the underwriters do me a favor and fancy
Ray sent you all right so I hope you
enjoyed tonight's show make sure you
tune in next week to the fancy Ray Show
cuz honey who I'm there
baby we going to get down with
it bye