but one thing that I have never
understood is that male comedians will
get on stage and tell you gross things
gross things about things they done to
other people things they do at home
boogers they pick I don't know the color
of their poop just weird gross crap
right the drugs they take the
unemployment they collect I don't know
just and after the show inevitably women
will come up to and go oh my God you are
so funny hey like what is happening I us
I would see it all the time it would
make me really frustrated because a
woman standing on stage telling jokes
gets a look from the men in the audience
the same look you give babies screaming
a grocery store like oh I'm not taking
that home like that's the look you get
and I'm like I need to turn this around
for myself I need to Google how to get
more hits how to drive more traffic how
to get more clicks or click-throughs or
so I was reading on the internet I found
on cosmo. comom that they suggest if you
would like more male attention you
should consider bedazzling your hooa
have y heard of this madness have you
guys heard of this it's when you put
sparkles on your chicky Parts you know
like clitter
anybody okay they got
that to me that is overselling what
should be an already hot commodity right
thank
you that's ridiculous right because to
me a sparkly hoo-ha the kind that greets
you do are going come on in we've got a
show it's all so clean so clean it
glowes see what the hands yeah you got
it you got it my vagina has always been
way more like
a I didn't know you were going to be
here
today most people don't make it this
far she talks a
lot see the kind of guy I need to date
is this guy right here with his head and
his hands you sir you probably never
looked at a [ __ ] and said not enough
flare can't go there have you hell no
somebody raised him right it's a
generational thing that's clap for him
clap for
him he is a brave soul that's the kind
of soldier that shows up to the bille
taking that Hill no matter what the
conditions he's going in you guys he's
not bitching about the foilage or the
obstacles or
the conditions or anything he just got
invited to the party and he's here to
dance the problem are these young
Millennial guys the add can't pay
attention said shiny
[Laughter]
objects I feel like I feel like my
vagina deserves its own song should I
sing a song for
the my V is
like no Nobody Knows the Trouble I've
seen nobody knows my
sorrow if you wanted something sparkly
clean you should come back
tomorrow a sad vagina song you guys I
did that joke one night at the comedy
club my parents came from Alabama to see
me do comedy they were excited to see me
for the first time and do it I did that
joke and it went great I felt good until
I realized that my dad was in the
room he was sitting just off stage like
right there and I was like
Daddy I'm sorry I talked about my hooa
in front of all these strangers and my
dad yelled that's all right I've already
seen
it like oh my God not recently you guys
not recently
[Laughter]