[Applause]
ladies and gentlemen I want you to go
wild and crazy one of my favorite acts
on the circuit please welcome The
Fantastic Mr Glenn wo Ladi
[Music]
gentl
yes hello
hello how are you great
man me
too now this is my show it's called you
don't go to hell for eating elephants
it's all about the location of hell so
uh does anyone know where it is before I
waste an hour of your
time well good you will find this hour
entertaining and informational
uh so I'm just going to have to do a
quick little test of the audience off
the top uh little just just just to see
what your capabilities are as a group
you haven't worked together as a group
before have
you so you'll be finding out a lot about
yourself with this test
also what I'll do is I'm going to tell
two jokes of varying degrees of
difficulty to
understand
and at the end of those two jokes I will
put both reactions into the comedy
machine at that point I will decide
whether or not I can leave the big words
in I will now begin with what I like to
call
joke number
one I'm a big fan of the band France
[Music]
Ferdinand although part of me wants to
have them assassinated just to see what
would
happen some of you get
it some of you waiting for the next part
of joke
number B and
G you missed it like a
bus but fret not because if you did not
like nor understand joke number one you
have plenty of opportunity to make it up
with what I prefer to call joke number
two
it's a piece of advice goes out to all
the single Lads single fellas single
Chaps in the house
tonight if you're going to start dating
a new
girl make sure you date a girl who eats
a lot of
chilies the end of the evening you can
look at her and say oh come on darling
your ass already
hurts
[Applause]
let me just say right here right now you
guys did way better with joke number
two start of the first world war still
quite a mystery to many of
you ass seex however that's the
international
language I always feel sorry for the
people who don't get
either sodomy history you got to do
something to fill the gaps life without
a hobby can be a cold gray lonely
place and only one of them get you
kicked out of the
library not the one you
think there's a lot of lonely Librarians
out
there
sh you like a dirty don't you
yeah I can take it dirty but I'm not
going to
swear I'll refuse to swear not the
swearing bothers me just that I don't
understand current swearing because when
you swear you're trying to be
offensive but the things that swearing
describes don't offend
me like [ __ ] that's just sex and if that
bugs you there's a lot of proof of it in
the room here tonight
night and
[ __ ] although I don't eat
it doesn't bug me it's a natural process
of Life it'd be worse if it didn't
[Music]
happen oh Dad oh Dad I made a
mistake get a
[Applause]
stick that's why I think in the future
swears are going to have to become
longer to make them something something
that's actually offensive like you show
up late to a restaurant your buddy's
pointing at his watch going what the
legalized pedophilia of brain dead
children time do you call
this that behavior is so pretending your
girlfriend's vagina's a dead guy's eye
socket so you can
come you my friend are the guilty orgasm
of a rape
victim
what what let me just remind you right
here right now you had every opportunity
to laugh at joke number
one but you did not take
it I might go to hell for that
joke I don't know I don't know I think
about heaven and hell I'm not sure I
don't if there is a heaven I I don't
think I can get in I think I'm a bit
hooped when it comes that although
thinking about my family heritage I do
think there is is a very strong
possibility I can get into Jewish
heaven now we're not
Jews but hear me
out oh cuz my granny was from Estonia
and before World War II she lived in
Estonia cuz that's the way it worked
before the war where you were from
that's where you got to
live then then Hitler and sty had a
really big fight in her backyard and she
had to [ __ ]
up but she stuck it out for a while she
stuck it out for a while and uh in in
Estonia trying to just make her life
there and in that time she hid Jews in
her basement during the war which by the
way is the only time that kind of
behavior is
[Laughter]
acceptable
got to be a war
on and if it ends let them
go if they come back they're
yours but if they don't they never
were I think I'm in
man but the whole concept of heaven and
hell is a little weird you know like uh
the old Pope when asked about heaven and
hell not the new pope not the guy who
used to play Cliff from
cheers oh I was so excited when I heard
Cardinal ratzenberger was going to be
the new pope I thought is he going to
play it like Cliff or come up with a new
wacky character or just play it as
himself but in the end it turned out to
be just a Nazi
oh where's the funny
there
no the old Pope when asked about hell he
said hell is not a place hell is a
metaphor state of mind if you will and I
thought that was really cool coming from
the head of one of the world's largest
corporations don't get on me for that
even if you're Catholic you can't get
offended by that joke you you know the
Catholic church has too much money you
know your religion has too much money
money if out of nowhere the Swiss show
up and guard your
leader show up like big red
conquistadors for some reason
hello what are you guys doing here we
keep an eye on
him
why bad things happen if bad things
happen to
him put him in a bubble
hell is not a place it's a state of mind
I thought that was a totally cool thing
to say until you find out more about why
he actually said it apparently he only
said it cuz he was trying to use it and
Scrabble where you can't use a
person all right then someone [ __ ] him
up the bum is
that got take every damn joke with you
people don't worry if you're religious
this whole show is not going to be just
making fun of religion just the last 10
minutes um no I actually I think that
the religious have been getting a bit of
a rough ride lately honestly like that
whole thing that came up like whether or
not to rename Christmas winter
festival what do you guys think of that
[ __ ] yes you're right thank you for
thinking your answers at
me luckily I have the brain capacity to
pick that up I probably shouldn't use
that power for
comedy I think it's [ __ ] man you
can't change the name of Christmas
that's a religious Festival like I'm not
even a Christian well I was born
Christian well I was born and then told
about one religion so I picked
it and I wouldn't have done if I was a
child I'd been told just a little bit
about
Hinduism come on man blue monkey
blue monkeys and a guy with the elephant
for a head oh
yes none of this
imagery why have you forsaken
me
closer to what he probably said oh for
[ __ ] sakes Dad what's up with this
[Music]
[Applause]
[ __ ] when I get back up there I'm
painting my room
[Laughter]
black cuz I would have made a wonderful
Hindu it's a lovely religion it's very
peaceful it's what the world needs a
peaceful religion Hinduism is great do
we have any Hindus with us this
evening
H so what is it about all you people
that makes Hindu people so
uncomfortable Hinduism is a lovely
religion you don't have to freak out and
have a riot if somebody writes an
offensive cartoon towards your God you
don't have to burn down the countries
that you live in which I'm sure Tau the
Dan's of valuable cartooning
lesson oh please stop running down the
Middle
East we'll never do it
again you can't cuz the two sacred
animals are the cow and the Elephant you
can't have a ride every time somebody
puts one of those in a cartoon you'd
have to burn down Mumbai every time
someone released a Babar
annual The Far Side those would be worse
cuz those are actually
funny like a Hindu gentleman reading The
Far Side going yes I understand the
inherent
humor how would a cow learn how to drive
a tractor yes I know it's very funny
it's bloody
offensive that's my
God ah and I don't mind making jokes
that have Hindu people in them cuz I
know they're really cool about their
religion is like I'm from Canada but I
live here in London it's a long story
actually it's not one time I moved to
London that's a really short story isn't
it I should put some ninjas in
it bulk it
up yeah I was trying to get into London
right but at the city walls all these
ninjas were stopping me
yeah I I would step left and the ninja
would step right because in the story
that's how it would work if you're
facing a ninja if you step left and he
step left you go right
by know they were all there stopping me
so I in the end I took the tube
in you can't fight a train Dark
Assassin could
not but it was on that it was on that
tube Journey that I found out Hindu
people are really cool about their
religion because because there has been
an advertisement on the tube for 3 years
and I've never seen anyone Arc up I've
never seen anyone get upset in any way
and that advertisement is for elephant
car
insurance and there's folks animal which
gives you an idea of who this insurance
is angle towards someone riding the tube
going I wonder what the big elephant
thinks I should do about
caring he seems like such a wise
elephant
the Admiral and the parrot has many good
things to
say I think go stick with a trusty
elepant there spokes animal is an
elephant dressed up like a beef
eater can you think of a more offensive
image to a Hindu
person
then an elephant that apparently only
eats
cows it's still nothing man cool oh
trouble I put you on the ground the
water
bottle but back to my original point you
can't change the name of Christmas
that's a religious Festival then you get
the people on the other side of the coin
going oh no you have to change the name
name of Christmas because we are a
multi- religional
society and Christmas does not include
everyone all right but if you change the
name of Christmas to some ambiguous
description of what it actually is you
got to change the names of all the
religious
festivals
yeah
Ramadan that becomes Uncle Tubby's
midnight pig
out
[Music]
seems pretty inappropriate doesn't
it do w-e that becomes the festival of
light some coming on that one rash hos
Hannah Jewish New Year that just gets
shortened to happy Jew
year hey got to laugh the same amount of
that one as you did the
other don't go picking sides here
folks you get me branded in
islamophobe which is always a term
that's bothered me cuz it's not a phobia
if you know why you don't like
it don't get me wrong I'm not starting
to Rally here or anything I'm not
singling out Islam I would never do that
cuz there the
craziest I was going to pick on anyone
I'd pick on the
Buddhist what are you gonna
do
Bo you want me to stop Bud bu you want
to stop you want me to stop poking you
with my buddh poking stick buh bu you
you want me to you're not supposed to
want
anything now I'm talking about all the
major religions cuz they piss me off cuz
you see religious leaders of all
different backgrounds talking on radio
and television going I don't get it man
the media is always on our
case and we're merely about
peace and
love for the most part those books are
about peace and love until you get to
the part in all of them where they teach
you how to kill gay
people
well that's not very peaceful we're
loving is they get weird about it too
they're like take them to the city walls
and killed him with a
rock are you positive God said
that and if he did what context was it
in like was he drunk at a party or
something I tell you what to do to
fot
God go
home you want me to
go you want me don't touch me you want
me to go
home well then give me my keys in your
homeo God's going to drive the heaven
bus hole woo
get in I
drive no hazle to me I'm omnip
putan I'm new I'm I'm
[ __ ] the gay people should be quite
flattered about the religious' beliefs
of them because the religious all
believe that God controls everything he
makes everything he can fight anything
except his urge to make gay people
[Laughter]
is he sitting up in heaven going why am
I doing
[Applause]
this I can't stop
myself I just made a really big
one I am such a little
[ __ ]
I'm going to get some breeders to kill
them all that's what I'll
do stronger
than cuz I I think it's ridiculous the
way that the religious carry on about uh
gay people and it's it's true like it's
not just religious people it's religious
leaders and that's what pisses me off
it's like religious people go yeah yeah
you go say it we've all elected you you
go tell them how we
you know and it's a polarizing argument
too you can't be for the religious and
for gay people and the religious started
because if you think about it you'd
never accept it the other way around if
gay people showed up to schools and
handed out pamphlets to the children on
how to kill the
religious yeah here little Billy take it
it teaches you how to stab them right in
their [ __ ]
turban it's okay God hates
them
CU they they SP vile about it too they
just say horrible things the religious
like I've seen them on radios and TVs go
you want to know what God thinks about
gay
people
Aid yeah that's how God would work
sitting up in heaven going man I hate
[ __ ] and I don't mind killing half of
Africa to prove
it my God I'm in prison
size hey there was a bonus joke in there
for
you God said my
god well if you think about it if we're
supposedly Made In His Image and we have
a need to worship he could also have a
need to worship and there could be like
16 levels of God till you get to one
that's not
[ __ ] oh come on it would make a lot
of sense if you died and God was
[ __ ] ah
now I get
it that's why you love us
all come here big
girl oh you're
strong by the way you can't get offended
by that joke cuz no in that joke God is
the best and I made a [ __ ] person
the best so if you're bothered by that
joke you're bothered by a [ __ ]
person being better than you
I had a lawyer look at the
show I'll tell you the story uh about 10
years ago I was with some other
comedians in Vancouver we went for a
dollar a slice pizza in the West End of
Vancouver which is a very high gay
population area of Vancouver and the
nightclubs had just gotten out so it was
full of the high Gaye and it was
restaurant across the street from us uh
that had a high gay clientele and I
assume they were in there
eating these two Camaros pulled up from
the suburbs which is never the start to
a good story two big shiny cars came in
from out of town and the children
rejoiced and he screeched up and all
these guys got out of the Camaros and
they had baseball bats and sticks and
they'd come to do a gay bashing but they
they didn't know any gay people except
all the other people in the car with
them that's not really the kind of thing
a normal hetrosexual would do with this
Friday night like yeah let's go to where
they
live I'm going to punch one right in the
[ __ ]
[Laughter]
so they go to run in but they think it's
going to be like a Benny Hill sketch
from the 60s like they'll get in there
and all the gay people be oh my God
what's
happening and it was like a Benny Hill
sketch and that they ran in then ran out
one second later being chased by the
weapons they brought in with them by
some of the musli leather clad
homosexuals you've ever seen in your
life
it was [ __ ]
beautiful have you ever seen a man in a
slightly too small leather cop hat at a
jawy angle and a pink singlet with
muscles like a snake that swallowed a
pig chase a man with a baseball bat in
his hand and Chase the other man who has
a
[Music]
mullet it's [ __ ]
lovely if you get one tattoo in your
life at that
inage and the gay guys were cool too cuz
these guys were young who did it they
were like late teens early 20s and the
gay guys were smart cuz they didn't they
didn't actually hit the guys with the
sticks cuz bruises heel they did a much
smarter thing they beat the [ __ ] out of
the
cars cuz now these guys got to go home
to their parents house next morning
their dad's like
son what happened to the
car uh
uh
bikers yeah there was a a
biker um a
cowboy red
Indian army
guy
policeman why didn't he break it
up so no closer to hell but it doesn't
really matter because hell very soon
will be
obsolete through science you know we're
going to be able to live forever soon
which um I didn't plan
for that's a bit of an ominous Spectre
you know eternity Jesus I don't even
have enough money to make it to
60 this why vampires only go out at
night they can go out in the day they
just can't afford
to got to wait for them sweet night bu
prices yeah we're going to be able to
live forever soon you know cloning and
stuff suant are freaking out like
cloning in particular they say if they
catch a scientist trying to clone human
beings they're going to put them in jail
prison not really a threat to someone
who can clone
themselves we've arrested this guy five
times
keep showing up can't speak any language
and dies in two
weeks we are the baffled
authorities you watch my little
princesses clone's going to change
everything clone's going to change the
nature of
crime
soon in the
future which is the only place soon can
take place
soon in the future fingerprints are
going to be obsolete soon in the future
police show up to a crime scene they're
not going to look for the criminals
fingerprints they're going to look for
the criminal's DNA take that DNA give it
to the scientist scientist clone that
DNA next night on the
news police are looking for this
[Laughter]
guy ever seen this
guy he's a very bad
man
what are you doing to
me shut up
clone I don't even know we gave you a
tongue aren't newscasters horrible with
clones in the future that make you a
little sick to your stomach me too can
you promise me something find people at
Kingston in the future and you all get
your own news shows and it's going to
happen there's lots of
channels be dice to your clones love
them not sexually though I don't want to
hear about that going on but if you
think about it cloning will change the
nature of the single
scene oh okay I'll set the seed for you
singles bar Meat Market you're in there
there's a lovely young lady she hadn't
looked at anybody in the bar that night
except
herself she's just standing beside the
bar with tits like Hannibal lecor an ass
that could make
[Music]
[Laughter]
spaghetti and instead of having to pluck
up the
courage go talk to her and then it takes
just that little extra more courage to
ask her if you could buy her an
overpriced cocktail on your Vis of
gold then you got to ask her to dance
and show her that you can't do that
either you got to get enough gumption up
to take her out to dinner once again on
your Visa card then if that goes well
you have to meet her parents if that
goes well you have to pay for a wedding
if that goes well maybe you get some
fellatio instead of that old
rigoll cut back to that same night same
bar you creep up behind her
pluck a hair and
[Applause]
scattle what are you oh my god Treat Her
Like a
[Laughter]
Lady It's A Wig
idiot then he'll go home and clone a
horse
now be good to your
clones when we' solved the crime that we
needed them for and we take the clones
and then we can give them to a country
with a large land mass and a small
population like Australia
ironically there's some clone convicts
for you hope they don't take over and
ruin it like the last
batch
I'm sorry if there's any Australians in
tonight oh je he just pushed her in the
head that's all it takes to start a
movement yeah I hate them
too I'm a kiwi I
care you don't even deserve a seat
Aussie no I'm I'm I shouldn't do that
because I know the hell of racism
also being a
Canadian in
England we're not
wanted no man it's tough cuz you know
there's a certain sort of person that
will only attach hatred to Country now
because they know racism is wrong but
they don't mind doing it for a country
you know and then then they meet me and
they're ready to hit me with the barrage
of [ __ ] because they think I'm an
American then they find out I'm Canadian
and everything's lovey
duy until they ask me a question in
French and I can't answer it and I go
right back being
American oh he one of these Canadian hit
is how
tedious now I meet them man I meet them
and they're funny cuz you can see them
they line up in their head like you can
see they got like Terminator eyes a list
of all the [ __ ] all the countries in the
world they find out you're Canadian go
Canadian then all the [ __ ] that's wrong
with the world goes down this side and
it lines up and they know how they're
going to judge you they're ready and
they fix you with their Steely glare and
they go
ah Canadian
are seal
[Music]
[Laughter]
killer seal killer out of all the [ __ ]
that's wrong with the planet you want to
hang me on the hook for being a seal
killer I didn't personally kill any
seals and even if I had you don't know
what they're
like horrible little beasts they go to
the mall with no pants
on they smoke in the no smoking sections
they speak in a hacky hacky hacky
language they wear bowler hats at juny
Angles but it's not
enough cuz you don't no
you don't know anything about seals all
you see is the images of us beating the
[ __ ] out of them but they never show you
the pictures of how they were acting
right before that fight
started you want to know what seals are
like I'll tell you cuz you don't know
you sit in your Ivory Towers on your
high horses wearing your golden
hats this is
what this is what seals find
funny all right say your name is Jessica
all right you're a mid-30s young lady in
Canada you work in the accounts
Department of a small firm it's your
birthday your friends and colleagues
have taken you out to a fine Canadian
chain restaurant that dots the
landscape you're sitting there and it's
your friend your colleague and cuz it's
Canada seals you have to invite
them sitting there and everyone's
singing summer of
what it's the Prelude to happy
birthday how do you do
it they put down your Wayne Gretzky
shaped birthday
cake 99
candles and everyone singing happy
birthday and you're touched Jessica
you're touched right there because it's
been a hard year you know that he's gone
but you're going to raise it as your
own and everyone's singing happy
birthday and you really touch because
you
know this is the one time of the year
that everyone you know thinks about you
at the same time and wishes you Good
Will and it touches you it touches you
to the Bone so much so that you cannot
hide that tear of Joy that's been
welling up in your eye and as it rolls
over the precipice of your
cheekbone you see out of the corner your
eyes
see and they're nudging each
other are you going to do it this
time I'm not going to do it this time
you do do it this time maybe Hugo wants
to do it I'll do it I'll do it every
time cuz I love
it nine times out of 10 Jessica halfway
through happy birthday a seal will [ __ ]
that
cake fur icing humping
blood where'd the blood come
from well I'm sorry that happen one too
many times then the tall trees had to be
trimmed yeah we did it we did it we do
it again give us half a
chance you just you just don't
understand because this is what happens
you get your information from the media
well who feeds the media green
piece and who secretly runs green
[Music]
pece
think about it man what does green Beast
protect the ocean and the trees where
the seals live the ocean where they
spend the rest of their time in the
trees watching
you
oh what's
that PO part on
orders
I don't get that is that warehouse
humor I don't get it kills down at the
shop every time I say it every day I say
that joke and
people ah you from
London yeah I used to think London was
having I thought I'd invented it cuz
like in Canada I never go got to see
hockey games because uh they were on
while I was at work so then I just moved
across the globe and they start after
work
now and then like mushrooms became legal
and I was like how am I doing
this but then they made mushrooms
illegal again which I didn't understand
at all like the government said yeah you
can have them we all start a party and
they just came along
no you can't hand him
anymore why not we don't
know but I know why do you know why
mushrooms are illegal
again
America yeah America freaks out when any
of their little buddies liberalizes
their drug laws and they get you to
change their social programs which I
don't I don't know what they're scared
of the world descending into peace
like all I'm saying is if if if the
world's number one arms dealer tries to
get you to change your social programs
take a look at why you know mushroom
heads don't need a lot of
bazookas well we do but we just wouldn't
use them on each other I'm going to
shoot a
tree seal
[Applause]
yeah they freak out man like did you
know that America sends a senator they
send a general they s an Envoy every
year to Holland to get them to try to
change their drug laws and every year
the Dutch are so cool just sit there and
go [ __ ]
[Music]
off you're going to tell us how to live
we invented
you yeah we did you don't think so
Yankee I can call you Yankee right
Yankee Yankee Yan Doodle
Dandy means American right or we'll go
to the root of the word Yonka Dutchman
abroad yeah you didn't know
that
well I got a little story I want you to
take it back to New
[Laughter]
Amsterdam couple hundred years ago here
in Holland we had corporations running
the planet yes I know you think you
thought of
it and then we got involved in a lot of
really pointless expensive
Wars and we lost our Empire
heart and then we got really [ __ ]
liberal
enjoy don't get me wrong man I'm not
trying to start an anti-American thing
because I'm not I'm not anti-American
like I quite like them but you see like
being Canadian we've made fun of
Americans for years years and years and
years and you know everyone just sort of
started jumping on board now but that's
why we're really good at it but it goes
too far sometimes like you're just like
having like a fun time teasing America
and then you know you might be hanging
out with Muslim people for the first
time like yeah we hate them too yeah we
hate them too we should kill
them Nobody Has To
Die
yeah cuz I just like I just I I don't
need to kill Americans I don't
understand that whole Al-Qaeda thing
hate the
West how primitive is your hate that it
requires a flat
Earth you think about it man if you're
on planet Earth which is Globes
shaped you hate a
direction you're actually hating off
into space
[Laughter]
you got a curve your
hate and then just stop there cuz if you
just hate a curvature of the earth
that's coming right back on
you you do not want to be a
self-loathing alqaeda
member it's where they get suicide
bombers
from well if you're in al-Qaeda never
show up to a meeting
depressed kicking the dirt around life
sucks my Rob sucks my beard sucks
everything sucks all I really want to do
is listen to The Smiths and read my
poetry you watch man olama will pick
right up on that one oh feeling a little
down are we
Ed what size jacket do you
wear
cuz I don't get I don't understand alqa
and I called him
up no I did I was in the public toilet
making a little extra
money well that's where I sawell my
t-shirts what did you
think no and I was in there and I saw
scrolled on the wall on one of the
cubicles it said for a good time call
al-Qaeda I called him up I said
ala I said said yes
Glen I said how'd you know my name I
said we're in the cubicle next to
you I
said I said quit saying her name
differently I said quit spelling it
differently I
said and they said are you comparing the
name of our terrorist movement to the
country and western song
alvara I said yes I am and they said
please stop and I said you kind of like
it and they
went I said
alaa I got some questions and they went
oh
Sho so alaa how come you always fight
the West and they went oh that's a many
lered answer Glenn I said well boil it
down he said
Glenn we fight the
West because basically the West is
fighting a secret war on
Islam and I said
alqaeda come
on [ __ ]
off I in
alaa if the West is fighting a secret
War on Islam how come you can build a
mosque anywhere you want in the west is
not how you fight a secret war and if
you look at the other world power on the
planet right now China where Islam is
basically
illegal don't you [ __ ] off and fight
[Applause]
China the West is the one power on the
planet right now who could possibly stop
China on our best day but we definitely
won't be able to Wei got little Al-Qaeda
tucking at her
sleeve look at me look at me look at me
what are you doing little
dude I got to go over there and fight
China they got all this
[ __ ] I warned him I said Al-Qaeda you
keep fighting the West 40 years from now
China's going to be in charge and then
your religion will be illegal you got to
treat your religion like a Class A drug
you got to get your kran from a drug
dealer then you'll find out what that's
all about get your kran home half of
it's a beino comic the other house is
selfhelp
book say the Karan man I knows it when I
read it me the
[Music]
Quan ala knows Al-Qaeda knows China is a
much bigger threat to their way of life
than we could ever be but they'll never
fight China for one very simple reason
and that is that China would kick
al-qaeda's
ass it's not like fight in the west
where half of us are like oh is
Guantanamo Bay
right is it
wrong China gives a [ __ ] about human
rights you fight China you'll be pining
for guantan
B sitting in a Chinese death camp going
do you remember the orange jump
suits I think that's what I miss the
most you could try but it wouldn't work
can't use terrorism in China oh you kill
my only daughter in
Terrorist now I'm free to have son I
always want
him
you try but it wouldn't work cuz one
plane would hit one building in Beijing
and then all you'd hear is
a and the Middle East would be
gone the rest of the world be like holy
[ __ ] what happened in the Middle
East
China I don't
know
you think
ah
no
how there no weapon that only kill AR
people doesn't
exist look on
Google that's that's the real reason I
think China was pissed off with Google
it wasn't Freedom of Information it was
make it something we can
say on world we can't say and that's
what you name
it [ __ ]
embarrassing
guo all right all right all right we'll
call it
cinnamon
not that one
either some of you are now got your
racist things up oh my God have we heard
racism does the world have to be stopped
it's not
racism race is a
physicality that was about
language it's
linguist which it's not either cuz that
means something
else if you're ever going to steal a
word don't steal the word that means guy
who knows all the
words you'll get
caught not racist if it be racist I have
to think I was better than Chinese
people and I don't all I'm saying is if
you're a native Chinese speaking person
and English is your second language you
will have difficulty saying G's and L's
together and I come by that honestly CU
I'm from Vancouver I grew up I delivered
Chinese food to Chinese restaurant
surrounded by Chinese people who every
day
tried to say the name Glenn
wool every day D
make I heard a lot
of G
woo I have to turn to my boss and
say no
Larry that's not how you say
it and wonder quietly to myself why a
man who got to choose his Western name
knowing full well he could not pronounce
L's or RS would pick the name
Larry it's more than
half oh folks we've had fun tonight I
think I've sweated through my little ski
jacket yeah that's the beep of
me uh folks are I think we've got to
wrap this up um is uh I've really
enjoyed talking to all of you you've
been fantastic um and when it comes out
um you'll have to buy
one you can look and say was I there I
was there all right I been Glenn thank
you good
night World ladies and
gentlemen
[Music]
to
the I want to go somewhere that they
make breakast all the
time I want to go somewhere with
[Music]
got make bunch of gravy on the
side I want to slam a giant glass all
day