[Music]
Christmas a
present it's
time to drink with
[Applause]
the been singing this song all day man I
need someone to help me out with the
tree yeah I don't think so the eggnog
says
no what's to say now mother I miss
Neil's tummy come
on help a brother
out oo I remember those yeah I got tied
up with them once they're still kind of
sticky man you know what Neil I mean
when it comes right down to it Christmas
is really my favorite holiday of the
year you know the smell of pumpkin pie a
little bit of eggnog in the belly and a
sharp increase in the suicide rate why
are you so happy about the suicide rate
why Neil it's less people I have to buy
for but you know who likes both suicide
and holidays it's our bartender the
Stars Mr Olie stetched wonder where that
tub of jelly is hey olly come on
[Applause]
out I feel like a
tool you feel like a tool but you look
great man I mean it's a chicken suit
they were all out of suits and I got you
the hat so you're like you know the
Christmas goose yeah if I'm the goose
then eat
me all right well we'll you know it's
going to make as Jolly as a shot let's
go make that but um here let's get my
Humble House boy Jesus to take care of
this hey Jesus where you at Fe in your
ear here uh these these don't work for
they're apparently kind of sticky um
here make the magic work on this if you
could ah see see and I clean all right
whatever we're going to go get drunk
[Applause]
all right what do we got this week Ollie
well you know I didn't always hate
Christmas when I was a little kid uh we
used to spend Christmas Eve at my
grandparents place and I was so you know
excited and and happy and everything i'
I'd just be bouncing off the walls and
they couldn't get me to sleep so Santa
could come and so there was uh something
my grandpa came up with and uh luckily I
was able to wrestle the recipe out from
him before he died uh in prison uh and
uh we call it Grandpa's candy
cane and after I sucked on Grandpa's
candy cane a couple times man I was just
out so to make Grandpa's candy cane you
take a shot
of UV green apple vodka vodka a fine
apple flavored vodka vodka you take half
a shot shot of Phillips Butters Scot
schnaps
shns you take a shot shot of lemon lime
soda
soda and then we want to cool it down so
it's nice and
wintry it's just like Grandpa
and then what do we do shake
it find a cup C and we strain it
stra
and Christmas here's Grandpa's candy
cane shots on the
house all right Grandpa's candy cane
please make way for our lovely and
talented assistance we're going to
spread around right now
all right everybody Grandpa's candy can
on three one two
3 tasty just how I remember God damn it
all it's like it's like you hate
Christmas or something Christmas always
brings up these bad
memories well I mean we're all friends
here I mean do you do you care to share
with everybody here these seem these
people seem open-minded to to traa yeah
tell us all come on there was this one
Christmas where o this is weird oh man
I'm going to
[Applause]
puke I feel like a
tul man that just happened yeah but it
sucks and Christmas sucks Christmas is
nothing but a bunch of greed and self
serving
platitudes and people go out and buy
crap supposedly to celebrate the birth
of this mythical superhero it's not even
historically accurate I mean Jesus was
born in August man that's that's it man
this bull every goddamn year around
December you become a real pantload
trust me by the end of this episode in
the next 2830 we'll I have a feeling
you're going to be filled with the
spirit of Christmas it's going to be
coming out your damn ears oo are we
going to learn a valuable lesson because
I'd like to be filled with some holiday
spirit man you have holiday spirit
running down your inner thigh I saw you
in the closet with that elf well he's
not exactly in the closet
anymore and he's not exactly an elf
either yeah wow it's like we have
montel's party this week isn't
it hey it's the doorbell oh doorbell
here drink your damn self Jolly we're
going to go see who's at the door
hey look at that turkey and he brought
us something guys you would not believe
what just happened to me nothing short
of a Christmas miracle hold that thought
go let's go tell olly because you know
what we're trying to fill him up with
Christmas spirit okay it's going to take
a hell of a lot of spirit let's give it
a
try all right Ollie I think it's about
to happen Jim has a story that's going
to fill you with Christmas genius you're
going to have it coming out your damn
ears Olie it was amazing here I am just
walk to the
party oh man it's getting wavy
[Applause]
again I was feeling down in the dumps
all day cuz I didn't have anything to
bring to the party and
then hey what's up man you need some
weed smoke crack rock crack rock
no but you got a turkey and what are you
a cop not a cop are you a cop what maybe
you don't know I could be a cop you
don't seem like a cop what are you
talking about I could totally be a cop
just not I'm not feeling it but why why
I'm working this man come on you just
don't have that command but I am
commanding the out of this right now man
now come on just don't see it but I
could be like Denzel from training day
if I wanted or something like like King
Kong ain't got nothing on me you know
listen relax Denzel I'm not feeling it
don't see it I apologize what about the
turkey do you have a
turkey yeah one
second here we go man five bucks five
now come on five
bucks come on
man oh man it's like High School guys
and that's how I got this turkey super
cheap too that is outrageous it's a
Christmas miracle you brought an illegal
street turkey into this house it's
probably laced with something or or at
least bone dry we'll be lucky if no one
dies from that hold on hold on I am an
expert in these matters I've been taste
testing Saddam Hussein's food for the
last 6 months oh that's that's where
you've been now you get sick of baby
Hearts after a
while Rosemary very
nice lemon pepper
and O
PCP good PCP blends with the lemon
pepper see the PCP blends with the lemon
pepper it is a Christmas miracle no it's
an emergency room Bill waiting to
happen man I call bu on this man we're
going to get the spirit in you no matter
what this is going to be great trust me
I mean we this is a miracle turkey man
you guys I'm feeling kind of man you
know hold on a second we let's what
should we do here
I hey guys let's go plant some trees
it's the right thing to do and it's an
Arbor Day tradition no this is
Christmas it's Christmas oh wait a
second but speaking of Christmas
tradition what's better than going and
meeting your neighbors let's go Carly
let's go scream at the neighborhood come
on everybody hey grab
your Neil Neil we're going Girling man
we're going to rock come
on will olly get Veronica's phone number
will Ian get another tie for Christmas
and Will Neil ever forgive Jim for using
his toothbrush stay tuned to find out on
drinking with Ian and impossibly Ian
Christmas what can be better than
drinking your favorite adult beverages
while watching a television show about
drinking adult beverages having a great
pizza Pizza to go with it if you order
from pizza luche right now in about 30
minutes you'll have a hot fresh
allnatural and utterly delicious Taste
Of Heaven while watching and drinking
straight to hell in fact our Studies
have shown that watching drinking with
Ian while eating a tasty Pizza luche
will make our already super delicious
show Taste even better wait it's The
Pizza luche that tastes great while
watching drinking with Ian Pizza
luche God needed another little angel
poor little guy had so much left in
[Music]
him well burgers are done
cheers cherish a classic Green Belt
premium you betrayed
me drinking with Ian is proud to be SP
sponsored by Gold Medal winner UV Vodka
no matter if it's UV blue raspberry UV
red cherry UV green apple UV Ivory
vanilla or UV orange orange vodka UV
flavored vodkas offer a premium product
without the high price tag please visit
UV vodka.com for additional information
and recipes and please remember to
always enjoy Philips products in
moderation
[Music]
yeah looking back on the track for a
little green
back got to
[Music]
[Applause]
find and then Lenny and squeegy came in
man it was brilliant I'm telling you man
all right let's do this I thought you
were going to get out of that damn
outfit it's too cold man this thing's
nice and warm besides you know I'm
hoping to get some plushy action later
don't tell me on top of hdden Christmas
you've been watching furry porn no I've
been watching Disney movies man those
things are great Robin Hood man the
chicken in Robin Hood she is so fine all
right enough of that do we have any
favorite carols we can do for these
people yeah yeah yeah 76 Trombones Jim
oh yeah that's Fourth of July how about
a Christmas tree we all know a Christmas
tree don't we it's really otan bomb okay
I I really don't give a damn
okay all right I I hear somebody
coming honey
carolers
a uh Jim canace off and one and two
Christmas tree
Christmas weird
um woman
hi just don't touch
my that's not too bad this one as well
as I thought it would it went better
than I thought it would we have a wallet
all right wait a second this dude's a
member of the damn green party he
doesn't have any dough see man I'm
telling you this holiday sucks it's a
lasagna of Lies is what it is it's a
layer of lies and a layer of lies and a
layer of ricotta cheese and a layer of
Lies that's that's really stupid I had
lasagna for lunch and I'm kind of hungry
you guys guys we got to get Neil and
side I think he's peeking all right
scw don't walk in life don't walk in
life
go well that was a big fat waste of time
I'm going to see if you got any sleeping
pills man no hold on here let's have a
drink and thi about this we'll get
Christmas going yet yeah guys I really
think we should get something to calm
kneel down too r Shard
a hey Shard a sounds like a good idea
you guys I'll go get it
all you all right man oh he's just being
a big baby he's fine grab Control to
Major Neil baby want his bottle come on
man wake up Neil oh big baby want his
bottle Ground
Control CH big
baby hey Ian can't find any chard a all
I got is this picture of iced tea check
the
Bantry
hey who brought
thisor Ian got some
hey guys who do we know that brings us
boxed wine man I got no
idea give
me that'll that'll keep him focused for
a while man this Christmas is sucking
more than usual I mean at least we can
say we hit a new low man no we can
totally turn this around Jim I'm glad
you're here could you could you
Enlighten us with a little bit of
holiday hi cou holiday haou huh yeah
yeah let's uh I've got a great for
President's Day starts off it's
Christmas you got a Christmas oh you
want a Christmas hike that would be nice
okay all
right yeah uh okay it's the
24th time to go home for Christmas I
live in a
box ladies and gentlemen hiu J always
here a little bit more F that's good Jim
but Japanese don't celebrate Christmas
yeah but then again neither do us Jews
hey everybody it's our Jewish friend
Dan hey Dan all right now according to
Mill Gibson you people hate Jesus why
are you at our party are you nuts free
PCP
turkey all right well we're trying to
get some of the Christmas spirit in Ali
and if you have it anybody should uh why
don't you tell us some of the teachings
of your desert trotting
people really are you kidding me first
off you guys didn't even invite me to
this party I only found out about the
PCP second off I don't see any Hanukkah
decorations in here it's real easy to
ask the Jewish guy to come in and Uncle
Tom about his Hanukkah holiday because
you guys want to feel important but I'm
sorry I mean you know you say you're
sorry but it happens every year I mean
it started when I was a kid Christmas
pageants why don't you teach us all
about your little Jewish thing so you
feel like you're part of it I don't want
to feel like I'm part of we get it you
say you get it but Hanukkah isn't even
an important holiday learn how to spell
or pronounce the thing for the first
I mean it's ridiculous settle down
settle I think we get it man I think we
get it
all all right fine turkeyy pretty moist
though no that's
good am I pretty now am I pretty now am
I pretty now am I pretty now am I Prett
uh oh we better take care of this I
pretty now am I pretty now am I pretty
now am I I am
will olly get Veronica's phone number
will Ian get another typ for Christmas
and Will Neil ever forgive Jim for using
his toothbrush stay tuned to find out on
drinking with Ian and impossibly Ian
Christmas a portion of drinking with Ian
is sponsored by The Onion America's
Finest news source and the AV club
bringing you reviews and commentary on
the Arts and and entertainment scene
available at new stands throughout the
Twin Cities and online at the onion.com
and avclub.com
triple calf draft energy drink is made
for the night life and not for sport
triple calf draft energy drink is only
available at establishment selling
Spirits mix triple calf with your
favorite intoxicant and you will come to
appreciate the lasting effects of the
world's first draft energy drink triple
calf tap one off and Spike it
[Music]
live music on drinking with Ian is
sponsored in part by Billy the Jack
Productions online at Billy Thee
jack.com
the drink with eat and crowd very easily
LED they will buy little plastic those
things you put on your finger that are
like little rubber
monsters these are drunken stupid
idiotic smelly people with a lot of
money drop us a line at sponsorship at
drinking with.com and make it
happen Jesus Neil come on man I've seen
Neil I'm barfing dogs eyeballs into the
H oh yeah that sounds about right I'll
see you guys when this wears
off Jim take care take care him you guys
I'll take care of this but promise me
one thing don't start the egg hunt till
I get back man that's Easter but he's
getting warmer yeah you guys trying to
confuse me nice try come on
Neil still not feeling it are you no
this is still a stupid holiday yeah I
don't blame you um but you know what
actually Christmas is all about it's
about capitalism man let's go get this
guy a gift gifts gifts are the worst
part of this holiday cuz no one ever
gets what they want I mean you might as
well just hand someone some cash and say
here I like you $2.50
worth but it's like the thought that
counts then that makes a
prostitution hey you guys got Neil
settled in upstairs he's coming to
upstairs what room man Ian I found your
gun wow I can shoot right through my
hand guys I'll take care of this I'll
get it all right let's get out of here
before the cops show up that's probably
damn good
idea who the hell are these guys it's
villinger 4 hey guys hey Merry Christmas
guys those
[Music]
tell
[Applause]
[Music]
about drinking
[Applause]
go
you know
[Music]
[Applause]
mail structure these are Neil's kind of
places you figure something would be
open look it's Christmas day nothing is
open on Christmas Day what do you expect
last year I wanted to get some Halal
goat meat and I couldn't because the
Halal grocery store was closed yeah but
I mean Christmas is a day of Hope for
Christ's sake man I gave up hope a long
time ago man but Neil is our friend so
there's always hope and there's got to
be something come on let's keep
looking no they're they're a heavy metal
B from oh I'm telling you they're not
it's it's all it's all F what's up
what's up man hey jesz man how you doing
yeah go man you need like rock crack
rock man I got smoke no way man you're a
cop what you're a cop no I'm not a cop
man look we don't have time to do this
again um you have any uh gifts or
anything I'm looking for one for my
friend Neil he's about this tall very
stylish very stylish man hang on man
I'll be right there you's got something
sweet all right this guy's got I don't
know man that's nicely take that you
don't know what it is it could be a bomb
this isn't a bomb that's a bomb it's not
ticket or anything man this is a live
present this is a fine good old
americanmade present right here isn't
it whoa whoa whoa Whoa man man man man
you don't think it's a
bom trying to be
safe $5 man $5 all right cool it's a
good deal you just hang out in alleys
and oh no man I got this gig right I go
into houses once a year usually through
the chimney you know and then I put
these presents all over the place right
and stockings by the tree and stuff man
it's going to make me a
fortune that going to make you yeah
wouldn't it make more sense if you just
broke into their houses and stole
everything it does make more sense man
I've been doing this for 500 years man
you're all right man I'm got to go tell
my elves all right all right going to be
a lot of sad kids next year I told you
this holiday is
stupid it's about time you guys got back
Neil's gotone catatonic hey Neil I got
you again
is that a bomb or
anything I tried I say we get a few more
drinks in us and shoot this day in the
head man I hate to say it but I think
you're right man this this holiday is
total crap I told you it's a lasagna of
lies and lies and ricotta cheese and
oregano and then some of those white
water
oh
God
Hallelujah
Hallelujah Hallelujah Hallelujah
[Applause]
[Music]
Hall oh wow oh manoo that was
weird hey hey hey Hees
Zeus um I think I made a little El vomo
in El you want to go check it
out see Senor I I clean bring
a hey guys what did I miss hey Neil's
back to normal it's a Christmas miracle
well it takes a little bit more than
some PCP to take me out of a party I
just hope I didn't do anything
embarrassing but you know what the best
part was I'm still drunk off all that
chardonay and I'm getting smashed on
this
vodka I was drunk when I got here I
never stopped
drinking you know this makes me think I
mean Christmas is a crappy holiday but
it is a great excuse for all of us to
get together and drink isn't it agreed a
happy Boxing Day to one and all damn it
close let's all get
hammered here Neil I got you a gift for
me oh that's so special I wonder what it
is a fishing pole open
it oh it's a
cute uhoh PCP lace Skitty
[Music]
w
d
e
e e